Previously on Mad Men.
But you're the new girl and
you're not much
so you might as well
enjoy it while it lasts.
Of course.
You know who else
doesn't wear a hat?
Elvis.
That's what we're dealing with.
Remind me to stop hiring
young people.
My mother passed away, recently.
I guess I already said that.
I am appreciative of
your talents and
I have made an effort to quantify.
Twenty-five hundred dollars.
Dance with me.
I don't like you like this.
Season 1 Episode 9
Shoot
Mommy, look at that!
Don Draper!
How are you?
Probably about like you.
Enduring the splendor of Fiorello!.
You know, we got that
Israeli tourism thing, right?
Mazal tov.
I ran into Jim Jordan from
B.D.O. at the Athletic club
with Frank from Y & R
Your name came up.
Three millionaires in towels
in a steam room.
- I don't know how to take that.
- Take it as a compliment,
a sign that you're destined
for greater things.
I think Jesus over Rio was
the best tourist campaign
I've seen in over 20 years.
It wasn't good enough
to land the Israelis.
That's not you.
That's the Tiny store you work in.
Now, if you were with me at McCann,
you'd have over 500 people
at your disposal,
and that's just in New York.
We can get a lot of things done.
Can it get me out of the second half
of this show?
All I'm saying is you've done
your time in the farm leagues.
Yankee stadium is on the line.
I changed my mind.
I decided you deserve
a visit to the bar.
Adele, this is Donald Draper.
- How do you do?
- If we're being introduced,
I assume that you're in advertising.
Would you both like to talk
about that some more?
Betty, my wife.
Jim and Adele Hobart.
Hello, Betty Draper.
Pleasure.
Your husband here was about to prove
that he can speak about things
other than advertising.
He's very interesting.
Well, then, come with me.
Let's get those drinks.
We'll be back.
Champagne?
Besides getting the handsome prince,
are you...
an actress or something?
No, I'm a housewife.
I did do some modeling
a lifetime ago.
I'm not surprised.
That is some face you've got there.
Anybody ever tell you you're
a dead ringer for Grace Kelly?
They used to.
You know what?
Coca-Cola is deep into this,
international campaign right now.
A european face like yours,
like Grace Kelly's,
might be a road we could go down.
We could put a call out for
a Grace Kelly type but...
I don't think we'd come this close.
You say you've modeled?
I'm retired.
- This is silly.
- Think about it.
Your coloring with a green bottle
and an irish setter.
Drink up.
It's back to Tammany* hall.
I like this show.
Very gay songs.
Well, we'd better get back in there...
Or leave.
Come on.
It was very nice meeting
both of you.
Good evening.
Why didn't you want to go to
dinner with Jim and Adele?
People like Jim Hobart
always talk business
because they have
nothing else to say.
I could see that.
You know, he gave me his card.
Really?
Tell you to put it under
my pillow or something?
No, actually.
He was talking to me about modeling.
Was he?
I don't think it was like that.
He said something about
Grace Kelly and Coca-Cola.
Well, then there's no need
to doubt his interest then.
I did model, Don.
Am I that wrong for Coca-Cola?
You're not wrong for anything.
So, are you going to go there?
How was Fiorello exclamation point?
It'll be six months before
I can get Don back into
a broadway theater.
We ran into this agency head.
Apparently, he's courting Don.
He gave me his card.
Asked me if I wanted to
do any modeling.
That's a heck of a line.
what did Don say?
He basically said the man was
trying to sleep with one of us,
and he didn't like
the idea of either.
I did do some modeling, you know.
I did not know, but
I'm not surprised.
Carlton calls you Grace Kelly.
Yeah, I was a model when I met Don.
A model in Manhattan?
Yes.
It was exciting.
But when I got started,
the summer after college in Italy.
Italy?
There was this Italian designer.
Giovanni.
He wanted to be called Johnny.
That's how much he loved Americans.
Well, he loved American girls.
It was more of an artist/muse
relationship.
So, he made you all this
and it was platonic?
No petting? Nothing?
Then put my hair up like this.
And Salvatore said he had
the Menkens' artwork,
but to meet him in
the Art department
because you're' going to
need a red pencil.
Any other good news?
I think the mail boy dropped
that off for you last night.
Welcome to the club. Call me. Jim.
Peggy, can you get me
an outside line?
Right away.
Now, why would you call me
out of the blue?
I appreciate the gesture.
It's not a gesture, Don.
It's an overture.
Let me tell you, you're
a hard man to run into.
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything.
The next step is a quiet rendezvous.
The Algonquin?
There's a small hotel.
Isn't that the song?
I don't know.
I'm not ready to wave
the flag just yet.
What about the details?
I'd rather do this face to face.
But you already know
what you're gonna say.
I don't have to tell you
the obvious limitations
of Sterling-Cooper.
But you're going to.
Do I need to be careful here?
It's a mom and pop.
McCann-Erickson is
an international company.
We have a network that extends
far beyond Madison avenue.
Europe, south America.
We're publicly traded.
We issue dividends.
Small is bad.
Do you know the kind of
clients we attract?
Pan Am, Coca-Cola,
Esso.
Can you imagine the lifestyle
that goes with handling Pan Am?
It's a panty dropper.
Television?
You could be in that in
a bigger way. You know that.
But you want to sell corn,
we do a show about Indians.
Imagine yourself in
a three year contract,
35 per antum, security set in stone.
Sterling probably hasn't let
you break 30 yet.
No comment.
I really don't like doing
this over the phone.
All I can say is eventually
you come up here
or you die wondering.
He gave me his card
right in front of Don.
Well, not right in
front of him, I guess.
Well, I told Don about it.
I was a model, you know?
In fact, I met Don on a photo shoot.
I was wearing this
Russian blue fox coat.
He was just a copywriter
at the fur company.
I remember he saw that
I didn't like giving the coat back.
That's always the hardest part.
He asked me out.
He wasn't shy.
I liked that.
I said no.
Then, three weeks later
the coat arrived at my apartment.
Who knows what kind of Indian
trading he had to do to get it.
I think I only had two more jobs,
maybe three, before we got engaged.
And then I got pregnant.
It's always a nightmare raising
children in manhattan,
so we moved to ossing.
Suddenly,
I really felt so old.
Tell me more about that.
My mother was very concerned
about looks and weight.
And I've always eaten a lot.
And I like hot dogs.
My mother used to say,
"you're going to get stout."
and then I became a model,
and she hated it.
Even though Suzy Parker
made $100,000 that year,
my mother hated it.
Manhattan.
She called me a prostitute.
You're angry at your mother.
What?
Are you going to talk now?
You are angry at your mother.
Of all the things I've said in here!
You're sitting up.
You don't listen to me.
You don't listen to what I say,
and then out of nowhere
you provoke me.
Tell me more about that.
I miss her.
I understand that.
It's good and bad.
She wanted me to be beautiful
so I could find a man.
There's nothing wrong with that.
But then what?
Just sit and
smoke and...
Let it go until you're in a box?
I don't care why
he gave me his card.
Where'd you get this?
Kurt teasdale over at Guild Bascom.
It's already on the air. They wanted
to do it before she had the baby.
Am I the alone?
I don't understand it.
Because it's in Spanish.
I recognize that finishing
school voice.
You can't govern and
listen to that all day.
I'm happy to give up any Spanish
speakers and hope this goes away.
Well, Cooper thinks if Kennedy
creeps up any more in the polls,
Nixon will panic and they'll get
desperate for our efforts.
He wants everything in place.
More risk.
Why are we doing this again,
and out of pocket?
One don't question
the wishes of our clients.
Clients come and go, Campbell.
Sometimes it's best to rid them
of unrealistic expectations.
Are you trying to say
that we can't win?
Nixon's got an eight point
lead in the polls.
Not much.
And we still haven't figured
out a way to make an impact
about the Nxon campaign's involvement.
My marching orders were
undecided states.
I think a plan of attack
would make Coop happy.
The 50-50's. Texas,
New Jersey, and Illinois.
No- it's easy to just
say that, isn't it?
I think women will hate her.
It's like their better looking sister
marries a handsome senator
and she's going to live
in the White House.
I'm practically jealous.
Hi.
I called.
I assumed you were staying
in the city.
The girl.
We gave her a little extra work
and now she's distracted.
Look at that.
It's raw, Don.
Don, I realized something today.
I miss modeling.
You always told me you hated it.
Maybe the passing of time
has made me feel differently.
Maybe it's Jim Hobart.
So what?
It's still an opportunity.
You want to go back to work?
A few days. I mean, is that so bad?
I get paid.
I can get ethel to watch the kids.
She watches them half the time now.
Well, that's three four-hour stretches.
I think it would be fun to go in
and be that girl again.
You're serious?
There will still be ham.
I promise.
Are you resolved?
Is this even worth arguing?
No, it's not like that.
It's just something I'd like to do.
Well, I can't stop you from
doing what you want to do.
You have no idea how boring
it is around here.
Really?
I would think one hour on
the Sterling-Cooper switchboard
would be a Russian novel.
They told me it would happen, but the
truth is you really just stop listening.
And put ice on your wrists.
Peggy, do you need to go home?
What?
The sweater.
Are you having one of those days?
It's not that.
I'd like to go home,
but I just don't think I can.
Then what is it?
You're not helping your silhouette.
I ripped my skirt.
You don't have a needle and thread?
It's a big rip.
Honey.
I've got a spare outfit squirreled
away. You can borrow it.
Not exactly dressed for that, are we?
I've lost men like you before,
and usually it had to do with
my unexpressed confidence.
I think you're one in
a million, Draper.
Those are nice clubs.
That bonus from Cooper
must've made you happy.
It was designed as a kind of an
armor against men like Jim Hobart.
How'd you hear about it?
I saw those clubs going down the
hallway. I thought they were for me.
They're from Jim Hobart.
What did he offer?
Bigger.
The world, basically.
It can't just be a number and a salary
because you know we're open to that.
Pan Am.
Pan Am?
It is not McCann-Erickson.
Big talent attracts big clients.
We can try and make that happen here.
That's true.
But don't be fooled. You hear
Pan Am you imagine London,
holed up at the Dorchester
with three stewardesses.
The truth is it's more like
a 20-hour boomerang flight
so you can make a coupon sing
in Spanish.
And when you have stockholders
like McCann does
you can't fire clients,
I know you'll hate that.
I thought about leaving once.
But, you know,
it's daunting.
Why entertain the prospect
of failure?
- That's a sad thought.
- No,
made me look at this place.
I don't want to sound sentimental,
but it's not just accounts.
Look around here at what you have.
You want to start over?
I haven't made up my mind.
- I'm taking this very personally.
- Why?
It's business.
Is it?
Mccann-Erickson is
the major leagues.
- Good. let him go.
- You're right.
- Maybe he'll take me with him.
- Can you imagine the money?
I heard he's making 30 already.
He's not ten times better than me.
You love him.
Everybody loves him.
Sure, his moods and
the way he talks.
I don't even know what
he's saying half the time.
Clients do.
I'll admit, she crossed
my mind once.
She's having a very bad
freshman year.
They went nuts for her writing.
Belle Jolie, she did that.
Belle Jolie was okay.
She obviously let it go to her head,
and other places.
Naw, I don't think it's the job.
I think we're seeing the real her.
It's one of those girls who slimmed
down before she got here.
Now she's here and there she is.
Who thinks about her?
Maybe she'll go with Draper too.
It's a tragedy.
A piece of fruit that went real bad
real fast,
and no one ever got to eat it.
Well, I got some work to do.
Suddenly, upon news of other success
a young man is filled with ambition.
Drop dead.
Harry, you busy?
Well, hello. I can't believe this.
I'm sorry I overdid it.
You're out of the business a
few years and things change.
Please, I'm overwhelmed
with the style of you.
Betty draper meet Ronnie Gittridge.
He handles the art for Coca-Cola.
He's also my brother-in-law.
- It is a pleasure.
- Look at her.
- What did I say?
- You ready to work?
- I'm excited.
- It's not that complicated.
He's either gonna tell you
to think about
something else or just stand there.
Jim thinks everyone
else's job is easy.
Shall we.
It's just a tryout.
No guarantees.
I told you, I've done this before.
Now, where did you get that dress?
So, basically, whereas
Secor previously
spent their money on
local print and radio,
we increase the network buy to 30%,
more points for each dollar.
Secor laxatives.
You know, I have to talk
to those people.
They're not what you would expect.
They have absolutely no sense
of humor about their product.
Who knew that college was gonna get
me out of the army and into laxatives?
College was the moment, wasn't it?
Fun and games,
and girls.
Were you in a frat?
Alpha Delta Phi.
Also known as cut ups.
We were the cut ups.
We had this stray dalmatian,
our mascot, Mamie.
So, it died, and in classic fraternity
manner we decided to throw a party.
Mamie's funeral.
One of the pledges pipes
in that our rivals, si-u.
They are so gung ho.
Si-u is throwing a beauty pageant
parade on main street
with the girl school down the road.
Now, my friend, Chip,
he's a lawyer now, says,
"why don't we go down there
and get a permit,"
"throw a grand funeral for Mamie,
and let the girls run away crying?"
that's great.
Did you do it?
We had police barricades and
30 brothers following that pledge
who had the honor of pulling
Mamie in a radio flyer.
That's beautiful.
Idiots.
Wait a minute.
Nixon and Kennedy are both buying up
airtime in these undecided states.
It's an arms race.
Nixon buys, Kennedy matches.
So, if we can't increase Nixon's
presence, we can decrease Kennedy's.
How do we that?
We make big buys in New Jersey,
Illinois, and wherever
for Secor laxatives.
Well, hold on.
- So, Nixon's selling laxatives?
- No.
We're selling laxatives,
Nixon's selling Nixon,
and Kennedy's watching
Mamie's funeral.
This is scary.
It is, isn't it?
It was for me.
Who was it?
I'm the girl, the girl with the Cola.
It's only a couple of days work.
You know, just a couple of photo shoots
and then some kind of testing.
But I guess you know how it works.
I do.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna ruin this.
I'm very happy for you.
I know you don't like it,
but I know you're
a little bit proud of me.
- Come upstairs.
- No.
Right here.
Okay.
How are these open already?
Well, Betty, we don't want life
to look difficult, now do we?
You're too much.
- Polly, no!
- Let her go.
If I see that dog in my yard again,
I'm gonna shoot it.
I see you got there and
back in one piece.
Yes.
And even though I got lost,
I sent Ethel home at four.
They went to the park
and to visit Ernie at Francine's.
All in all, everyone had a nice day.
So, how was it?
There was this man, Ronnie.
I don't even know what his job is.
Ronnie Gittridge.
He's the art director... I met him.
He is such a character.
He tells funny stories.
I brought the form home.
I thought you could help me fill
it out so I can get paid.
I'd love to.
Sweetie pie?
What happened?
I had a bad dream.
Get in bed with daddy.
What was your dream?
I don't want anyone to shoot Polly.
No one's gonna do that, honey.
Yes, mr. Ford said he would
because Polly ate
one of his doves.
They're pigeons.
He said this to you in your dream?
No. He said it today when
Polly ate the birdie.
He wasn't hurt that bad.
He could fly.
No one is gonna hurt Polly.
Come here.
Night-night.
Now they can't play in the yard?
I'm gonna get my robe on and go over
there and find out what happened.
Two in the morning.
He's our neighbor.
He'll make it worse.
I'll talk to him.
You should have Ethel talk to him.
Don, they play in the yard
when I'm here too.
And she didn't tell you?
I'm sure they didn't tell her.
They probably wouldn't
have told me either.
They'll be over at Francine's
for the next shoot anyway.
It's one day.
I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
Maybe not.
She's never slept well.
That's not true.
Did you see those big tears?
I really want to get a picture
of her crying one day.
I have to say, Don, Lucky Strike even
in this lawsuit is stronger than ever.
It was a brilliant campaign.
Like some supersonic jet
flying right over the market.
I was there. Great work.
Thank you.
Sorry to interrupt
who is responsible?
We've made a significant
commitment for as yet
unproduced Secor laxative
commercials.
This didn't go by me.
No. It went by Bob Wilkins
in media right to me.
Who is responsible?
Mr. Cooper sir, it was me.
You thought of this?
Well...
I bear some of
the responsibility as well.
What did they do?
Every commercial block on air
in the land of Lincoln is
clogged up with
laxative buys.
And a little bit of Nixon time.
The Kennedy people won't know
what to do with themselves.
They're going to have
to put his pretty face
on the radio,
and with that accent.
Nicely done.
I didn't think you had it in you,
and I mean that.
- Thank you.
Inspired.
Congratulations, boys.
Peggy, you want to write that down?
Don said congratulations.
Are we done here?
I really thought it was gonna
go bad for a minute.
- I was sure it would.
- No kidding.
You almost let me detonate
1,000 feet from the ground.
So much for camaraderie.
Mr. Rumson sent this over.
Unopened! Very nice.
Hildi? Stay. Have a drink.
It's an order.
No, thank you. I'm going to
my parents after work.
You know, when something good
happens to me, it also happens to you.
I know that. I said congratulations.
You should do something with that
sourpuss. You're very beautiful.
Just being honest.
I love watching you walk.
I should go.
You should.
is he in?
Always nice to see you.
I can give you my assurance
that nothing good
will happen to that boy,
though I can't seem to keep my word
on that, hard as I try.
I might ask you to take me with you.
I see no reason to leave.
Or maybe I see a million.
A million?
Is that what it's gonna cost me?
I was thinking more like 40.
45 is good.
I'm not gonna be a little girl and
ask you why you stayed.
I know it's not money,
and I hope it's not to keep
your foot on Pete Campbell.
I like the way you do business.
Well, I try to be as civilized
as you can be.
No contract.
45 and no security.
Well, what's in it for me?
If I leave this place one day,
it will not be for more advertising.
What else is there?
I don't know. Life being lived.
I'd like to stop talking about
it and get back to it.
I've worked with
a lot of men like you,
and if you had to choose a place to die
it would be in the middle of a pitch.
I've done that.
I want to do something else.
Jim Hobart, McCann-Erickson.
Of course.
Line one.
Incredible pictures. Am I wrong?
No, you're not.
So, your wife's already here
with us. I know she's happy.
Why don't you join her?
- I don't know about that, Jim.
- You can do better than that.
You know what I'm offering here?
It's Yankee stadium. I know.
What? Did Sterling
come to the rescue?
Is it about money? I have to say
I might've judged you wrong.
It's not.
I'm surprised.
I thought your wife coming
here meant you were interested.
No, that was her idea.
Can't blame me for trying.
Maybe not but...
Can't exactly say that
was a big league move.
All's fair.
No stone unturned, right?
It's a pity to lose both of you.
You're a very lucky
man landing that woman.
What's going on with mr. Draper?
Even if I knew, I wouldn't tell you.
Very good.
I've been meaning to give this back to
you. I had it completely dry cleaned.
Why don't you keep it?
Have it taken in here
and let out there.
It's your dress.
Hot tea. That's a good idea.
What are you talking about?
You are falling prey to a very
common situation for new girls.
- I'm not new anymore.
- Well, that's just it.
Don't you want to do well here?
I'm the first girl to do
any writing in this office
since the war.
Marge told me.
Writing?
Is that what this is about?
I thought you were doing
that to get close to Paul.
Thank you again.
I heard you were being
considered for an account
because a client's wife
saw you and thought
it would be okay if
he worked with you.
You know, you're not a stick!
And yet I never wonder
what men think of me.
You are hiding a very
attractive young girl
with too much lunch.
I know what men think of you.
That you're looking for a husband,
and you're fun,
and not in that order.
Peggy, this isn't China.
There's no money in virginity.
I'm not a virgin.
No, of course not.
I just realized something.
You think you're being helpful.
Well, I am trying, dear.
I'm going home.
Did you have a good day?
I did. It was splendid.
Well, Betty, I have some good news
and some bad news.
There's bad news?
The client's moving the international
work to London.
More Audrey Hepburn,
less Grace Kelly.
I see.
As for us, well, we're going back
to the malt shop.
The good news is you have two
wonderful sets of pictures
to start your book again.
That's true.
I really am sorry.
This was fun.
You can keep the dress
and the hairstyle.
I don't do that for everyone.
Honey, it has nothing
to do with you.
Thank you.
What do you think, Paul? Should
we move this whole thing
down to MacDougal street?
Doing great here.
Good, she left.
Probably wasn't gonna
happen for her tonight.
Depends how much we drink.
How drunk do you have to be?
My brother works at the exchange.
They call a girl like her a lobster.
All the meat's in the tail.
Are they giving you guys a bonus?
Will you calm down?
Come on!
Drop you at the station?
Sure.
Campbell, you sucker punched me.
What is wrong with you?
Come on.
You just had a fight and
I was not part of it.
Either you two make up,
or I do not stand a chance tonight.
Perfect timing.
The children are down,
but only because they were
running around all day.
They fell asleep in front of the TV.
- How did it go today?
- Good.
Fun.
They were talking about a whole
string of other possibilities for me.
But honestly,
I don't think I want to
work anymore.
I don't like you coming
home to some...
Whipped together mess of
whatever's left in the fridge.
And frankly, I don't like
Manhattan on my own.
It's harsh.
It can be.
And what am I going to do?
Run around the city with my book
like some teenager
making a fool of myself?
If that's what you want,
and it's my job to give
you what you want.
You do.
Look at all this.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Birdie,
you know I don't care
about making my dinner
or taking in my shirts.
You have a job.
You're a mother to those
two little people
and you are better at it than
anyone else in the world.
At least in the top 500.
I would've given anything
to have had a mother like you.
Beautiful, and kind,
and filled with love like an angel.
You're sweet.
And this does not taste whipped up.
No.
It's good, isn't it?
- Have a good day, daddy.
- You, too.
We're going to the community center
to watch them fill the pool.
That sounds fun.
- Have a good day.
- I already am.
Mommy, I'm eating.
Be careful! Don't jump off the bed.
Okay!
mrs. Draper!
What the hell are you doing?
Mrs. Draper!