Previously on Mad Men.
I hope you're aware that I'd love
to throw my hat in the ring.
I am now.
Hopefully, if you follow my lead,
you can avoid some of
the mistakes I've made here.
- Hello, Joan.
- Like that one.
Hildy, you should do something
with that sourpuss.
You're very beautiful.
You have a problem with Nixon?
I Don't vote.
Hear, hear.
Can you mail this for me
today?
Mr. Draper?
Season 1 Episode 12
Nixon vs. Kennedy
America is still going
to the polls at 4:00.
With some precincts opening
as early as 12 this morning,
voters across the country
are deciding
who will hold the most
important office in the fr--
Herman Phillips,
Bert Cooper.
Actually, "Herman" goes on
my checks. People call me Duck.
My research says I was
not to call you duck.
- You should have told me that.
- I Don't know.
I like when you say Herman.
Herman was in London with Y&R.
Isn't this a step down?
I Don't know. Moving back to the power
center of the universe, New York,
and the chance
to put on some weight.
English food.
I actually ate a kidney.
He landed Amican Airlines.
You could make something
like that happen here.
You have to spend money
to make money.
So you're not promising anything.
Why would I do that?
My goodness, he does want this job.
I hope you play your cards
close to the vest with clients.
I will keep that in mind.
Here's a test. O'd you vote for?
If I say Nixon,
you'll think I'm buttering you.
And if I say Kennedy,
you'll want to reform me.
So I'll say Nixon.
That's nice to see.
Cooper has a smoker
at the Waldorf at 6:00.
- Marge told me.
- 23 skidoo.
At 6:15, we turn on the returns
and send for some ice.
Party at the in-laws'.
Another ending to a perfect day.
Jennifer and I were going to get
tickets to can-can.
It's empty, you know.
She says apparently the phone company's
a war zone on election night.
That's what I'm hoping
for around here.
You'd better hope she's sitting
at her switchboard
and not doing what we're doing.
It's my wife.
Besides, what if Nixon loses? Won't that
put a damper on things around here?
Who cares? They
didn't want our help.
You should care.
I do. It matters for the nation
and for Sterling Coop'.
But tonight, either way.
If Nixon wins, we win.
If Nixon loses--
Let me console you.
That's him.
Duck Phillips.
I know his name.
Because it's Duck?
I grew up with a tuck.
At least that has an air of dignity.
Don took him to Cooper.
That's a first.
I heard he disintegrated in London.
Got involved with some woman
he met at the british museum.
Her name was Rosetta.
Rosetta Stone.
He's divorced. Lives in a hotel.
So what's this? His last stop?
No. He's a killer, but he's--
He's damaged goods.
They're bargain hunting.
He's the best one
Draper's paraded around.
Let's see if Cooper's smart
enough to know that.
Can I help you?
What?
Mr. Campbell would like to see you.
Send him in.
Thank you, sweetheart.
So that Duck fellow,
I heard he fell a part in London.
American Airlines.
$7 million in billings.
He's not going to bring
that with him.
Listen, Don, I Don't feel you've taken
me seriously as a candidate.
Candidate for what?
For the head of account services.
We may have had our differences,
but Roger knows I've done
everything I could to emulate him.
Roger's not involved in this.
Anything else?
I have the loyalty of
our most important clients:
Calvin Highland, Lee Garner.
These men trust me.
They invite me to their
grandchildren's christenings.
When Walter veidt need a urologist,
he called me for a recommendation.
Look, you're good at your job.
Cooper loves you.
What's the hurry?
It's been twand a half years.
I could have jumped
ship a hundred times.
Is that supposed to persuade me?
I have tremendous value
to this company.
I'm aware of that.
But I Don't think you are.
I am. I just hope you realize
that, the way things stand,
there will continue to be
someone senior to you.
Why? What can they offer?
All I'm asking is that
you think about it.
There are men younger than me
with his job at bigger firms.
Cooper sign off on what's-his-name?
Duck?
I'll keep you posted.
He's got a big lead.
See you at the victory
party in the morning.
Absolutely.
Well, good night, Don.
- He's gone!
- Olly olly oxen free!
With early returns just coming in,
our NBC computer
putting senator Kennedy's odds
for victory at a grim-sounding 22-1.
This is not good.
And liquor stores are
closed tonight.
Draper has plenty of booze.
We could ask her to join us.
That might soften her up a bit.
I have a bottle of absinthe
in my office.
- Isn't that illegal?
- It's marvelous.
I become incantatory.
And what does that mean?
It means he starts making up words.
Can someone freshen this?
We're no going to make it.
Really?
If I let you into
that supply closet,
it is not going to be
the sack of Rome.
What do we have too much of?
Rhum, crème de menthe,
dog biscuits.
May the best man win.
It matters national and... local.
Stop that. You're going to break it.
Look. They're doing math.
What do the numbers say?
Who the President is going to be.
- Hello.
- Daddy! Hi!
I wasn't expecting you.
I thought you were going to be
watching returns at the office.
What are you doing up?
Mommy said it was okay.
I'm watching the news.
Nixon definitely won our precinct.
You should have seen the line.
Mommy said to ask you. What's the...
Electoral college.
I Don't think that's a conversation
appropriate for children.
Come here.
Do you want something to eat?
I'm going to fix a drink. You?
I'm set.
Senator Kennedy seems to be closing
the gap on the vice president's
early lead.
State-by-state, Ohio, Illinois--
- Come here.
- What?
You'd better run.
Go, Allison!
- White!
- Pink!
You can tell me, or I can find out.
What color panties are you wearing?
What? My g--
Blue!
Who had blue?
Can I walk you home?
I used to think
I'd find a husband here.
I think I'm going to go home.
No, Don't go. It's going to be fun.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you asleep?
What is that?
Nothing.
Myrna found it on the top of the closet,
and I didn't want to look at it.
My father has a box like that,
and I looked at it
when I was a little girl,
and it was a mistake.
So you didn't open it?
Peter, I Don't want secrets.
I can't sleep.
I know.
I've seen it the last few weeks.
You're not very quiet,
and every time I see the closet door
is open and that box is gone
I know you're out here.
And you never looked in the box?
It's not yours.
- What are you doing with it?
- I got it by mistake.
So give back.
It's peculiar.
It's not yours.
Come to bed.
Vice president Nixon seems
to have carried
predominantly catholic hudson county--
Kinsey, yore a liar.
I couldn't find any absinthe.
Who said you could go in my office?
We were exploring.
But all we found was a large
collection of mad magazines
and this...
fascinating dramatic piece.
Death is my client--
A play in one act
by Paul Kinsey.
Give it to me.
"Peter Tollifson"--
"An animal in the board room
and the bedroom."
Now, rember, he's angry.
Why do I have to play Tollifson?
- I wanted to be galt.
- Tollifson is the hero.
He thinks.
Galt's a thug from the wrong side
of the tracks.
You Don't want to be galt.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry. I Don't have the pages.
"I worked with Tollifson
for four years."
"I shared everything,
but I never knew him."
"I thought I knew him."
"He used to talk to me."
"I can't control my genius."
"I'm not some boorish natural
like that hack Cosgrove."
That's crackerjack, kinsey.
"Your genius beamned."
"Perhaps."
"You can make anyone buy anything."
"Anyone but me."
Turn the music down.
...now have confirmation
that the state of Ioha
has indeed gone
to vice president Richard Nixon.
I'm-- I'm really tipsy.
I feel awful.
No.
It was me.
I'm-- I'm drunk.
I'm happy...
But not myself.
I've never really
seen your eyes before.
There they are.
Just the two of them.
What's going on?
I Don't know.
It'll be all right in the morning.
He'll win california.
Turn it off.
Sit down.
No.
You can't sit down in that dress.
You look so different
when you're drunk.
You're not going to call me
Orson Welles again.
You loved that.
Who wouldn't like that?
What did I do wrong?
You have a big mouth.
- Joan, I never said--
- You have a big mouth.
I do.
I'm not proud of it.
Did you like the play?
No.
The meaner you are,
the more I like you.
I know.
Just like that?
I thought we could dance.
1, 2, cha-cha.
Hildy, wake up.
It's cold in here.
It is. You have to get dressed.
I can't find my glasses.
That's too bad.
Tremendous.
Yes?
I hope I didn't step on them.
Damn it.
There's an optometrist on Lexington.
Great. Of course.
I Don't want you to be worried.
It didn't mean anything, okay?
You're not drinking for taste.
Don't be such babies.
Oh, God.
It's definitely not helping.
I'm sorry. Does it offend you?
My shirt.
And my mad money. Who did this?
I stole your blouse.
I'm not joking. I had $3.00 in here.
If I give you $3.00,
will you keep your voice down?
You're animals.
I'm reporting it
to building security.
Striking resemblance
to Broderick Crawford*.
Peggy Olsen, highway patrol.
I've read three different newspapers
with three different results.
I'm sure you know something I Don't.
I just spent the night
literally in a smoke-filled
room at the Waldorf with
every republican luminary
save MacArthur and Jesus.
There's been widespread fraud.
Daley gave Joe Kennedy
every corpse in cook county.
Otherwise, Nixon wins.
It shouldn't have been at close.
But it is. It always is.
Those jingles.
When they got Frank Sinatra,
I knew they would close the gap.
So what does he do now?
Walk away? Concede?
A recount in Illinois alone
means 30 days
without a president.
You Don't want to win like at.
But you want to win.
He got 50% of the vote, maybe more.
This way he lives
to see another day.
- What happens?
- Neil from P&G said
if Kennedy is willing
to buy an election,
he's probably willing
to play ball with us.
The optimism of
the American corporation.
It's a football game to them.
- Doesn't seem fair.
- Fair?
Very good.
Where do you think you're going?
If I were you, I would be very,
very careful from now on
about the way you speak to me.
Can I help you?
What's that?
It's yours. It came to me
by mistake.
Well, thanks.
Have you reconsidered my qualifications
for the head of account services?
Would it disappoint you if I told
you it hadn't crossed my mind?
I feel strange having
to talk to you in this way.
Spit it out, Campbell.
I know that your name
is not Donald Draper.
It's Dick Whitman.
I Don't know who Donald Draper is,
but according to my friend Russ
at the department of Defense,
Dick Whitman died in korea in 1950,
and Donald Draper
dropped off the map.
Although he's 43 years old,
in which case
you look remarkably good.
- That's kind of elaborate.
- Really?
I wish I knew more.
I bet a lot of people do.
Get out.
- You're making a fool of yourself.
- You can deny it.
But I know it's true.
I can see from your face.
You should leave.
You should think about
how Bert Cooper will react
when he hears this information.
What information?
You're not who you say you are,
and there's obviously a reason.
Come on.
I would like you to reconsider
my qualifications.
You said everything
except "or else."
Assuming this information
is true, which it isn't,
it sounds to me like
you're blackmailing me.
I'm not.
I'm hoping you'll realize
that this all can be forgotten.
It's not like you're
a deserter, is it?
When you threaten someone
in this manner,
you should be aware of the fact
that if your information
is powerful enough
to make them
do what you want...
What else can it make them do?
It's very simple. And it's not a threat.
It's just a job.
Think about it.
Whitman.
Yes, Sergeant.
What is this?
This is it.
One? I'm supposed to have 20.
This is going to take a month,
and it should take 4 hours.
Well, you're whining
to the wrong guy, sir.
At ease.
This is for officers.
You can bunk next door.
I'd introduce you to the men, but
you're looking at the complete company.
Where is everybody, sir?
They were gone when I got here.
I'm an engineer.
They're in some action
5 miles over that mountain.
You want to go?
The answer is no.
The locals stopped
showing up three days ago,
which, by the way, is not good.
You're going to be
doing all the digging.
- Digging what?
- Well, this unit-- That's you--
Will be establishing
a field hospital, but first we're
going to be digging fighting
positions on four sides.
What are you doing here?
Are you poor?
- I volunteered.
- You're kidding me.
Well, they got me with college.
But I'm three years six months--
Nearly a civilian.
I'm supposed to be building
swimming pools, not latrines.
You any good with that rifle?
I wouldn't want you
to mistake me for Chinese.
Much practice as I've had, yes.
What misconception traveled down
the road and made you want to be here?
- A movie?
- No. I just wanted to leave.
I'll bet you're reconsidering
if this was a step up.
Miss Menken,
Mr. Draper is here to see you.
Please hold my calls.
Did you run over? You're flushed.
Let's go away.
Really? Where?
- Anywhere.
- Warmer weather?
Sure.
How about Los Angeles?
Mexico? I have money.
I have money, but
I have a store to run.
Don, are you well?
- No, I'm not.
- Did something else happen to roger?
No.
Something happened, and...
I want to go, and I want you
to come with me,
and I Don't want to come back.
- What happened?
- What does it matter?
Isn't this what you want?
Of course, I've thought about it.
My God. We've talked about it.
I just--
I just didn't think it would happen--
I mean, especially this way.
I just...
Don't want to be without you,
and I Don't want to be here.
I can't just leave.
- Maybe this weekend--
- Rachel.
No. This isn't how
I thought it would be.
What is the difference?
We'll go somewhere else.
Well start over like Adam and Eve.
What, are you 15 years old?
My father--
- Can't we be together here?
- There's nothing here.
What about your children?
I'll provide for them.
And live in Los Angeles?
My God, you haven't
thought this through.
I feel sick.
You're wrong. I know
exactly what I want.
You want your children to go on without
a father? You know how that felt.
Are you having an attack
of conscience after all this?
No. I'm watching you talk
because I feel I Don'tnow you.
You know more about me than anyone.
You won't even tell me
what happened.
Why are you doing th to me?
What kind of man are you?
Go away, drop everything,
leave your life?
People do it every day.
This was a dalliance,
- a cheap affair.
- Rachel, Don't.
You Don't want to run away with me.
You just want to run away.
You're a coward.
Please go now.
Get out.
Peggy, this is my office.
Does this door mean nothing to you?
I'm sorry, Mr. Draper.
I didn't know you were
coming back. I just--
I just--
Calm down.
Stop it.
I didn't mean to yell at you.
Got to be some semblance
of privacy left here.
I had to get away from them all
for a minute.
Drink this.
Sonny from the elevator
and some janitor--
I Don't know his name--
They got fired.
That's why you're crying?
It was my fault.
I called security.
They weren't even here last night.
Peggy, I need to be alone right now.
I know.
I Don't understand.
I try to do my job.
I follow the rules,
and people hate me.
Innocent people get hurt, and--
And other people--
People who are not good--
Get to walk around
doing whatever they want.
It's not fair.
Finish it.
I've thought about what you said.
Glad to hear it.
And then I thought about you
and what a deep lack
of character you have.
I can understand
your frustation, Don.
I'm not enjoying this
any more than you are.
I'm hiring Duck Phillips.
- Don't make me go to Cooper.
- I'm not making you do anything.
You haven't thought this through.
- I have.
- Really?
You're just going to go up to
the office and tell Bert Cooper.
If I have to.
- I Don't want to.
- Let me ask you.
How do you think he'll react when
you tell him this story of yours?
You expect him to promote you
- after the way you've behave?
- I think he'll appreciate the loyalty.
You haven't thought this through.
I Don't know.
But I'm pretty sure you won't be
working here anymore.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
I'm going to take care
of this right now.
Is this like in the movies
where I have a gun
and you Don't think
I'm going to shoot you?
I will shoot you.
I won't let you
hold this over my head.
So you'd rather blow yourself up
than make me head of accounts.
Why can't you give me what I want?
I've earned this job. I deserve it.
Why? Because your parents are rich?
because you went to prep school
and have a $5.00 haircut?
you've been given everything.
you've never worked
for anything in your life.
For gosh sakes, Don't you realize
you're going to lose everything?
I'm giving you a way out.
Would it be so bad?
Why is this so hard for you?
You' really going to do this?
More bad news?
If you came here
to drown your sorrows,
I'm not really much of a drinker.
No. I just wanted to say--
I'm pulling the trigger on Duck Phillips
as new head of Account services.
Good.
Well done.
what?
I have to bring this up to you.
Only because I believe
if I kept it from you
in the end it would be
damaging to Sterling-Cooper.
It has come to my attention,
completely by accident,
that Donald Draper here
is not who he says he is.
His real name is Dick Whitman,
But...
Dick Whitman died
in Korea ten years ago.
It stands to reason that...
he is a deserter at the very least
and who knows what else.
Mr. Campbell,
who cares?
- What?
- Who cares?
Mr. Cooper, he's a fraud a liar.
A criminal, even.
Even if this were true, who cares?
This country was built and run
by men with worse stories
than whatever you've imagined here.
I'm not imaging anything.
the japanese have a saying:
a man is whatever room he is in,
and right now Donald Draper
is in this room.
I assure you,
There's more profit
in forgetting this.
I'd put your energy
into bringing in accounts.
Fire him if you want.
But I'd keep an eye on him.
One never knows how loyalty is born.
- Sir, what do we do?
- Keep your head.
Don't shoot at anything
unless it shoots at you first.
What?
Shut up! Just stay down!
Do they know *** hospital?
We're nuts if they know that.
- Is it over?
- I Don't know.
- You think they'll be back?
We didn't shoot back. That helps.
You pissed yourself.
What?
Did I?
How are we doing, Lieutenant Draper?
On behalf of the President
of the United States
and the citizens of
the United States of America...
I present you with this
purple heart medal.
The concussion was minor.
You'll feel like yourself in a week.
The Colonel here has
some good news for you.
We're releasing you to
the reserves for your last 80 days.
You're going home.
That's good news.
you're going to be okay.
Lieutenant Draper, private Whitman.
You were the last person who
knew him in his chain of command.
We'd like you to take him home.
I think it would mean something.
Lieutenant Hayes, how are you doing?
On behalf of the President
of the United States
and the citizens of
the United States of America...
This is us, Lieutenant.
Lieutenant Draper?
Just go.
I can't.
There he is! I see him!
Who?
Dick. He's on the train. I see him.
No, he's right here.
but I saw him.
- I saw him in the window over there.
- Stop it.
No more of that.
It must be hard for you.
Did you know him?
A little.
you got your whole life
ahead of you.
Forget that boy in the box.
look at you.
Let me buy a soldier a drink.
...my congratulations
to senator Kennedy for his fine race
in this campaign, and to all of you--