Don't.
Previously on
AMC's Mad Men...
Don't what?
This is the one.
Who is she?
She's the soul of the world.
What does it mean?
The only thing keeping
you from being happy
is the belief that
you are alone.
Do you miss London?
God, yes.
Stop telling what to do,
I know what you want.
So do it.
I joined the army, Joanie.
You're gonna be taken care of
and I'm gonna be a surgeon.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Remind me...
when did you stop
taking the pills?
They ran out on the 2nd.
I'd say I would
expect to be fertile again
at the end of the cycle,
Although from my experience
it's more likely a month.
All this time
I've been afraid to skip one
- But it could take a month?
- Why don't you join him
for basic training?
It would boost
the men's morale.
From what I remember,
San Antonio is lovely
this time of year.
We don't know when he's going.
You've been married
two years, Joan?
Most gals your age don't wait.
We have a plan.
Jojo, I know it's none
of my business,
But I only went to Korea
because they made me.
I didn't have
a choice or a wife.
All I want to know is
if my husband and I
can start a family...
When my husband
and I can start a family.
Go get 'em.
- Walter.
- Yes?
I just want
to make sure that...
You know I've had
a couple of procedures.
I just want to make sure
they don't affect anything.
A couple?
I only remember one.
There was one before that.
Should I be worried?
Was the other performed
by a physician?
She said she was a midwife.
Well, you got pregnant
subsequently,
And I know everything
went fine here
And, physically,
everything looks fine.
Like the song says,
"whatever will be will be."
Happy new year.
Good morning,
Mr. Draper.
Good morning, Allison.
- Coffee?
- Yes please.
Ah. I'm glad
I caught you
before you left.
The flight's
not until 12:30.
Well, still you've got
to fight the tourists
for a taxi,
Then if you hit traffic...
Triborough bridge,
Somebody's always
running out of gas
and I think you know who.
So I saw on your way
to Acapulco you have
24 hours in Los Angeles.
- What do you want?
- The brown derby,
Bill asher...
he'll probably
try to cast you.
- Morning, don, Harry.
- Hello.
- Am I interrupting?
- No.
I'll see you
at the traffic meeting
this afternoon.
We're still
doing that? Why?
Just go to England already.
Stop feeling guilty.
Take two weeks...
you'll be twice as happy.
I'm happy when I'm working.
I'm sure another day
and a half of work
Will not come close
to the amount
Of fiddling about you did
in Los Angeles this year.
Okay.
Happy new year, don.
Oh, there you are.
Please make sure
he signs these.
If I don't see you,
happy new year.
Enjoy your family.
Would you like
to sign these now?
Might as well.
So what will you be doing?
Don't worry.
I'll be here
till the bitter end.
No, I mean for new year's.
I'm gonna go see
my sister in Patterson
over the weekend and...
I don't know...
probably Times Square.
I always wondered who did that.
It was a little
scary last year,
But I think we'll
have a whole bunch
of girls this time.
- And sailors.
- I'm sure.
- but for the rest
of the week,
If you want me
or someone else on your desk
for West coast hours,
- I can arrange that.
- I'll be fine.
Well, I'll let you know
when you should leave.
Thank you.
- Why is the door shut?
- I don't like pipe smoke.
- He's very considerate.
- Could you tell him I'm here?
What is this regarding?
Sorry to bother you,
but since Roger's not here,
I am sending Caroline
uptown to get me
Some fried chicken for lunch
and I know you like it.
- Interested?
- I am.
- Breast? Thigh?
- One of each.
Oh, I wanted to ask you...
I would like
to put in a request now
For a few days off
the second week of January.
You have new year's off.
My husband's a doctor.
His schedule's not flexible.
Why don't you
go home and ask him
how he would feel
About some nurse asking
for a holiday immediately
following a holiday?
I would be happy with two days.
Our financial planning
and expense budgets
for next year...
- I'll need you
to assist me.
- We can do it now.
No one knows why
we're here anyway.
Because there's work to do.
And I understand
that all men are dizzy
and powerless to refuse you,
But consider me
the incorruptible exception.
Fried chicken indeed.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have asked.
Don't go and cry about it.
Excuse me?
I said don't go
and cry about it.
Hey.
- Get off my porch.
- You actually came.
- What the hell
happened to your leg?
- It's broken.
It didn't work that well
to begin with.
How are you?
Aw. You just need
a little r&r.
What happened?
Don't fry eggs in bare feet.
Sit down.
- What do you want?
- Half of what you have.
- You've got a leak.
- I fixed the roof.
It just needs a little makeup.
- Call a painter.
- I don't know.
Once it stopped smelling,
I kind of forgot about it.
I wondered whose car that was.
- Hello, dick.
- Hello, patty.
- It's been too long.
- Stephanie.
Stephanie.
Last time I saw you,
you didn't have front teeth.
They're helping me while
I'm in my fragile state,
Although no one asked them too.
- Can I get you something?
- No, we live in South Pasadena.
It's a long drive.
Are you staying?
- Just for the night.
- Here?
Patty, remember you
told me to tell you
if you were intruding?
Try to keep her off her feet.
The cast isn't stable
and we don't need
any more accidents.
Aunt Anna, I just left
everything on the bed.
I don't know where things go.
You can tell by looking.
She's never gotten over
me flunking home-EC.
dick, fix her a drink.
- Are you drinking age?
- Yes, but don't bother.
Stephanie is studying
poly-sci at cal.
She should be studying music.
Berkeley?
Are you sitting in?
I agree with what
they're doing,
But somebody's
gotta go to class.
- Steph, are you ready?
- Why don't you two
stay for dinner?
Glenn and I have
a bridge game
at the Dickson's
And he's expecting
a dinner of his own.
Good, 'cause I only
want her her to stay.
- How will she get home?
- I have a car.
Or she'll spend the night.
You can get her
in the morning.
Okay, you figure it out.
Good night, sweetheart.
You know I'm very grateful.
If I don't see you,
dick, happy new year.
Happy new year.
I'm going to wash
the road off me,
And then we are
going to that place
with the beer and abalone.
Perfect.
Sounds like there's
towels all over the bed.
- Why am I staying?
- I wanted him to meet you
And I know you've got grass.
Hello.
Ah. Come over here.
- Is that your dinner?
- I love your chicken.
- How was the doctor?
- Everything's good.
Good.
I have to go.
Let me at least heat it up.
You can take it with you.
Peabody's offered
his place in the Poconos
for the 14th and 15th.
Greg, I can't
get away, not then.
Joanie, I have
to work new year's.
I had to trade it for January.
Then get one of
the Jewish docs to do it.
- You worked
on their holiday.
- Joanie...
You don't think
I'd rather be smelling
perfume than Lysol?
Tell me what you want me to do.
I guess it's not
your problem too.
Why don't you just not show up?
- I'll lose my job.
- We'll make it.
- Until when?
- Until I leave for basic,
And then it's just
a couple of weeks
and then I'll be home.
And then you're
going to Vietnam.
- We don't know that.
- Oh, that makes me
feel better.
Just keep marking off
the days on the calendar
While keep planning
for our future.
I'll see you tomorrow
when you're on your way out.
- You don't even know
when you're going!
- Soon.
- so I'd say Laura was
the worst roommate.
She had a nervous breakdown.
One morning she's
reading the bible
Instead
of her psych book.
The next morning
she woke me up,
Leaning over me
with this crazy smile,
And said, "morning, Stephanie.
Have you heard
the good news?"
There are worse things.
No, there aren't.
Where did you go
to school, dick?
♪ when you first try
to shoot the curve... ♪
I strung together
a few nonconsecutive years
In night school, city college.
A self-made man.
What's it like
taking off your suit
and returning to the wild?
I really don't
like how political
you're getting.
I'm not political.
I just don't understand
who's in charge.
You're in charge.
Trust me.
I work in advertising.
You're kidding me.
It's pollution.
So stop buying things.
Don't think
that's not possible.
I'll say this in terms
I will be right back
after this brief message
From Jan and Dean.
♪ just try a "Quasimodo"
or "the coffin" too... ♪
I like to think I had
a bit of a hand in that.
you and God.
Young people are gonna save us.
♪ so get your girl
and take her tandem... ♪
How would you feel
about me bringing
the kids out this spring?
Really?
You know how badly
I've wanted to meet them.
♪ you're an
asphalt athlete... ♪
So what, I'll be their aunt?
Wait till they tell Betty that.
You told me
you told her everything.
She'll understand.
I don't think
she'll ever understand.
You had to know she'd be hurt.
♪ why don't you skateboard me?
Why don't you ♪
♪ grab your board
and go... ♪
After I told her
I felt... Relieved.
I kept thinking
how small it was
- Compared to
how long it went on.
- Small?
I know. I...
It's just...
♪ why don't you
skateboard me? ♪
- ♪ why don't you ♪
- ♪ grab your board ♪
♪ and go sidewalk surfin'
with me... ♪
I could tell
The minute she saw
who I really was...
She never wanted
to look at me again.
♪ if you're FD
of sand dunes... ♪
Which is why I never told her.
- Oh, dick.
- ♪ quaint little villages... ♪
I'm sorry she broke your heart.
♪ you're sure ♪
- ♪ you're sure
to fall in love... ♪
- I hait coming.
♪ with old Cape Cod... ♪
I ought I'd play something
so you two could dance.
How the hell am I gonna dance?
I don't know how
you ever danced to this.
Come on.
Keep your hands
at 100 and 2:00.
♪ served by a window
with an ocean view ♪
- ♪ you're sure ♪
- ♪ you're sure to
fall in love ♪
♪ with old Cape Cod... ♪
So you picked this song
because it's old?
That doesn't mean it's bad.
It's kind of corny.
I think it sounds
like she's inviting us
To a very beautiful place
Where there's
no surfing at all.
Have you ever been there?
Mmm, no.
♪ remind you
of the town... ♪
But... Every time
I hear this song,
I want to go.
♪ if you spend an evening,
you'll want to stay ♪
♪ watching the moonlight
on Cape Cod Bay ♪
♪ you're sure to... ♪
I know for a fact
you did not break
that leg making eggs.
I used to love sitting,
And now that I have to,
I hate it.
I should get home.
I'll drive you.
I'll put the top up.
That's okay.
I'll hitch.
I do it all the time.
You'll get picked up
by some creep.
I guess this is safer.
So are you married or divorced?
Couldn't I just be single?
no.
I mean I'd be surprised.
I'm divorced.
Do you go on those dates
where you sit there
And ask each other questions?
It's a means to an end.
But nobody knows
What's wrong with themselves...
And everyone else
can see it right away.
thank you very much.
It was my pleasure.
So what time's
your flight tomorrow?
Noon.
Unless you think
I should change it.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
You're so beautiful and young.
Anna and I never had
A romantic relationship.
But you love her.
For lots of reasons...
And in a very different way.
I have to tell you something
And I probably shouldn't.
I promised...
I wouldn't,
But I see you two together
And I know I have to.
Okay.
Anna is...
She has cancer.
- What?
- It's why
she broke her leg.
It's in her bones.
It's all over her body.
I'm sorry.
Cancer. Shit.
I'm so sorry.
Of course she's not
gonna say a damn thing.
She doesn't know.
- What?
- The doctors said
She doesn't have long,
so there's no reason
to tell her.
Some quacks out in Pedro?
What are you going
to do about it?
My mom got a consultation.
Your mother does not
get to decide that.
Please don't make me sorry
that I told you.
I didn't want you to leave here
And not know.
Good morning.
I woke up in a panic
Because I thought
I might've missed you.
But it doesn't look
like you're ready to go.
I thought I'd stay
a little longer
if it's okay.
Hell yes.
Stay as long
as you want.
We'll see.
If I had rolled over on this,
I would've had
to smoke the dress.
How'd you sleep?
I was feeling no pain,
as they say.
In fact, I don't know
if I would've woken up
If I hadn't heard
that jet fly by.
And I thought, "oh my god.
Dick left already."
There's all kinds
of aircraft here, you know.
If we stay up tonight
and we get lucky,
We'll see something
you'll remember.
if we keep smoking that.
I've seen u.F.O.S.
There was a lot going on
during the missile scare,
But it was different.
You saw a u.F.O.?
Mm-hmm. You don't have
to do that, you know.
I want to.
I'm not gonna fight
watching dick Whitman
Paint my living room
in his shorts.
I'm so damn proud of you.
I count on that.
Does that scare you?
The idea
of another civilization
on another planet
Smart enough to find
a way to get here?
It doesn't scare me,
But the odds are against it.
Well, I saw
something once
And I'm telling you
it knocked me sideways.
I started thinking
of everything I was
sure was true
And how flimsy it all might be.
You don't need to see
a u.F.O. To know that.
That's not a great way
to think about things.
I know everything
about you
And I still love you.
Are you just gonna
paint that corner?
'cause a patch
of new paint is just
as bad as a stain.
What the hell
is going on?
- You're gonna get arrested.
- No, you are.
- That's breaking and entering.
- I thought you had
a flight to catch.
I changed my plans.
You just can't keep
your pants on, can you?
You never know what's
gonna set her off.
- I need to talk to you.
- I bet.
I heard you car
pull up at 2:30.
- She's half your age.
- What's your plan?
Just gonna let her
wake up one day in agony
and you tell her it's over?
I'm going to assume
that you've done everything
In your limited means,
but I'm here now.
She's gonna see
some real doctors
And she's not gonna
live in the dark.
We showed the x-rays
to specialists... everybody.
- It's very advanced.
- Specialists?
- You don't think she knows
something's going on?
- She had polio.
She's been going to doctors
since she was eight.
Maybe... I don't know.
She hasn't let on,
so this is the way
it's gonna be.
I understand
you feel guilty,
but don't.
Go to Acapulco.
There's nothing
for you to do here.
She is very
important to me.
I'm gonna do what I have to.
You have no say
in the affairs
of this family.
You're just a man in a room
With a checkbook.
I'm sorry.
Please do the decent thing.
The longer you're here,
The more likely you are
to say something.
She thinks you brought
the pot, I bet.
If it wasn't for my niece,
We'd have killed
each other by now.
She means well
and she's family.
I wouldn't have picked her.
I'm just saying
Not everybody has that.
You have your kids.
I bet that's better.
It's different.
I have to tell you something.
What's wrong?
I have to go.
I'm sorry.
I... I thought
I could stay,
but I can't.
Oh, I don't care.
I want you to.
I want you
to do everything
you want to do.
I'll bring the kids
out at Easter.
We'll go to Catalina,
see the bison.
Acapulco.
Do you think
there's more Mexicans
here or there?
Joan.
Open it.
They're beautiful.
It's so encouraging
to see someone happily
married around here.
Peggy, why don't you go home?
- I'll tell everyone you have
something important to do.
- Really?
- I have to buy a dress.
- Oh.
New year's eve,
big group of girls,
- You'll want to stand out.
- No, I'm spending it with mark.
My boyfriend?
happy new year.
Excuse me.
"darling, I've been an ass.
- Kisses, lane"?
- What?
I am not your darling
and I don't want your kisses.
- What?
- I thought American men
were bad enough,
But none of them has
ever so consistently
Made me feel
like a helpless,
stupid little girl.
Calm down.
I did send you flowers,
But I also sent flowers
to my wife in London.
The sentiments
were very different,
I assure you. Sandy!
Um, is everything okay?
- Yes.
- Just get back to work.
Sandy!
Did it ever occur
to you how sensitive
these deliveries were?
How often do I send flowers?
I ordered the flowers
from Rhinelander's.
They assured me
they were going to contact
your florist in London,
And somehow
they mixed them up.
It's not my fault.
Sandra,
everyone makes mistakes,
But the fact that you're
the kind of person who cannot
accept blame is egregious.
I don't know what that means.
It means I can't believe
I hired you.
You had one simple task.
I don't even know
if I can call to apologize.
What exactly did
Mrs. Harris's note say?
It said, "Joan,
forgive me. Lane."
You're fired.
Go get your things.
You'll be paid through
the end of the year.
Those instructions
you understood!
I'll have Megan clean this up.
- What are you doing?
- You inspired me.
Would you like
to sign your work?
- Really?
- Pick a spot on the wall.
You should swim as much
as you can there.
It'll clear your head.
And no cliff diving.
Hey.
You'll be fine.
You'll make the best of it.
You always do.
You know you can call me
if you need anything.
- Goodbye, Anna.
- Goodbye, dick.
Mr. Draper?
Happy new year.
hey, what are you doing up?
I figured since
we missed it here,
We could celebrate it
in Hawaii.
Oh, look at that.
I'm sorry.
I ate dinner at 3:00.
A bowl of cottage cheese
in the cafeteria?
How about a glass
of fresh-squeezed
orange juice?
Sure. The nurses
spent five minutes
Trying to get this girl's
contact lenses out.
She was screaming.
It turns out
Her friend was the one
with the contact lenses.
Oh! God!
Oh God.
- Let me see.
- I cut it really bad, Greg.
- It really hurts.
- Jesus.
Hold this.
Just take me to the hospital.
Sit down.
- Greg, you don't
have to do this.
- Would you stop?
Isn't there some
medical ethical law
- Against operating
on your wife?
I want you to calm down.
For me, this is like...
I don't know...
filing some papers
is for you.
I do it all the time.
I don't do that anymore.
I have other people do that.
It's really throbbing.
Let me get my coat.
Hey, since when have
we had that bird's
nest on the ceiling?
I usually save that for kids.
Now don't move.
One hillbilly says
to the other,
"you wanna play
20 questions?"
The other hillbilly says,
"what is that?"
He says, "I write something
On a piece of paper,
"And you get 20 questions
to guess what it be."
So he takes out
a piece of paper
And writes "donkey damn" on it.
The other hillbilly takes
a second to think and asks,
"can you eat it?"
The other hillbilly says,
"I might reckon
you could."
The other one says,
"is it donkey damn?"
Cohen told me that.
Aw, come on. It's fine.
I'm not crying 'cause it hurts.
Everything's gonna be okay.
When?
Joanie.
I can't fix anything else,
But I can fix this.
Hello?
I thought you were in Acapulco.
I didn't feel like it.
You should be in England
with your family.
Oh, too much to do.
They'll be back soon enough.
I have a sandwich
in the refrigerator.
It's very large.
No thank you.
- Do you mind?
- Help yourself.
- I received something
Rather special
from my father
for my birthday.
- What is it?
- Who knows?
He's one of those alcoholics
Who thinks
that he's collecting.
Chin-chin.
- There's no...
- no bite at all.
- well...
- ...I will let you get back
to your business.
- Ah.
- I made a discovery
As I slowly pulled back
from the records.
I can't take
any more bad news, lane.
Although things are
precarious financially,
It's been a magnificent year.
lane!
what?
Come here.
We're going to the movies.
Do you think we should?
Does howdy doody
have a wooden dick?
"Zorba the Greek"...
seen it, but would
see it again.
"it's a mad mad mad world."
No kidding.
- "send me no flowers."
- no.
"the guns of August."
I hate guns and I hate August.
It's all over the rug.
We'll have to smoke the dress.
I don't know that one.
"the umbrellas
of Cherbourg."
Catherine Deneuve.
Apparently it's for
all the young lovers
of the world.
This movie is very good.
You know what's
going on here, don't you?
- Handjobs.
- Is that right?
What percentage do you think?
Do you mind?
Monster!
You like it here.
I do. I do.
Even alone.
You remind me of a chap
I knew in school.
We followed him around
in a pack
And he didn't notice
we were there.
He died in a motorcycle crash.
Mmm.
Rebecca convinced me
That you were all
on holiday together...
Without me.
I suppose we haven't
been very welcoming.
Campbell's friendly,
Although I believe
unintentionally.
But my wife is
quite severe with people,
Including me.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I, um...
I wanted to bring our families
To New York for the holidays,
But she was terribly homesick.
We had an argument...
A series of arguments...
And she left.
I then weakened
and sent her flowers.
Huh.
Tried to, anyway.
Then we had a rather
solemn phone call
In which she told me
she was not returning.
Then she put
my son on the phone.
That's tough.
How did you know
when you were done?
It wasn't my decision.
And I've learned the hard way
Not to give advice
in these situations.
You were
supposed to tell me
to get on a plane.
Is that what you want?
Or is that what
people expect of you?
I want my beef.
Ah. Here it is.
I, uh,
Was going to call
a lady friend of mine.
I'm supposed
to meet her downtown.
Do you want her
to bring a friend?
Oh, no no.
No thank you.
What are you gonna do?
We can pretend it's new year's.
It actually is.
If you don't mind.
It's the least I can do.
- I'm not hungry.
- What? Not hungry
For this...
- Beautiful piece
of American meat?
I got a big Texas belt buckle!
- Yeehaw!
I'm thinking,
"did my mother get suspicious
and call the fuzz?"
"we know you're
practicing self-abuse.
Please come out
with your hand up."
Aw. I see we have
an anniversary
here tonight.
Look at these two...
George and Martha.
Tell me, what's it like
when your eyes meet across
a crowded men's room?
Wall street,
does it bother your parents
that he's so ugly?
At the end of the night
When it's just
the two of you,
who picks up the check?
We're not homosexuals!
We're divorced!
don't.
Oh man. Now they're
gonna fight in the car
all the way home.
"honey, why'd you provoke
the comedian?"
Okay, now welcome
a talented young musician
Whose mother says
he's the next Bob Dylan.
Yeah.
Candice, this is lane.
And this is my friend Janine.
- Hello.
- A pleasure.
I guess I was wrong.
You're not queers.
You're rich.
A warm welcome
for Rudy Jenson.
- You ladies look lovely.
- Why thank you.
It's true.
I love this song.
Really?
He wrote it.
Don't.
She'll believe anything.
- What?
Let's get out of here.
You have no mixers
at all and no food.
I love your apartment.
It's very manly.
It came this way.
I think Norman mailer
shot a deer over there.
I love deer.
Get your tail
in here and help me.
she seems to know her way
around in your kitchen.
What's that like?
I told you I don't like
Giving advice
in these situations.
Why don't you show me around?
I suppose I am
a bit curious myself.
Not in there.
What happened to Acapulco?
She does not go to Barnard.
Guys like him like that.
Come on. Let's go
in the other room.
No. Here.
- Morning.
I'm terribly thirsty.
We'll have coffee in a minute.
Just a glass of water, please.
What do I owe you
for the evening?
- Don't worry about it.
- I should pay.
The girl...
how much was she?
$25.
Fascinating.
Here's $30.
Well, I shall be running along.
Thank you for
the welcome distraction.
sorry.
All right. Gentlemen,
shall we begin 1965?
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com