Previously on Mad Men.
When I told you,
you had everything...
I was wrong.
I'm serious Don,
don't talk to me about her.
That makes me feel cruel.
You always get what
you want don't you?
I got you.
Advertising... really?
Work.
I still don't understand what you do.
Draper... who knows anything
about that guy?
No one's ever lifted that rock.
Dick?
Richard Whipin?
Holy smokes... is that you?
Season 1 Episode 5
Five G
Well, this will look good
in your office.
What, take that thing on the train
like some kid who won at the four h?
Besides, no one wants to look like
they care about awards.
But you do.
Isn't it sad?
Roger was very eloquent.
He likes to be recognized
for selling,
creative is less important.
Creative helps sell.
But he gave the speech.
Look at you in this Tuxedo.
Say it for me...
Pleasure to meet you, mrs. Draper.
Enchanted.
It's 8 o'clock.
Shit.
Oh, my lord.
Mommy,
Ethel's downstairs,
she's making us breakfast.
Sally, mommy has a headache.
What's that thing?
Daddy's boss won an award.
Daddy won one too.
An award for good horses?
Go downstairs and eat something.
I think there's Alka-Seltzer
in the kitchen.
Are you okay?
Just do it in the kitchen,
I don't want to hear the bubbles.
- Congratulations, mr. Draper.
- Thank you.
I hear advertising age ran a picture.
Fortunately, no one reads that.
That's really amazing.
I'll get mr. Campbell and mr. Kinsey,
they wanted you to know,
they were waiting but they left.
That's rude.
They said something about the
new key award going to your head.
- Congratulations by the way.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations to you too.
- Thank you, Peggy.
Congratulations for what,
being the only one on time
for this meeting?
I was just telling Peggy,
I got a short story published.
Good for you.
With The Atlantic Monthly*.
Look at that.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
What does this have to
do with you, Kenny?
"Tapping a maple on a
cold Vermont morning."
Cosgrove here got
a story published in the...
The Atlantic Monthly
You're kidding?
I look forward to reading it.
Keep it, I've got copies.
Congrats indeed!
A thing like that!
You're a writer, you write?
Yes. The weird thing is short fiction
is not my strong suit,
I have two novels.
Novels, about what?
One is about a roughneck
on an oil rig,
who has to move to Manhattan because
his wife's mother is sick.
The other one is, well,
a woman who's a widow,
she kind of got stuck
with this family farm,
no one will help her
except this boy.
Those don't even sound stupid.
Thanks.
I mean, they both sound good.
Want to read one?
I do, but I also want to talk about
Liberty Capital savings.
Right.
Talk, one of you.
As you know, Jack Carney* says
they want a new promotion,
interest rates are level,
some kind of irresistible fireworks
that bring people to the bank,
even if it's just to visit.
I hate it when they say fireworks.
Especially when they keep
talking about a toaster
with a warming tray on top,
or a blender.
A blender's nice.
Jack keeps talking about
escalating the toaster awards
in order to lure women in,
which is silly when
you think about it,
because other than
a few working girls,
most women aren't in
charge of the banking.
Not in my house.
They visit the bank.
They do.
All we do is try to get the girls in,
families,
but you know what?
Men need their own accounts,
beyond the family.
Men.
I can see that, discretion,
discretionary.
Statements sent to the office.
Yes.
Liberty Capital private account.
No...
Executive account.
That's why he won an award.
The accounts won the award.
I have a call for you
from Vics Biterbeck.
Hello, mr. Biterbeck.
It's me and don't ask who
or you'll spoil the mood.
Who's Vics?
The trumpeter.
I was thinking about playing
the horn this afternoon.
Where are you calling me from?
I just had a phone put in.
Really, instant connection,
just like that night
at the ticket booth
in Grand Central.
Midge, I'm at work.
Just get down here.
I want you to pull my hair
and ravish me,
and leave me for dead.
I'll be back after lunch.
Kenneth Cosgrove,
I think I'm gonna vomit.
Who in the hell is Ken Cosgrove?
He's from Burlington, Vermont,
his father is a salesman.
What the hell does that
have to do with it?
I can't believe he got published
and didn't tell anyone,
until it came out.
He kept walking around
like the idiot he is.
I have this story about
this crazy night I had,
where I ended up in Jersey city
with all these negroes,
and we all got along,
can you imagine
how good that story is?
No.
It is.
It's a national magazine.
That hurts too.
That was it...
That's what I called for.
You can go.
You can't call me at work.
You're scared I'm gonna get
lonely all the time,
start having conversations with you,
and ring you all the time saying,
"when are you gonna come over?"
This is working right now.
And it worked today.
Look, I'm sorry your life is
in a million pieces,
it'd be easier for you
to have one less.
I hurt your feelings.
You didn't like my call a little bit?
I'm here.
And you waited until you were done
to make me feel bad
about the phone call.
I like that you come in here,
acting like somebody else.
Must be so intense above 14th street.
And you shoot down on the train...
That look, when I open that door,
sometimes you're preoccupied,
but then you always...
Well you always...
Change gears.
I don't even think about it.
I know.
I like being your medicine.
Okay.
What's wrong with it?
Just tell me,
I can tell you don't like it.
I do!
And I love that you're sitting
alone at your typewriter,
drinking a scotch, thinking it up.
But you don't like it?
I mostly read the classics,
it seemed strange to me,
it's too modern.
Really?
That's kind of a compliment,
but I don't think you mean
it that way.
I just think it's odd that
the bear is talking.
The bear is not talking.
It's what the hunter imagines
the bear to be thinking.
I's well written,
why don't you submit it?
I was going to when
I finish dickering with it.
You can run it by Charlie Fittich,
he has one of those big
publishing jobs, doesn't he?
Your friend, Laura, kept saying
how he makes things happen there.
- Why would I do that?
- Because he can help us.
Call him, ask him
to look at the story.
Why now?
Do you know who Ken Cosgrove is?
He's an account executive
just like me,
did you know that?
My father reads the damn Atlantic.
So what!
You don't want to be a writer,
I thought it was a hobby.
He's out there,
people know who he is.
Pumpkin,
Charlie Fittich?
I'm surprised.
You can tell what this means to me.
You said you'd do anything for me.
I don't understand you.
You were so upset when I told you.
Told me about what?
Peter...
That he was my first.
Well...
This...
helps make up for that.
Let Charlie Fittich
see what he's been missing.
Okay.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Traffic meeting is starting
in the conference room.
Really?
Cosgrove, I'm serious, I think
it shows tremendous fortitude,
and I'd like to see more
of it around here,
people finishing things.
I guarantee that in the bottom drawer
of every desk in this place
is the first ten pages of a novel.
But?
The story itself was not
much to my liking,
but I think it showed an
uncanny understanding
of what most people like.
I guess so.
What'd you get paid
for that, $100 bucks?
About that.
Ought to keep you working here.
So, miss Holloway,
would you like to take the reins?
Let's start with maytag, mr. Cosgrove.
You want to complain about the copy
now that you're a big writer?
Production needs 50 percent up front,
and we're waiting on a check.
And when will you be calling
the client about that?
I spoke with them last week, and
I'll check with them
again this afternoon.
Aren't you good.
Rio de Janeiro?
The double page spread
we ran in life,
and town and country,
was so successful
they want to resize the ad
to run in Reader's Digest.
- Big ad.
- Little magazine.
Sal's problem.
Lucky Strike?
Sales are great, lawsuit is pending,
you're the one who's supposed
to keep an eye out
- on what's happening in Washington.
- After the election.
I'm sorry, do you mind?
I'll take any excuse to get out
of this meeting.
His name is Adam Wigman.
Tell him... where is he?
Reception.
I should...
I have to deal with this.
Sure-sure, you better come back now.
- I got this.
- Okay.
Can I help you?
It's you.
It's really you.
Dick,
I can't believe it.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I know, I'm grown up,
but Dick, it's me,
it's Adam...
Your little brother.
It's Don.
It says Donald Draper,
but I knew it was you.
Are you upset?
Are you mad at me?
I don't even know who you are.
I know I look different,
I grew up tall, okay?
But it's me, Dick.
Look, I'm a janitor at
American Calculator
in the Empire State Building,
and I found this in someone's trash,
I thought I saw a ghost.
I think you've mistaken me
for someone else.
You can't even look at me.
Okay, you're at work,
I can come back another time.
No.
There's a coffee shop three blocks
west of here,
Delight,
I'll meet you there at noon.
That's swell.
and everything's all set for
the Liberty Capital meeting?
Yes, of course, all set.
Well, thank you all.
I'm glad everybody could
make it sound like
they're working so hard.
I can't believe this,
it is really you.
What do you want from me?
I don't understand this.
You have nothing to say to me?
Nothing to ask me?
Dick, I thought you were dead
and you're right here.
That's not me.
Can't you even say my name?
Adam...
That's not me.
It is.
What happened to you?
Why did you do that?
Why did you leave me?
I couldn't go back there.
I knew you weren't dead.
I knew I saw you that day, hiding
in the window in your uniform.
I was only eight but
I knew it was you.
That was a long time ago.
I can't believe when I saw
that picture in the paper,
I thought, it looks exactly like him,
except around the eyes.
Donald Draper?
What kind of name is that?
What difference does it make?
People change their names.
I guess.
What happened to her?
Mom?
She wasn't my mother,
she never let me forget that.
She's gone...
Stomach cancer.
Good.
Uncle Mac took it pretty hard,
he passed too.
Are you sure you don't
want anything?
I know I've got this lump
in my throat,
I'd love to eat right now,
but I can't.
Did you miss me at all?
Of course I did.
It's good to see you.
You look well.
I would of rather had
lunch with you.
I know, but I have an appointment
with the decorator for
our new apartment,
another time, I promise.
You said you enjoyed the story.
Yes, I did,
as much as anyone can
enjoy that kind of thing.
So, you like it or you didn't like it?
It doesn't matter
that I publish it, right?
Yes, it does.
Have you been seeing Laura Still?
Yes, she's terrific,
- fun.
- She really is.
I want to talk to you
about something
that has nothing to do with this.
Okay.
I miss you.
I miss being with you.
That's very sweet to hear.
I know you're married.
It doesn't have to be more
than just being with you.
I can't.
Charlie, I...
No, I can't, I'm a newlywed.
Maybe like in some movie,
sometime in the future
when we're old, maybe then.
I want you now,
I don't want you old,
I want you now.
I know you'll never leave him.
I can keep a secret.
No, Charlie...
Please.
Sally, don't run.
Okay.
Hello.
My goodness, you're mrs. Draper,
aren't you?
Hello, you must be Peggy.
I recognized your voice.
So nice to finally meet you
in person.
This is Sally and Robert,
we're here for our portrait.
Of course,
I guess I knew that.
Is he in there?
Not right now, but please go inside.
I'll be right back.
Joan?
My god, Joan, I need your help.
- Let go of me.
- Mrs. Draper is here,
and they're having
their portrait taken,
and he snuck out, and
I don't know who to lie to.
Calm down, just breath slowly.
Mr. Draper is out and I don't think
I'm supposed to know where he went.
That happens.
But they're taking
their pictures today,
and I would of reminded him,
but he slipped out before I could.
It's his fault, he comes and goes,
and never says anything.
Where is he?
If I make an excuse to mrs. Draper,
she could catch him in it,
especially if she just leaves,
or even worse, then he'll know
that I know where he was.
Where is he?
I don't know.
You do know, and
you're going to tell me,
or I'm not going to tell you what to do.
- I can't believe you.
- Well?
He sees this woman.
He saw her the other day.
He came back all greasy and calm.
No.
God, now I told you. I'm the
worst secretary in the world.
- Who is she?
- I don't care... please hurry.
Peggy, use your noodle.
You're making this so complicated.
You go out there and you
entertain her and the brats.
Get some hershey bars from the cart,
and tell her that you don't know
where he is,
and you forgot to remind him,
it is the truth,
and when he comes back,
let him have an excuse,
he'll have one.
And you'll just start
apologizing for, well,
just how stupid you are.
That's probably what
I would of done anyway.
God, now I really
shouldn't of told you.
You shouldn't of told me.
I'm not gonna tell anybody, but
you shouldn't of told anybody that.
This isn't how I imagined it.
- I'm sorry.
- You keep saying you're sorry.
Where were you all this time?
Around, here mostly.
I'm not mad at you,
I just want to know.
I mean, look at you.
Who is, Donald Draper?
I mean, do you have a wife,
kids?
I'm gonna go.
That's it?
Want me to pay for lunch?
- No.
- Let me.
You didn't have anything.
I don't understand why
you're being like this.
When I was little, I used to imagine
this day happening, and here it is.
I don't understand... I'm family.
I just want to be
a part of your life.
Adam, that's not gonna happen.
I'm gonna walk out that door.
That's it.
I'm not buying your lunch,
because this never happened.
I don't like black licorice either.
Are you sure we should wait?
I think so,
I can't believe I forgot.
Are you missing your lunch?
No, it's okay, I brought it.
Well, you'll probably
be going out tonight,
might as well take it easy.
That's true.
Do you have a boyfriend,
a steady?
No, I work a lot.
Some blind dates.
I remember those...
The disappointments.
Mr. Draper's office.
How's it going?
No thank you, I'm staying in.
Mr. Draper treating you well?
Yes, he's been very patient
while I've been learning
the ropes around here.
Don't you just hate it when
his mouth runs on and on?
Excuse me?
I'm joking.
You probably know more
about him than I do.
You look so beautiful in that light,
you should take
the picture right there.
I did want to look good.
Mr. Draper, I...
- The portrait.
- What happened,
where were you?
We were just about to leave.
I'm so embarrassed,
I forgot to remind you.
No, I forgot to check in
before I went to the printer.
I'm such a fool, I don't know
where my head is.
I'm so sorry, mrs. Draper,
please forgive me.
No, it's nothing.
All we need is some wet paper towels
to get the chocolate off,
before we go in front of the lens.
We'll have to do that on the way,
they must be waiting for us
at the studio, come on.
Nice to meet you.
Don't worry about that.
Thank you.
They're terrible.
No, they're not.
Don was late, it ruined
the whole thing.
Carleton's always late.
You can see what's important
to them.
We are very important
to them, stop it.
How'd you like to be in
Helen Bishop's family portrait?
There's a big hole there,
believe me.
I want to take them again anyway.
Sally looks fat.
I don't think so.
The worst part is,
Don will think they're fine.
Here, maybe this one.
Blow that one up.
It will hold you until
the Christmas card.
The color is off on these too.
Am I wrong?
I really expect the royal treatment
when I go to Don's office,
and I seldom get it.
It's like walking into
another country,
where I don't speak the language.
At Carleton's, I feel like I'm stupid,
all that manhattan talk.
Our husbands...
They're our better out here,
aren't they?
Infinitely.
We took your idea of product,
and applied it directly to the bank.
Banking products not
household products.
You said banking products
weren't sexy.
We went down some
really dumb roads like
bank accounts for children,
and then Don here had this
roaming candle of an idea, Don?
I think Paul has a handle on this.
The modern executive is a busy man,
he leads a complicated life.
He has business expenses,
family, leisure,
how are you supposed
to keep all that straight?
Well, now Liberty Capital
is gonna help you with that.
What is this?
An account for a man that is private,
the statements come to
the office, not your home.
I see, for organizing your life.
If it needs it.
Liberty for the libertine.
That's good.
Does this say that to you?
It will if you put
the word private in there,
instead of Liberty,
executive private account.
What are you laughing at?
A portion of our customers
are already,
I believe, doing this,
there's just no name for it,
and we had no way to charge them.
I like the torch,
it says don't get burned.
It could start some
uncomfortable conversations
in a lot of homes, but,
It's better than a calendar.
Let's talk placement.
Hello.
I opened everything but that one.
One is about a roughneck
on an oil rig,
who has to move to Manhattan
because his wife's mother's sick.
The other is about...
You know, I just finished reading it,
it's really a great story.
Thank you, that means a lot.
It's nice to see someone's passion be
rewarded.
You know what?
I don't have a copy of it,
and I wanted to give it
to my girlfriend.
You said you got
like 50 more copies, right?
Maybe I do,
if not, it's on every
newsstand in town.
Good to hear.
You're leaving?
Yes, for the day.
Okay.
I'm going home. You can reach me
there if necessary.
I always wondered
why he's ignored me,
probably cause he's so good looking,
he can go outside the office
for whatever he wants,
most of these fellows can't.
He seemed different to me.
Well, either way, you have
to do your job.
Keep his record clean
here and at home,
honestly, if he sees that in you,
you are a solid gold.
That's my job?
Yes,
that's his private life... private,
that's how these men are,
and it's why we love them.
- I don't love him.
- Fine,
look if you're even thinking about
passing judgement, then you're
in the wrong business.
- Okay.
- You need to relax.
I have never come over here
and not seen you with a look on your
face that said, "I need a drink."
This job is odd.
But it's the best.
Listen, kenny.
- What?
- Listen,
I know I've been a bear,
but I've been competing
neck and neck
with people in this place,
I didn't know I was competing
with you too.
You lost.
Hello, sweetheart.
Hello, dear.
Well, I have some good news.
Charlie Fittich came
by the house this afternoon.
Did he, here?
I guess your lunch did go well.
Wasn't lunch, I told you that.
So what did he say? Don't tease me.
He said he was going
to get you published.
That is incredibly swell news!
When... where?
Boys Life* magazine.
What?
It's a $40 fee, and
a lot of people read it.
Are you kidding me, Boys Life?
That story was good enough
for The New Yorker*,
and don't act like those magazines
do everything on merit.
I thought you'd be happy.
For a year's work.
You don't want me
to have what I want?
You're going to be published.
Boys Life...
Probably next to some ad
for exploding cigars.
I could of gotten you
in The New Yorker,
or in the encyclopedia
brittanica if I wanted to.
So, why didn't you?
Why would you do that to me?
Why would you put me
in that position?
I talked to my father
about the house in Cape May.
He said our dates are good,
august won't be a problem.
That's good.
I wish it wasn't so far
from the city,
then we'd see more of you.
It's not that far.
And I hate you spending
august in the office.
Although I liked your girl,
Peggy, she's fresh.
As the driven snow.
You sound disappointed.
Did you read some terrible
article in look magazine
that I should know about?
I like her.
A woman can't just not remark
on her husband's secretary.
Don, are you okay?
No, I just might have to go back to
the office, I haven't decided yet.
Phone!
Hello.
I need to see you tonight,
are you busy?
For you, of course not.
Good, I'm leaving now.
From where?
25 minutes.
I don't even know what you drink.
Whatever you have.
I'm so glad you changed your mind.
Come in,
sit down.
I know it's terrible,
it's temporary, I hope.
Look at you...
You look more like you now.
I came here because
I wanted to talk to you,
and explain something to you.
Yeah, you gotta stop
that kind of talk.
This isn't so hard.
Adam, listen to me,
I have a life,
and it only goes in
one direction, forward.
What are you drinking, gin?
I found it in one of the offices,
under a couch,
three quarts, figured
I could take one.
Coffee.
I can do that.
So, no Abigail, no uncle Mac,
nobody huh?
I know, it's strange.
Your office is really nice.
I figure from that award,
you must be pretty important.
I don't know, I guess so.
Everyone always said, you were too
smart for your own good.
Of course, uncle Mac thought
you were soft,
but you're not, are ya?
No, I'm not.
What are you doing?
It's $5000.
That's all there is.
I want you to take it,
and I want you to leave New York,
and I don't want to see or hear
from you ever again.
That's not what I wanted.
That's not right.
That's all I can do for you.
You're serious, aren't you?
You thought I was dead...
Just go back to thinking that.
Where do I go?
Adam, that is $5000.
Make your own life.
I have too much here.
Its gonna be okay.
How'd it go?
Cris averted?
Papers are on my desk.
Do you want to go visit the kids?
No, I just want to go to sleep.
I want to talk to you
about something,
and I don't want you to get upset.
I won't.
I know you hate going to
my family's house in Cape May,
and I know even though my father...
No, it's great-it's great.
I'm looking forward to
it already, I swear.
But I know you don't like that my
father might be there for part of it.
I just don't like the way
he looks at me.
You took away his little girl.
I was
thinking...
Maybe we should just
buy a summer house,
something closer that's ours.
I mean, I know we had a good year.
I don't know, Bets,
I think Cape May will be fine.
We're not that flush right now.
There's nothing to be worried about,
I'd just rather wait til' next year.
Good...
Because I like seeing my dad.