Do you know how hard it is
to see you walking around here?
Previously on Mad Men.
Glen! Young man, what is wrong with you?
This room is occupied!
I'm getting another account?
It's an assignment, not an account.
I've never really
seen your eyes before.
Herman Phillips, Bert Cooper.
Actually, "Herman" goes on
my checks. People call me Duck.
Want something a little
stronger there Carlton?
I Don't want you telling Francine
that I suggested
something that I didn't.
It's $5000.
I want you to leave New York,
and I don't want to see or hear
from you ever again.
Season 1 Episode 13
The Wheel
I like this for the powder room,
but definitely not the bedroom.
- It's a little busy.
- I'm not sure.
It's not the curtains I'm worried
about, but the cabinets.
Nixon didn't stand a chance.
The Browns trounced the Redskins,
31-10.
The result of that last home game
has correctly predicted
the last six elections.
I wish someone would have
told me that.
Of course, it's really
a 50/50 chance of being right.
I want to treat you like a son
because...
I feel that way towards you.
Trudy told us that you were up for
a promotion and
you didn't get it or something.
- I wish she hadn't.
- Now, she loves you.
And honestly, I think you need
to take a little focus off your work.
This from one of the top salesmen
at Vicks Chemical.
When you started talking about that
Clearasil company you bought...
Now, that was kind of worth
bragging about.
Did you know that there's a surge
in adolescents right now?
I'll tell you, Sterling Cooper
and yours truly would love
to help you deliver that message.
See? Now that's what
I'm talking about.
The only family and business you should
be mixing is the production of a child.
And what did Trudy say about that?
About what?
Tom, loose lips sink ships.
I was just saying that work
isn't everything, you know.
It's like that song says:
tend your own garden.
What song is that, Daddy?
I don't know.
- People say it. It's true.
- It is true.
Tend to your own garden.
That means...
you know, start growing things.
Daddy!
You're embarrassing us.
It'll be the best Christmas present
this one ever had.
And hell, Thanksgiving's Thursday.
And I guess I should
go to Keppler Farm
to get some acorn squash.
What am I doing?
They have squash there.
Very good squash, actually.
I wish you would come.
Birdie, I'm a partner.
80% of my business rolls
out next week.
It just seems silly for me
to go down there
for a 12-hour Thanksgiving.
What about...
Sally and Bobby's
childhood memories?
There was no reason
you couldn't have it up here.
You know my brother's children
are animals.
They can't make the trip up here,
and I don't want my dad to be alone.
I'll take a cab to the train...
and William will pick us up,
probably in some new car.
You know what? I...
I don't think you want to go.
I'm sorry. Was I unclear about that?
I don't understand why you can't
make my family your family.
Ken is perfectly happy
to have me here.
What do you think it's like?
He's a bachelor. It's dirty.
I'm not complaing.
I don't think it's a good idea
to spend money on a hotel right now.
If you're so worried about
my well-being, let me come home.
That's not what I meant.
I mean, I know how it sounded.
Jennifer.
Yes.
I'll quit if you want me come home.
I miss you...
...so much.
Those the legendary
secret files of Bert Cooper?
No.
I got a call from Abraham Menken.
I'm sure you know that
his daughter will be
unavailable for
the next three months.
Taking some sort of
ocean voyage to Paris
and what not.
I hadn't heard that.
- But otherwise?
- There is no otherwise.
Why is this man calling me?
I don't know. Is he unhappy?
As a partner, I do not expect
your personal preferences
to interfere with our business.
Who says they have?
It was the tone of his voice.
He's her father.
That's it, cowboy.
Francine.
I'm coming in. I'm freezing.
You're in your slippers.
I've been outside waiting
for you to come home,
just sitting in the car hoping
no one would see me.
What's going on?
Are your kids home?
No. What happened?
I'm so stupid.
So damn stupid.
You're not, Francine.
Whatever happened,
you're not stupid.
My mind hasn't been so sharp
since I had the baby.
And Carlton gave me a stack of mail,
and honestly I think
I just threw it away.
And four days later,
the phone was cut off,
so I had to go to the phone company
and pay it, or, you know,
he'd have a fit.
And I had to do all
this without him knowing.
How perfect.
I don't understand.
They gave me the bill.
It was close to $18.
There were all these calls:
long distance.
MH. MH? Manhattan?
So I called one.
A woman answered.
I had just...
I said, "I'm calling from
Carlton Hanson's office. "
She said, "Really?"
I said, "He wants to have dinner
tonight at the usual place."
What made you say that?
What woman would
he be calling in Manhattan
who answers her own phone?
Married women.
Lots of women answer
their own phones.
So he's calling some married woman
from my house
while I'm upstairs sleeping?
Maybe it's a cater.
Maybe he's throwing
you a surprise party.
Do you know he spends two nights
a week at the Waldorf?
I'm so stupid.
Assuming the worst...
The worst is that I'll poison him.
He's so stupid, he'd drink anything.
I'm gonna have
a house full of people.
I'll poison them all:
his parents,
my parents...
my kids.
Stop it.
Stop that, Francine.
You're emotional.
- It doesn't mean...
- Damn it, Betty.
I know everything.
What am I gonna do?
I've been sitting outside in the car.
What do I do?
I thought you'd know what to do.
Me? I... Why?
I don't know.
I'm s...
so embarrassed.
He doesn't know you know.
I know that.
I should go.
No. Don't.
You'll be okay.
Mrs. Draper?
Sorry I'm late.
It's okay, Carla. You can go.
- You want me to unpack the groceries?
- I'll do it. Just go.
Good-bye.
First things first.
When I call a meeting,
if you arrive after me,
you are late.
Boys, the stock in our stable:
Lucky Strike, Bethlehem Steel, Maytag.
No automobile, airline,
pharmaceuticals.
Tobacco *** list.
You're Cosgrove, right?
"The power health
behind the Rejuvenator".
Actually,
it's called The Relax-a-Cizor.
- What the hell is it?
- It's weight lost device.
With a female pleasure payload.
Really?
I'm offering a $100 bonus
to the first man
who brings me a meeting
with a decision maker.
Gentlemen, here's a list of people
you should be having lunch with.
I want you to run into people,
go through old year books.
This means everybody.
Writers, too.
Bringing in business is the key
to your salary, your status,
and your self-worth.
I went to the Athletic Club today,
and I sat in the steam
for an hour and a half.
In that time, I lost 4 pounds
and learned that Kodak
still isn't happy
with the campaign for
the new slide projector.
Is any of this sinking in?
"It's true that
while simply relaxing,"
"I can get all the benefits
of calisthenics."
"A simple regimen of
three 20-minute sessions per week,"
"combined with a sensible diet,
will restore your youthful glow."
"I love the way it makes me feel."
"The Relax-a-Cizor."
"It's my little secret."
Thank you, Annie.
One more time... Rita.
"I never thought
it would happen to me,"
"but I regained my youth
and my happiness."
- Todd?
- "Just ask my husband--"
I think we're both going
to agree on Annie.
Which one is Annie?
Believe it or not, I like Rita.
She's got that voice:
randy and knowing.
Like the Relax-a-Cizor.
Annie belongs on TV with
Rita's voice dubbed in.
Norma, thank you. You can go.
Whatever the...
special properties
of the Relax-a-Cizor are,
what we are selling is confidence,
a better you.
That woman isn't a better anything.
Annie is a confident,
beautiful woman,
and you can hear it in her voice.
I can't believe
I'm in this argument.
Sorry about that, Rita.
Hi, Annie. We'll do this tomorrow.
Check with Peggy here
for your session.
If I get a hard time about this,
I'm telling people it was your idea.
It was my idea.
Just a minute, I'll be right back.
Do you have to ?
That's... risky business.
It is, isn't it ?
What darling?
You can say anything to me.
I can't provide for a child
on what I make.
Don't worry about that.
How can I know?
You can't.
Really?
You can't worry about that.
So stay here.
Hi, Birdie.
It's 9:30. Why didn't you
just stay in the city?
I have work to do here as well.
Do you know where
the slide projector is?
So you're not going to
see us for four days,
and you're not going to see us now.
Right when I walk in the door?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I just...
I had a terrible day.
Sit with me.
What happened?
Francine told me Carlton has been
having an affair.
Really.
She was in pieces, Don.
I didn't know what to say to her.
Well, what couldyou say?
I'm surprised she told you.
Why?
She's like a sister to me.
Of course she is.
I never liked Carlton.
He was never my favorite.
She should poison him.
Now you think she should kill him?
How could someone do that
to the person that they love?
That they have children with?
Doesn't this all mean anything?
Who knows why people
do what they do?
Come on.
Bring the wine.
It's actually, a hell of a gadget.
Continuous, doesn't jam.
They call it the Doughnut
or the Wheel.
They're expecting something
along those lines.
Kodak reinvented the wheel.
They're going to hear that 10 times.
They actually want you to use
the words "Research"
and "development" in the ads.
But if you could find a way
to put the Wheel and the Future
into something with some legs,
you could make me look good
my first month here.
"I never thought
it would happen to me,"
"but I regained my youth
and my happiness."
"Just ask my husband."
"I swear, he looks at me
like the night we met."
"It's true that while
simply relaxing"
"I can get all the benefits of"...
Annie, I'm sorry.
We have to get a level here.
No, we don't.
She doesn't sound very confident.
She just started.
Give her a direction.
Okay, Annie.
Confidence.
Okay.
"I never thought
it would happen to me,"
"but I regained my youth
and my happiness."
"Just ask my husband."
"I swear, he looks at me
like the night we met."
Annie.
- Yes?
- Are you married?
No.
I could have told you that.
Well, try and imagine
you're you, Annie,
and now you have everything.
You're beautiful, you're slim,
you're the beloved prize
of a handsome man,
and you have everything
when you use the Relax-a-Cizor.
It's too bad your voice
is so annoying.
"I never thought
it would happen to me,"
"but I regained my youth
and my happiness."
"Just ask my husband."
Hold on, Annie. We have a problem
with the tape recorder.
Say something to her.
Make her feel beautiful.
You know, the confidence
that comes with beauty.
Pegs, a woman who looks like that
will never sound confident
because she never is confident.
*******
Annie has guts to give the bachelor.
The juiciest gazelle
is the easiest to catch.
Can I... I have a bit of
a cold in my throat.
Can I get some pineapple juice?
There's a glass of water
in the corner.
It's great for your throat.
I didn't believe that, either.
Let's try it again, Annie.
Happy, confident, beautiful.
"I never thought
it would happen to me,"
"but I regained my youth
and my happiness."
"Just ask my husband."
"I swear, he looks at me
like the night"...
Annie.
You're married.
Maybe you put on a few pounds,
but then you got the Relax-a-Cizor,
and you're back to being you,
right now.
I don't know that I understand.
Annie, what don't you understand?
l am being me.
Just give me a second.
I'll get it the way you want it.
"I never thought
it would happen to me, but"...
this would happen to me, but... "
"I never thought
it would happen to me, but"...
Look Pegs,
******* in front of me
Don't do that to me.
Kenny, be professionnel would you.
This is not working out.
We're going to have to let you go.
You could have gone
in there and said that.
In this order,
I want you to go after her
and console her.
And after you make plans
or whatever you need to do,
call Rita.
The older lady you liked?
She's probably home with
the Relax-a-Cizor right now.
Can you get me the...
Brighton Hotel, Times Square?
- Brighton.
- Yes.
Sorry to bother you so late.
I'm looking for someone.
A tenant of yours some...
some months back.
A guest.
I'd love to know if he left
a forwarding address.
His name is... Adam Whitman.
Right. Can I ask what you want?
Just a forwarding address.
I'm trying to contact him.
He has red hair...
over 6 feet.
Now, listen.
I know who you're talking about.
Jesus, I...
hate to be the one to tell you this,
but he hung himself.
What?
Adam Whitman.
I'm sorry.
Left the building a bunch of money.
The city took it.
It was in the Post.
I hate to be the one
to give that news.
Hello.
Yes. Hello.
Who is this?
This is Dr. Arnold Wayne.
Mrs. Albertson, I have warned you,
this is inappropriate.
Are we on fire?
Don.
No. I...
dropped a cigarette
in my waste basket.
Harry, come here.
I want to talk to you.
Harry, I want to talk to you.
I can explain.
What is the benefit of that thing?
it sells projectors to people
who already have them.
Yeah, the Wheel.
Stacks, you store your slides in it,
and it's ready to go.
I took pictures for the paper
at Wisconsin.
The machinery is definitely
part of the fun.
It's mechanical.
What did you take pictures of?
Girls, mostly.
You could go up and ask them
their names afterwards
like you were going to
put it in the paper.
And some other stuff.
Artsy-craftsy stuff.
Think of it hell about it.
Artsy, like what?
Like the reflection of a tree in a pond?
Worse.
I did a whole series that was just
handprints on glass.
You know, the way it fogs up
around your heat.
And take it off, take a picture.
Black and white, I suppose.
Of course.
I was always fascinated by the cave
paintings of Lascaux.
They're, like, 17,000 years old.
The bison get all the attention,
but there are also
all of these handprints,
tiny by today's standards,
with paint blown all around them.
Signature of the artist.
But I thought it was like someone...
reaching through the stone
and right to us.
"I was here."
Are you okay?
That'll be all.
Glen?
I'm not supposed to talk to you.
Who says... Who said that?
My mother and my father.
I don't care.
My mother's going to come out.
Glen...
I can't talk to anyone.
It's so horrible.
I'm so sad.
Don't cry.
Please...
Please tell me I'll be okay.
I don't know.
I wish I was older.
Adults don't know anything, Glen.
I don't really
know how long 20 minutes is.
Of course, dear.
Don, I hope I'm not bothering you.
I just wanted to let you know
I took Duck's talk very seriously.
And without having to crack
my Deerfield yearbook,
I've brought in an account.
Good for you.
It's a piece of
Vicks Chemical Company.
Clearasil.
Better potential than any traditional
pharmaceutical, I believe.
That's a real account, Campbell.
How'd that happen?
I'm not embarrassed to say
my father-in-law's
a former salesman,
now executive there.
That's generous.
He's interested in my future.
Congratulations. I'm sure,
with a little bit of lawyering,
you're entitled to that bonus.
I got the bonus.
And Cooper gave me
some book by Ayn Rand*.
He seemed assured,
as I hope you are,
that I have a significant investment
in this company.
Well, you do now, don't you?
It matters to me that
you're impressed.
I am.
Self-worth and status.
You said it.
Thanksgiving.
It's very n-nerve-wracking,
having to deal with getting
the family together.
My mother didn't...
cook last year
because she was so sick.
And now I'm going to have
to deal with Gloria.
But it is Thanksgiving, and...
I'm grateful for things.
Like this.
This... has helped.
Don doesn't think so, but it has.
Being able to talk.
Just... Just me and you
and your little pad.
It has helped.
Still, I...
I can't help but think
that I would be happy
if my husband was faithful to me.
My brother's children are
very badly behaved, and...
he spanks them.
Don has never laid
a hand on the kids.
He's kind inside.
But outside, it...
...it's all there in my face every day.
The hotel rooms.
Sometimes perfume.
Or worse.
He doesn't know what family is.
He doesn't even have one.
It makes me sorry for him...
...when in fact I...
I should be angry...
very angry. You know?
But I put up with it
like some ostrich.
It's interesting, isn't it?
The way he m...
he makes love?
Sometimes it's what I want.
But sometimes it's obviously
what someone else wants.
I suppose it means I'm not enough.
But maybe it...
...it's just him.
Don Draper and Salvatore Romano,
this is Joe Harriman
and Lynn Taylor.
No Eastmans today, unfortunately.
They're all back in the lab.
It's a wonderful facility,
but they don't take vacations.
What do they show,
slides of them working?
So, have you figured out a way
to work the Wheel into it?
We know it's hard because wheels
aren't really seen as exciting
technology, even though
they are the original.
Technology is a glittering lure,
but there's the rare occasion
when the public can be engaged
on the level beyond flash,
if they have a sentimental bond
with the product.
My first job,
I was in-house at a fur company
with this old pro
copyrighter, a Greek named Teddy.
And Teddy told me the most
important idea in advertising
is "New".
Creates an itch.
You simply put your product
in there as a kind of...
calamine lotion.
But he also talked about
a deeper bond with the product.
Nostalgia.
It's delicate...
...but potent.
Sweetheart.
Teddy told me that in Greek.
"Nostalgia" literally means
the pain from an old wound.
It's a twinge in your heart far
more powerful than memory alone.
This device...
isn't a space ship.
It's a time machine.
It goes backwards, forwards.
It takes us to a place where
we ache to go again.
It's not called the Wheel.
It's called the Carousel.
It lets us travel
the way a child travels.
Around and around
and back home again...
...to a place where
we know we are loved.
Good luck at your next meeting.
Don, I have to warn you,
I'm not alone.
It was beautiful.
Congratulations, mein Kommandant.
They called from the lobby.
They cancelled their other meetings,
including DDB.
Not just a victory for us.
It's a victory for civilization.
There's also more celebrating.
Mr. Campbell, here.
Your father-in-law called.
He'll be in before Christmas.
I've got to get married.
No, thank you. I'm good.
- Here's how.
- Cheers.
You know what, Pete?
I've got a way for you to turn
this account into a home run.
He's on a roll.
Clearasil.
You know who buys that?
Young girls.
What a difference it makes
in their lives to be blemish-free.
I believe it does.
We have the perfect writer for that.
Peggy Olsen.
That's funny.
Freddy Rumsen and I were both
very impressed with her insight.
- Freddy Rumsen.
- If I can weigh in...
Come on. That Belle Jolie thing.
Plus you should have seen her
in that booth yesterday.
She was like Kinsey but with balls.
Stop joking already, will you, Don?
Excuse me?
This is my father-in-law.
He's expecting the very best.
I'm expecting the very best,
not some little girl
who'll walk away.
You'll have to give back
that copy of Ayn Rand.
Do you know how hard I worked
to get this account?
- Who the hell is she?
- Peggy is not even
a copywriter.
She's a... a secretary.
Peggy!
Yes, Mr. Draper?
Miss Olsen,
you are now a junior copywriter.
Your first account
will be delivering Clearasil
to the spotted masses.
What?
Don't act surprised.
Is this really happening?
Yes, it is.
My goodness.
I will do my sincere best.
Good to hear.
Mr. Campbell, here,
will brief you after the holiday.
Of course.
That'll be all.
Thank you, Mr. Draper.
I said congratulations, didn't I?
Although sometimes when
people get what they want,
they realize how
limited their goals were.
So I guess I'll put you in
with Victor Manning.
David Steuben got fired.
Fired?
People hated his work.
Will I get business cards?
Please make all your requests
through Bridget.
Of course.
Peggy, I know you know it all.
Remember, just because
you now have a door,
don't forget that once you didn't.
Think of the other girls,
or they won't think of you.
Vic Manning, I'd like you
to meet Peggy Olsen.
She'll be taking Mr. Steuben's desk.
Nice to meet you.
I don't feel so swell.
I think I should go home.
I have to stop eating off the cart.
If you're trying to find a way
to go out and celebrate,
you should ask your secretary
to cover for you.
Very funny.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
- You, too, Joan.
David and I have a deal.
No meetings in here, okay.
And no music.
What can we do for you today?
My stomach hurts really bad.
I think I had a bad sandwich.
Let's take a look.
My God.
Honey, you didn't mention
that you were expecting.
What?
You're going to be a mother.
That's impossible.
You want us to call your husband
or your boyfriend?
- I don't understand.
- Stop talking.
Now, listen, we're going
to get you up to Maternity.
No. No, that's not possible.
Do you feel that?
- My God!
- We need a wheelchair.
It hurts!
It's going to be okay. All right?
- We just want you to calm down.
- You don't understand.
We need a wheelchair!
Have Dr. Wilson in Psychiatry
Hello, darling.
Were they having a party
at the office?
Yes.
I think I should...
lie down.
That's a good idea.
Sure. Rest up.
But make sure you're awake later.
Daddy!
Would you like to try to feed him?
Don't you want to hold him,
sweetheart?
Hello?
What are you doing here?
Daddy! Are you coming with us?
No, he isn't.
Daddy has to work.
But you can drive us to the station.
I haven't called the taxi yet.
I'm coming with you.
Really?
You are?
I'll pack the car.
We'll be there before noon.
- Daddy's coming with you.
- Daddy!
Hello?
Hello.
T H E    E N D