Previously on Mad Men.
What's happening to me?
Do I need to see someone?
I don't know.
Do you have any idea how unhappy
I was before I met you?
I was thinking of leaving my wife.
Was he a good kisser?
Let's just say he had
more practice than I did.
You don't want me
to have what I want?
Why would you put me
in that position?
Your hair is so beautiful,
you look like a princess.
Well, I don't know about that.
Can I have some of your hair?
Season 1 Episode 7
Red in the Face
I know you said to call at night
but I haven't been alone.
I understand.
I have a moment.
So how is she?
It's only been a short period
in therapeutic time.
But she's making progress?
She's not particularly
forthcoming yet.
Well, what has she been
talking about?
Mostly she seems consumed
with petty jealousy's
and overwhelmed with
everyday activity's.
Basically we're dealing with
the emotions of a child here.
She wasn't always like this.
Well, we're finding that
this kind of anxiety is not
uncommon in housewives.
And let's not forget the death of a
parent is extremely destabilizing.
So that's it.
No that's the beginning certainly.
As she becomes more forthcoming,
we may be able to shed
some light on the deeper issues
as she talks more.
- There are deeper issues?
- Usually.
These are not groundbreaking
revelations mr. Draper.
I'm concerned obviously.
Of course, we both are.
Time and talk, that's what
I recommend right now.
And again, evenings are
better for me.
Well I appreciate your time.
Mona I am drinking
my milk right now.
Go to Mims.
Bring the heiress.
The mount claire air might wipe
the scowl off her face.
Call me from there.
I'll try to make it out
by sunday afternoon.
I just got off the phone with U.F.C.
And they're having the Nixon boys
stop by at the end of the week.
- With Nixon?
- No, thank God
otherwise I'd have to move
the piano out of my office.
Hopefully
he'll decide he needs us.
The ones with the best product
make the worst client.
Stop smoking so much!
It's a sign of weakness!
Do you know how Hitler got Chamberlain
to give him everything at Munich?
He held a conference at
an old palace
that forbids smoking.
And after an hour and a half
of not smoking,
Neville Chamberlain would've
given Hitler his mother
as a dance partner.
All I can get from this story is
that Hitler didn't smoke...
And I do.
Goodnight peanut.
Last one to Chung Lee's gets
to wheel Kenneth Cosgrove,
published author, home
in a baby carriage.
Hardy-har-har.
Hello there.
Good news...
Mona and Margaret are going out
of town for the weekend,
Mona's mother feel down the steps.
You're really blessed.
Come on over.
I'll put on whites, we'll pretend
it's V.J. Day.
What goes in there, an aspirin?
I suppose I could've taken
this suitcase anywhere this weekend
and I don't mean your apartment.
I got us a couple of sandwiches and
filled the thermos for the train.
Mr. Sterling this is Carol,
my roommate.
Nice to meet you, Carol.
Miss Halloway I have
an accounting question.
We will go away...
Not tonight, some weekend
coming up...
Puerto Rico.
I don't care if it's Cuba,
I need a little notice.
You've got a lot of rules red.
Be good girls.
I don't mind you staying late just
as long as you're not trying
to milk us for the dinner money.
It's work.
Just cause tomorrow's friday
doesn't mean I expect to be pulling
your head off the keys in the morning.
What are you doing tonight?
Working and going home.
I'll let you enjoy that one honey
but I was talking to donald here.
I'm on the 5:31.
Reservations at home,
I've had those...
Easiest ones to break. Besides
they love it when you keep
- them guessing. It adds spice.
- You trying to get me in trouble...
Betty's cooking.
One drink, you owe me that.
Did I miss something?
No, Don and I talk all the time
when you're not around.
In fact, we're gonna do it
right now. Don, shall we?
- Well, good night boys.
- Good night, Paul.
I love doing that.
You seem like a busy little girl...
Draper pushing you around enough?
What does that mean?
Burning the midnight oil
is not good for your skin.
No it's... it's for something else.
I'm working on copy.
On your own?
Mr. Rumsin liked what I did in
the brainstorming thingy.
Sanitary Napkins?
No, lipstick.
What I say?
It's the Belle Jolie account.
Your wife called from
the Four Seasons
they've been seated.
Thank you Hildy.
Want me to take a look at it?
I do it for a lot of the fellas.
Really?
Yeah, really.
That would be super.
Well, we're all in it together.
So they fired all the guys
in the middle
and moved up their mailroom staff
right before all the salaries
got expensive.
Smart.
Is that what we're gonna do?
We're not gonna do anything.
At a certain age they lose that.
What?
That glow of pure youth.
It's like they hit 30 and
somebody puts out a light.
I don't think those two have
30 years between them.
Hope it does-it looks
like a lot of fun.
Well, you'll have to let me know.
Jesus you must be starving.
I know I am. What's Betty making?
I don't know.
Mona hasn't cooked since
Margaret stopped eating.
They're fighting it out...
I'm the one that gets hurt.
I'll call Betty...
Tell her we'll be three.
No!
You sure?
Are you kidding?
She'll be thrilled.
When's the last time she saw you?
We'll take my car, it'll save you
a train trip.
- My eyes are burning.
- That's impossible.
That better not be daddy saying
he's going to be late.
Don't do gymnasts in the house.
Draper residence.
You're are coming home, right?
Yes, I'm coming home...
Unfortunately Roger has decided
he needs a home cooked meal.
You're-you're kidding. I don't know
if I have enough food.
Berty what do you put in
that freezer I bought you?
Frozen food.
What do you want me to say?
Betty, this steak...
Are you sure you don't want some?
No thank you, Roger.
I'm a vegetarian sometimes.
Mona has a little calorie book
she keeps on the refrigerator
always has her nose in there.
Maybe she wants to look good for you.
You got a nice thought.
Well I was pudgy as a girl
if you can believe it.
I came into Home EC in the eighth grade
with a pattern for big girls pajamas.
The teacher asked who I was
making the pajamas for.
I didn't realize how much weight
I'd lost that summer...
Swim camp I guess.
Went from tadpole
to pollywog that year.
Sounds like a lateral move.
When I was little in the summer
we used to swim at night,
in a pool not the ocean.
Warm air, light dancing in the blue.
Night swimming... it's divine.
Sometimes naked.
Believe me on those nights
it was very difficult to go to sleep.
You ever experience that, Don?
Trouble sleeping?
Never.
Your husbands a funny son-of-a-bitch
you know that, Betty?
We used to swim in a quarry.
By the way you drop your "G's"
every once in a while,
I always thought you were
raised on a farm,
someplace with a swimin' hole.
What do you say we go to
a commercial break,
brought to you by more liquor.
You two...
Jesus, don't tell me
it's your anniversary?
Don't worry, Sally got
this frosting machine.
"Mommy and daddy."
simple, to the point...
she writes like her father.
I'll get hers, you get your own.
Three on a match.
I never understood that.
Is that like three on a horse?
Trench war... first war...
They used to say first man
lights up they notice you.
Second man, Jerry takes aim.
Third one,
Auf wedersehen.
But the professional wisdom says that
one of our guys came up with that
as a way to sell matches.
Do you tell your kids there's
no Santa Claus?
He'd never do that.
Tell us another story...
A true one though.
Well...
My father was in the trenches...
With a bayonet.
Think about that.
Poking a man to death
three feet away from you.
What does that sound like?
Don never talks about the war.
The war? His war you mean.
Not much to say.
You boys used up all the glory.
We did didn't we.
Of course my old man will always
have one on me... that bayonet.
My biggest hit came when
we were running oil
down in the islands in
the south China sea.
The pacific was all about gasoline.
People forget that.
You know what, I don't like to
talk about it either.
Dear, I'm sorry.
Not much.
Now you have to tell us.
Well...
The third day we picked up
a dina circling the convoy,
a recon plane. They were mapping us
for the nip suicide submarines
up ahead-citens,
basically warheads with motors.
Made us feel good to know
we had such a dedicated enemy.
That's one way of thinking about it.
And maybe I was bored but I thought
"we should get that little plane."
bored... what about scared?
That never comes into these stories.
You're making me look
bad in front of the lady.
That's impossible.
Finish your story.
Well we gave it to them,
right at 12 o'clock.
He was going away
from us but we hit him.
I watched him dive into the waves
just beyond the horizon.
And it was strange because
we knew it was over for him...
But we didn't see or hear much.
The next four hours I took us
off course just to swing by.
Looking for a hole in
the ocean I guess.
We saw the wreckage...
No shoot, no body.
It's incredible that something
that heavy can float.
Isn't that something.
- But they gave you a medal.
- They did,
but not for that,
it was for drinking.
Can something be done
about this sadness?
What switch to gin?
Did you check the golf bag?
I might have something out in
the garage left over from new years.
I don't care if it has ants in it!
Roger please, the kids.
Sally will be happy her cake
was such a hit.
Make sure you tell her...
I ate the "M" in mom.
I can't believe you've had
two babies.
Don't do that.
You've been making eyes
at me all night.
You can't tell me that I'm not
giving you hot pants.
You smell so good.
I can make more coffee.
I just want you to know,
that when I go to sleep tonight
I will be thinking all about you.
What did you go to Russia to get that?
No I ran down the street
knockin' on doors.
Come on you two! Come on out here
and wish me a bon voyage!
I was just saying what
a lucky man you are-
beautiful children.
Enjoy it.
One minute you're drinking at
a bar and they come and
tell you your kids been born. Next thing
you know they're heading off to college.
Well I should be on my way.
I'll take this for the road.
I'll walk you out.
Magical night.
That's my car!
There you go.
Lights!
What was that?
What?
That.
Him.
Thought someone turned the oven on when
I came back in here with that bottle.
- That's ridiculous.
- Bullshit.
Nothing happened Don,
other then your drunk boss
ruining our evening.
Can we leave it at that?
You seemed to be having
a grand time.
I liked the wine.
You made a fool of yourself.
Why would you say that?
You were throwing yourself at him...
Giggling at his stories.
I was being friendly.
He's your boss!
I don't like to be treated
that way in my own home.
I know what I saw.
You want to bounce me off the walls?
Would that make you feel better?
Sometimes I feels like
I'm living with a little girl.
Humps, where were you last night?
I had a dinner with my in-laws
at the Four Seasons*, poolside.
Sounds refreshing!
Norman Mailer.
Mayor Wagner.
The Naked and the Dead*.
What's in the box?
It's a wedding present. We got two.
But, what is it?
It's a chip and dip.
Let me see.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna have to go to
somebody else's wedding.
I'd like to know what
people are returning.
What?
I don't know what to say.
You got two of these?
What is it?
You have your fingers in your ears?
It's a chip and dip.
You have your friends over.
You put chips on the sides
and dip in the middle.
- Dip?
- Yes.
We went to these people's house
and they had one.
It had sour cream with these
little brown onions in it.
It's very good.
You'll have to give me
that recipe, sometime.
Cost twenty-two bucks.
Shit!
So, I'm going to return it.
Today?
Freddy Rumsin's cousin
works at General Mills.
- We're all going to Ratazys for lunch.
- Maybe dinner.
No, I have to return this thing.
"Today," she said, I'm sure.
I like doing things for her.
You're right. I'm sorry.
When you finish shopping,
come to join us.
I hear they make a great
grasshopper, mildred.
Mr. Draper...
Mr. Sterling to see you.
Send him in.
Something for the golf bag.
That's the good stuff.
I take it you got home in one piece.
Well, I made it as far as
the Knights Inn off the deconic.
I know that place.
It's got great water pressure.
Yeah, I slept in the car.
About last night...
What about it?
When a man get's to the point
when his name's on a building,
he can get an unnatural
sense of entitlement.
What does that mean, Roger?
You're not gonna make this easy?
I don't even know what this is.
One night, years ago, I got very drunk.
I drive home to my building.
Pull into the garage.
Park in my spot.
I get in the elevator...
It's late, there's no operator.
Go up to the 12th floor. Get out.
I'm walking down the hall.
It's pink and orange.
I remember how ugly it was.
Suddenly, my key won't
fit in the door.
It wasn't my building.
So, I guess what I'm saying is,
at some point, we've all parked
in the wrong garage.
Thanks for the bottle, Roger.
And?
Betty's gonna want that glass back.
Good man!
Maybe I should get
a case of those, huh?
This is taking a long time.
Is it that complicated?
The blue box...
you must be a newlywed.
- That explains it.
- Yes, it does. Adorable.
My husband, he'd rather be
drinking at lunch.
Even when we were
newlyweds, I think.
He's in advertising.
I'm in advertising. Sterling Cooper.
He's at B.D.O.- media buyer,
Jim Wallace.
Don't know him.
That's because you're here at lunch.
Next?
I'm here to return this.
There's nothing wrong with it.
We got two.
That's why we suggest that people
register, to avoid duplications.
We did register. We got two.
Do you have your receipt?
It was a gift.
Rosemary, we have a bridal return.
- Him?
- Bridal registry.
It's a chip and dip.
We got two.
That's practically four of something.
Name?
Campbell.
I suppose you don't have a receipt?
Gosh, I wish I did...
no, it was a gift.
There's nothing here.
Perhaps your wife told you
she was registering, and in the end,
forgot to give us her name.
Her name?
Yes, it's under the maiden name.
It's Vogel.
Why would you do that?
I don't know.
Humps!
Humps the camel Campbell!
Matherton,
what are you doing here.
Getting my racket re-strung.
Men's room back this way?
Down the hall,
past the water fountain.
What are you doing here?
Returning a wedding gift.
Not mine, I hope.
No, it's a chip and dip.
Trudy's aunt...
that's Trudy Vogel,
do you mind lovely?
What is it?
It's a chip and dip.
You put chips on the side
and dip in the middle.
For entertaining.
It's a beaut!
Hell of a wedding, by the way.
Your cousin, Bethany,
bridesmaid bridesmaid.
Connecticut college
for women, indeed!
I think I found it.
That's nice.
Good to see you.
We should do this, sometime.
I'm comin' back for you.
Do you have a receipt?
No, I... I might've already said that.
It was a gift.
I can give you store credit.
I was expecting cash.
I'm sorry.
Isn't there a way we could
work this out?
Let me buy you a drink.
I have an expense account.
The best I can do is put
the store credit in your name
so you can spend it here.
I would think about spending it
on you, if you gave me cash.
It's $22.
Store credit.
Thank you.
By the way, Matherton...
He has the clap.
Same price as a chip and dip!
Amazing!
And I was gonna try
to make you feel bad,
by telling you where
Carlotta's stocking's at.
What the hell is that for?
It's for me.
22 caliber, bolt action.
Use it in good health.
Why not?
Boys will be boys, right?
You couldn't hit the side
of St. Patrick's with that.
It's good for twenty yards.
it's your 4:30, mr. Campbell.
The Nixon brain trust
is coming in tomorrow.
The nomination is expected as a lock.
All we need is an opponent.
The rumor is, Lynden Johnson's gonna
be making a play at the convention,
so we may not be going
against Kennedy, at all.
Then we have to worry about the south.
It's going to be Kennedy.
Boston Blackie won west virginia.
Now, where does that leave us?
Nixon, experienced in office,
know's foreign affairs.
He probably learned that when they
were throwing rocks at him in Caracas.
Knows the real threat of communism,
home and abroad.
He's not helping himself
keeping quiet on Castro.
True, but he's not a catholic.
Our hands are tied there.
Nixon thinks hitting the catholic
thing is a bad idea.
- They're going to say that.
- To us?
They believe it. It hasn't held up
in any of the primaries.
Kennedy keeps making
opponents apologize.
- For what?
- For being intolerant.
This is Dick Nixon
we're talking about.
You may be too young to remember
the pink lady congress-
woman from california.
He practically shot her
in the face to win.
If it is Kennedy,
Nixon will lower himself
to the occasion.
It's going to be Kennedy.
Good. Catholic son of a millionaire.
A boy too scared to do anything
but go on vacation.
I met him.
He is a boy.
He's only four years
younger than Nixon.
But has he been sitting next to
the leader of the free world
for twice that time?
He's inexperienced.
He doesn't even wear a hat.
I don't know.
You know who else
doesn't wear a hat?
Elvis.
That's what we're dealing with.
Remind me to stop
hiring young people.
America does not want some greasy kid
with his finger on the button.
Now, if the adults can weigh in?
Communism, taxes, health care.
Kinsey, you wanna write this down,
or should I call a girl in?
Hi, honey! I made a roast beef.
Just cut the strings.
More roast beef.
You know, it's just me tonight, right?
That was a wedding gift
from my aunt Letty!
And you go and get some stupid toy!
I can't believe you!
That was for us!
You're always telling me to grow up!
I can't believe you!
Halls let me ask you something.
Mr. Campbell?
I thought take you up on
your offer to look at my work,
but if you're in the middle
of something...
What's that?
A wedding present.
I really appreciate it.
You ever been hunting, Peggy?
No, I don't think so.
You either have or you haven't.
I went a couple of times
with my uncle.
New Hampshire.
I saw my cousin shoot
a rabbit by coney island.
It's an incredible sensation.
You have to be very quiet.
Take it down with the first shot,
or you scare it away.
Then sometimes, you have to go up
and finish it off.
Then you tie it to the bumper
and you go home.
But you know what
I've always wanted to do?
I would pick it up...
Throw it's back legs
over my shoulder
and I would drag it through
the snow to this little cabin.
And there,
I'd hang it up between
a couple of trees.
Cut it open.
Drain it.
Dress it.
And then I'd take
my big hunting knife,
and I'd cut this loin.
Right out of the side.
Then I'd go into the cabin
and there'd be this woman,
waiting for me,
standing by one of those old stoves
with the big black pipe,
and I'd hand it to her.
And she put it in a cast iron skillet
and then I'd sit at the table
and she'd bring it to me.
And I'd wipe my knife on my knee
and then I would eat it,
while she watches.
That would be wonderful.
I'll take a look at this for you.
Thank you.
Can I get a ham sandwich?
And you know what, I'll take a cherry
danish, the big one in the back.
Thank you ma'am, here you go.
Helen!
Hello!
Hi, Betty.
How are you?
I'm well.
And how's Glen?
I wasn't going to say anything.
I was just going to go right on by.
What's wrong?
I was going...
I was going through
Glen's treasure box the other day
and I found a lock of blonde hair.
Your hair, he says.
Well, I don't know what he told you.
Glen doesn't lie,
not when he's caught.
- I'm not saying it's a lie.
- Betty!
- He asked me for it.
- And you gave it to him.
He is nine years old.
What is wrong with you?
He was a bold man,
that first ate an oyster.
I believe that was Jonathan Swift*.
What, are we naming them now?
Look at you.
I had no idea you were such
a fan of the mulusk.
Never really gave them
a chance before.
But, I'm acquiring a taste.
It's like eating a mermaid.
You ready for another or have you
topped off your tank?
You're leading this dance.
All right, what the hell,
it's the G.O.P. .
They'll never smell it over
the stench of brill cream.
Another round.
Wait!
Are you still good with these or
do you prefer your beloved rye.
Today, I'm on the Roger Sterling diet.
Easy on the Vermouth,
another dozen of these.
Me, as well.
I've always thought you were a man
who could keep up, Don.
Anything else, gentlemen?
Did you know they served cheese cake
to the Olympic athletes
in ancient greece?
So, what's an extra lap or two
around the steno pool for us.
Two cheese cakes.
And don't let me see
the bottom of this glass.
What were we talking about?
Yes, the Russians.
Shooting those dogs into space.
I believe we've branded
them cat lovers
and moved on to the subject
of true love.
Right!
Desi and Lucy*, please!
He's divorcing her, again.
Did he wake up one morning and say,
"oh, yeah, I forgot, I hate you."
what makes a man marry
the same woman twice?
I believe, in his case,
it was the allure of orange hair.
I like red heads.
They're mouths are like
a drop of strawberry jam
in a glass of milk.
I think I woke my ulcer up.
Drinking milk,
I never liked it.
I hate cows.
You keep matching me like this, you'll
have an ulcer of your own, any day now.
One more?
Instead of coffee, sure.
But then, we should get the check.
Hey, Burty I have the shirt.
What is this?
Bobby spilled some concord grape juice
down the front of it... I washed it.
This is Ernie's shirt, not Bobby's.
Well, what do you know.
Did you have a party
you didn't invite me to?
I'll invite you.
It's going to be a dinner party.
And I'm just trying the wine,
you know,
develop my palate.
Do you want some... it's a split.
There's another glass.
How are you?
I'm good.
Maybe I will try some.
Betty...
Jill Sandifer was in the market
earlier today.
What?
Is it true?
You're my friend, Francine.
Are you coming over here to do recon?
I'm worried about you.
I don't know what happened.
I kept thinking in the car
on the way back.
"Did that really happen?"
then I just put it out of my mind.
Well, what did happen?
Whatever you heard.
I don't even wanna hear it.
I have my own version and it's plenty.
It's okay.
Honestly, I don't know anyone who
wouldn't wanna take a good poke at her.
She's so selfish.
Those long locks
and that pathetic job
at Benson's jewelry.
Carlton went in there to buy me
some earrings.
I'm sure she loved that.
Then I saw the Benson's jewelry
wrapping paper,
I almost threw it in his face.
And that John Kennedy, I hate him.
Really?
What will people think?
I think they'll be glad to know
you're not a marshmellow.
Do people think I'm weak?
No.
It's just you're so sweet
and perfect.
I'm not.
Well, it does seem that way.
Look, it'll all be forgotten.
We don't have to include
Helen Bishop anymore.
Let her know who's side
we're all on.
My mother
always said,
"you're painting a masterpiece."
"Make sure to hide
the brush strokes."
she was really beautiful.
Then I think,
you know...
Why am I doing all of this?
I'm not that vain.
What does Doctor Wayne say?
Nothing,
except, "tell me more about that."
I'm still dying to try it.
I'm pretty sure
Doctor Wayne tried to look down
my neck line the other way.
He sits behind me.
And as far as I'm concerned,
as long as men look at me that way,
I'm earning my keep.
Then every once in a while,
I think,
This is something else.
I don't want my husband to see this.
I love to be looked at that way.
You should get out of here.
Nap time is about to end.
Well, I'm just glad you're okay.
We haven't gone over the Nixon thing
you're prepared, right?
The only way.
I'm sorry gentlemen.
Mr. Sterling, Mr. Draper...
I'm waiting for service.
So am I. What are you talking about?
We're out of order.
Crap!
When will it be back up...
Shall we wait?
We've got our best man on it.
That's a comfort.
Jesus, we're already late.
I'm terribly sorry, Mr. Sterling.
It's certainly a believable excuse.
We could go back to lunch.
No, Cooper would have a seizure,
if he hasn't already.
So...
This is ridiculous!
A building this big,
what if there was a fire?
Then you're walking down.
It'd be easier.
We should check the elevator.
Maybe, it's up again.
I think we'd hear it go
on the stairwell.
You think?
Roger, I don't know.
Maybe they're late, too.
Or maybe we can get
them to come down,
and have the presentation on
the eight floor landing.
- There's plenty of seats.
- Damned elevator.
What do you wanna do?
We're almost there.
The hell we are!
We can waste another five minutes
talking about it, if you want.
Let's go.
Get behind me with that thing.
Six to go.
I've been counting.
- You wanna rest a minute?
- No, sir.
No I don't.
Keep moving.
I forgot, navy men.
I love red heads...
with big breasts.
We'll find you one if
we still have jobs.
You want me to run ahead?
Run?
My name is on the building.
They can wait for me.
I gotta stop talking.
I'm fine.
I just lost my tie clip.
I'll find it... go on.
You sure?
I said, go on!
Found it.
- Where the hell were you?
- The elevator's out.
That's quite a hike...
where's Sterling?
He's coming.
Here are the troops now.
Lou, Michael, Charlie, Don Draper.
Our creative muscle.
Hopefully, a little brains, too.
Sorry to keep you fellas waiting.
The elevator's out.
Pete Campbell, of course.
We've spoken on the phone.
He'll continue handling
things for you,
and when I say "handling,"
I mean he runs everything by me.
And of course,
my partner, Roger Sterling...
We heard the elevator's down.
Those boys over at United Fruit*,
talk about you like invented
the damn banana.
You all right.
Get us some ice water!
Oysters.
I can see that.
Twenty-three floors.
I'm just sorry I missed this lunch.
We were with some quakers.
Had cottage cheese.
Well, let's let Roger re-group.
I'll be right in.
You okay?
Fine.
Good.