Previously on Mad Men...
Don and Megan sold Heinz
last night over dinner.
Way to go!
You should be shaking her hand.
It's just beginner's luck.
Mr. Sterling will be handling
the day to day,
but everything he knows,
I'll know.
Do you know you're
good at all of it?
I have nothing, Don.
Megan!
Congratulations!
There's a point when you go from
going home on the 5:25 to the 7:05.
I didn't want
to play cards anyway.
I was supposed to talk to
Dunphy, but he's sick again.
You know, the other top
salesman in my department,
he reads all day long
and I'm out here on
the train hustling people.
I'm really having a lean month.
Okay, Howard, I knew
this day would come.
Look, I already have
life insurance.
It came with
my junior partnership.
And it's six times
my annual salary,
and after two years,
it covers suicide.
So make your pitch brief.
Are you kidding me?
What?
Look, I wasn't gonna
put the arm into you,
but you have a kid.
I guarantee you that policy
pays the company and not you.
Imagine everything you have
just stopped short
the minute they put you
in the ground.
I don't think
you're right about that.
Oh, I'm positive.
Forget it.
I'll leave that to you
and your sleepless nights.
I'm surprised
you're not doing better.
- You like my new tie?
- Yes.
You know what a new tie means?
It means I have a spectacular
new side dish in the city.
Strawberry blonde.
Tiny thing with huge tits.
24th floor, 24 years old.
I got an apartment.
What's your wife say?
She's happy because
I provide for her.
She's not worried about
what might happen to her
if something happens to me.
Aren't you worried
you're going to get caught?
I'll be right back.
I have a Jack shapiro calling for you.
Well, for Megan Calvet.
Thank you so much, Dawn.
So shot for shot,
it's "A hard day's night"
until our mop-top
in the white leather jacket
ducks into
the Chevalier Blanc Pub.
Notice the white chess piece.
Then we're inside
and we're in color,
but there's even more girls.
The music cuts
and they stare at him
like at the end of The Birds.
"You may have second thoughts
about wearing Chevalier Blanc.
It's more trouble
than it's worth."
So we've been looking
for a piece of music.
It really has to have that
sound that the movie has.
Well, that sound
is The Beatles,
who you said
are impossible to get.
Oh, don't worry.
There's a million bands
that sound like that.
Or we'll make our own.
All we want is the
chaos and the fun,
that sort of, um,
adolescent joy.
We know what
The Beatles sound like.
We'll do our best.
Great.
Well, we'll get back to you
on that and the schedule.
Great seeing you both.
You, too.
Make sure in the casting
that this guy is more
like Calvin than Rick.
Usually you have to go to one
of your finer men's rooms
to find a man like Rick.
So nothing about the applause?
It was their idea.
Now what about the song?
Like I said,
there's a million of them.
Herman's Hermits,
Chad & Jeremy,
The Merseybeats, The Zombies.
Eh, you really think The Zombies are right?
It's gotta be right.
You know what--
I'll ask Megan. She'll know.
You wanted to see me?
See anything you like?
- Are you asking if I ski?
- No.
I want to know
which skis you want.
Or take them both.
Do they explode or something?
Yes, Allen Funt sent them over.
Do you want them or not?
Because they want you.
- The skis do?
- Roger O'Hara took it upon himself
as head of the head ski company
to demand your handling
of his account over my lunch.
- Really? - Yes. You're making
quite a name for yourself.
Why are you telling me this?
Relax. It's good.
It's what
I've always wanted--
Sit back, let the business
roll in while you pass the jug
with some schmoe from
Lutherville, Maryland.
Huh.
Go on, take them.
Yes.
I suppose I will.
And I got to see that.
Where have you been hiding all day?
I was about to leave.
I've been working.
I thought you were, too.
Nope.
Why don't you come with me,
dress up another
drab client dinner?
- Don--
- Hey, let me ask you something--
When did music
become so important?
It's always been important.
I mean jingles, yeah.
But now everybody keeps coming
in, looking for some song.
And they're so specific.
You love specific.
But I have no idea what's
going on out there.
Well, no one can keep up.
It's always changing.
We're going
to Danny's Hideaway.
You have to go
and I have to work.
See you at home?
I promise.
You're leaving late.
Is it snowing out there?
No. Sporting goods
account.
And they're already giving us presents.
That's good.
They're giving me presents
and I've never even met them.
Are you a really good skier?
Like famous?
Heh.
Well, good night.
I thought we were working.
Don just called.
I have to meet him for dinner.
Nothing I can do
about that, I guess.
You can go home, too.
I don't know.
They're not right.
They're exactly
as you dictated them to me.
They're exactly like
they're supposed to be,
but they're not it.
Maybe they are.
Go ahead.
Thanks.
Good night.
- I'm sorry.
- Excuse me?
You didn't happen to see
Howard Dawes on the train?
Are you Beth?
Um, yes.
He talks about you often.
I'm sorry, he doesn't
talk about anyone to me.
Peter Campbell.
We should switch cars.
I don't know how I'm gonna
get these in there.
Except I locked my keys inside.
He should have been home by now
and I'm afraid maybe he
fell asleep on the train.
He's done that before.
Oh, uh, now that I think of it,
I saw some fellow corner him
in the oyster bar.
He may be a while.
I can notify a Locksmith
for the car and the house.
Can you just drive me home?
The house is open.
I'll deal with this in the morning.
Next time we turn,
I'll warn you.
When's the next train?
You know what?
I'll give you my number.
And when Howard calls
from the station,
I'll shuttle him home.
He' not coming home.
He's staying in the city.
We got an apartment.
"We."
Oh.
You're enough of a stranger that
I've never heard your name,
yet you know where he is
and I don't.
I don't know anything.
Did you know
that was a stop sign?
You're an awful driver.
Are you from Manhattan?
Yes.
And I just learned.
I could never live in the city.
What's wrong with it?
Well, I love it, but all the
hobos and the panhandlers...
There aren't that many.
Well, they always accost me.
I think it's because
I make eye contact.
And then I always
give them money
and I can't stop thinking about
them for the rest of the day...
Wandering around,
sleeping in doorways.
When I was little,
I tried to make my father
give one money and he wouldn't.
He said, "We couldn't
take care of everybody."
I guess we're supposed to
get used to not seeing them.
Yes.
That's exactly what happens.
Hello?
- It's me. Is Megan there?
- Isn't she with you?
Yes, we're
playing a hilarious joke on you.
She left a while ago
to meet you at the restaurant.
When?
I don't know--
after you called.
I didn't call.
Oh.
She must be at home.
I'm at home.
Maybe she went
to the restaurant
and missed you
and now she's on her way home.
I don't know where she is.
Do you know where Abe is?
Goodbye, Peggy.
It's a lovely house.
Is it harder to lie to me
now that you know me?
Howard is working,
I'm sure of it.
I don't even think he'd care
if I was alive or dead.
I'm sorry, but you're
being very dramatic.
You drove me home.
Now leave me alone.
I'm not leaving until I'm sure
you're not hysterical.
You don't know
what you're doing.
You just want
to get back at him.
Don't you want me?
You can have me.
Are you really worried
that Howard's coming home?
Hello?
Hello? Peggy?
Pizza House.
I used to be like this.
What do you mean?
Just reckless.
I can't believe that happened.
Say something.
I've had men paying
attention to me
since before
it was appropriate.
They don't care what I say.
They just watch my lips move.
I'm listening
to every word you say.
Your irises
are so blue and round.
Have you seen those pictures
of the earth from space?
I have.
I'll take that as a compliment.
It didn't bother you to see the
earth tiny and unprotected,
surrounded by darkness?
So you don't like my eyes?
This can never happen again.
What?
No, of course. I--
No, I mean it.
- Okay.
- You should get home.
I don't want to leave you here.
Why not?
I'm fine now.
I'm going to have a
snack and go to bed.
I don't want to leave you.
Thank you for the ride home.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Where were you?
Peggy said I called you and
you were going to meet me?
Oh, I went out for a drink
with Joey and Troy.
Had to lie to Peggy
to get out of there.
I've done that.
I'm hungry. I'm going to get
some crackers or something.
- You want anything?
- No.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
I'm sorry.
I had no idea he was gonna call.
It's not what you think.
Don't put me
in that position again.
I cannot lie to him.
- I lost a night's work. I couldn't sleep--
- Would you stop?
A friend of mine knows somebody doing
an off-off-Broadway show.
I read on the weekend
and then I got
a callback last night
and I didn't want to miss it.
But I didn't get it,
so that's it; it's done.
Why can't you tell Don?
Tell Don I still want
to be an actress?
Do you?
I know copywriting's hard,
but you're doing great.
You shouldn't give up.
I wouldn't tell you this if I
didn't think you had talent.
The other day they asked me to take
Stan's originals down to the printer,
and I thought all I have to do
is throw these in the trash
and they'll fire me
or at least they'd yell at me
and I could
cry enough and quit.
And then I realized
they'll never fire me.
You want to quit?
I don't know.
What do I do?
You know there are people
killing to get this job.
You're taking up a spot and
you don't even wanna do it?
I'm sorry I told you.
You didn't.
I caught you.
And then you act
like you want advice,
but you've obviously
already made up your mind.
Because he's so easy
to talk to?
Well, you can't
keep lying to him.
It's so simple when it's
someone else's life, isn't it?
You're right.
I don't care what you do.
Phil Beachum is not just the
boss, he's the head of desserts.
Head of desserts?
Please tell me he's 300 pounds.
He's big, just not
as big as you'd like.
Anyway, pat Wallace loved
the way you and Megan--
You know, your banter.
- Dawn, where's Megan?
- She's not coming.
I'm sorry.
I was just
saying how Pat Wallace
loved the Mr.
And Mrs. Draper bit.
And you're gonna go
to the test kitchen,
taste a couple of different
formulations of Cool Whip,
and maybe put on
a little show to his boss,
you know, as a courtesy.
So, Don, if you could
bring everybody up to speed.
Well, I don't know what anybody
knows about Cool Whip.
I read a 30-page dossier
that fails to use the words
"fake whipped cream."
Because it's a nondairy
whipped topping
that comes frozen and then
melts into this miracle.
Just do the bit.
Okay.
Honey, I don't even
think I want dessert.
- You love dessert.
- You love dessert
and you just want me to have
some so you can have some.
I made two.
- What is it?
- It's Cool Whip.
- It looks like whipped cream.
- Just taste it.
- Is it a topping? - Well, you can
have it on ice cream like this
on fruit or cake
or just by itself.
- Just taste it.
- So it's a dessert?
- Is it sweet?
Just taste it.
That's it.
That's the line-- "Just taste it."
People are gonna be
yelling it at the TV set.
- It's adorable, right?
- It's a nice twist
on the stupid husband
and pushy wife
because they actually
like each other.
Are you going to be in the ads?
No. I tried.
They're not interested.
Cool Whip's not interested
or Don and Megan aren't interested?
We're not interested.
- Don't you like it?
- No, I do.
Just absorbing it.
Hello?
Beth?
It's Peter.
I know who it is.
I want you to get on a train
and meet me in the city.
- Anywhere.
- No.
- Okay.
- Just a minute.
What do you want?
Nothing.
You came over to me.
You opened the door.
Are you still there?
Was your secretary on the line?
No.
I'm at a pay phone.
You're taking away
all my fears.
I mean, suddenly I don't
think about the fact
that you ride with my husband
on the train twice a day and
that you live 20 minutes away
and I'd see your wife
at the market, if I ever went.
I know, I know.
Are you sorry I called?
Just... stop.
Enjoy the memory.
Leave it alone.
I mean, fantasize about it.
I will, too.
But... don't call me again.
Don.
What's the matter?
I have to talk to you.
What's wrong?
I, uh-- I lied
to you last night.
Okay.
I told you that I went
for a drink, but I didn't.
I had a callback for a play.
Okay. So?
I feel really bad
about lying to you.
And now you're telling me.
- You do that a lot?
- Audition?
- No, lie to me.
- No.
- Did you get it?
- What?
No. No, I didn't.
But it was incredible, Don.
I think I was pretty close.
My heart was racing.
I mean, I'm rusty.
I need to go back to class,
but I realized something.
- What?
- I miss acting.
I think I gave up too easy
and I don't even know
how I stopped.
I never made a decision,
that's for sure.
We can't be
in the Cool Whip ad.
It's bad for business.
No. I just
keep thinking
I could be on Broadway
or off Broadway
or-- I don't know--
films, even.
Sweetheart...
Sometimes we don't
get to choose
where our talents lie.
I mean, what you did
with Heinz--
It took me years to be able
to think that way.
Well, I can't explain it,
but I felt better
failing in that audition
than I did when I was
succeeding at Heinz.
Because that was about
making the client happy.
Wait till you walk
down the street
and see the work
on a wall or on TV,
that's when you feel something.
Do you know that
I can't even stand
going to the theater anymore
because all I feel is envy?
And I know the next
thing is bitterness,
and I don't want to feel that.
Okay. So what
do you want to do?
I mean, there's no guarantee.
And I'm so grateful.
This gave me
so much confidence.
But I never tried
as hard at acting
as I did at advertising.
And it'll never be for me
what it is for you.
Look, I know it's uncomfortable
for you with me there.
There's a shadow
over everything.
I put you
in a terrible position.
There are 20 firms that
would be glad to have you.
I don't want to do it, Don.
You don't want to do it?
I'm sorry.
Since I was a little girl,
it's all I ever dreamed about.
I understand.
I don't want to keep you
om your dream.
You're so good to me.
So what do you want to do?
I mean, you woke me up
in the middle of the night.
It's obviously
some sort of emergency.
Well, I can finish up my work
and then help train
the new person.
You want to
train somebody? No.
We'll go in tomorrow
and you'll say goodbye
to everybody
and we'll get you on your way.
Really?
It's what you want.
I don't know what to say.
I love you.
I love you, too.
- Morning.
- Megan's quitting.
- Oh.
Yes. So I think today's
going to be her last day.
Okay.
How do you do this?
Do you want to have a seat?
It's not like that, Joan.
She's up for a part in a play,
and even if she doesn't get it,
she's decided to go back
to acting full time.
Well, I'm sure
she'll be wonderful.
Do we make an announcement?
Do we have a party?
What's the protocol?
Why don't we have the girls
take her to lunch?
I mean, she's not
disappearing, is she?
No, she's not.
Don, I'll take care of it.
There you are.
Yep, been here for a while.
Well, I wanted to
tell everyone, actually.
Megan, are you okay?
I'm not going to be
working here anymore
and it's really hard
to tell everybody.
Hey! Megan's
talking to you.
Go ahead.
I'm so sorry.
I'm not going to
work here anymore.
Did he fire you?
That son of a bitch!
No.
No, I'm going back
to try acting again.
- Are you kidding me?
- Stan.
- No, I'd better get used to it.
- Oh, I was...
- Gonna miss you.
- Me, too.
Acting is fascinating.
It's probably easier for girls.
But let me ask you, do they
always give you clothes
or do you have to do it
in your own clothes?
I-- I don't know.
Yes, they give you a costume.
- Shoes, too?
- Yes.
Break a leg.
See you around.
I think I'm in the middle
of a lot of things,
but Don told me that I was
just supposed to hand it over.
Are you sure about this?
Peggy...
I've always appreciated
what you've done for me,
not just yesterday.
I should see Joan.
That takes a lot of guts.
I'll tell you
what takes guts--
Never having money for lunch.
She owes me, like,
$15 at this point.
What am I gonna do,
ask Don? Call her?
I think it's clear
why she left.
- That's not why.
- Well, why?
Come on, reality got her.
You work your ass off
for months,
bite your nails, for what?
Heinz baked beans.
Why are you so late?
I missed the early train.
Megan's gone. She quit.
She's gonna be an actress.
Joan just told me,
like, five minutes ago.
Is that so?
It doesn't shock you?
No, not really.
What about Don?
Please. They do whatever
they want, even to Draper.
Well, the good news is
we don't have to look
over our shoulders anymore,
wondering what
she's gonna tell him.
They work it over
in their minds,
turn it off and on
when they feel like it,
and we're just there,
waiting at attention.
It's not the way
it's supposed to be.
Trudy pregnant again?
Have you seen those pictures
of earth from space?
- Of course. - Do they make
you feel small and insignificant?
No, Jennifer does that.
And I'm not small, Pete.
Don't know if you've ever
heard that about me.
Save it for your
convention whores.
Hey, keep it down.
I'm asking you
a serious question.
I like the pictures
of the earth.
I find them to be majestic.
Why do they give you
a glimmer of hope
in the midst of rejection?
A little thread
to hang on to--
A misplaced word,
a suggestion of the future.
Under a court of law, it
would look like an accident,
but it's not.
So we're not talking
about Megan
and we're not
talking about Trudy.
Why do they get to decide
what's going to happen?
They just do.
So enjoy your lunch.
I'll see you after.
I have to get my box.
Do you really wanna come
back here and do this again?
I'll bring it home.
Thank you.
I'll see you at home.
You will.
Hey, chief, good news.
Rick from chevalier
found a song they like
for the "hard day's
night" spot.
Bet it's his
boyfriend's favorite.
Help yourself.
I think it works pretty well.
Not that it matters when
they send it over, right?
♪ The leaves of brown
came tumbling down ♪
♪ remember
in September... ♪
- Are you kidding me?
- Why am I listening to this?
- You know we can't get The Beatles.
- It's not The Beatles.
This song's, like,
30 years old.
But it's happy and it's fun.
And Don thought
it was The Beatles.
- And they like it.
- Turn it off.
It's stabbing me
in the fucking heart.
Why are you cursing?
- Can you excuse us?
- Sure.
We're due at the test
kitchen tomorrow.
And they're expecting, uh...
What do you want to do?
We can just cancel it.
We're not canceling. Tell them Megan's sick.
Peggy will do it.
Sure.
I'll let her know.
I wasn't expecting to see you.
Yeah, well, tonight I go home,
have dinner with the wife,
everything's in balance.
You know, Howard,
I talked to my office
and it turns out you were
right about my policy,
so I let them set me up
with a broker.
Oh, well, why'd you do that?
You didn't even
give me a chance.
I'm telling you, aren't I?
I got all the paperwork
at my house.
I can go home, have some
supper, and stop by later.
Well, our baby's been sick.
You know, I could
just stop by right now.
- Beth's a great cook.
- Is she?
We missed you at Megan's lunch.
I guess you have
some extra work.
No. I told her I'd rather go
to my own lunch with her.
I'm not gonna lie--
I did not see it coming.
I thought she would fail here.
I feel bad.
I think maybe
I was harder on her,
scared her away.
Second wives-- It's like
they have a playbook.
I don't think she's like that.
Peggy, she's going to be a failing
actress with a rich husband.
No, I think she's good
at everything.
I think she's just
one of those girls.
Then you had every right
to be hard on her.
Did you know that he met Betty
Draper doing a print ad?
Did you know she was a model?
That's the kind of girl
don marries.
Good night.
Beth? Honey?
I don't know where the
hell my kids are.
Hello.
You have a lovely home.
This is my friend
Pete from the train.
He has, believe it or not,
an insurance emergency.
Oh.
- I really don't want to be an intrusion.
- It's fine.
We've always got
room for one more.
- Where are the kids?
- At my mother's.
Now, don't tell me--
You're... 32.
I'll be at the hotel
Pennsylvania at 12:30.
No.
I don't want that.
Then throw it out.
Your old man died young,
but in a plane crash, right?
That's right.
Howard, may I speak with you?
Where are you going?
She's got a migraine.
It's baked chicken.
- I can set a table.
- I don't know.
You've got me
in a little trouble here.
Don't run away.
Okay.
You shouldn't cook
in bare feet.
Hello.
Don't get used to this
because there is going to be
a lot of crying from rejection.
No, I'll try and hold it together.
Beef bourguignon.
Taste.
It's hot as hell.
I thought for sure
you'd come home drunk.
Megan...
It's okay.
Do you wanna
fix yourself a drink?
Don...
I love you.
You're everything
I had hoped you'd be.
You, too.
They're arranged in
varying degrees of sweetness,
the sweetest at the end.
It's like cheese.
You have to try the camembert
before the gorgonzola.
And we have to use clear bowls
because everybody
used to pick the blue one.
Go ahead, start
and we'll take notes.
- Mm.
We'll start with
your thoughts, Ken.
Well, I can't imagine it
tasting any better than that.
Welcome to the creative
cookery kitchen.
You know, I always like to
say you're in for a treat,
but today
it sounds like we are.
How's it going?
Did I miss anything?
- They just sampled "A."
- And?
It's not whipped cream, but
it's delicious on its own.
- Now you answer your wife, right?
- What?
Listen, Phil,
don's wife is sick.
This is Peggy.
She's the copywriter.
- Aw, really?
- It'll be just as good.
Go ahead.
- Honey.
- Yes, dear?
I was just going to say
I don't even think
I want dessert.
Well, I made two.
Don't do that.
Don't you wanna
know what it is?
- It's Cool Whip.
- That's right, it's Cool Whip.
Just try it.
Honey, is that
really what you want?
Yes, I want you to try it.
Don't you want me to taste it?
Yes, just taste it.
Why? Is it a topping?
Yes, and you can
put it on ice cream
and cake
and-- and fruit.
So it's a dessert, then?
Just try it already.
Just taste it.
Well...
- Thank you.
- A pleasure.
- Mm-hmm.
- We'll talk soon.
I'll be right back.
I am so thirsty.
Look, I think you did great.
It wasn't what
it was about anyway.
They know we're
going to cast it.
You think the actress can
remember to say, "Just taste it"?
You didn't want to rehearse.
You ran it through
one time half-assed.
Look, I've done it a bunch.
I knew my lines.
Do you think Megan would come
back and do it in the office?
- Megan is not the problem.
- You didn't want her there!
You were threatened
by everything about her.
I spent more time
training her than you did
and eight months defending her.
Defending her?
She was great at it!
She thinks advertising
is stupid.
No, she thinks
the people she worked with
are cynical and petty.
- Listen--
- I did everything right,
and I am still
getting it from you.
You know what?
You are not mad at me, so shut up!
I'm sorry, you can't
smoke in here.
- For God's sake, are you avoiding me?
- Yes.
What happened?
She's following her dream.
That's admirable.
I gotta say, I can see
her as an actress.
Not that she's insincere,
but, you know.
She's very sincere.
I sure as hell didn't get to
choose what I wanted to do.
- My father told me.
- I was raised in the '30s.
My dream was indoor plumbing.
You know what?
She wants to have a baby.
- This is just the beginning of
her process. - I don't know.
I suggested that path
on our honeymoon.
She said my kids were enough.
Jane wanted a baby,
but I thought,
"why do that to somebody?"
Why shouldn't
she do what she wants?
I don't want her
to end up like Betty.
Or her mother.
You gotta go home,
let her know
that there's a routine.
It'll keep you both
out of trouble.
Mona's dad told me that.
I was afraid I was going to
leave for class and miss you.
Oh.
You said you didn't know
what was going on.
I bought you
the latest Beatles album.
Start with this one.
Have fun.
♪ Turn off your mind ♪
♪ relax and float downstream ♪
♪ it is not dying ♪
♪ surrender to the void ♪
♪ it is shining ♪
♪ yet you may see
the meaning of within ♪
♪ it is being ♪
♪ it is being... ♪
♪ Love is all
and love is everyone ♪
♪ it is knowing ♪
♪ it is knowing-- ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ love is all
and love is everyone ♪
♪ it is knowing ♪
♪ and ignorance and hate,
they mourn the dead ♪
♪ it is believing ♪
♪ but listen to the color
of your dreams ♪
♪ it is not leaving ♪
♪ oh, play the game existence
to the end ♪
♪ of the beginning. ♪