Previously on Mad Men.
I'm not gonna pretend
I don't want your job, but
There's plenty of room at the top.
I found out who's moving into that
little dutch colonial down the street.
- Who?
- Her name is Helen Bishop.
She's divorced.
Really?
What do you do, just kiss
women all the time?
Women you aren't married to?
Of course not.
When I came over that night,
you know,
I was there.
I'm married now.
Season 1 Episode 4
New Amsterdam
How fast were you going
when Mr. Adams jumped from the car?
Se-sev-seventy-five?
And-and where was that,
in your driveway?
How far had Mr. Adams
gotten in the lesson?
Back, backing out?
It's not Lenny Bruce...
but it's good.
But this is better, it's funny.
This guy used to be an accountant,
did you know that?
Really?
He's not anymore, is he?
Your wife is here, Mr. Campbell.
Thank you, Hildi.
Lunch date, good idea.
You married folks,
must be nice to spend
some time together.
Hello lovely.
You can do better than that.
Trudy, you know the fellas,
Ken, Paul, and Harry, of course.
You'll notice only men
coming out of there.
I know, you all work so hard.
- How's Jennifer?
- Good,
swell actually, considering
she's still at the phone company,
nothing I can do.
That's not true, you could
give her a baby.
You're all in on it together.
Nice to see you all again.
Do we have a lunch date?
Because Hildi, she can
show you the book.
No, but I'm taking you away.
I don't think taking you
to lunch is part of my job.
Do you have something today?
No.
I thought you'd be happy to see me,
I called Hildi and
asked if you were free,
it will only take a minute,
I promise.
I'm sorry, that's great,
where are we going?
It's a surprise.
Don, I'd like you to meet my wife,
Trudy Campbell.
Don Draper, nice to meet you.
Congratulations, you're
a very lucky girl.
I know, most of my friends
can't find a good man.
Believe me, I'm the lucky one.
Yes you are.
He's essential to the process
around here,
I think we're almost as happy
to have him as you are.
I don't think that's possible.
Well, maybe you're right,
nice to meet you.
He's so nice,
not at all like imagined.
1500 square feet, two nice bedrooms,
I don't know if that includes
that maid's room.
Have to be a pretty small maid.
...and it's on the market for 32,
but Elaine, the realtor, says
we can get it for 30.
Lovely...
you know that I want to
give you everything.
We don't have to pay
for the whole thing at once,
we can get a mortgage.
I make $75.00 a week, now,
I know you're not good at math,
but that's $3500 a year.
You'll make more.
Eventually,
but if we put ten percent down,
that's an entire years salary.
Sweetheart, we're not in this alone,
we're a young couple
that needs a little help.
Did you see the sink
in the master bathroom?
It's the same one they have
in the pierre.
Hello.
Mr. Draper... didn't expect
to see you back here.
Well, we're, uh, screening
a television commercial,
it will probably look better
when it's breaking up "Bonanza".
His work is wonderful,
he's perfect for Menken's.
So he keeps telling me.
Well, I'll let you see
Miss Menken out.
How are you?
I'm fine,
my family is fine, the weather
has been spectacular.
Rachel, listen...
What are you doing?
I don't know,
I don't want it to be like this.
Yes, well...
We both know how we'd like it to be.
Can we at least have lunch sometime?
I really can't see a reason for that.
"Church bells rang out,"
"and the air was filled
with flying birds,"
"what a joyous parade
it was back at the palace,"
"no king could command
anything finer."
"The end."
The end.
Again?
Daddy ll see you in the morning.
Helen, come on,
I know you're in there!
Damn it, Helen,
Open the door!
Excuse me, miss...
I know you can hear me, miss!
Look, can- can I use your phone?
I'm her husband,
I'm supposed to see my kids,
and I- I know she's in there,
I just called from the gas station.
No, I'm sorry.
Are you serious?
I'm sure you are who
you say you are,
but I don't let strange men
into my home.
Can I come in?
Of course.
I'm really sorry, I'm so embarrassed.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Yes you do...
I was at the window.
Did you let him in?
Yes.
He's not a bad man.
Do you want some coffee?
It's a joke really,
Dan hardly saw the kids at
all when we were married,
he works in Manhattan,
life insurance,
now all of a sudden,
he can't live without them.
Of course, if he does die, I'm set.
I'm joking.
What happened?
I'll tell you exactly,
he had a lot of friends in the city,
there was poker, and tennis,
drinks at the river club,
turned out none of them were men.
I'm.. I'm sorry...
I really just meant tonight,
what happened...
Please, I figure I might
as well say it,
that's what you've all been
guessing anyway, right?
We haven't all been doing anything.
Okay...
The strangest part of it is that,
I think he's angrier at me
than I am at him,
of course, my father got a lawyer,
an army buddy who just
hammered the hell out of him.
I've always loved that house.
Hello.
He has to go right upstairs
and have complete quiet for a while,
he works so hard.
I should get back,
my kids are asleep.
Boat's in the water,
and your cousin sarah, had her baby,
named it after your uncle Skip,
I think that's nice.
Everything's already in the trunks,
I do hope you and Trudy
will be making it out to
the house this summer.
We'll try, I'm not sure I'll be able
to take the time off from work.
Work?
I still don't understand what you do.
I'd hate for you to
miss the Blackberry's.
Run into you at the club,
you're working,
at a restaurant, you're working,
taking people out to dinner,
wining and whoring,
no job for a white man.
She's made such a nice
addition to the table,
so nice and appreciative.
There's a lot more to it than that.
Advertising, really?
See, if someone were to tell me
there's a lot more to the law,
I'd believe them.
I can't explain how
business works to you.
Trudy found, an apartment
that she likes.
Did she, where abouts?
83rd and park, very nice.
Are you sure you want
to be that far uptown?
It's not that far, dad.
It falls off after 79th.
No darling,
they fall off after 86th,
it's a very nice area.
It is...
And well...
It's actually kind of expensive,
so...
we're going to need help
with the down payment.
Really?
Yes.
No, I don't think that's a good idea.
And why is that?
I just don't think it's a good idea.
You thought it was a good
idea to help Bud, when
he hit that girl on her bike in
montauk last summer,
what did that cost?
I presume it's your profession
that is responsible for
this lapse in your manners?
I'll pay you back.
It's not about the money, Peter,
you know that.
Why is it so hard for you
people to give me anything?
We gave you everything,
we gave you your name,
and what have you done with it?
Did you have a nice visit?
They're very keen on us coming out
to Fisher's island this summer.
Can they help with the apartment?
I didn't bring it up,
my dad's been having
some health problems.
Sweetheart,
what's wrong with him?
Nobody knows.
Walter, how's it going?
Never had much luck,
unless I'm playing
against Campbell here.
He's known for losing gracefully.
You know our director,
Salvatore Romano.
Did you have a good time
in the city last night?
When I come into town,
I like to just do my business
and go home.
Unwind with the psalms.
No man should have to
live out of a suitcase.
What do you fellows have for me?
Well...
We take for granted
the things we need the most,
water, oil, electricity,
steel,
I was thinking about
the last time you were here,
looking out this window at this
incredible city and saying...
"It's all steel."
New York city,
brought to you by Bethlehem Steel,
city of Pittsburgh,
city of Chicago, Detroit,
St. Louis,
full page ads in targeted markets,
newspapers, trade publications,
throw in a few billboards
so your employees can brag
to their girlfriends.
They're kind of plain, aren't they?
Reminds of those W.P.A. ads
before the war.
Walter, you've been
doing this long enough,
you know we could throw
this artwork away in a minute,
but the sentiment, the idea,
it's so basic, you feel like
you already know it,
you just haven't thought
of it lately.
Cities... are made of steel.
Bethlehem Steel!
I might be wrong, but these
feel like ads for cities!
You're making our company look like
a middleman for another product.
Well, would you prefer
an I-beam on a plate,
with a pat of butter on it?
No need to get cute, Don.
... Just making a point!
Steel is not something
that you can buy at the supermarket.
But it is a commodity.
I'm surprised,
I believe this is fairly close
to what we had talked about.
We talked about a national strategy
that would involve the virtues
of this essential commodity.
I believe it was more specific.
Walter has expressed himself...
Now walter,
if this does not meet
your expectations,
I'm sure Don can find
something that does,
right Don?
I hate to be a pain in the ass,
but, if they didn't just
lay there so flat,
I don't know maybe it's because
I'm not from a city,
they... just...
bother me!
Look, if we can persuade you
to stay in town another 24 hours,
back at the Saint Regis of course,
it would give us a chance to come up
with something with more impact,
get you tickets to a broadway show,
there's a new one, "Bye-bye Birdie".
I don't like birds either.
Well, something else then.
Pete, I think Sal can show
Mr. Blythe out... Walt.
Sorry about that,
they are good drawings.
No, the W.P.A. was a very
respected style...
20 years ago.
What the hell was that?
Come on, Don,
that's not the first time someone's
been unhappy,
give it a haircut,
he's a second time guy anyway,
I could feel that.
And I could feel he was
sentences away,
I'm that kind of guy.
He didn't like the idea.
Someone hadn't prepared him
to like the idea,
an idea he was extremely
enthusiastic about three months ago.
I'm sorry I didn't lower
his expectations enough.
You do your job, take him sailing,
get him in a bathing suit,
leave the ideas to me.
I have ideas.
I'm sure you do,
Sterling Cooper has
more failed artists
and intellectuals
than the third Reich.
You know what, I have good ideas.
In fact, I used to carry around a
notebook and a pen just to keep track.
Direct marketing, I thought of that,
turned out it already existed,
but I arrived at it independently,
and then I come to this place,
and you people tell me that I'm good
with people, which is strange,
because I'd never heard that before.
Draper residence.
Betty? Helen Bishop, are you busy?
No, I'm just finishing up dinner.
Of course.
Listen, this may be truly rude, but
I was wondering,
I'm supposed to be stuffing envelopes
at Kennedy headquarters tonight
and my sitter just canceled, and
I hate to back out because, well,
you know, New York state
is so important.
I didn't know that.
Anyway, I was wondering
if you could come over
and watch the kids for a few hours.
Right now?
You know what, I shouldn't of asked.
Well, let me just get dinner
on the table,
I guess Don can watch the kids.
Really?
Gosh, that would be
wonderful, take your time.
You're a lifesaver, truly,
I can't tell you how much
I appreciate this.
Hiroshima, I know.
Cleaning lady and
babysitter are one.
Stop.
It's charming.
That's beautiful, Glen.
Except he could wake the baby.
Glen, stop that now!
You remember Mrs. Draper?
She's going to take care of you
while I'm gone,
no ironing.
Ironing?
I give him five cents a piece,
he loves doing it.
There you are!
I swear to god, I am so exhausted
when I get home from
the jewelry store that I just
kick these off, and I never
know where they end up.
You, Glen Bishop, in bed after
"The real McCoys", no discussions.
You look very nice.
I keep the place poorly lit.
I guess there'll be
a lot of nice men there.
Yes, I guess so,
although it's mostly women.
Have you seen the candidate?
On the news, he's handsome,
but I'm not sure who
we're voting for.
I'll bring you back some literature,
I'll be back before 10:00,
I promise.
You gotta get that lux soap campaign
over to Sterling Cooper,
Janet Leigh and Natalie Wood,
now there's a day at the office.
Is that an orange?
I'm telling you- you boys,
you've got it made,
martini lunches,
gorgeous women parading through,
in my next life, I'm coming back
as an ad man.
Well, there's slightly
more to it than that.
I'd keep that to yourself.
I met his boss yesterday,
you should of heard
the nice things he said.
He's not my boss.
Well isn't that nice,
to be appreciated for what you do.
We have some great news.
Already?
Honestly you two, it's not that,
we found an apartment.
Well that's exciting too.
Yes, well, unfortunately it's
a bit out of our price
range right now.
I've been looking in the neighborhood,
- and it seems very well priced to me.
- What's it going for?
32, but the realtor says
we can get it for 30.
- Around here?
- 83rd.
- But...
- How many rooms?
Five, two bedrooms,
two baths, a terrace...
I don't know,
I'd have to look at it first.
Thank you!
Sir!
I'll take Tom or dad, you got me?
It's very generous for you
to even consider it,
but I think we'd rather wait.
For what?
Start your life already,
you're gonna be a rich bastard
on your own someday,
waiting's a bunch of bullshit.
- Tom cat!
- It is!
Your confidence is really...
well, it's swell,
but honestly, I'm not sure
it's a good idea.
I am!
Pete, this is an investment
for me and you,
And my jellybean
over here, of course.
Thank you!
You're gonna love it,
we'll be so happy there.
I knew they'd help us.
I know you did.
Come on,
you can't possibly be angry with me.
I'm just not sure taking that
kind of money is a good idea.
He's not paying for the whole thing!
It's still a lot of money,
and I'm not sure what it means.
It means we get the apartment.
Do they get to tell us
where to put the furniture?
They're not like that,
you would of taken money
from your parents.
- That's different!
- Why?
Because,
that's my money,
I'll get it eventually.
So this is my money.
Sweetheart,
he wants to help,
it makes him feel good.
Well what about me?
Well, what about me?
You always get what you want,
don't you?
I got you,
that's all I really wanted.
Excuse me, can we turn on park?
I need to meet a client downtown.
Hush, it will only take a sec.
The armory...
When are they gonna tear
that dinosaur down?
I'll be right back.
I'm in here!
Glen, I said get out!
Young man, what is wrong with you?
This room is occupied!
What do you have to say for yourself?
Look at me,
that was very bad!
You know better than to walk
in on someone like that-
that room is private,
extremely private,
well that's all I'm trying to say.
Now look at me.
Don't you think you owe me
an apology?
Well?
I'm sorry.
Well good,
that's not the way to behave, okay?
Now, it's all right,
I'm not angry anymore.
You're pretty.
Well, thank you dear.
Really pretty.
That's sweet of you to say.
How old are you?
Well, I'm the same age as your mother,
how old is your mother?
She's 32.
I'm 28.
Your hair is so beautiful,
you look like a princess.
Well, I don't know about that.
Can I have some?
What?
Can I have some of your hair?
Glen... no!
Just a little piece?
You won't even miss it.
Now off to bed with you,
and no radio.
Good evening gentlemen.
Walter, I'd like you to meet
my cousins, Charlotte and Wendy.
Ladies, it's a pleasure.
We were hoping you were
Pete's friends.
You must be the man of steel.
Will you look at that,
you could lose a nickel
in those dimples.
I thought your cousin Wendy
was a redhead.
No, that's my cousin Doris,
she wasn't available this evening.
Well, I think we can make do
with this branch of the family.
I'm glad you decided to stay over.
So am I.
Bottle of champagne for the table,
and another round of these,
plus one.
You know, I had some thoughts
about your campaign today.
Did you?
Well, I was trying to express
the essentialness of steel,
and I thought,
"Bethlehem Steel",
" the backbone of america",
what do you think?
Unbelievable!
Did Draper tell you to try
and sneak this one by me?
No, I was...
Campbell, get off the clock.
We have two lovely ladies here,
the only backbone
I'm interested in now
is right here.
So... tell me, Wendy,
what do you do when you're not
lighting up rooms with your smile?
I'm an actress,
and I take some classes at hunter.
Do you?
I would of thought you slept
all day and bathed in milk.
How was it?
It was nice, very quiet.
In case you're interested.
Thank you.
I'll be sure to look at it.
I can't thank you enough.
I hope that I can return
the favor sometime.
Please, don't even think about it.
Looks pretty familiar.
Well, I wanted to maintain
our original strategy,
but I think the word play
achieves what you're looking for,
the idea that from the acorn,
that is Bethlehem Steel,
comes america's great cities.
I know this isn't the idea
you want to sell me,
so don't sell it so damn well.
Excuse me?
The backbone idea,
Campbell pitched it to me last night.
I like it.
What backbone idea?
"Bethlehem Steel,
the backbone of America,"
wasn't that it?
Right.
It's concise, strong, and frankly,
I like that you were so
enthusiastic about it,
you couldn't wait to tell me.
Thanks again, boys.
Pleasure to make you happy, Walt.
Hope your visit to New York
was productive.
I'm warming to the place.
Nice work.
I told you I had ideas.
Yes you did.
Good one,
enjoy it.
You know what I think?
I think I did something good,
and you got the compliment for it.
Listen Pete...
I need you to go get
a cardboard box,
put your things in it,
okay?
You picked the wrong time
to buy an apartment.
Everybody out...
now!
Remember Pete Campbell's last day?
It's today.
What happened?
While I was breaking my neck trying
to fix the hash he made yesterday,
he was out at the St. Regis
pitching copy...
His copy!
That little shit.
It was hard to see her,
all alone like that,
supporting herself with that
sad little job at the jewelry store,
frozen food.
I mean I know she gets
some kind of help, but
still, she looks so exhausted.
She tries to put on a brave face.
Honestly, I think she's jealous of me.
I've seen it before,
I was in a sority.
I mean, seeing happy
families all around,
but I don't know what I can do, I mean,
I can't just disappear, I live there.
Of course, my real concern
is those children.
I mean, the baby won't know the
difference but that poor little boy.
The person taking care of him
isn't giving him what he needs.
You know?
Gentlemen, please.
You really love that thing.
You were cute back then.
Pete Campbell?
On his way out.
Sorry to hear that.
Well, can't be avoided, I'm afraid.
I wish I could agree with that.
He's a junior account executive
who brought his own idea
to a client,
in a bar!
There are rules.
There are other rules.
What's the problem?
New York city is a marvelous machine,
filled with a mesh of levers
and gears and springs,
like a fine watch wound tight,
always ticking.
Sounds more like a bomb.
How much do you know
about Pete's family?
Nothing, except they put out
a mediocre product.
His mother is
Dorothy Dikeman Campbell,
the Dikemans owned pretty much
everything north of 125th street,
which I don't know how good
your geography is,
but that's a fair chunk of the island.
So they're rich, so what?
Well, no...
His grandfather dropped it
all in '29... panicked.
Some people have
no confidence in this country.
What's your concern then?
Well, I don't want
Dorothy Dikeman Campbell
standing on the dock at
Fisher's island this summer,
talking about how badly
Sterling Cooper treated her son.
I don't think any of us want that.
We lose him,
we lose our entree to
Buckley deak, the Maid stone club,
the Century club, dartmouth,
Gracie mansion sometimes.
It's a marquee issue for us.
See my point?
Absolutely.
He's more valuable
to the agency than I am.
Don't fool yourself,
there's a Pete Campbell
at every agency out there.
Well, let's get one
of the other ones.
You're going to need
a stronger stomach,
if you're going to be
back in the kitchen
seeing how the sausage is made.
Thought it was a big watch.
You handle the words,
you know how much
we want you here with us.
No doubt about that.
Don's a big boy, Burt...
Aren't you Don?
Well, thank you, sir.
There you go!
I'm glad we're all better now.
what you did...
is totally unacceptable.
I realize that.
I want you to be very clear
about this, you were fired.
I wanted you out,
Cooper wanted you out,
and you would be
if it weren't for this man.
He thought you deserved
another chance.
That's right,
he fought for you.
I don't know what to say.
Say nothing. You're here,
because of Don Draper's largess.
Thank you- thank you so much.
Now, I know that your generation
went to college
instead of serving,
so I'll illuminate you,
this man is your commanding officer,
you live and die in his shadow,
understood?
- I won't let you down, Don.
- Jesus, Campbell!
Don't ever say that.
I bet daily friendship
with that bottle
attracts more people to advertising
than any salary you could dream of.
That's why I got in.
So enjoy it.
Doing my best here.
Enough!
You don't know how to drink,
your whole generation.
You drink for the wrong reasons.
My generation,
we drink because it's good,
because it feels better than
unbuttoning your collar,
because we deserve it.
We drink because it's what men do.
What about shaky hands?
I see a lot of that too
with you boys.
No joke.
Your kind, with your gloomy
thoughts and your worries,
you're all busy licking
some imaginary wound.
Not all imaginary.
Yeah, boo hoo.
Maybe I'm not as comfortable
being powerless as you are.
Pardon?
You know, you shouldn't compete
with Pete Campbell.
- I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
Not on a personal level,
but for the world.
I don't know, maybe every generation
thinks the next one
is the end of it all.
I bet there were people in the bible
walking around complaining
about kids today.
Kids today, they have
no one to look up to...
Cause they're looking up to us.
Of course, if you're not going to
have live-in help,
that back room can be used
for any number of things.
I don't think we'll be having
live-in help
just yet, do you sweetheart?
No, I think we'll be managing
on our own for now.
I'm so glad you could come.
I'd like you to meet
Mrs. Clifford Lyman,
she'll be one of your new neighbors,
and she's on the co-op board.
Of course, you know these two.
Where's the nursery at?
Thank you, Tom.
Now, I don't want to hear that again.
Mrs. Lyman, Trudy Campbell,
so nice to meet you.
Well aren't you darling,
the two of you.
A pleasure.
Now, I know I shouldn't ask,
but I have to,
your mother in-law
was just telling me
that your great-great grandfather
was a farmer with Isaac Roosevelt,
is that right?
Yes, that's true.
That was Nicholas Dikeman, right?
On his mother's side.
Can you imagine, orchards
on 204th street?
He's buried at the church
of the intersession.
My goodness,
wait until I tell my husband
there's going to be a Dikeman living
in the building, he'll be so thrilled.
Sweetheart, tell
Mrs. Lyman the story
about your great-great aunt
getting in that fight with
the british soldier and the hessians.
You tell it dear,
you tell it so much better than I do.
Well, I think it was
his great-great aunt, or
great-great-great, I'm not sure,
but it was before
the revolutionary war,
and the Dikemans owned
a large tract of land...
"Manhattan" by Ella Fitzgerald.