General Motors, General Electric,
lon Physics Corporation,
Bell Telephone Laboratories,
Cosmic Inc.,
Electro-Optical Systems, Incorporated,
Texas Instruments, Inc.,
General Dynamics Corporation,
Hughes Aircraft, Martin Marietta,
Westinghouse, Aerojet,
Radio Corporation of America,
semi-conductors and materials division.
Sounds like a hell of a stock portfolio.
It's everyone who's building a rocket.
Do you know, if we stay in Beverly Hills,
even though the convention's
in Santa Monica,
we'll be halfway to Pasadena.
Pasadena?
Isn't it just people with T. B?
Jet Propulsion Laboratories
and Ray Bradbury.
As much as I'd like to indulge
your Twilight Zone fantasy
of being shot into space...
Believe me, it's our fantasy, too.
This is a business trip.
I don't want either of you coming back tan.
What if I have to play golf?
As long as you lose.
Crab Colson guarantees there will be
some astronauts there.
Really? My nephews
would love an autograph.
Astronauts love golf.
I'll see what I can do.
You're there to sell,
but you're also there to listen.
Every scientist, engineer,
and general is trying
to figure out a way
to put a man on the moon
or blow up Moscow,
whichever one costs more.
We have to explain to them
how we can help them spend that money.
Well, it certainly would
behoove us to find out...
Campbell, you do the talking.
Kinsey, you do the listening.
Don, you wanted me to remind them
about the congressmen.
We know.
They control the purse strings.
No. They are the customer.
They want aerospace in their districts.
Let them know that we can help them
bring these contracts home.
Did you read anything that she prepared?
Maybe I should send her.
You know I'll stay out of your way.
Of course.
Lounging at the pool.
They'll think you're
a young Barbara Stanwyck.
Doesn't that sound like fun?
If you're there, it will make me look
less serious in the office.
Next time.
It's a week, Tweety.
I suppose I can go to
my parents' place in Rehoboth.
Now you're making me feel bad.
Is that the only alternative?
They keep asking to spend time with me.
Well, us.
They're concerned.
About what?
Nothing's happening.
Why do you insist on making me
angry before I go to bed?
There are some very reputable agencies.
We can't even talk about this?
Do I have to put my foot down?
What's wrong with it?
It's someone else's child.
Once you see a beautiful little baby,
you'll fall in love.
You know you will.
It's not natural.
I felt that way.
But it changed.
We would have our pick.
We are ideal candidates.
We have means,
and we've been to doctors,
so it's on the record that it's something
we've been wanting for a long time.
Do your parents just think
I say no to everything?
We're not related by blood,
and you love me.
Hello.
It's me.
What time is it?
It's 10:00. Are you sleeping?
No.
William called.
My father had a stroke.
Jesus.
Three days ago.
Gloria didn't even call me.
She had William call.
Is it bad?
She said he's up and around, talking,
but she wouldn't put him on the phone.
I'm coming to get you.
No.
Bets, it's not up for discussion.
Take the kids to Francine.
I don't want to wake them.
Fine.
I'll be by in the morning.
God.
You know, I've been
dreaming about a suitcase?
Everything's gonna be okay.
Sure.
Everything's perfect.
I'll be by at 8.
Bye-bye.
Hello, Betty.
Hello, Gloria.
Hello, Don.
Look at the two of you.
I swear to you,
the doctors say it's not serious.
We can get a room down the road
at the William Penn.
Nonsense.
Where is he? Can I see him?
He's getting dressed.
They said he should do things on his own.
Come sit.
Don't do that.
We're supposed to keep it dim.
I don't know why.
Let me check on him.
William. I wasn't expecting you.
- Good morning.
- Look who's here.
He doesn't seem that bad.
Don, good to see you.
Sorry about your dad.
We'll get by, right?
Judy's coming later.
She's dropping the girls off at her mother's.
Gloria, everything is copasetic.
It'll be nice to see her.
It's an angel.
Hi, Daddy.
That's what I needed.
Hello, Don.
Get that look off your face.
Good to see you, Gene.
I'll take a visit from you two
any way I can get it.
Where are the munchkins?
With a neighbor.
Pop, did you see Don's car?
You finally step up to a Lincoln?
Coupe De Ville.
Ice-blue, white top.
Very nice.
How you feeling, Daddy?
It's a tempest in a teapot.
You should've seen her in the ambulance.
Well, we were halfway to the hospital
before I noticed I was in my nightie.
A woman my age should not travel that way.
I wish you'd called earlier.
The other partners at Don's firm
know all kinds of doctors.
In New York, right,
where everything's better.
Always with her brow in a knit,
my Ruthie here.
Ruthie, my love, have you offered
everybody coffee?
I'm Betty.
Of course you are.
Gene, this is Betty, your daughter.
It's not Ruth. Ruth is dead.
Nobody wants coffee, Daddy.
Don, you were able to get off work?
I'm here.
- You want a drink?
- I'll get some ice.
What did the doctors say?
It's just like last time.
What?
Last time? This happened before?
Don't get mad at her.
It's a couple little strokes.
Runs in the family.
You know Gene.
Always has to be the one
taking care of things.
So, Don, how did you come?
Did you take the Turnpike?
Yes.
Look at this. It's my lunch date.
Hello, baby. You're early.
You remember Ken and Pete?
Hello, Sheila.
Want to get in a few more meals
before you lose him to the Golden West?
What are you talking about?
We're going to Los Angeles together.
It's horrible, but somebody has to go.
Where?
Californ-l-A.
Thank you, Pete.
Come on, Campbell.
Time to put something else in that mouth.
Nice to see you.
I was going to tell you at lunch.
Why are you going to Los Angeles?
Come on. Not here.
It just came up.
The election's not for months.
We can register voters in October.
It has nothing to do with the election.
You know that.
If you don't mind,
I'd rather face Mississippi
and those people screaming at me
and maybe getting shot
after I go to California.
Are you scared?
Don't pretend like it's not scary.
Look, I have to go.
Why? What is so important?
It's a convention.
I'm not allowed to talk about it.
Hello, Mr. Kinsey.
Please, Hollis. It's Paul.
This is Sheila, my girlfriend.
Nice to meet you.
Did you ever really plan
on going down South?
How could you ask that?
This just came up.
You can always get another
job at a grocery store.
I can't just walk into an ad agency.
I can't believe you.
All you do is complain about
that place and those people.
That's not true.
Well, I'm going.
I guess I'll just hop in Billy Kaplan's bus
with ten strangers.
Why can't it wait?
19th Street.
This was all supposed to be ours.
I keep thinking what would have
happened if Dad had lived.
He'd be on his knees to us.
What about all that money
Dad gave to Lincoln Center?
Get that back.
You can't take a donation back.
Listen, I'm as upset as you are.
We're about to finally buy in Millbrook.
How long can she afford to live?
By golly, Pete, maybe we can
get rid of her tonight.
Remember Rope?
Well, look, all we have to do
is go over there, get her signature,
mourn over the loss
of our birthright, and move on.
I hate going there.
The smell.
To the end of the line.
Does Judy want kids?
We have a five-year plan.
Although secretly I think Judy hopes
we're that childless couple
people invite over.
Trudy?
We've tried.
That must be disappointing.
Adoption.
People do that.
They do.
So, the Yankees are having a hell of a year.
Do you take Bobby?
All the time.
We really thought you were going
to make it to Cape May.
Although without Betty there,
everyone had a turn at winning.
Elizabeth's got a mind for cards.
Where were you?
I was hiding in the tree house.
It's like a tomb in there.
I don't know how Don's standing it.
Is this the last picture of her in the house?
I don't know.
And where's the ottoman with the birds?
I don't know, Betty.
I mean, can you blame her?
I wouldn't want to live with Mom's ghost.
She's a silly woman.
All that talk about her underthings.
Daddy used to fine us
for small talk, remember?
Conversation is an art.
Well, it is.
How long has he been like this?
He was acting queer
on the golf course last month.
Let one of the colored caddies
really have it.
Look, Gloria's helping us.
Okay? I don't want to get stuck with him
just because I cared enough
not to move away.
Don works in Manhattan.
You know I wish I could be here.
You only have two kids.
Lord knows Don could afford
to build him a house
in his backyard if he wanted to.
Stop counting other people's money.
And the jardinière.
The what?
It used to be right there.
The ceramic thing?
I think we have that.
Do I have to go around and write my name
on all the things that I want?
Bets, you're drunk.
Well, I hope everybody's hungry.
We're minutes away.
Why is that window open?
Well, look at that. You found a corner.
You're pulling your end.
Can't say the same about him.
Don's helping.
Who know what he does, why he does it?
I know more about the kid
who fixes my damn car.
Dad, you're hurting Don's feelings.
It's okay.
Nobody has what you have.
You act like it's nothing.
My daughter's a princess.
You know that?
Dinnertime.
What's going on?
He has no people!
You can't trust a person like that!
Daddy.
Fine. Let's go eat.
Come on.
I have no appetite.
Birdie, you should eat.
Stop it, Don.
Nobody's watching.
And here, Mother.
How many of these are there?
Hello, all.
I brought my pen.
Hope I didn't miss anything.
Other than dinner, no.
Hello, Mother.
I think it's nice that even though
you let Bud do all the work,
you found time to grace us
with your signature.
Yes, well, anything I can do.
I just hope you don't get too used to this.
To what?
This family.
It has come to my attention
that you and Trudy
are considering a child that's not your own.
Is this true?
It just came up.
How is that possible?
Peter, I would hate
to have to exclude you
from what is rightfully yours.
You have to keep at it.
You know what, Mother?
This is not a topic of conversation.
I think you know how your father felt
about the whole idea.
It's suitable for some.
But really, you're pulling from the discards.
My father?
- Yes.
- Pete.
Your husband spent everything you had.
Spent it with strangers.
All of it.
What are you talking about?
I'll messenger these
to your office tomorrow.
That's a swell idea.
The tone of your voice... I don't like it.
That, too?
Stop being dramatic.
Bud, what is my fiduciary state?
Tell her.
Well...
We had to liquidate your holdings
to ensure your future comfort.
Why?
Who asked you to do that?
The market took a turn for the worse.
Real estate?
I think I would have heard about that.
Yes, well, don't forget
to send those by my office.
Do you want me to
lay everything out for you?
It's been a day.
I just want to go to sleep.
You're smoking like a chimney.
It gives you wrinkles, you know.
Good morning, everyone.
Gene.
Morning, Don.
I have some batter left.
Would you like some waffles?
No. This will be fine.
And coffee.
- Morning, everybody.
- Do you want breakfast?
No.
I had no idea.
Please, Judy, it's okay.
No, it's yours. I feel terrible.
I didn't know your mother promised it to you.
Really, Judy, it's okay.
I wish he hadn't brought it up with you.
I'm putting it over here.
Isn't Viola coming today?
Later.
There's no chance she'll miss you.
- Leave the dishes.
- Nonsense.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
Now that you've fed me,
why don't we go upstairs?
Gene!
I'm fine.
I don't know what to say.
He's so mixed up.
Gene, you are mixed up.
You're mixed up.
He's tired. He didn't sleep last night.
Of course.
Dad, you have to go back to the doctor.
I already have an appointment for Monday.
So... Daddy, what would you
like to do today?
Finish that puzzle?
Sure.
And maybe drive into town.
Get you a milkshake.
That's a grand idea.
Come in.
Finally.
I told her to call you.
You should have called me.
Hello, Viola.
And you two look good, considering.
How are the children?
They're good.
I'm gonna make some calls.
You should be here every day.
That's not up to me.
Why not?
You've been here longer than her.
He needs you.
I don't know about that.
And you let Gloria and Judy
ransack the house.
You want to give me your temper?
He doesn't know who I am.
He's very, very sick.
You don't know how nice it is
to hear someone say that.
Is he dying?
I was at Elkins Park Hospital on Sunday
when they talked to her.
It's just gonna get worse.
I don't know how much more I can take.
Well, this day comes eventually,
like it or not.
I'm an orphan.
You are supposed
to take care of your husband
and your beautiful children now.
They are yours.
You'll see.
The minute you leave,
you'll remember him
exactly the way he used to be.
It's all good outside that door.
Want these upstairs?
No. I have to put it all in the wash.
I'll go get the kids.
Francine promised them
the pool tomorrow.
Carla will bring them home later.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Don.
What?
I think you should leave.
Really?
Yes.
Bets, you're upset.
I am.
And I know how you feel about grieving.
I think I should be here for you.
That's your reason.
What do you want me to say?
I want to be here.
You need me here.
Why?
Nothing's changed.
We were just pretending.
Good afternoon, Mr. Draper.
Hello, Donna.
Allison.
Of course.
Surprise!
And this beautiful layette.
We've also attempted
to fortify your castle.
Lucky Strike, Martinson Coffee,
Pampers, and some Clearasil,
for when it gets bigger.
You raided the storeroom for me.
Now, Daddy-o, we've given
this a lot of thought.
You are going to be blessed
with a stinking miracle.
Stop it!
So, in assessing the damage
to your private life,
we've gotten you some reading material.
What do you get for the man
who's about to have nothing?
- No, no, no, no.
- Speech, speech.
I'm very touched by this party.
That's the whole point.
You're not going to be touched.
I got it, Paul. Knock it off.
I want to toast all of you.
And let's hope when this baby comes
that he likes Luckys.
Here's to the little one,
whatever it may be.
- Cheers.
- Salut.
I just wanted to say Happy Birthday.
What's this?
Tiffany's?
Who's it from?
From Jane.
And Roger, I'm sure.
Will you cut the cake, dear?
Mr. Draper.
I wasn't expecting you till tomorrow.
How is everything?
About how those things are.
Joan, if you don't mind,
can I borrow you for a moment?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
And you have your meeting
with Mr. Odino at 10 tomorrow.
And then Lee Garner, Jr.
And the TV department at 3.
Cancel everything.
Yes, of course.
Reschedule for Friday?
No. Clear the week.
So. How was your family emergency?
Memorable. Thank you.
I assume that means everything's okay?
I'm leaving for California tomorrow
for the Rocket Fair.
Good for you.
Sunshine, bikinis.
But didn't we already send a couple men?
Campbell and Kinsey?
Not yet.
Well, Campbell has got to go.
I've held his hand through 30 phone calls.
Very good, Don.
Bring me a bag of oranges.
I'm sure Joan here can hold down the fort.
She's been doing it so far.
Told you you'd be in good hands
with Miss Holloway.
I'll need you to send a memo to Mr. Kinsey
explaining this change in plans.
I'll take care of it.
You look like you didn't
get any sleep last night.
I did.
Go ahead. Lay down.
I'll keep the drunks away.
I heard it's very hard
to get anything done there
because of the weather, you know?
People don't work.
Sounds good to me.
I'm sure I'll be going sometime
in the next few months.
All the networks keep saying
how I need to come out
and shave my face.
I mean show.
What's in this?
You're just gonna fly off
and leave your wife and newborn?
I just want to say
that I am so happy for you
and that you're gonna be the best father
and that I'm really happy for you.
Thank you.
- Mr. Kinsey?
- Yes, Joan.
Mr. Draper wanted you to be informed
that he will be going to Los Angeles
for the convention.
Great. We won't have to fly tourist.
No. It's just he and Mr. Campbell going.
What?
Don's going with Pete?
He can't do that.
I'm sure it must be disappointing.
I'll need your tickets and your badges.
That's not right. Why can't we all go?
I really need everything right away.
Or are they at home?
Is there any cake left?
Hey, Sheila. It's me.
No, I know that.
And I want you to know
I've thought about it...
Let me finish.
I'm going to stand there
arm-in-arm with you
and make a stand.
It's not just about you and me.
I know that.
No one's been shot lately. Okay?
I love you, too, baby.
Peggy.
May I speak with you?
Heck of a party.
Yes.
I'm going away, you know.
Of course.
On a plane.
What do you want me to say?
That I wish I was going?
Everybody does.
I've never even been on a plane.
Well, I have.
But not since my father died.
I'm sorry.
I'm not scared.
It just seems significant, is all.
Statistically speaking,
it's very unlikely that it will happen
to two people in one family.
That's true.
Besides, it wouldn't be the worst thing.
Excuse me?
I hate my mother.
What do you think of that?
Come on, you must have an opinion.
I don't know the circumstances.
I don't know what I should expect from her.
I don't know her.
Like Bud and I turned out so great.
Who's to say it wouldn't be better?
So it's not yours. That could be good.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But I think your flight will be fine.
You should go home.
Everything's so easy for you.
It's not easy for anyone, Pete.
Have a great trip.
What's there?
Glen?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
How long have you been out here?
I don't know.
A few days.
What happened?
I didn't know if I was
going to see you again.
And then you weren't even home.
Did you run away?
So?
I think you should tell me what happened.
My dad wants Charlotte
and me to live with him.
My mom doesn't care.
I'm sure that's not true.
She just wants to be with her boyfriends.
Does she have a lot of boyfriends?
I guess.
They give me things.
I haven't seen you in so long,
except driving down the street.
I know. I know.
Can I use the bathroom?
Do you want me to wash your clothes?
Is that shirt okay?
That almost fits you.
Go ahead.
Why are you alone here?
It's the middle of the day.
It's lousy.
You understand why your mother
was mad at me, I hope.
Yeah.
Because she doesn't understand.
That's true.
I'm not going home.
Because I know I'm a problem for them.
Glen.
I know I am because
they keep saying I'm not.
Did you do something?
No.
But my mom is never home.
My dad has another baby.
His wife is pretty mean.
Where's your mother?
I don't know.
Writing pamphlets and handing them out.
I'm pretty responsible.
I brush my sister's teeth
and put us both to bed.
That's very sweet of you.
Aren't you going to eat?
Can I tell you something?
Of course.
I don't like ham.
I don't like meat at all, actually.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to make you
some macaroni and cheese?
I came to rescue you.
Did you bring your cape?
I'm not joking.
We can go anywhere. I have money.
Glen...
- Mommy! I missed you!
- Mommy!
I missed you, too.
How is he?
- Who?
- Your father.
He's not good.
Carla, this is Glen Bishop.
Sally, Bobby, you remember
Glen from down the street.
Hi, Glen.
Hi.
Why don't you take Glen upstairs
and show him the trains Daddy got you?
You can use the controls.
Go ahead. It's okay.
What's he doing here?
You're really bad.
You think you can do any better?
If I couldn't, I'd give up trying.
What don't you like
about the speed shear?
Glen, can you come in here?
Glen, get over here now.
I was worried sick.
Glen, you have to go home.
You can't do things like this.
Let's go. Your father's on his way.
I hate you.
Apologize right this minute.
No, it's true.
I hate you.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Come on. Let's wash up for dinner.
Advertising, if anything,
helps bring on change.
The market... and I'm talking
in a purely Marxist sense...
dictates that we must include everyone.
The consumer has no color.
Betty, I'm sorry, but we really need to talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
I don't know why he was over here,
but this has to stop.
Nothing's going on.
Except that Glen feels alone.
Honestly, I don't blame him.
What did he say?
Nothing.
But it's obvious.
He depends on you for everything.
You're supposed to be taking care of him.
You're his mother.
And he gets nothing.
I thought with Dan out of our lives,
it would be different.
Glen's right.
I'm not a very good mother anymore.
Don isn't living here.
I'm sorry.
We haven't told the children.
Is it over?
I don't even know.
That's the worst.
Do they see him?
He takes them to dinner.
They don't know what made them
so special all of the sudden.
I don't know.
For me, it wasn't that different
without him there.
Sometimes I feel like I'll float away
if Don isn't holding me down.
The hardest part
is realizing you're in charge.
As you can see, the pilot has turned off
the "No Smoking" sign.
We're expecting clear skies
en route to Los Angeles today.
It should be a pleasant day,
82 degrees and clear,
with a light Santa Ana wind.
Trans World Airlines...
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA