Previously on Mad Men.
Your girl full of surprises.
She really stood out,
brainstorming wise.
Here's your basket of kisses.
What size Cadillac do you take?
You know the rules.
I don't make plans.
My neighbor posed for that.
Believe me,
he always looks very relaxed.
Don's in advertising.
How do you sleep at night?
You must think I'm a creep.
Why are you here?
I had to see you.
I thought take you up on
your offer to look at my work,
Season 1 Episode 8
The Hobo Code
Hold the doors, please!
Thank you. Good morning.
Good morning.
Draper has you in early, huh?
What's he up to?
I don't know. I kind of
came in for myself.
Okay.
Honestly, I couldn't sleep.
I'm just filled with nerves.
The service elevator is out.
Do you mind?
I'm moving today.
I'm supposed to go byat lunch
and supervise the movers.
Probably lose the rest of the day
watching other people work.
Well, that is a big day.
What do you have
to be nervous about?
Nothing.
Just, I think, Mr. Rumsen
is presenting my copy today
to the Belle Jolie people.
A thing like that.
We really took the local, didn't we?
It's 7 in the morning.
I'm very sorry, sir.
Here we are.
I'm going to hop down for a coffee.
Would you like some?
No.
Are you sure?
Come in here, please.
Close the door.
There's no one here.
Do you know how hard it is
to see you walking
around here every day?
- Your skirt. It's tight.
- Just pull it up.
Be careful.
Listen,
maybe this isn't the right time
to mention this,
but I want to clear the air.
I know I told you I would read
the copy that you wrote, but...
I haven't.
I'm glad.
I thought you just didn't like it.
That's too bad.
I know what you're going to say.
No.
You don't.
You haven't been right once.
I have all these things going on
in my head, and I can't say them.
Do you think about me?
I'll be honest.
A few times.
You're only 20 yards away.
Not right now.
I wake up in the morning, and
I look into Trudy's eyes, and I think,
"We're supposed to be one person. "
But whatever I try...
there are all these things
going on in my head.
She's just another stranger.
You're not alone in this.
I'm sorry I ripped your blouse.
It's okay.
Look who's off the clock again.
He's speaking Italian to his mother.
My stars.
Two weeks in, and
she's already a goner.
He talks to his mother a lot.
Mr. Crane? I'll connect you.
Because he's not married.
Well, he's in the Art Department?
What does he look like?
Did you see that movie
Marty with Ernest Borgnine?
He lived with his mother.
Stop teasing her.
Yes, right away.
My guess is tall, dark,
and handsome,
but I'm a glass-half-full
kind of gal.
She is so thoughtful.
- Let me get my purse.
- Forget it.
Mrs. Sterling will be calling
before lunch time today.
Please put her through
directly to me.
- Done.
- Ask her. She'll know.
Salvatore Romano
in the Art Department.
Do you know him?
Handsome. Very debonair.
Cologne, but not the cheap stuff.
Something European, maybe.
You're so specific.
You have voices.
I have other things.
Thank you so much for holding.
- Good morning.
Mr. Cooper wanted
to see you in his office.
Tell Mr. Sterling
I'll be right there.
No, it's just Mr. Cooper.
Thank you, Peggy.
What happened there?
I caught it on something.
I might start keeping a spare.
Come on in.
I'd prefer you didn't
smoke in here right now.
Don, I am appreciative
of your talents, and although
that cannot be measured,
I have made an effort to quantify.
$2,500.
I...
Thank you.
That's what you say.
Have you read her?
Rand.
Atlas Shrugged*.
That's the one.
Yes. Yes, it is.
See, I know you haven't read it.
When you hit 40, you realize
you've met or seen
every kind of person there is,
and I know what kind you are.
Because I believe
we are alike.
I assume that's flattering.
By that I mean
you are a productive and
reasonable man and in the end
completely self-interested.
It's strength.
We are different...
unsentimental about all the people
who depend on our hard work.
Take $1.99 out of that $2,500
and buy yourself a copy.
I will.
Hello, there.
Hello.
Are you Traffic, or are you
here for casting?
I'm... I'm not a model. I'm new.
Excuse me, Marty,
who's doing the Firestone comps,
you or Frank?
Neither of us. Sal,
we were talking to Miss...
Lois. Lois Sadler.
I'm new here. Switchboard.
Marty Faraday.
- Why would they hide you?
- Hi, Lois.
Duane Davis.
Salvatore Romano.
Sorry about the mess.
No, it's divine.
I work in a closet all day,
so just to come out
and walk around is wonderful.
Is there anything I can do for you?
I'm such a featherhead.
I need to get my paperwork
in to Accounting, then
find my way back
to the switchboard room.
Am I close?
No. You're not even
on the right floor.
I'll walk you there.
No. Just point me there. I'm fine.
Go upstairs,
make a left outside of
the stairwell, follow the wall
past the ladies' room.
Nice to meet you.
That ate up some time.
I like when they flirt with me.
She was flirting with him.
You know, I had the salesman
pushing this tie on me
for 20 minutes.
I'd have bought it right away
if I knew it worked.
It's not the ties.
They always talk to you.
They can tell you make money.
I told you,
you don't need money to dress better
than you do, Duane.
Mr. Campbell, I have your wife.
What line?
Light up a line, will you?
No, she's right here, in person.
Send her in.
Hello, my love.
Hello, homeowner.
What are you doing here, lovely?
I thought I'd come get you
and we could go together.
We could even walk.
It's 30 blocks.
It's beautiful outside.
I have a busier day
than I thought.
Well, then let's do this here.
I said I'd meet you there if
my schedule allowed,
and now it doesn't look so good.
No, you didn't, and I'm here now.
What does it matter?
This is my office.
How do you think it looks?
Like you are beloved by your wife.
You see what happens when
you just show up like this?
We fight.
I came to celebrate us
having our apartment,
which I for one am happy about.
And you have ruined it.
I'm sorry.
I'm just busier than I thought.
Let's have a glass of Champagne.
I'm sorry.
We're going to live
there a long time.
There's no point in
being superstitious.
It's as simple as E Pluribus Unum*:
from many, one.
From many shades of lipstick,
one that belongs to her.
From a basket of kisses,
she picks one.
It makes her unique.
It colors her kiss.
And her kiss, well,
it colors her man.
Belle Jolie lipstick.
"Mark Your Man".
I only see one lipstick
in your drawing.
Women want colors,
lots and lots of colors.
"Mark Your Man". It's pretty cute.
You like this?
Well, maybe we should cut down
to five shades, or one.
I'm not telling you
to listen to anyone,
but this is a very fresh approach.
It's okay, Kenny.
I don't think there's much else
to do here but call it a day.
Gentlemen, thank you for your time.
Is that all?
You're a nonbeliever.
Why should we waste time on Kabuki*?
I don't know what that means.
It means that you've already tried
your plan, and you're number 4.
You've enlisted my expertise, and
you've rejected it to go on the way
you've been going.
I'm not interested in that.
You can understand.
I don't think your three months
or however many thousands of dollars
entitles you to refocus
the core of our business.
Listen, I'm not here
to tell you about Jesus.
You already know about Jesus. Either
he lives in your heart, or He doesn't.
Every woman wants choices,
but in the end, none wants to be
one of a hundred in a box.
She's unique.
She makes the choices,
and she's chosen him.
She wants to tell
the world "He's mine".
He belongs to me, not you.
"She marks her man with her lips."
He is her possession.
You've given every girl
that wears your lipstick
the gift of total ownership.
Sit down.
No.
Not until I know I'm not wasting
my time.
Sit down.
You know how to get back
to the Roosevelt?
We could have someone walk you over,
or just meet you, if you're interested.
You're a troublemaker.
Although it is a place
to get into trouble.
They just did this incredible
renovation.
It reminds me a little
of a steamship.
And the people...
I was in the lounge last night,
and I end up having a drink
with Robert Mitchum.
Actually, many drinks.
Now you know we wouldn't
steer you wrong.
Nice work. I think you may be
right about this.
We'll never know, will we?
What?
It's not a science, Hugh.
We'll do our best.
That Jesus thing.
I don't know what to say.
Probably better than dangling him
out the window by his ankles.
That's just a story.
Don's never actually done that.
Ken, you will realize
in your private life
that at a certain point
seduction is over
and force is actually
being requested.
He's a kid. He thinks
it's the other way around.
Peggy, ice!
We'll need some.
Should I just put it down?
How much ice?
How do you take it?
Home run, ballerina.
Go ahead, before Joan Holloway sees.
You call that celebrating?
The meeting was so long,
I was worried.
We barely finished the presentation,
and he bought it.
No, he's bring modest.
Donald walked around
the village three times
and then set it on fire.
Oh, my God. Can I see it?
It's marvelous.
I thought it was going to say
"It's the mark you make
on your man".
Was it, now?
You may be a writer, honey.
Really?
You're arrogant.
You want another drink?
I don't know.
Not a writer.
Can I keep it?
No.
What are you doing?
Don't ever put your name on a list.
They keep track of everything
we do here.
Have you never heard
of Joseph McCarthy?
It's the bowling team.
My God. It happened.
- They loved it.
- What are you talking about?
I'm heading out. Don't look for me.
I have errands to run.
My Belle Jolie copy. They loved it.
- Congratulations.
- That's so fascinating!
I'm glad your other work
was suffering for a reason.
They poured me a drink.
- Who?
- Mr. Draper,
Mr. Rumsen, Mr. Romano, and...
I'm so jealous.
Don't be. I was just...
I shouldn't be bragging.
They sold Peggy's copy.
My word.
Actually, they changed it
a little bit, but it worked.
- We're celebrating.
- How about it?
Five minutes to 5,
we head to P.J. Clarke's.
Perfect!
It's going to be a hell of
an afternoon traffic meeting.
Champagne.
When did that happen?
Another grateful client stopped by.
I thought you were moving today.
I was looking forward
to seeing you in coveralls.
Yes, well, I managed to explain
to the concerned party
that I already have a job.
Do they ever stop asking for things?
Hello.
Hildy, she must have gone to
lunch already.
- Congratulations.
- Yes.
I hear you're quite
the little scribe.
You can trust Ken's opinion here.
He's a published author.
But he can't write copy.
I don't like to limit
my words that much.
I also hate puns.
Come on.
Admiral: the television
that won't go down the tubes.
Shut up.
So you going to celebrate?
Well, yes, actually.
A bunch of us...
just the girls so far...
are going to P.J. Clarke's tonight.
Forget tonight.
I heard Cooper, Sterling,
and Draper already left.
Am I wrong?
What about Mr. Rumsen?
Freddie Rumsen's at P.J.'s right now,
and he doesn't know there's a party.
3:00, after the traffic meeting.
Joan's a tattletale.
I don't know, Peggy.
I'm kind of senior ranking when
those other men are gone.
Speaker of the House.
He'll be there.
I should probably go home, actually.
If we're starting at 3,
you can go home at 5.
It'll still be after work.
We all work so hard,
I think we all need it.
Why not?
Toodle-oo.
Mr. Romano,
I was headed out to lunch,
but I have a phone call for you.
I'm glad I stayed in.
It's disconnected.
Everybody's talking
about the meeting.
Miss Olsen said your artwork
was spectacular.
She did, did she?
Anyway, a bunch of us are taking her
out to drinks. P.J. Clarke's?
She deserves it.
You have to come.
This is Lois Sadler, by the way.
I know that.
I'll be there.
Good.
Can I help you?
Can I help you, sir?
It's Don.
The ad man.
He's okay.
Excuse me, fellas.
Just because I can't call you
doesn't mean you can't call me.
Pack a bag. We're going to Paris.
- What?
- Paris.
Now?
Yeesh.
Where'd you get that?
It's a bonus.
I'm not sure what for.
I bet.
What do you say?
I called Idyllwild.
We can have breakfast at Versailles.
I'm sorry.
I have a special night planned.
I thought you didn't make plans.
Is he joing us?
Yes. He has to.
He looks kind of square.
Kibby just came four days
straight from Juarez.
May I?
I've been thinking about
this since Port Authority.
Stay. You'll love it.
We're going to get high
and listen to Miles.
That's your plan?
We can do this first and then do that.
It'll be a lot more fun.
Sit down. Relax.
Next to me, Icky.
Where did you find him?
You know you need to leave the Village
for a decent screw.
I'll take care of him.
Do you like it?
I feel like Dorothy.
Everything just turned to color.
The words.
You are good with the words, man.
Well put.
Kibby, why don't you make
yourself useful
and get me a glass of water?
My word, I need to get one of those.
No, thanks.
Maybe.
We realize there's no music playing.
Just the...
Good afternoon, ma'am.
I'm embarrassed to ask,
seeing as we all have it
hard right now, but is there any way
I can trouble you for a meal?
I'm willing to work for it.
Look around you.
We're not Christians here no more.
That is not true.
Fine, fine.
Work will feed your soul, but
there's no work left here today.
Come back tomorrow?
Nonsense.
You'll stay with us and eat with us,
and work tomorrow.
I will have to boil
those clothes, though,
if you're going to sit at my table.
I'm not offended.
It would be a relief to me as well.
Dick Whitman,
stop digging holes.
Build a fire under the cauldron.
Hiya, kid.
What did I say to you?
Reminds me of myself.
That doesn't surprise me at all.
So we thank you, Lord,
for this bounty we are
about to receive
that we may share it
with those in need.
Amen.
Amen. Amen.
Thank you again.
Thank you so much.
This smells delicious.
Where are those manners from?
Let him eat and be on with it.
I'm from just east.
About New York, originally,
some other places.
New York.
It's how you took to being
on the bum so easy.
Archie, no one takes to charity easy.
I'm just saying I bet he don't know
which end of a weed to pull.
That's the truth, sir.
I only know some farm work, but I've
seen mills and docks and factories.
I've been a worker.
Are you a communist?
No.
Yeah, I imagine they're
different, all right.
They take a club to the jaw
like anyone else.
They are souls,
but they can't be saved.
That's true.
My mom always said that life
is like a horseshoe.
It's fat in the middle,
open on both ends, and
hard all the way through.
Tomorrow...
when you've finished some work.
Bless you.
I had to see this place for myself.
Good.
It's something, huh?
No Bob Mitchum?
- What are you drinking?
- Campari with a twist.
You know, when I mentioned
the renovation,
I didn't know if you heard me.
I've been curious about
seeing this place.
I'm actually involved with architects
on this department store.
Signage, mostly.
I like this room, although I am
its prime target: traveling salesman.
In that suit?
I should say not.
No, I'm not one of those boys who
looks forward to a business trip
to escape the wife and kids.
I'm really a homebody.
But New York?
When you arrive, and that train starts
slowing down and it gets all dark,
my heart pounds, and I think,
"I'm going to climb that staircase
and be in New York."
I take it for granted.
It is a masterpiece of some kind.
Wherever I'm staying,
I always demand a view.
It's building after building.
Little compartments filled
with possibilities.
What's that from?
42nd Street?
What?
No. I'm just saying it's...
it's like you can do anything.
I'm two ahead of you. I have to eat
something, or I'm going to continue
to rhapsodize.
What time is it?
I bet you don't have
an expense account.
I'm not saying Peggy doesn't
have something upstairs.
I'm just saying at Sterling Cooper
things are usually happening downstairs.
I didn't know that.
God, the whole office is here.
I don't see the Art Department.
What about those two?
I think I had too much to drink.
You are very petite.
Going back to the well. Interested?
Dance with me.
I don't like you like this.
Literally,
"With flies."
The espresso beans mean health,
wealth, and happiness.
Seems redundant, I mean, if you
already have health and wealth.
So, are you happy?
I'm one of those people who thinks
the minute you ask that,
you're not happy, so...
no.
You're loud, but you're shy.
I feel like I'm getting
my fortune told.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
So what do you want to do?
I don't know.
Let me break off with
one of the writers,
have my own little shop
where copy follows art
and not the other way around.
No, I mean my view.
You have to see it.
It's all the way to the park.
Of course it's dark now.
I don't know.
May I?
I...
don't know what to say.
It's Elliot.
And, Salvatore, you don't
have to say anything.
No, I... I just...
No.
Have another drink.
Think about it.
Elliot, I have thought about it.
I know what I want.
I know what I want to do.
I know what you're thinking.
I'll show you.
What are you afraid of?
Are you joking?
This...
has been a pleasure.
Don, are you all right?
I don't know.
Probably the guy in 2F.
He uses his wife like a speed bag.
Man.
I was going to truck down
for some carrot juice.
Wait, wait.
Thank you.
- Smoke?
- No.
He speaks.
I'm supposed to tell you
to say your prayers.
Praying won't help you
from this place, kid.
Best keep your mind on your mother.
She'll probably look after you.
She ain't my momma.
We all wish we were from
someplace else,
believe me.
Ain't you heard?
I'm a whore child.
No. I hadn't heard
anything about that.
- You don't talk like a bum.
- I'm not.
I'm a gentleman of the rails.
For me, every day is brand-new.
Every day's a brand-new place,
people, what have you.
So you got no home.
That's sad.
What's at home?
I had a family once: a wife,
a job, a mortgage.
I couldn't sleep at night tied
to all those things.
Then death came to find me.
Did you see him?
Only every night.
So one morning, I freed myself
with the clothes on my back.
Good-bye.
Now I sleep like a stone: sometimes
under the stars, the rain.
the roof of a barn.
But I sleep like a stone.
So where do you go?
Tomorrow I'll be leaving
this place, that's for certain.
If death was coming
anyplace, it's here, kid,
creeping around every corner.
Here.
You're an honorary.
This is how we talk to each other.
On the front gate of every house,
there's a mark.
It's a code, just like
you heard on the radio.
See...
That's a pie.
It means the food here is good.
This one...
That means watch out
for the nasty dog.
This one here...
That means a dishonest
man lives here.
And this one...
That means tell a sad story.
Here.
Don't be scared, kid.
You ain't a man yet.
Of course.
What?
You two.
You're in love.
What?
That's ridiculous.
Every day I make pictures where
people appear to be in love.
I know what it looks like.
Looks like a magazine.
Love is bourgeois.
You're breaking my heart.
Dig. Ad man's got a heart.
The grownups are talking.
Don't defend him.
Toothpaste doesn't solve anything.
Dacron sure as hell won't bring back
those ten dead kids in Biloxi.
Neither will buying some Tokaj wine
and leaning up against a wall
in Grand Central pretending
you're a vagrant.
You know what it's like to watch
all you ants go into your hive?
I wipe my ass with
the Wall Street Journal.
How come every time we have a party,
the ladies have to sit and
listen to the men talk?
Look at you...
satisfied, dreaming up jingles
for soap flakes and spot remover,
telling yourself you're free.
My God. Stop talking.
Make something of yourself.
Like you?
You make the lie.
You invent want.
You're for them...
not us.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but there is no big lie.
There is no system.
The universe is indifferent.
Man,
why'd you have to say that?
Paris.
Now. Let's go.
No, I can't.
Buy yourself a car.
The cops.
You can't go out there.
You can't.
- Sir.
- Good evening.
Wake up, Bobby.
Come on, kiddo.
Daddy.
Your sister's sleeping.
Ask me anything.
What?
Anything.
I'm tired.
Ask me.
Why do lightning bugs light up?
I don't know.
But I will never lie to you.
Well, sir,
I believe that does it.
I'll be on my way.
Thank you, again,
for sharing your home.
Good luck to you.
Be on your way already.
- Good morning, Peggy.
- Good morning, Mr. Draper.