Mrs. Draper, sorry about the chill in here,
but my wife took the oil heater upstairs.
I'm fine.
So, as I thought last week,
the spotting was not caused
by your horseback riding,
but rather, as I suspected,
you're going to have another baby.
Really?
Well, we've been here before.
You'll have to start
eating right, sleeping,
avoid strenuous activity,
no riding.
Just take it easy.
That's what husbands are for.
I can't believe this.
I understand this was a surprise,
but blessings come that way.
Of course.
I'll need you to undress
so I can examine you.
Dr. Aldridge, are you sure?
Are you concerned
about your appearance?
You've been blessed
with a very resilient figure.
Dr. Aldridge, I can't
have a baby right now.
Mrs. Draper, if we're having
the conversation I think we're having,
there are alternatives, obviously.
But I find it hard to believe that,
as a married woman of means,
you would even be considering that.
That is an option for young girls
who have no other options.
I guarantee,
the minute you tell your husband,
your friends,
you'll stop worrying.
Get in the swing of things.
Let's see if I can wrestle
that heater from Charlene.
With love from Ken Cosgrove
and Pete Campbell.
Why'd you need it today?
Cooper wanted the ad
revenue projections early.
Why?
Great. Clearasil is missing.
Honestly, I don't know.
You don't think it's anything to do
with Draper being AWOL
in California, do you?
No, I figured that out.
Campbell says there's
an aerospace gold rush.
I bet Draper's landing a big one.
I haven't heard anything.
Or he's breaking off,
opening his own shop in L.A.
Or he's finding a good spot
for Sterling Cooper West.
I'd love to go to California.
I could get a convertible.
Whatever it is, they're evaluating us.
If Kennedy's speech goes past 8:30...
that's Lucy and then Danny Thomas
and then Andy Griffith...
I'll take it in the shorts.
Why am I sick to my stomach?
Good. You're here.
I'm waiting on a call
from North American Aviation.
It's 10:00 there.
They should just be getting into work.
I was just wondering if you told anybody
about Clearasil yet.
I guess it must have slipped my mind.
I don't know what's going on,
but Harry said
there's some kind of
emergency accounting.
Everybody had to turn in
their numbers early.
What am I gonna say to Duck?
That my father-in-law hates me?
Pete, just tell the truth.
Don't worry about the outcome.
People respect that.
Thank you.
I don't want you blaming Creative.
How long have you been here?
Half an hour.
I didn't want to bother you.
Where have you been?
You disappeared.
I had to have some time
to think about things.
Must be nice.
Needing time and just taking it,
all on your own terms,
not wondering what anybody thinks...
me, the children...
Bets.
I'd do anything I could
to undo what happened.
What happened?
I was not respectful to you.
Well, now I know I'm not crazy.
That helps.
I can't walk away from this.
I want to be with you.
I want to be together again.
I don't know.
Honestly, things haven't been
that different without you.
I need to see the kids.
I can't deal with this right now, Don.
I'll call.
We'll make arrangements.
Thank you for seeing me.
What's your poison?
I don't know.
It's okay, Campbell.
Whatever you're having.
Sit down.
Clearasil is pulling out.
Sales are strong, Creative is strong,
but we are not suited
for business together.
Your father-in-law.
Yes.
That's a sticky wicket.
Indeed.
I'm working on something to replace it.
Campbell, I'm counting
on your discretion here.
Okay.
The British agency
Putnam, Powell & Lowe
is taking a controlling share
of Sterling Cooper.
Clearasil is in conflict
with Lever Brothers.
We're merging...
well, being merged with.
Your loyalty and enthusiasm
during the American Airlines thing
showed real character.
Thank you.
I'd like you to replace me
as head of Accounts.
I'm trusting you with this information
because I am going
to be the president
of the new Sterling Cooper.
Congratulations.
Congratulations to you.
I don't know what to say.
You say "Thank you,"
and then you don't say anything.
Such news has to be
broken in the right way.
Is Don on board with my promotion?
I'm the president.
I don't need his permission, do I?
Right.
If Don shows up, he'll fall in line.
He'll have to,
or find another profession.
That's why God put
non-compete clauses in contracts.
Well...
thank you.
Good evening, my fellow citizens.
This government, as promised,
has maintained the closest surveillance
of the Soviet military buildup
on the island of Cuba.
Within the past week,
unmistakable evidence
has established the fact
that a series of offensive missile sites
is now in preparation
on that imprisoned island.
The purpose of these bases
can be none other
than to provide
a nuclear strike capability
against the Western Hemisphere.
Upon receiving the first
preliminary hard information
of this nature,
last Tuesday morning at 9:00 a.m.,
I directed that our
surveillance be stepped up.
And having now confirmed...
...the Soviet Union
for supplying Cuba in this
new military buildup
and asked Russia to stop
arming Castro's Cuba.
The President did not order
a direct military action...
Welcome back.
Hildy.
...if we are prepared
to sink Russian ships carrying...
...Eastern Daylight Time,
the Armed Forces of the United States
are under instructions to stop...
Mr. Draper, you're
a sight for sore eyes.
Hello, Joan. It's good to be back.
How are you?
Like everyone else today,
very distracted.
Don.
Hello, Peggy.
You look well. How was California?
Sunny.
Do I work for you now?
I hope it's okay.
Mr. Sterling gave me
permission to switch.
I landed the Popsicle account.
So, other than her office and haircut,
is there anything new
I need to know about?
After you.
The world continues without us.
There's no reason to take it personally.
Do you want to know
if you've been missed?
That's half your correspondence.
Mr. Sterling has been very anxious
to speak to you on a daily basis,
and Mr. Phillips, of course.
I'll need the copywriters
and Sal in here
to get me up to speed.
Call Roger in a half an hour
and tell him I'll meet him
in a half an hour.
And Mr. Phillips...
maybe I'll run into him
in the men's room.
I sent your paychecks home.
I assume you've spoken to Mrs. Draper.
Did she call?
Not today.
I think that's enough to start.
We have a safety protocol
for Civil Defense.
I don't want to start a panic,
but I think people
have the right to know.
Trust me. I don't think
there'll be a point
in taking those stairs
or diving under a desk.
So, you're back.
What happened?
One minute I'm standing
next to you in the carport,
and the next I'm tap dancing
for General Dynamics.
Sorry I missed that.
I can't drive, Don.
It's amazing I made any meetings at all.
But you did.
Of course I did.
Did you ever think I'd left you there
because I thought
you could handle it?
How did it go?
I'm this close
to North American Aviation.
Then I was right, wasn't I?
You handled it.
Good work.
I know you want everything
the minute you want it.
Sometimes it's better
to wait until you're ready.
So you think I'm ready?
Yes.
You proved it.
Now I have to play
a little catch-up ball.
Of course.
Welcome back, Don.
You wanted to see me?
About three weeks ago.
Hope you were looking
for a job in California,
because you're going to need one.
I'll stack my absences
up against yours any day.
You can't just do that.
It was important.
And from what I can see,
the walls are still standing.
They are.
But we sold them
and the rest of the company
to Putnam, Powell & Lowe.
What?
It's done.
They're coming in Friday
to discuss strategy,
management structure, and logistics.
You'll find one of these
buried in a stack of crap on your desk.
So how much?
You'll clear a little
over half a million dollars.
Best vacation you ever took.
Look who suddenly
has nothing to say.
Duck put it together.
Ran into them in a bar or something.
Duck was in a bar?
He doesn't have a wife.
Any conflicts?
Well, Mona hasn't been pleasant
since my engagement.
No. With the deal.
But congratulations.
Thank you.
Very few conflicts.
Coop and Alice jumped on it.
I wasn't going to make trouble.
Well, now you can go
back to your office
and figure out
how much I made on this.
I guess so.
Kennedy's daring them to bomb us,
right when I got a second chance.
We don't know what's really going on.
You know that.
As Mr. Khrushchev and Mr. Castro
push our leadership towards
the threat of nuclear war,
it is tempting to be angry.
But I urge all of you to remember
that even on the cross
Jesus forgave his transgressors.
And although we cannot control
these frightening events,
let us take charge of our own souls,
and let us prepare ourselves
for the most important
summit meeting of all.
And so we pray.
We are all sinners, every one of us,
but at least give us the courage
and the common sense
to admit it,
to confess it,
and to repair it.
And give us the assurance
that when this temporary
life on earth ends,
we will be welcomed
back into your arms
in your heavenly kingdom.
Amen.
She's awfully quiet.
I think I know what that's about.
She's terrified like the rest of us.
I think she's being smug
because she has a bomb shelter.
Really? I don't even like to go
in the subway.
There's no air.
I prefer you stop talking about this.
You're upsetting my daughter.
Well, The Times says you should tell
your children the truth.
You tell your children.
Carlton says he heard
the market crashed
because there are Russian
troops off Key West.
They're closing the Interstate.
They can't do that.
Marie, I'm about to leave.
I'm done, okay?
It's nice to feel the warmth
of the community in a time of crisis.
Mrs. Draper, I'll be with you in a minute.
I wish we had a shelter
so I could slam the door in her face.
Betty, you're wan.
Do you want a Miltown?
It's the only thing that's keeping me
from chewing my nails off.
No.
I'm pregnant.
Congratulations?
Jessica was an accident.
Look how happy I am now.
It's not a good time.
But is it ever?
Look at this world we live in.
I can't do it.
What am I going to do?
Well, what can you do?
I don't think you understand.
It's not a good time.
Are you serious?
Yes.
There's a doctor in Albany.
If you go to Puerto Rico,
they do it in a hospital.
Of course you don't want
to go down there right now.
No.
Sometimes the best thing
is just to do nothing and wait.
Mrs. Draper, I'm ready for you.
I'll come by and check on you.
No, I'm fine. You're probably right.
What are you doing in here?
And where's Virginia?
The Soviets fired on us,
or we fired on them
or something. Fix it.
I came in to get away
from this speculation.
Damn it. You see what you did?
I hope the Soviets got a guy like you
to build those missiles.
Everyone's looking
at each other in the street.
They're looking at you
because you've got Castro's beard.
Now they want a list of people
in all the departments.
So? That's you and Danny Lindstrom.
They're counting all the money.
They're counting all the people.
You said this was about an L.A. Office.
You told us it wasn't bad.
Someone knows what's going on.
I swear, if it wasn't important,
I wouldn't have asked.
We're doing what we can.
The phone company's
completely overloaded.
Actually, Lois,
this is more of a security issue.
Certain calls may have been made
using the code words "Los Angeles."
Lois, have you heard anything
about them opening
a West Coast office?
You know I'm not allowed
to talk about what I hear in there.
You can tell us.
It's not going to hurt you.
We'll really owe you.
Well...
Have you ever heard
of Putnam, Powell & Lowe?
London?
Yes. Trans-Atlantic.
Mr. Phillips has made a deal
for them to buy Sterling Cooper.
No.
No!
It's done.
They take the keys Friday.
Are they purchasing
Sterling Cooper,
or are they combining with them?
It's a merger.
From what we could put together,
they want a New York office,
and they want it filled with us,
but there's definitely
going to be some...
redundancies.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
If any of you gets to stay,
one of you has to take me
off the switchboard.
Yeah. Of course.
Lf.
- Daddy!
We missed you.
I missed you, too.
I like your hotel room.
There's a rollaway
there for you, Bobby.
We can go to the movies
or Chinese food.
I want you to behave yourselves,
and brush your teeth.
Do you want to join us?
Mommy doesn't like to eat.
No, I have plans.
Do you want to pick them up
in my office tomorrow?
No, drop them off in the morning.
I'm going riding. Carla will be there.
Okay.
Good night.
Good night, Mommy.
Can we order room service?
How can I help you?
Can I get a glass of water?
Sure.
What else?
I don't know.
A gimlet.
Thank you.
The gentleman's taken care of it.
Tell him I said thank you.
I will,
but it means he's going
to come talk to you.
We'll see about that.
I think this is the place to be tonight.
I walked through Times Square.
Empty.
Doesn't seem real, does it?
That's true.
You don't look worried.
I'm trying not to think about it.
To not thinking about things.
What's your name?
Thank you so much for the drink.
I'd just like to enjoy it,
if you don't mind.
No. Of course.
Nice meeting you.
...degrees for New York City.
Cloudy skies.
Further action of an unspecified nature
is being considered to deal
with the continuing
Soviet missile buildup in Cuba.
That statement from
Department Press Officer Lincoln White,
a revelation
that construction of missile sites
is continuing.
It's delicious.
You're crazy.
Can I have a milk shake?
What's wrong with root beer?
Daddy?
Lt'll take 45 minutes, you know.
Daddy, knock-knock.
Who's there?
Dwayne.
Dwayne who?
Dwayne the bathtub.
Mama, I'm dwowning.
Can we watch TV?
Can you watch these for me, please?
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting.
I'm married.
I was just about ready
to come by and pick you up.
I know, Wally, and I'm sick about it.
I could just die.
Yeah, well, before you go
and do something like that,
I got an idea.
What if I got Beaver to call your sister
and see if he could
talk her into going?
Say, maybe that would work.
So what is your name?
What are you doing in there?
We were just about to close.
Anita wanted to come,
but she's with the children.
That's where she should be.
My mother baked.
Thought we'd all
appreciate something fresh
if we get stuck in here.
And how are you?
I don't know.
Nuclear war.
We could be gone tomorrow.
Well, isn't that always the case?
That's true.
You believe in God.
I've seen that in you
from the moment we met.
Sometimes I feel
he called me to this parish
to reach you.
No. I didn't know that.
Well, it's true.
Hell is serious and very real,
and unless you unburden yourself,
you cannot know peace.
I understand that, Father,
but you're upsetting me right now.
That is your guilt, Peggy.
All that God wants is for you
to reconcile with him.
Don't you understand
that this could be the end of the world
and you could go to hell?
I can't believe that's the way God is.
Good night, Father.
Really? The silver?
There could be looting.
A mob is going to come
to the 14th floor
of this apartment building?
I wish you would come with me right now.
What if something happens?
Rehoboth Beach
is 90 minutes from D.C.
You don't understand these bombs.
Your parents' deck chairs
will be on Fifth Avenue.
Are you trying to make me more upset?
If for some reason
the train doesn't work,
just take a few hundred
dollars in cash
and pay someone to drive you.
This is ridiculous.
If I'm going to die,
I want to die in Manhattan.
Stop that kind of talk, Peter.
There's no difference, Trudy.
And I want to be here,
and you want to be with your parents.
Why do you always
make it about that?
And yes, I love my parents,
and they love me.
Do you?
If you did, you'd want to be with me.
You're right.
I'll help you pack the car.
The first Russian ship
that proceeded through the area
patrolled by our Navy forces...
Bad news.
What?
The conference room's signed out all day.
And I checked the fridge.
There's canapés, really good ones.
They shampooed
the carpets last night.
Campbell.
PPL's coming in today.
You told me she told you that.
You're not worried?
Why'd you come in?
I don't know.
I'm just waiting to see what happens.
I talked to my father-in-law about it.
Regime change is always tricky.
You want to stay neutral.
The loyalists are always hung,
and you don't want to get
caught in the fallout.
What's wrong with you?
Aren't you loyal to anyone?
They don't care about us.
We're just a bunch
of salaries on a ledger.
They'll draw a line
and get rid of everything below it.
I like this company the way it is.
Have a minute?
From the look of this,
that might be all I have.
May I?
I'm coming to you anonymously, Don.
I know something
I think you should know.
What?
I know about the merger,
and I know that Duck Phillips
is going to be the president.
How do you know that?
He told me.
Why would he do that?
Picking sides, I guess.
Why are you telling me this?
I don't know.
I just thought if I was you,
I would want to know.
Thank you.
You know they stopped
a ship this morning.
I bet the Russians are reconsidering,
now that we made a stand.
Carla, what's this?
That's from Mr. Draper.
"Dear Betty,
"I'm sitting in the Roosevelt
"looking at the backs
of Bobby and Sally's heads
"as they watch TV.
"I'm not letting them
change the channel
"because watching
the news makes me sick,
"and they can see it.
"I think about you
and how I behaved
"and my regret.
"I know it's my fault
you are not here right now.
"I understand why you feel
"it's better to go on without me,
"and I know that you won't
be alone for very long,
"but without you
I'll be alone forever.
"I love you.
Don."
Gentlemen, now that we've done
haggling over the dowry,
it's time to slip into the tent
and spend a night with the bride.
We imagine that Sterling Cooper
will remain somewhat autonomous.
You bought us.
We don't expect autonomy,
but who's going to be minding the store
when you all fly back to England?
Since we've worked with him before
and he knows both companies,
Duck Phillips will be
President of Sterling Cooper.
My goodness.
Obviously, I accept.
That makes sense.
Congratulations.
Well, I promise, in spite of this title,
I will treat the founders
of Sterling Cooper
with the respect they deserve.
Duck, it has now become your meeting.
Tell us what you see.
I find myself a little unprepared here,
but I know this.
I'd like to bring this company
into financial maturity.
The last two years,
we've been held back.
Good Creative is important,
but it can't be running the show.
Our business is about
buying time and space,
and right now that means television.
The bigger we are,
the cheaper we can get it.
I don't think I heard
the word "client" once.
Well, Bert,
when the economy is good,
people buy things,
and when it's bad, they don't.
There's no reason for us to be tied
to Creative's fantasies of persuasion.
It certainly is an ambitious way
of thinking about things.
What?
I think it sounds like a great agency,
and I think Duck is the man to run it.
I just don't think I'll be a part of it.
You don't want to be a part of it?
If this is the agency you want,
Duck is the man for the job.
This is what I'm talking about.
Artistic temperament.
Don, is this really necessary?
It is.
Because he loves this room
and hearing his own voice
and saving the day.
Except this time,
he's got to get with the team.
Don, you can either honor your contract
or walk out that door with nothing
and start selling insurance.
I don't have a contract.
We're close.
We didn't think we needed one.
Gentlemen.
I sell products, not advertising.
I can't see as far into the future as Duck,
but if the world is still here on Monday,
we can talk.
Don, hold on.
Let him go.
It'll take a second to find some kid
who can write a prose poem
to a potato chip.
Calm down.
Let him throw his tantrum.
The man disappeared
for three damn weeks,
and I put this deal together.
What more do you need to know?
Duck, would you
excuse us for a minute?
Of course.
This doesn't affect the merger, does it?
No.
He never could hold his liquor.
Mr. Draper, your wife called.
She wants you to come home.
You should go home as well.
I can't even think right now.
Greg says they put St. Luke's on alert.
Your bag.
I don't need it.
Good night.
...this correspondent
that there is more
firepower now in Cuba
than at any time during World War...
Why are you smiling?
Because you're still here.
I was hoping
the train would be empty.
Have a drink with me.
Okay.
Why are you still here?
Trudy must be worried.
What is it with you?
What?
You never let me talk
about what I want to talk about.
What do you want to talk about?
About what you said about the truth.
Can I tell you the truth?
Why wouldn't you?
You make it so hard.
What are you talking about?
You.
I've been thinking
about everything that's going on.
And I thought...
who'd care if I was gone?
I mean, Trudy would care,
but she doesn't know me.
But you do.
And I know you.
And I think you're perfect.
I'm not perfect, Pete.
Yes, you are.
And I wish I had picked you then.
Pete.
I love you.
And I want to be with you.
What?
Didn't you know that?
Pete,
I could have had you in my life forever
if I wanted to.
What do you mean?
I could have had you.
I could have shamed you
into being with me.
But I didn't want to.
I don't understand.
You got me pregnant.
I had a baby,
and I gave it away.
What?
I had your baby,
and I gave it away.
Are you serious?
You can't be serious.
I wanted other things.
I don't understand.
Well,
one day you're there...
and then, all of a sudden...
there's less of you,
and you wonder
where that part went,
if it's living somewhere outside of you.
And you keep thinking...
maybe you'll get it back.
And then you realize...
it's just gone.
Why would you tell me that?
I'm sorry, Pete.
- Daddy!
You're home.
At about 2 p.m.
Yesterday afternoon,
set out to intercept the Marucla.
She was assisted
by S2F's tracker aircraft.
The Pierce made contact
with the Marucla...
They finally went down.
...at about 10:30 p.m. Last night,
Eastern Daylight Time.
Sometime after midnight...
I have to talk to you.
The Pierce was joined by the destroyer
Joseph F. Kennedy.
I have something to tell you.
What?
I'm pregnant.
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA