You're asking if I've seen these before?
They've been running this for ten years.
The Playtex people are jealous.
They shouldn't be.
Maidenform is a dream,
but Playtex is a bra.
I've never seen either brand go wrong.
I had four of these up in my dorm.
I didn't even know what advertising was.
Why now? Sales are strong.
Someone has a wife with an opinion.
They would like to do
what Maidenform is doing,
not what we're doing.
Why? Then they both
have the same campaign.
I love how they don't need a diagram.
Peggy, do you wear Playtex?
And if so, why?
I do,
and I agree with
the 95 women we surveyed
about how well it fits.
I find they both open easily.
I like a happy client,
although you'd think
someone would be able
to talk them out of jumping
onto a bandwagon
- as solid as this.
- Maybe they want us to raise the bar.
Why, because their share
of the market keeps increasing?
You see them every four months.
Why not throw them a bone?
Let them see they're paying for creative.
Just wrinkle it a little.
I went to sleep in my bra,
and I thought I was so-and-so.
Thank you for that.
Just for fun, let's say
we're looking for new,
and by new I mean old Maidenform.
Peggy, you dig in around
Playtex's unique benefits.
Just the man to do it.
What do I tell them?
Tell them you couldn't get a hold of me.
Mr. Phillips, your ex...
your wife...
Mrs. Phillips...
Pauline. I see her.
Thank you, Joyce.
Hey, fella.
Hey, Chauncey. Come here.
Someone made you
smell like a girl, yes.
Come on. This way.
Hey, slugger.
Hey, Dad.
- Precious.
- Hi, Daddy.
- You look well.
- So do you.
How's your mother?
Worse. She's very erratic.
Did you see the guy up at Brigham
that Bob Levinson recommended?
I don't want to talk
about this right now.
I can't leave right now.
I wish you would have told me
that you were going to be early.
Well, I know you're not
good in the afternoons.
That's not true anymore.
You know that.
Okay.
You two have a good time.
I will try and call you from Nana's.
Did you get a suite?
They opened up the room next door.
I even got a rollaway for Chauncey.
'Cause he's a good boy. Yeah.
We're going to have
a wonderful time on the town.
I got tickets
for A Funny Thing Happened.
We saw it.
Not from these seats.
I should go.
So, you'll have to wait
a little while in my office,
do your studies, work up an appetite.
It's Memorial Day.
All I have is German vocabulary.
Hey, Duck. Sorry to bother you.
Nice dog.
Who are these?
This is my son Mark
and my daughter Patricia.
A handsome family.
And this is Chauncey.
I hope he can't smell cat on me.
Freddie and I work together.
Can I bend your ear a minute?
Spit it out, Freddie.
We're going to need
another box of brassieres.
Yes. Of course.
Enjoy your holiday.
Come on, Chauncey.
Her skin cleared up,
but she still looks unhappy.
She's a cheerleader.
For who, the University of Dour?
Does she have any cute friends?
These are the top three.
I'm sorry, but compared to the kids
on American Bandstand,
they look miserable.
Those kids are drunk.
Really?
I don't know.
What about the idea of them
going on a date?
Mr. And Mrs. Fresh Face.
We could do multiple panels in print,
but it would really translate to TV.
How?
Like a contest?
No, it's a story.
Anticipation as they get ready,
fixing their hair to look perfect.
Their skin, it's not even on their mind.
They're two kids
who used to have a problem.
Thanks, Clearasil.
Maybe, but it's prom night,
and it ends with him at the door
and her and a corsage,
the first moment
they see each other.
And Dad with the Brownie?
Clearasil...
and some kind of line.
What about "Thanks, Clearasil"?
I need to think about it.
I can work with that.
You want to run this
by your father-in-law?
Eventually.
Have a nice holiday.
So how the hell are you, Don?
Good. How are you, Crab?
Glad to be in shorts.
You don't play?
I don't mind watching.
Whenever it's this hot,
I think about that summer
they executed the Rosenbergs.
It was always about to rain.
I remember that.
We were still in Manhattan.
- I don't miss it.
- Yep.
We get them to close Sing Sing,
we'll be in Shangri-la.
I keep having this dream
that there's a power failure
and the gates open.
Hadn't thought of that.
Let's change the subject.
Eventually, I just said, "Fine.
"If Lem Jones Associates is falling apart,
maybe it's time to move on."
I hadn't heard about that.
I guess you PR men have the best PR.
Yeah, I went to Rogers & Cowan
and left it burning behind me.
What happened over there?
I was on the team that took the fall
for the Cuban Revolutionary Council.
The Bay of Pigs?
The CIA hired us
to help inspire the Cuban people
to a coordinated wave
of sabotage and rebellion.
You handled that?
Not as badly as they did.
But I don't know when Don's going
to be able to get away.
High-class problems, my dear.
Marcie, we should say
hello to Chuck and Ann.
I didn't know you belonged here.
I've been coming here
since I was a kid.
We're guests of the Pattersons.
Where's Tara?
Over there, I think.
I haven't seen you riding.
I suppose that's true.
I know you changed your schedule,
and I'm afraid I had
something to do with that.
No. Don't be ridiculous.
All I wanted to say is
please ride when you want.
I'll stay out of your way.
It's very nice to see you.
Arthur, it's okay.
As we used to say in college,
let's be friends.
Good. Because I think
you would have enjoyed
seeing me get nosed
into the trough the other day.
No.
Yes.
Mommy! Mommy!
Well, it's nice to see you.
You as well.
It had nothing to do with Kennedy.
Still, all that vigor disappeared
when he found out
he couldn't get anything done.
It's Versailles.
Jackie's smiling all over the world.
He's chasing starlets.
Everybody's happy.
I'm building a bomb shelter.
Really?
If you see Petra, don't mention it.
She doesn't want people to know.
Good seeing you, Don.
Let me know if you need a reference.
We'd love to have you here.
If I could have everyone's attention
for a moment.
Please be seated.
It is a tradition
that we have our ribs and fashion show
on this day every year.
Well, this is not to dim
our resolute admiration
for the fortitude of those
who have so nobly served our country,
many of whom will not be
enjoying ribs this afternoon.
If you could please stand,
all servicemen,
for a moment of our
insufficient appreciation.
Including Lester Aaron.
Lester was a Rough Rider.
Please, heroes, on your feet.
Can you close the door?
You're letting the air out.
Those look delicious.
It's not the club,
but at least you know
I washed my hands.
How are things in the circus?
Damn serious.
What is this?
J&B.
The network sent me a case.
This is why I don't have a TV.
You want something else?
He'll suffer through it.
Do you know where you're summering?
We were thinking Point O'Woods.
I have to work, though.
Mother's going to expect you on Fishers.
I see her crossing the widow's walk
with an eye to the sea.
Peter.
I was on the phone
with her the other day,
and you were all she talked about.
- Really?
- No. I'm kidding.
I don't think I know
what's funny about that.
Judy, would you help me
with the corn?
Now, listen. Don't scrimp.
Take a vacation.
Don't Trudy's folks have
some incredible vacation spread?
It's not about the money, Bud.
I'm very important to the agency.
My absence is felt.
Yes. Well.
Let's see how
the Ottomanelli Brothers treated us.
And here's Annette Fogel
ready for the playa.
That's Spanish for beach, gentlemen,
and that's where you'll want to be.
If something sportier
is what you're looking for,
- check out...
- I have to go.
...last year's singles champion.
Really? You're really going?
I wouldn't think you'd want to leave this.
People will be working. I should stop by.
Okay.
You're going to miss the sparklers.
Call me from the emergency room.
Oh, and this delight, Judy Sawyer,
is ready for the beaches of California,
where she loves to do the Watusi.
Room 301.
Hello.
You're there. Good.
Yes.
But there's been a change of plans.
I'm spending the day with my son.
We're going to the beach.
Your son?
He's 18.
I don't know why
I never brought him up.
Jimmy will be at the Beverly Hills
for the next ten days.
Los Angeles. That's far away.
No. It's some club in Kentucky.
Still far away.
I could stay out at the beach,
and you could join.
You never saw it.
Don't do that.
What? You never think about it?
No.
I do. All the time.
The car on its side,
your body crushing me.
I don't know why I think about it.
Maybe I do.
I'll call you.
I'd like that.
Morning.
Hello.
I ran that "Thanks, Clearasil" thing
by my father-in-law.
He loved it.
I'm glad.
The libraries were closed yesterday.
What did you do?
I was working,
and then there was a barbecue.
It was too hot.
Trudy and I saw Liberty Valance.
It goes along for a while,
and then it takes a turn
and ends up exactly where
you thought it was going.
John Wayne shot him.
Have you seen it yet?
It's okay. You saved me 50 cents.
I'm sorry. I hate people who do that.
I know you don't like the line.
Look, it's all about keeping
your father-in-law happy.
I do my job, you do yours.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Just play with it.
Okay?
So you're still out there in Brooklyn?
Yes.
Where again?
Marine Park?
No, I moved a while ago.
I'm on my second apartment,
in Prospect Park.
East 83rd Street.
It's a ghost town.
But my brother came to my cookout.
Who were you with?
My family.
Pete, look, I really do
have a lot of work to do.
Of course.
Let me know where you land.
How was your day off?
Restful.
I went to the beach.
Too much, I see.
I got it behind my knees.
I couldn't sit down.
Morning.
Good morning, Mr. Sterling.
Has your wife seen that yet?
Do me a favor.
Let me be there when it happens.
Is that why you're here?
Concerned for my well-being?
Here's your cigarette. Be on your way.
But wait. There's more.
You are going to have lunch with Duck.
Perhaps on a train car,
because I want you to sign an armistice
on American Airlines.
What are you talking about?
I've been in the meetings.
Errol Flynn is gone,
and so is my taste for swordplay.
You two need to put them away.
I have.
I've been married for over 20 years.
I know the difference between a spat
and spending a month on the couch.
Don't go to bed angry.
Two hot chocolates.
I don't want it.
Sure you do.
It's good when it's hot
to drink something hot.
If you continued with the Scouts,
you would have learned that.
Patty, you can use the phone,
but Miss Morrison works for me, not you.
Daddy has a morning meeting.
There's a food cart.
It'll be here in 20 minutes.
No scraps for Chauncey.
I have money. I have $150.
Mark.
That's good.
How did you get that tidy sum?
Mr. Reeve gave it to me.
And why would he do that?
Because he wants us to be happy
when he marries Mom.
We all want you to be happy.
And whatever his intentions,
it's very generous.
He already asked her.
Well.
You must have known eventually
that your mother and I
might be starting new lives.
We understand. We don't care.
It's not easy for her.
With you away at St. Paul's now,
she's lost her man of the house.
Franklin Reeve is a good man.
Mom's going to stick you with Chauncey.
What?
We're supposed to say good-bye to him.
She can't make you do that.
Dad, he's your dog.
And I've learned to live without him
so you two kids
could have some consistency.
Frank's allergic.
Your mother will be here in a half an hour.
Where are we?
We had an interesting idea.
We?
Are you on Playtex?
He wants to get credit for his idea.
You sure about that?
Well, we went out the other night,
after the meeting...
you know, a little extra hours after hours...
and I looked around the bar.
We all did.
From what I understand,
Playtex has an amazing bra,
but it doesn't take you anywhere.
Well put.
So I was thinking.
Women right now
already have a fantasy,
and it's not going up the Nile.
It's right here in America.
Jackie Kennedy and Marilyn Monroe.
Every single woman is one of them.
Watch this.
Jackie.
Marilyn.
Marilyn...
Well, Marilyn's really a Joan,
not the other way around.
That is an idea
and an impressive presentation.
Well, you always say
it's a 24-hour-a-day job.
Apparently, I've already signed off on it.
I don't know if all women
are a Jackie or a Marilyn.
Maybe men see them that way.
Bras are for men.
Women want to see themselves
the way men see them.
You're a Jackie or a Marilyn...
a line and a curve.
Nothing goes better together.
Which do you think I am?
Gertrude Stein.
I would say you're more classical,
Hellenic.
Irene Dunne.
I love Irene Dunne.
Peggy, you're going
to have company on this.
Congratulations, Kinsey.
You forced your way onto an account.
Mr. Phillips is here.
Sorry I'm late.
Get back. Out.
Who's the new account man?
It's Chauncey. Sorry about that.
Listen, any idea
when I can schedule Playtex?
We're laying track.
I think you can bring
the train in tomorrow.
Something new, I hope.
Can I drop some crumbs, at least?
Two sides of one woman...
Jackie by day, Marilyn by night.
Maybe it's two girls.
But definitely two flavors...
vanilla and cherry.
Sounds good.
Don, your girl says you're free for lunch.
She's in charge.
Come on, Chauncey.
Come on.
Thought you all were listening.
Let's go.
Freddie.
What, sweetheart?
I wish you would have told me
you were going to work Tuesday night.
If you have something better,
I'll run it by Don.
He already likes that.
Yes, he does.
Isn't that our goal?
I'm not saying I had a better idea,
but now I'm not even a part of it.
All I had to do was be in that bar.
Believe me,
you didn't want to be in that bar.
The work's done.
Now go write me some titillating copy.
Mr. Draper is here to see you.
Send him in.
Are you coming by to pick me up?
No.
It's just I wasn't really planning
on coming back after lunch.
Any way we can have
this conversation now?
Conversation?
Roger told me it was
just a friendly lunch.
I know.
People start giving you things.
They think it's cute.
I've got a crate of that crap somewhere.
That's quite a playing field you have there.
I don't like anything on it but ashes.
I thought maybe your secretary
was better than mine.
Nobody's secretary's better than yours.
You creative directors.
All I can say is it's been hard
to figure things out around here.
Eighteen months in?
We can't be that unusual.
I'm doing the job you hired me to do.
I tell people that Sterling Cooper
is the only place to be.
You've been pitching more to me
than you have to clients.
What does that mean?
It means you've been
selling their ideas to me
more than mine to them.
When I was in the Marine Corps,
I missed duty.
Fell down the steps or something.
My squad leader covered,
but then I confessed to the men.
He laid down some rifle fire for me,
and I acted like I didn't need it.
That's not the situation
I want to be in here.
So what, you're covering for me?
Who am I in this story?
I'm grateful, Don.
If you hadn't brought me in,
where would I be?
Some fifth wheel at McCann?
Look, I did everything I could
for you on American Airlines.
It was a risk worth taking.
People think of us differently.
What do you want me to say?
That we're on the same team?
That I love being in your unit?
Sarge, I'm scared?
You have an "I told you so," okay?
Can we move forward?
I'm the one that looks bad.
It hasn't hurt the company.
Yes.
Of course we can.
And I will tell Roger we had lunch.
Well. Good, then.
Okay.
Where did you come from?
You don't want to know.
Wait.
I love it.
I'm warm and I'm cold.
What time is it?
A little after 4.
I have to get ready.
Where are you going?
My daughter's in a play.
Daughter?
Is that everyone?
She's at Sarah Lawrence.
How much preparation do you need?
You don't want me to go.
I took the afternoon off.
For me?
You're a lion, aren't you?
Now I know what you like.
You can go.
I know I can.
Do you want to stay here?
Watch TV?
Go through my things?
I would never leave you alone in my place.
Yes, you would.
Stay.
Relax.
Believe me, I'm the same way.
It has to come out somewhere.
I'll get you out in time
for dinner, I promise.
What's going on?
You here to audition?
No one told me about this.
I'm taking pictures.
You can look at the pictures.
I didn't know you'd want to come.
Is Paul in there?
A lot of guys are in there.
You can come in if you want.
No. I'm just surprised
because I have an eye for this.
Don't worry about Kinsey.
I won't let him put anything together
without you.
Who's next?
Hey, girl.
You look lost.
Chauncey.
Here he is.
I apologize, Chauncey.
I thought you were a girl.
Beautiful dog.
Where have you been hiding him?
I made my wife give him back to me.
Missed him too much.
I like dogs.
Dogs are better than wives.
Never a problem communicating.
I like having one in the office.
Makes us look more easygoing,
friendly, you know, to clients.
Maybe I'll bring one in, too.
What breed do you have?
I don't have one.
I was going to get one for the office.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Good night, Campbell.
Come on, Chauncey.
What were you doing
in Sterling Cooper?
There was a casting call for Playtex.
Right.
The fellas are calling it the bra-ditions.
That's funny.
You work there?
I do.
Want me to find out how it went?
I already know. Not well.
I find that hard to believe.
Well, they fall in love
with a picture of you,
and then you come in,
and they're disappointed.
But it doesn't make any sense
because all they need is a picture.
I didn't bring my camera with me,
but I can't imagine it
being better than this.
I don't know. Maybe I look tired.
I just flew back from working in London.
London?
What's your name?
Peter Campbell.
Oh, my. Account executive.
I love the taste of Scotch.
Thank you.
Stop. Turn around.
Let me look at you.
When I first saw you,
I thought you were foreign.
Really? Is that right?
Hold that.
I have company.
I'll be right back.
Who was that?
- My mother.
- Really?
What, you didn't think I had a mother?
It's okay.
Hold on.
Up the long, delirious, burning blue,
I topped the windswept
heights with easy grace
where never lark or even eagle flew.
And while with silent lifting mind
I strode the high untrespassed
sanctity of space,
put out my hand,
and touched the face of God.
You want me to fix you something?
What's that?
Cereal.
No. That.
Do you like it?
I bought it at the auction.
Can I speak to you a minute?
What? What's wrong?
Where are you going in that?
Swimming.
You asked me if I like it. I don't.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
a 15-year-old lifeguard.
a bunch of tennis pros,
not to mention all those loafing
millionaires taking the summer off.
- Do you want to be ogled?
- Oh, Don.
Everybody bought one at the auction.
It's desperate.
I didn't know that.
I have to go.
See you tonight.
Joan, there you are.
Are you aware that I'm
on the Playtex account?
What about it?
Please tell the girls
I am to be included in all the memos.
Sure. For a moment there,
I thought you were just another person
coming to ask me about my brassiere.
Why aren't I on the list?
I don't know what to tell you.
I'm not involved in that.
There's business going on,
and I'm not invited.
I'm a good drinker.
What are you asking me?
You know how this office works.
Parts of it.
Forget it.
I've never had your job.
I've never wanted it.
You're in their country.
Learn to speak the language.
You don't talk that way.
I don't need to.
And honestly,
you've never listened to a word I've said.
You want to be taken seriously?
Stop dressing like a little girl.
Jacqueline Kennedy,
Marilyn Monroe.
Women have feelings
about these women
because men do.
Because we want both,
they want to be both.
It's about how they want
to be seen by us...
their husbands, their boyfriends,
their friends' husbands.
Here's the idea, very simply.
The bra is called the Harlequin.
In fit and form,
it should be your very best.
It comes in black and white.
Jackie, Marilyn.
Same incredible fit,
two different women.
And the beauty of it is
it's the same woman,
the same model.
Look at that. It is.
And even if you don't notice it,
you still get a bit of an "Aha"
when you read the copy.
"Nothing fits both sides of a woman
better than Playtex."
It's a very impressive idea, Don.
I like the girl.
So will your customers.
It's a very flattering mirror.
This definitely moves you
into Maidenform's neighborhood.
But sales have been so good
when we talk about
how well our brassieres fit.
I don't know what to say.
We were talking in the cab
on the way over.
Let Maidenform have
women's imaginations.
We'll take their money.
I couldn't have said it better myself.
Well, I apologize for the goose chase.
We're very sorry.
No one else can have
this campaign, right?
It's yours.
We'll keep it on file for you.
A pleasure.
- Thanks again.
- Thanks for coming in.
That was a waste of inspiration.
These people.
Don't worry. It's not your fault.
They made up their minds
on the way over.
Why put up a fight?
I think we bought
a couple years of security.
If they ever decide
they want to go that way,
they know we can do it.
Listen, we would love
to show our appreciation
by entertaining
you gentlemen tonight.
And you can put it on our bill.
Make sure Don knows he's invited.
Where should we go?
Surprise us.
If we were to take you
to see some girls in their underwear,
would you feel like you're at work?
No. That sounds good.
Well, let us clear the decks.
6:30 at the Tom-Tom.
That's on 44th and 8th.
We will be there,
and the tab will be open.
I'm going to go tell Campbell.
Take care.
Good to see you.
- See you there.
- Bye-bye.
Mr. Phillips.
We have artwork
in the evening papers, son,
and I don't have them.
Someone's supposed
to put them on my desk,
Friday or not.
Should I get some?
What do you think?
I'll be right back.
It's flattering to be able
to keep you interested.
Stop talking.
Why don't you want me to talk?
You know you want me to.
Do I?
You do.
Touch me.
No.
Don't stop torturing me.
I want the full Don Draper treatment.
You're spoiling the mood.
I wanted it, and I got it,
and it's better than they said.
What?
Have no fear.
You're known as a connoisseur.
You have lots of fans.
Are you talking about me?
I wasn't, no.
Well, who was?
What?
Who?
Sarah Tierney at Random House.
I don't know who you're talking about.
Stop.
This is nobody's maiden voyage here,
handsome.
You have a reputation.
Enjoy it.
Does it make you feel better
to think that I'm like you?
My goodness.
Gloves come off.
I like this.
You want to blindfold me?
What are you doing?
Are you going?
I told you to stop talking.
Thank you.
People are going to think
you're the mayor.
Hey, look, it's Peggy.
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I heard we were celebrating.
I thought I'd stop by.
Did you now?
- Stay for one drink.
- Okay.
You're staying all night, honey.
Now you got the best seat
in the house.
Tell me what you want for Christmas.
Yeah!
What do you want for breakfast?
Grapefruit.
Hey, Daddy.
Hey, you.
I'm not going to talk.
I don't want you to cut yourself.
Are you okay, Daddy?
You know what, Sally?
I think you better leave me alone.
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA