Previously on AMC's Mad Men...
Sally needs to see a psychiatrist.
Why? Because she couldn't hear.
She's out of control.
I thought you'd be concerned.
You've crossed the border
from lubricated to morose.
Ken has accounts.
Fillmore Auto Parts because
entered the nation arena.
Abe. Are you with Joyce?
Are you?
It's basic training. I'll be back.
What am I gonna do?
Who I'm gonna talk to?
I'm just gonna take you to your door.
Why is that?
Because that's as far as
I can go right now.
Sync by n17t01, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
I'm interested in today.
That was Friday.
Look, I'll clear lunch plus one hour
and we'll grab a sandwich
and discuss this face to face.
I'm hanging up.
Is it broken?
The lamp?
What are you doing all the way over there?
It's too hot.
Would you settle for a leg?
I'd be grateful.
It's cold
and soft.
I'm the softest.
So which one of us is gonna
look at the clock first?
I caught it when I was picking up the lamp.
I'm already late.
For what?
Secor laxatives.
Did I spoil the mood?
What do you have to do?
I have a 4:00 at Erwin Wasey.
Doing what?
I can't tell you that, Mr. Bond.
I told you.
What are you working on over there?
I don't tell 'em what I'm doing for you.
You're not lying in bed
with them right now either.
Do you know what a Chinese wall is?
I really should go.
Can I get in the bathroom first?
Just take your time.
Let yourself out.
Lock the door behind you as a courtesy.
You wanna leave me here?
You sure?
I'm taking everything interesting with me.
I don't understand. Do you honestly think
my book isn't better than Ogilvy's?
Mine's got a story.
It's got mystery, intrigue, romance.
I tell you what else it's got:
It's got examples
of how to sell things.
Hold on.
I'm on the phone.
It's Mrs. sterling.
She's leaving for the weekend.
It's only Wednesday.
They have phones in Southampton.
Ira, I don't want to sound ungrateful.
I just think...
Hello? Hello?
Shit.
Come in.
These need signatures, not initials.
Caroline said you refused?
It's just so much more work.
I was just giving her a hard time.
Can I interest you in the same?
And I'm supposed to tell you in person
that Mr. Pryce will be taking off
the last two weeks
of August for his son's visit.
You had to tell me that in person?
- So depressing.
- He doesn't want a memo circulating.
He's afraid people will stop working.
What are you doing in August?
I'm not sure.
Well, what are you doing this afternoon?
The same thing I do
every afternoon... Working...
Which is what I'm trying to do right now.
It's not cute.
Joanie.
Jesus. I'm sorry.
What did you say to her?
What does that have to do with you?
Her husband got called up.
He's going to Vietnam right after basic.
Vietnam.
That's not good.
It's okay. We've all been
walking on eggshells.
Good afternoon, all.
I know you don't like to be bombarded
the moment you walk in,
but Fillmore and Secor
are both coming in tomorrow.
I can't move forward
with either until you sign off
on what I worked through lunch to finish.
I'm sorry. I had a long lunch,
went for a swim.
Come back in an hour. I'm taking a nap.
It's a business of sadists and masochists,
and you know which one you are.
- Oh hi.
- Peggy, your boyfriend's here.
Satisfaction guaranteed.
- Why are you here?
- Thought we could get a drink,
- shoot the bull.
- Sure.
- What time? Where?
- * When you're alone *
* and life is making you lonely *
- * you can always go... *
- 7:00, P.J. Clarke's.
* midtown *
I'll meet you in the lobby.
Ooh, down below.
Give it a break, jughead.
Oh, I'm not shocked
by your lesbian hijinks.
I just hope you know you can never do
what a man can do.
That's true.
Bad news. Don showed up. We're on at 4:00.
How was your siesta? Are you refreshed?
- Yes.
- Dr. Miller returned your call.
She said not to wake you
and you needn't return.
But she got the message
and you're gonna have to wait.
- Thank you.
- Are you going to the toilet?
I have to hire more copywriters,
but these men come in and I know
the better they are,
the more my job is in danger.
Oh my.
Look who's here... Abe.
Peggy, I don't know if you remember
Abe Drexler from Kellogg's loft party.
- Hi, I'm Peggy.
- I remember.
Abe, you want to join us for a drink?
Yes, please do.
Oh, stay. I'll just stand here.
Can I get a Johnny Walker with ice?
Ah, he didn't hear me.
You know what? I'm gonna go play darts.
- Take my seat.
- Are you sure?
Pay for that. See you kids later.
I'm sorry. She's...
Always so damn self-amused.
What are you talking about?
I was gonna stop by your office,
but I didn't want to get you in trouble.
Then I thought about finding out
where you live, but that's weird.
So anyway,
- it's nice running into you.
- I don't know what to say.
That's very flattering.
Well, that's how I meant it.
Johnny Walker. Rocks.
The bartender here listens to me.
- May I help you?
- Are you Joan Harris?
- I am.
- We're from madam Inga's.
You are to receive massage,
manicure and pedicure.
- Can we?
- I didn't order this.
It's a gift from a friend, tip included.
- What friend?
- I'm not allowed to say this.
In Greece right now? Make no mistake,
that's a revolution.We are a hair away
from everything falling apart
in every society. It's so tenuous.
All these corporations just throw
their money at everyone
to keep the status quo intact
'cause the people outnumber them.
But in the blink of an eye,
they could overturn everything.
It's an illusion that
America's so organized
that it could never happen over here.
- Are you from Brooklyn?
- I am.
- Me too.
- I don't hear it.
One more drink and it'll come out.
Okay.
What am I talking to you
about corporations for?
- You must deal with them all the time.
- I guess.
Vick chemical, American tobacco,
but most of them are family businesses...
Samsonite, Fillmore Auto Parts,
- sugarberry...
- Fillmore Auto Parts is worse than a corporation,
- what with the boycott and all.
- What boycott?
The southern stores won't hire negroes.
Says who?
It was in "The voice."
It was in a couple of places.
I don't think that's true.
I would've heard that.
It is true.
That doesn't seem like them.
I'm sure they're perfectly nice
for racists, you know,
and obviously your company has
an investment in looking the other way.
Well, it's a complicated idea,
but in advertising,
we don't really judge people.
We try and help them
out of these situations.
Certainly we would try and stop this.
If it's true, it's not good
for their business.
Jesus, I don't even know where to start.
You would've done a campaign for Goldwater?
You kidding?
That would've been spectacular.
- Did you vote for him?
- Of course not.
Wha... civil rights isn't a situation
to be fixed with some P.R. campaign.
It's an inequality that
the world has its eyes on.
I know.
But I have to say
most of the things negroes can't do
I can't do either
and nobody seems to care.
What are you talking about?
Half of the meetings
take place over golf, tennis,
in a bunch of clubs where
I'm not allowed to be a member
or even enter.
The university club said the only way
I could eat dinner there
was if I arrived in a cake.
There's no negro copywriters, you know.
I'm sure they could fight
their way in like I did.
Believe me, nobody wanted me there.
All right, Peggy.
We'll have a civil rights march for women.
I have a really early day.
It was nice to see you again.
Wait. Hey hey hey. I'm just saying
they're not shooting women
to keep 'em from voting. That's all.
Oh, Jesus. I'm really sorry.
I'm much better on paper.
You're opinionated
and you're criticizing me.
That's not what I'm doing.
This is discourse.
I knew I shouldn't have let Joyce leave.
Have a good night.
A three-letter word for a flightless bird.
Emu.
Nope. It starts with an "l."
The hell it does.
Good morning, Mr. Draper.
Could I get some coffee?
And let me know when Dr. Miller arrives.
It's hard... The way she breezes past me.
She's pushy, that one.
I guess that's what it takes.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- And thank you.
- For what?
That was very thoughtful.
I knew I was rubbing you the wrong way,
so I thought, why not have
someone rub you the right way?
- I brought you bear claws.
- Caroline won't let me have one
unless it's on the end of a real bear.
- Well, anyway.
- Joanie.
- It'll be okay.
- People love to say that.
Look, I know you're having a tough run.
Let me get you a meal, hmm?
Take your mind off things?
Of course.
I forgot for a second that you're
incapable of doing something nice
without expecting something
nicer in return.
I didn't mean anything by it.
Honest.
Just thought you could use a night out.
- Thank you. I'm fine.
- Good.
- What are you doing here?
- I wrote something.
I kind of wrote it for you.
I would love it if you read it.
"Nuremberg on Madison Avenue"?
- What is this?
- It's what I was trying to say last night,
but without, I don't know,
my abrasive tone.
- Read it.
- Right now in front of you?
Nah. Take your time.
I'll wait over here.
I have a lot to do.
I came all the way up here. I want
to know what you think, okay?
These domesticated suburbanites
still have a primitive desire
to get their hands dirty,
but have they have become so
removed from nature that they can't.
They don't know how to hunt
or swing a hammer
- or fix their cars.
- You mean like these two.
Actually, no. I'm from Vermont
and Don's a competitive fly fisherman.
What our findings show
is that this demographic
will spend a good amount of money
for the satisfaction of being useful
with their hands.
Ladies love a man
who's good with his hands.
You think a mechanic
comes in and sees these jokers
looking at fan belts,
he's gonna stick around?
- No offense.
- What's the difference?
Our inventory's the same.
I think if they see
a coat and tie on aisle 4,
they'll think our prices went up.
I know I would.
Listen, salt of the earth, we need
more than mechanics to survive.
You ever hear of Sears?
They'll kill us.
We agreed we all had to agree.
Don't we have enough problems
with the boycott?
Look, I don't want to get involved
in a family squabble,
but I can't move forward
until you agree on a strategy.
What if there were a way
to market to both groups?
"Fillmore Auto Parts.
Where the pros go and everyone's welcome."
- It's a little corny.
- It's great and you know it.
That's not a strategy.
That's two strategies
connected by the word "and."
I can do "where the pros go"
or I can do "everyone's welcome,"
- but not both.
- Sure you can.
Someone has to make a decision.
There are three of you.
Vote.
Sean, what do you think?
I d-d-d-d...
D-d-d-don't know.
What?
You'll have to excuse me for a moment.
Continue, please.
Why d-d-do we
have to c-c-convince him?
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
I am so sorry. Who are you?
My name is Vivian Winters
and I'm going to assume you're her father
since that's what she's led me to believe.
Don. What exactly is going on?
I found her on the train between carriages
trying to avoid the conductor.
I didn't have enough money.
Megan, could you take her to my office?
Go.
Thank you.
Can I pay you for the ticket and your time?
You're just very lucky I ran into her
before someone else did.
The types on that train?
Someone should keep track of her.
You're right. I didn't know.
Men never know what's going on.
I offered you money and I said thank you.
She looks so chubby in the pictures.
Get her mother on the phone now.
What do you think you're doing?
I wanted to see you and I didn't
want to wait two weekends.
Well, you can't do this.
This is very serious.
Mrs. Francis on the line.
- Guess who's sitting on my couch right now.
- What are you talking about?
I'm talking about a stranger
bringing Sally to my office
- because she got on the train with no money.
- You're kidding.
Carla was supposed to pick her up
after the doctor.
- How the hell did this happen?
- Dr. Keener thought it would be good for her
to walk from camp to her
appointment by herself.
Great idea. Thank you, psychiatry.
Don't yell at me.
She needs to learn responsibility.
You need to learn responsibility.
Now come get her.
I've got a business to run here.
Because it's so easy.
It's so much fun to take care of her.
Enjoy.
- What?
- Enjoy, Don.
I'm meeting Henry in the city
tomorrow night. I'll get her then.
Don't move and don't touch anything.
I don't want to hear it. Just make sure
she doesn't leave that room.
Hey.
Are you serious with this?
Everyone knows who represents
Fillmore Auto Parts.
- We're the agency of record.
- But I was defending you.
We have a religion in this country
and it's business. You're not a priest.
You're just another congregant.
So I'm not a war criminal.
Look, why should someone nice
like you have to do this?
Why should you be a part
of that corruption?
It's a waste of your
and a million other artists' gifts.
If you publish this, I'll lose my job.
Maybe you're better than this.
I'm not a political person.
I don't have to defend myself.
You're political whether you like it or not.
And you're not supposed to be insulted.
- You're supposed to be flattered.
- Are you crazy?
You inspired me. I wrote this for you.
I guess I read you wrong.
You look so earnest.
I need your word that you'll destroy that.
Sure.
I won't bother you again.
Miss Blankenship.
Miss Blankenship, are you all right?
Caroline. Oh God. Caroline!
- Oh. Do not come out of there.
- I know!
- What now?
- Excuse me, Mr. Draper.
I'm really sorry to bother you again.
Are you sure?
- I'm afraid so.
- What happened?
Jesus.
Poor thing.
Should we call an ambulance?
The coroner.
What about them?
- I'll attend to this.
- Sally's in there.
- Why?
- She's visiting.
Megan, get a man, and we'll need a blanket.
There's an afghan on Mr. Crane's couch.
She seemed fine just a minute ago.
So where are we?
- Have we agreed on a strategy?
- I'm not sure.
This is where we are.
Correct me if I'm wrong, gentlemen,
but we believe by holding onto
Fillmore's reputation
as a place for professional mechanics,
we can actually attract men of all types.
So it's something like
"Fillmore Auto Parts.
For the mechanic in every man."
And although it seems immaterial to you,
- the Fillmore brothers like it.
- Unanimously.
What was that again?
Fillmore Auto Parts.
"For the mechanic in every man."
My mother made that.
Can we get your signature?
I'm the president.
I think this is a winner.
Gentlemen, always a pleasure.
Ken, can you show them out?
Of course. This way.
My goodness. I was just talking to her.
Listen, my daughter
is sitting in my office.
- What?
- She decided to run away today.
- Sally?
- I'd really appreciate it
if you could go in my bag,
get my keys, take her to my apartment
and just... Sit with her.
Are you sure?
I would have my secretary do it,
but she's dead.
No, of course.
Okay, do you want to introduce me?
I mean, what do I say to her?
Do we really have to have
this discussion right now?
You're Faye.
Find Cooper and Roger at lunch
and stop them from bringing
Secor back here.
Sally, this is my friend Faye.
She's going to take you to my apartment.
- Why?
- You don't want this to get worse, believe me.
Hello. My name is Faye.
I know. My dad just said that.
Stop.
- Where are they taking her?
- She's going to the morgue.
No, she's not.
She's going to Frank E. Campbell.
Anyone track down her family?
She has a niece. I'll call her.
I'm sorry, Bert.
Roger.
You should go home.
Yes. Take all my calls up here.
Okay.
So Fitzgerald says, "I promised to pour
this whiskey over your grave
earlier, but do you mind
if I pass it through me kidneys first?"
- Are you all right?
- Oh, damn it,
I don't want to die in this office.
I almost have twice.
Stop it.
If it looks like I'm going, open a window.
I'd rather flatten the top of a cab.
You are not going to die in this office.
Poor Ida.
She died like she lived...
Surrounded by the people
she answered phones for.
I'm gonna go to my favorite restaurant
and have a glass of cyanide.
Or you could join me.
I don't know.
- I'm gonna kill myself, Joanie.
- No, you're not.
Go get your things.
I'll meet you in the lobby.
I got it.
- Hello, daddy.
- Don't "hello, daddy" me.
Go sit down.
- How was it?
- Great.
We watched a little TV,
one of us took a nap.
You want to stay? You're gonna need to eat.
I know, but I have dinner plans.
Thank you.
Glad I could help.
- Good night, Sally.
- Good night.
Can we order a pizza?
I want you to promise me
you're never going to do this again.
I promise.
Why did you always pick this place?
No chance of running into anyone
and, of course, cherry cheesecake.
Well, the clientele
is older than I remember.
But not us.
I wish you would talk to me about things.
My husband doesn't like it.
I know it's tough,
but he must've known about
the possibilities when he signed up.
I wasn't consulted.
You're kidding.
Because you always tell Jane
about all of your decisions?
She's the woman behind the man, isn't she?
Did you listen to my memoirs?
I just have them transcribed
and recycle the tapes.
And you're not a little curious
if there's a chapter called "Joan"?
There'd better not be.
I know. That's the problem.
And every time I think back,
all the good stuff was with you.
And I'm sorry I keep pestering you.
I just can't help myself.
I don't expect anything to happen.
I appreciate that.
Can I ask you something?
Yes, I'm still mad at you.
Are you going to marry Faye?
What? No.
Is she your girlfriend?
- No.
- She had your keys.
I gave her my keys.
She knew you had peanut butter.
Everyone has peanut butter.
Well, she said she wanted to meet me.
Why would she want to meet me?
Look, I do like her,
but we just work together
and I talk about you a lot.
Do you like her?
- She seems nice.
- Well, good.
Maybe you'll get to see her again sometime.
Oh.
Get out some plates.
'Cause I didn't want to take a cab
on Broadway. It's a beautiful night.
I don't like this neighborhood anymore.
What happened to it?
Miss Blankenship,
you're not missing anything.
- Do you know what time it is?
- I do.
Oh God.
You know what to do.
- Rog...
- Yes. Yes, we do.
Look down. Everything's going to be fine.
- There you go.
- What about her?
Give me your bag.
Rings.
That's everything.
We haven't seen anything.
I can't breathe.
- I want to scream.
- Don't. Come over here.
- You have to calm down.
- My ring. My ring.
Stop it. Everything can be replaced.
You're fine.
Don't stop.
Are you sure you don't want
to call your mother or your brothers?
It's 9:30. They're asleep.
Daddy, I love you so much.
I love you too.
Did you brush your hair?
I want to live with you all the time.
You can't do that, honey.
Why not? I'll be good.
Where are you gonna go to school down here?
What about your friends?
What about your brothers?
They could live here too. I'll watch them.
Sally.
Go to sleep.
- Sally?
- I made French toast.
You know I don't like you using the stove.
Oh, daddy, I do it all the time.
And there's no shells in it.
Do you want me to turn on the TV?
We can watch "The today show."
No.
Where'd you learn how to do this?
Carla taught me.
What's on this?
Mrs. Butterworth's.
Go get it.
That's rum. Read labels.
Is it bad?
Not really.
Get dressed and I'll get you
a bun at the office.
Can't we do something?
All right, here's the deal. No negotiating.
I'm gonna call in, move everything to noon,
and we're gonna go
to the Central Park Zoo.
- And the dinosaur museum?
- One or the other.
We only have till noon.
You finish your breakfast.
I'm going to get ready.
You want me to get Don to do it?
Of course, he didn't really know her.
No, he didn't.
Caroline, get Mrs. Harris.
It's regarding Ida Blankenship's obit.
That ought to get her in here.
This is an insult to her.
I can't think of anything.
And I have no office in which to ruminate.
Cooper's trying to write an obit...
Something sharp and sweet.
Well, Mr. Cooper,
shall we say,
- "beloved friend..."
- Mmm.
"...devoted caretaker..."
Put "quietly in her sleep," of course.
What's her profession... secretary?
Executive secretary.
She was born in 1898 in a barn.
She died on the 37th floor of a skyscraper.
She's an astronaut.
Hey.
Is this what it took to get you in here?
Look, I'm sorry.
It was in the heat of the moment.
And there was a moment. You know that.
I'm not sorry,
but I'm married.
And so are you.
I feel something
and I know you do.
Good afternoon.
- Hello.
- Sally, this is Megan.
- Where's Miss Blankenship?
- She went away.
I'm helping out for a little bit.
Her mother should be by at 5:00.
Can you handle five minutes?
Are you hungry?
She ate plenty.
I'm gonna get coffee and check in.
Shit. Now we can't leave.
Huh. Harry said on the form
where it says "cause of death,"
they wrote "Don Draper."
How long do you think Yvette Mimieux's
gonna last on his desk?
I say we start a pool
on whether she's fired, quits or dies.
Where's Dr. Miller?
- I don't know if she's coming in.
- She is.
Well, the Fillmores want a jingle,
a c-c-c-catchy tune.
Don't do that.
Harry says no rock 'n' roll
if we want middle-class men.
He was pushing Perry Como.
And we had Pat Boone, Roger Miller,
Frankie Laine, Duane Eddy.
I'm glad I came in for this.
How about Harry Belafonte?
Everyone likes him.
I'll get you tickets to Harry Belafonte.
Believe me, he ain't selling
auto parts for these guys.
Well, maybe it'll help them
with their image in the South.
They don't want help.
Have you ever been to the South?
'Cause they have a way of doing things
and it doesn't include Harry Belafonte.
The Fillmore brothers are from Boston.
Same thing.
Well, why are we doing business
with someone that doesn't hire negroes?
Our job is to make men like Fillmore Auto,
not make Fillmore Auto like negroes.
Pick one, get it written and recorded
and if they want to change it,
we will charge them to change it.
How about dean Martin?
He's friends with Sammy Davis Jr.
Does that work for you, Peggy?
Mrs. Francis is going to be
in the lobby any minute.
I have to cover reception,
per Joan's orders.
Go ahead.
Your mother's going to be
downstairs in a minute.
Get your things.
I wanna stay.
Well, you can't.
I want to stay and
I don't know why I can't.
Because you have to go home.
I'll be good. I promise.
- Come on.
- No.
- Let's go.
- No! No!
No no! I'm not going anywhere! Stop it!
- Do you want me to carry you out of here?
- I'm not going.
I'm not leaving. I hate it there!
Is everything okay?
- Can you talk to her?
- What?
Please. I can't bring her back
kicking and screaming to her mother.
I don't have much child psychology.
Just talk to her.
Dr. Faye wants to talk to you.
Hi, Sally.
Remember me from yesterday?
I know you don't want to go,
but you have to.
- Your mother came all the way out here.
- You don't know my mother.
Sally.
Sally,
sometimes we have to do things
we don't want to do.
- Shut up.
- What's gotten into you?
- I don't think I'm helping here.
- We don't want your help.
- Let's go, now.
- Stop it! No! Stop it!
It's gonna be all right.
No, it's not.
I fall all the time.
I was coming to get you.
Mrs.... Your...
Sally's mother is in reception.
Thank you.
I was worried about you.
Come on, let's go.
I was waiting in the lobby at 5:00.
- We lost track of time.
- Well, now I'm late.
Sally?
- Say goodbye to your father.
- Goodbye.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Hi. Are you here to see Peggy?
Can you make me one of those?
No. No, I can't.
- I can't do anything for you.
- Why are you upset?
You shouldn't have put me in that position.
Things happen. I didn't plan it.
You asked me to go watch her.
There was no one else to do it.
And just now? What the hell was that?
I'm not good with kids.
That was not your fault.
Well, it feels like there was
a test and I failed it.
God knows I'd be lying
if I said it didn't cross my mind:
Would I meet your children?
When would I meet your children?
But I don't have any.
I'm sorry.
I love children, but I chose
to be where I am.
I don't view it as a failure.
It doesn't matter.
I mean it.
Jesus. What a mess.
Part of it's good, right?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go. I didn't really sleep.
We can have dinner this weekend.
I'll pick a place.
Good.
Why are you drinking here?
Come on.
I don't know what kind of surprise
you're gonna spring on me.
So Abe Drexler pulled a boner.
It's to be expected.
He seemed so nice.
He's a man. He won't be happy
until he turns you out.
What's that supposed to mean?
Gotta be their girl.
It's the way they want it.
Maybe it's biology.
It's like men are this vegetable soup
and we can't put 'em on a plate
or eat 'em off the counter.
So women are the pot. They heat 'em up.
They hold 'em. They contain them.
But who wants to be a pot?
Who the hell said we're not soup?
I don't think that's true.
It's been my experience.
But you know, I wouldn't
have helped Abe out
if I didn't think he was
some very interesting soup.
Listen, go ahead without me.
Another time.
Are you angry or lovesick?
I don't know.
Night, Peg.
Could you hold that?
Hello.
Sync by n17t01, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com