Previously on "Pan Am".
MI6 will want answers.
I have to take
a lie detector test?
You have a dead body
on their hands, Kate.
You're not begging
to come upstairs?
Some things
are worth waiting for.
You're trying
to distract me.
I'm trying to tell you...
I like you.
- I have to talk to you.
- Can it wait?
Hello, Dean.
It is you and me, Colette.
That's all that matters.
I've always loved you.
I don't think I've ever seen
a morning more beautiful.
Penny for your thoughts?
En route to Rome last June...
During our layover,
I saw you come out of the hotel
with a man in a gray suit.
So I'm guessing
that he was...
A handler from MI6.
Part of my mission there.
And Paris...
You left me at dinner
and told me you had the flu.
I had to sneak away
to make a drop.
So everything...
Everything
I didn't understand
was because you were a spy,
and I was in the dark.
Not everything.
Women are conundrums,
even when they aren't spies.
How about the reason
you called off our engagement?
I didn't know how I was
supposed to be your wife
when I had to...
What,
when you had to lie to me?
Keep my cover, Dean.
But that's over.
I'm free of MI6.
We can be together.
Who is "we," Bridget?
The woman I thought
I knew,
who I loved...
She was fiction.
No.
The woman who fell
in love with you... she was real.
And then... and then
you're just... you're gone.
You left,
and I was forced to move on.
To Colette?
Well...
You have to admit,
last night was wonderful.
And a mistake.
It was my mistake.
I never stopped
loving you, Dean.
And I want to be
your wife.
The question is,
what do you want?
Hello?
Yeah,
this is captain Lowrey.
Uh... yeah.
I-I can get on the next flight
out of Heathrow.
Of course. Let... let him know
that I'll be there.
Uh, bye, now.
I gotta get to New York.
You seen my cuff link?
Is everything all right?
Yeah, uh...
Juan Trippe requested
a meeting with me
in New York. Tomorrow.
- Juan Trippe?
- Yeah.
What does he want?
I don't know.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
So let me get this straight...
The... the chairman
of Pan Am
just flew you back to New York
for a private meeting?
That's right.
What'd he say?
Apparently Khrushchev
and Kennedy
have opened a hotline.
The cold war's thawing.
Mr. Trippe wants Pan Am to be
the first Western airline
- to fly...
- Wait. To the Soviet union?
Yeah. He wants to open
a new route,
so he's sending
a diplomatic mission.
Morning. How are you?
To the Soviet union?
That's what he said.
Well, how come you get to go
and I don't?
- That he didn't say.
- Ugh!
You know what this means,
don't you?
You're Trippe's ace,
the new face of the jet age.
Doubtful.
Next thing you know, he'll
name the airline after you.
Highly doubtful.
Well, if I don't get
the U.S.S.R.,
I'm making the best
of my time off.
How much "yes" you think
a karat will give me?
How much "yes" from who?
What do you mean, "who"?
Amanda.
Wait, this is the girl
your parents set you up with?
- Uh-huh.
- A month ago?
- Thought you hated her.
- Ohh.
When you know, you know.
And you know?
I do!
Oh. Does she?
That's what I aim
to find out.
Just gotta pick
the right moment.
I guess we're both
on a mission.
What,
you don't like onions?
Onions?
In your eggs?
Congressman?
I'm sorry.
I like them better than
I like the "Village voice,"
I'll tell you that.
You're still fixated?
On this worthless piece of
yellow journalism? Yes. Quite.
"Despite insisting
he's a republican to the core,
"an anonymous source
close to the congressman
"claims Rawlings'
public policy stances
don't match
his private beliefs."
Eggs.
Eat.
It's the "Voice."
What do you care
what they think, anyway?
I don't, but I also don't
appreciate sources
with inside knowledge
conspiring with the enemy.
Aren't you
"conspiring with the enemy"
when you're with me?
I don't consider you
the enemy.
Oh. What am I, then?
You're
an important constituent
with an interesting world view...
And, uh...
Something on her lip.
On my lip?
Yeah.
Cute.
Yes, you are.
Which is why I think
it's time to show you off.
I'm having a cocktail party
for some wealthy donors.
Be my date.
What am I supposed to do,
just sit on your arm,
all quiet and docile?
You're supposed to be
your smart,
opinionated,
wonderful self.
Hey. Come on.
Consider it
your coming out party.
It'll be fun.
Oh, my God,
Richard!
You didn't answer my knock.
That doesn't mean
that you can let yourself in.
I deserve
that much privacy.
Not anymore. You're in with us
all the way now.
You knew I'd be stopping by
sooner or later.
We're going to Russia.
Of course
you'd be stopping by.
One of our double agents
has gone silent.
Code name... Anastasia.
Girlfriend of
a high-ranking KGB official.
She lives not far from the hotel
where you'll be staying.
Six months ago,
I was a courier.
And now you want me to pull
this woman out of Russia?
Go to her building.
If she's still in the game,
there'll be a potted sunflower
in her window.
Confirm Anastasia is active
and alive,
and we'll do the rest.
Oh. How very magnanimous.
Be careful.
You're going to Moscow...
The beating heart of communism.
You get made for a spy there,
you don't ever come back.
Enjoy the motherland.
- Pan Am -
Ep. 11 - Diplomatic relations
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Hello, stranger.
Colette. Hey.
I'm really sorry we didn't get
to connect before I left London.
Oh, that's all right.
Gave me a chance to think.
And... have you?
I'm still afraid of what
Bridget's return means
for you and I.
But for the first time
in my life,
I'm not going to let my fear
get the better of me.
I want to be with you...
As terrifying as that is.
- I just hope...
- No, no, no.
I-I do. I want
to be with you, too.
I'm so sorry. I need to...
- Oh, brief the crew.
- Right.
Of course. But... but when we
get to Russia, can we...
Talk more?
- Yeah.
- Please.
I'll see you soon.
Yeah.
Hi.
Our every move
will be watched,
literally, by the Russians.
So be careful
about what you say,
about what you do,
about who you choose
to talk to.
That said,
this is an historic flight.
It's an opportunity
to trail-blaze
not only a new route
for Pan Am,
but ongoing relationship
with the Soviets.
Which is why we damn well
better not
foul this thing up, right?
Sorry for the dramatic entrance,
but why sneak in
with the ground force
when you can soar in
on the Enola Gay
and drop the bomb?
All right. The plan...
Wheels up at 1600.
Then ten hours to Moscow,
where our job will be
to spend four days
showing the Russian bear
the majesty,
the beauty,
and the good graces
of the American eagle.
If all goes well,
you can tell your grandkids
that you were the crew
that got Russia for Juan Trippe.
Excuse me.
Dean Lowrey,
boy wonder, right?
- That's me.
- I'm George Broyles.
Captain Broyles.
Well, it's damn nice to meet
and glad you'll be holding down
my right seat.
I'm sorry... your right seat?
Or left seat.
I'll flip you for it.
As for the rest of you,
we'll have plenty of time
to chew the fat
over the vast Atlantic,
all right?
Two hours to takeoff,
my friends.
Who is that?
Oh, that's a sky God.
What exactly is
a sky God?
World War II pilots.
Big heroes.
Broyles flew a dozen
bomber runs over Berlin.
Mr. Trippe gives him
and his kind carte blanche
to use the airline
whenever they like,
however they like.
Fuel at 43 degrees West
will be 138,000 pounds.
You guys always insist
on having Russians
aboard these flights
into Moscow?
Safety measure.
For Americans.
So we don't crash
into the Kremlin.
Ivan's not so bad.
That's nice to know.
Your sister Laura seems nice.
We're all happy to have you
back and safe, Bridget.
We have hardly any assets...
In the Soviet Union,
no eyes on the ground to know
what Khrushchev is up to.
This is a huge opportunity.
Are you working?
Bridget, you know I can't.
Talk about it. I know.
Oh, it's just so odd...
Being on the outside again.
The silence is deafening.
I take it Juan didn't tell you
I was coming along for the ride.
No. Juan didn't.
That's his style.
Wants to keep us all
on our tips, you know?
Look,
it's a compliment, Lowrey,
him choosing you and me.
Juan knows if he wants
to invade Russia,
he's got to send in
the big guns.
Well, just do me the favor
of not shooting me
in the back, will ya?
Do you think we'll get
to see Red Square
or Lenin's tomb?
This must be hard for you,
stuck on a 10-hour flight
with Dean's ex-fiancee.
You've heard?
Oh, rumors...
And I saw you two talking
in operations.
You know,
it seemed intimate.
Is it true?
I won't say it's not.
Have you talked to her...
Bridget?
No, not yet.
Uh, we were friends.
We were close friends.
You didn't do
anything wrong.
Let me help.
Thank you.
I haven't quite got
my rhythm back.
Speaking of rhythm,
I hope yours and mine won't be
too badly affected by...
You and Dean?
I thought...
Well, we all thought
you had gotten married.
If I had known
that wasn't the truth,
I would have never...
I know.
Dean told me
all about you two.
When you had drinks
in London?
Yes.
Yes. Drinks.
Dean and I... we spent
a long time talking,
and don't worry, Colette.
I shall respect whatever
Dean decides to do.
I've been calling.
And I've been hanging up.
Don't be a child.
You're the one
who took what I wrote
and twisted it for
your stupid "Voice" article.
How exactly did I twist it?
Yes, I have issues
with some of Chris's beliefs,
but to say that he's
a hypocrite...
"Chris"?
Well, you two are cozy.
That he doesn't actually
hold these beliefs
is not what I meant.
Which means he's more
of a warmonger
than I made him out to be?
Take a hike, Mike.
I don't understand
what's going on here, Mags.
You know, one minute
you want to destroy the man,
and the next
you're on a first-name basis
with the biggest death merchant
in congress.
Wh...
You're sleeping with him,
aren't you?
Well, I'm not sleeping
with you anymore, Mike,
so other than that,
it's none of your damn business.
Unbelievable. You...
Well, I-I just came by
to warn you that
the congressman's staff
is obsessed
with uncovering the source
for my article.
Are you threatening
to tell them it's me?
I just came by
to give you a heads-up
that they're not stopping
until they figure out
who the rat is.
Other than that,
enjoy your life,
future Mrs. Congressman.
Pan American World Airways,
we welcome you to Moscow.
I am Olga Dubovik,
representative of Committee
of Diplomatic Relations.
We are delighted to show you
famous Soviet hospitality.
There will be banquet tonight
in hotel ballroom,
and over next few days,
we hope to build
trust and admiration
for our two great nations.
You see those guys
over there
with the grim looks?
KGB minders. Mind them.
We know you will enjoy
your stay here.
As comrade Stalin famously said,
"gaiety is
most outstanding feature
of Soviet Union."
So...
You and Bridget on the flight,
uh, did you two...
Yes, we talked.
Everything is fine.
Good.
That is the smallest bathtub
I have ever seen.
Well, at least there is
no hot water.
Old-world charm
with third-world plumbing.
I hope you find amenities
to your liking.
Oh, well, there are
a few things we could use.
Oh.
Um, soap, maybe.
Is there a market nearby?
No.
No?
You cannot leave hotel,
not without
hospitality ambassador.
Oh, and that would be you?
Mm-hmm.
Have Mayer's Soviet sister.
Next she'll want
to be checking our girdles.
I will arrange tour
for ladies, yes?
1400 hours?
Mm-hmm.
Wait. Why is not
Kate Cameron here?
Uh, what? Uh, I'm sorry?
I'm sorry. I'm... I'm lost.
I was looking...
Kate, it's about time.
Captain Broyles, I was...
W-wondering where you were.
Okay?
Okay.
What did you say to him?
I told him that you had
a very important client
waiting for you.
A client?
Oh, he thinks I'm going to...
Kate, I'm kidding.
What are you doing
down here, anyway?
I must have hit the wrong button
on the elevator.
The wrong button?
What are you doing
down here...
With all this?
A little...
Diplomatic relations.
Pack of ciggies in Moscow is
worth more than a faberge egg.
and you brought this all
on our flight?
Kate, I think
you better go back upstairs
before your KGB pal comes
looking for the menthols.
Well, thank you again
for opening up your home.
Not at all.
I'm surprised all these people
wanted to venture out
on a cold night to hear
what I have to say.
Oh, ignore him.
He's just being modest.
Maggie will disagree
with me on almost anything.
Well, only when you're wrong,
which is... often.
Ted!
Oh, excuse me, please.
I didn't know
you were going to be here.
Uh, neither did I.
Uh, apparently, Amanda's parents
backed the congressman
in his first race.
Uh, Amanda, this is Maggie.
We work together at Pan Am.
Sorry. We walked over,
and my hands are freezing.
And then Teddy wanted to go
for a carriage ride in the park
in the middle of November.
I thought it'd be romantic.
Who are you, and what have you
done with Ted Vanderway?
Speaking of romantic,
you're the last girl I'd ever
expect to be on the arm
of a republican.
You're forgetting,
I'm a Pan Am stewardess.
I'm trained in diplomacy.
Yeah, well,
then who are you,
and what have you done
with Maggie Ryan?
In Red Square, you will see
notable armory museum
and tomb of unknown soldier,
honoring brave heroes
who won great patriotic war
for allies.
Olga, uh, do you know where
Ostenazenka street is?
Ostozhenka.
It's the street where
my grandfather grew up.
Your grandfather?
He's from Moscow?
Uh, well, he lived here
until he was 5.
Oh.
Uh...
If we could... if we could
just go down this way,
uh, I might be able to find
his address.
Uh, no. Is not on tour.
It would mean so much to me
and my sister
if we could learn more
about our Soviet heritage.
Mm.
This is Communist Party housing,
provided free, of course,
by glorious decree of presidium.
Let's get in a photo. Go.
Ready?
One, two, three.
I didn't do anything.
I...
Don't touch her.
Hey.
What... what is he saying?
He wants your film.
Okay.
Laura, just give it to him.
But she was only taking
a picture of that building.
He says
it is act of espionage.
Espionage?
That is ridiculous.
They come with us.
No.
- What?
What?
Kate.
Laura.
What's happening?
They are being detained
for questions.
What... what questions?
What did they do wrong?
They were taking photos.
Of a building.
A Soviet building,
housing many of
our illustrious party members.
It is not unthinkable
your CIA would use stewardesses
to gather information.
Where are they being held?
I cannot tell you this.
You... then...
Then I need to go to the U.S. embassy.
You may not leave hotel.
Of course, you are still
welcome to our hospitality.
So what do we do now?
Well, we start by not arguing
with useless bureaucrats.
Just sit tight. They'll be
released soon enough.
And you know that
for a fact how?
I was an army air corps liaison
to the russkies during the war.
Spent a lot of time with 'em,
drank a lot of their vodka,
got to know how they think.
They have a word...
"Zapuguivaniya."
What the hell does
that mean?
Well, it translates loosely...
Into "intimidation."
They can, uh,
keep people on their heels
without ever throwing
a punch.
But they invited us here.
No. Some of 'em did.
Some didn't.
Mistress Olga... she works
for the presidium.
She doesn't speak
for the KGB.
But, look, they made
their point.
It will all blow over.
I'm not taking any chances.
I want you two
to go back up to the room.
You pack up
Bridget and Laura's things.
I'm not gonna risk them
planting anything in their bags.
Well, I think Rawlings
is a shoo-in for '64...
No matter what
"the Village voice" says.
Oh, a bunch
of lefty propaganda.
I'm surprised Khrushchev isn't
on the editorial staff.
Did anyone try the rumaki?
What do you
say we get out of here
and go for a walk
or something?
Um, we just here.
What's gotten into you?
Uh, just stuffy, I guess.
- Well, take off your coat.
- I'm fine.
So don't tell me
that you believe everything
that they print in that rag.
Oh, well...
The reporting in the "voice"
is actually quite nuanced.
"Nuanced"? They said
that Rawlings called goldwater
- a fanatic.
- Since when is having
- an opinion a crime?
- Well, since when did
communist rhetoric start
passing as journalism?
Well, maybe Chris doesn't want
to march in lockstep
with goldwater
and his red-baiting thugs.
- What?
- I hardly think that...
Oh, you hardly think?
Well, maybe that's
your problem
to begin with,
you ignorant buffoon.
Can I, uh, talk to you
for a minute?
It doesn't make any sense.
Why take Laura and Bridget?
It could have
just as easily been you or me.
They were making a point.
Yeah, but to think
one of us is a spy. It's...
I know. It's ridiculous.
Colette?
"D. L."
Dean Lowrey, right?
It could have been here
from a long time ago.
Yet here it is now...
Inside Bridget's suitcase.
No one knows where we are.
We don't even know
where we are.
Laura, we
are going to get out.
Just breathe.
Have you had these types
of attacks before?
The last time was
at my wedding.
How did you get through it?
I ran away.
Well, that's not really
an option here,
but I-I can imagine
it must have been terrible.
Running out on my fiance?
You have no idea.
Oh, I didn't...
I didn't mean
you running out on Dean.
I'm so sorry.
That's fine.
Dean and I will be
all right...
But you wouldn't have said
that two nights ago.
Can we keep this between us?
Dean and I, in London,
we... we had a moment
of weakness.
You and Dean?
What about Colette?
I-it just happened,
you know.
I-I feel awful about it.
We go.
Where are you taking us?
No questions.
What the hell was that
all about?
Well...
You told me I should be
my wonderful, opinionated self.
I said opinionated,
not deranged.
You just called one of
my biggest donors a buffoon.
Actually, it was
an "ignorant buffoon."
It was you.
You were the leak
behind the "Voice" article.
No. I...  I mean...
Yes.
I submitted that article
before we started
whatever it is that
we've started...
But you did say
all those things.
There's a difference
between what I say in public
and pillow talk.
So...
You don't actually have
any convictions of your own?
Oh, I forgot.
Your conviction is
to get elected.
I...
I envy the simple universe
that you live in.
It must be nice having
all the answers.
I didn't realize having
principles made me simple.
Thanks for the education.
I've been waiting
for the right moment,
uh, to give this to you,
but I-I can't wait anymore.
Um...
Amanda Hartford
Mason, will you marry me?
Yes.
- Teddy, yes.
- Okay.
Aw.
Ohh. She said yes!
Hey.
Thank you. Thank you.
Let's see the ring. Ohh!
- All right.
- I'm through waiting.
I'm gonna go out
and deal with this.
Great idea. You two take out
the KGB agent.
I'll steal a tank.
We'll blast our way out.
This isn't a John Wayne movie.
You're 1,000 miles
behind the iron curtain.
You can't just go out there
guns blazin'.
Do you have a better idea?
Look, we do not want to make
this an international incident.
Uh, a-as opposed
to what it is now?
You know, for the first time
since the war,
our relations are thawing.
You think the Soviets want
to screw that up
over a couple of stewardesses?
That is my sister
you are talking about,
and I know
you know people here,
people with connections.
Yeah, I have connections,
but not the kind to get us out
of a situation like this.
Yeah? There's no one
you can bribe?
Couple packs of cigarettes?
Your attention, please!
I must inform you,
trip has been canceled.
You will be escorted to airport
and depart immediately.
No. Hey! I want to talk
to somebody
that actually has
some authority around here.
I am sorry. There is
nothing that can be done.
What about
our stewardesses...
Bridget Pierce
and Laura Cameron?
Do not be concerned
with them.
What the hell does
that mean?
It means they stay. You go.
Maggie?
Are you okay?
Oh.
It's the last time I buy
this cheap mascara.
Hey, what you said
out there...
Oh, it was stupid.
I have a big mouth.
No.
I... wish I could be
more like you.
There's nothing harder
than standing up for yourself.
You were...
Strong and brave
and honest.
Never apologize for that.
Well, then I'll
apologize for not being honest.
This mascara is not cheap.
Men are idiots.
I know.
Sometimes I think
women are just...
Better.
Me, too.
You know who I am?
You cannot be here.
Please. You must go.
I need your help.
You cannot come inside.
KGB is watching always
and listening.
Yes. Let me explain.
I know why you are here.
I have heard about
two Pan Am stewardesses
detained as spies.
And one of them is
my sister.
They told me that your boyfriend
is high up in the Kremlin.
You could go to him.
That's impossible.
What you are saying
is suicide.
I'm sorry,
but I cannot help you.
I don't care if it puts
you or me in danger.
One way or another,
you are going to help me,
and you are going
to do it now.
"Albers, Lawrence".
"Benson, Scott".
"Broyles, George".
"Cameron, Kate."
Right here.
Captain Broyles,
can I talk to you?
"Fineman, Rachel".
"Harmon, Gerald."
I found someone who can help us
get my sister back...
Someone high up
in the Kremlin.
Yeah, sure you did.
His name is Vitaly Berzin.
He is
on the Central Committee...
And this is
his private number.
You're kidding, right?
He is willing to intercede,
but it's going to take cash
and a lot of it,
and I know you have it.
How does a Pan Am stewardess
have connections at the Kremlin?
How does a Pan Am pilot
smuggle thousands of dollars
in black market merchandise
across international borders?
He's
waiting to hear from you.
Who are you?
I'm a concerned sister.
We should all have sisters
like you.
Bus to airport has arrived.
Pazhalsta gather belongings.
You leave in two minutes.
Why are you not starting
engines?
Because I'm not flying
this plane.
Neither is he.
This aircraft lacks
authorization
to stay in Soviet Union.
You will only make
situation worse.
- I don't care about your authorization.
- You will fly.
And you'll get off
of my flight...
That won't be necessary.
You want to make
this situation worse,
then you go ahead.
Shoot me, 'cause I'm not
flying the damn plane.
Where are they taking us?
I'm not... I'm not sure.
There's
a KGB interrogation facility
outside Lubyanka.
Interrogation?
They will question us
separately.
They'll tell you things
I said about you.
Do not believe them.
Okay, I won't.
I won't, but how do you
know all this?
Stay strong.
You, too.
You have friends in high places.
Now you go.
Ohh. Oh!
I guess we'll have
a good story to tell
at Thanksgiving.
All right, ladies,
let's get, uh, wheels up
before they change
their mind, huh?
That was pretty gutsy
what you did.
Well, I didn't know what else
to do. Guess it worked.
Yeah. As the Russians say...
"Kto ni riskuyet
tot ni piyot shampanskava."
Translation?
"He who doesn't risk
never gets
to drink champagne."
Captain...
The left seat is yours.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm happy to inform you
we have just left
Soviet air space.
One minute,
we're in the back of the van,
and the next,
we're at the airport.
How did that happen?
I guess somebody at Pan Am
pulled some strings.
You think it was that easy?
I have no idea.
Well, the worst part is
they took my new camera.
Thank you.
For what?
Well, for being, uh...
For being patient.
Colette, look, there...
There's something
that I need to tell you.
Where did you find this?
You tell me.
Colette, I don't... I don't want
to lie to you ever
about anything.
Then don't.
Say what you need to say.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com