Previously on "Pan Am"...
You smell like whiskey
and cigarettes.
You smell like... Paris.
I don't wanna worry
about you
and I don't wanna
take care of you.
Who's asking you to?
Well, it ain't much,
but it's home. Welcome aboard.
My mind is full of you.
You follow me like a ghost.
Are you in danger?
Tito has put
an entire nation in danger.
- You want him to spy for you?
- For us.
You want me to turn him?
Welcome to the big leagues.
I am a jelly doughnut!
Berlin, right?
"The Village Voice."
You remember.
I hear you have...
Amazing credentials. Ow.
You'll have to excuse her.
She's been drinking
sloe gin fizzes.
There is a lot of alcohol in it,
but they just taste so good.
That's
an enticing combination.
Here. Take mine.
She triples the sugar.
Great song.
Listen,
earlier on the plane...
Joe, this... this is
Maggie's friend Sam.
Sam is, um,
he's into s... philosophy.
Nice to meet you.
"We have all been in
this white doghouse too long."
Excuse me?
Malcolm X.
Right.
You two have fun.
Hello, miss.
I seem to have left my lighter
at your establishment.
I'd like to return it
to you, Mr. Lonza,
but you'll have
to describe it first,
make sure it's yours.
Smooth...
Cool to the touch,
hot flame.
Why, that describes
any old lighter.
Well, then I guess, um...
I'll have to inspect it.
It's definitely yours.
You know, when you called
in the middle of the night
and said,
"come over to my place,"
this isn't exactly
what I expected.
Oh? What did you expect?
Something that involves
a few less people.
Well, as far
as I'm concerned, Michael,
you're the only one
in the room.
Mm!
No.
Four times.
In a row?
Mike Ruskin
of "the Village Voice"?
Has
very impressive credentials.
Colette, truth or dare?
Dare.
Of course.
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm.
Something Colette
would never do.
Mm. Okay, okay.
Oh, got it. Fly the plane.
Don't be ridiculous.
It has to be something
she can actually accomplish.
A girl on the "Clipper Horizon"
made it happen.
Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yes, and six months later...
She was married
to her captain.
Mm. Well, Dean does seem
awfully fond of you.
Oh, I doubt he's that fond.
Fine.
Tie a knot in the stem.
- Hmm.
- No hands.
Ohh.
Ooh.
Now Laura.
Okay. Truth.
I took nude photos.
I was supposed to wait
for the question, wasn't I?
The "Life" magazine
photographer?
No.
Laura, what were you
thinking?
I was thinking that I wanted
to embrace my sexuality
on my terms.
Most girls do that
with a bottle of a red
and a roomy backseat.
Maggie! I didn't do that.
I didn't do that. No, it was...
It was about self-expression...
And he
wasn't the right guy for sex.
He was the right guy
for nude photos.
What,
there's a right guy for that?
Sorry to interrupt, ladies.
I know you girls thought
this flight was a freebie,
but Pan Am's doing a little
favor for Uncle Sam.
Shuttling sailors,
to be precise,
sailors who spent
the last six months underwater,
so let's... let's clean up
the girlie business.
Mm.
Is there... is there something
wrong with your mouth?
Ah.
Oh, impressive.
Mm.
Okay. I think
we're done here, ladies.
- Help me up. Ohh.
- That's not funny.
Welcome to Pan Am.
Please take
a seat in our first class.
Welcome.
Welcome aboard, sir.
Joe. Name's Joe.
Welcome to Pan Am.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Here you go. Stay dry.
Thanks. Best debriefing
of the month.
Ciao.
You're leaving?
Well...  Sharing a room
only works most of the time.
Right.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Have a good night.
Joe.
I... thought you left already.
I hit the head.
Listen, you better keep
this joint a secret,
or every bluejacket
and boatswain in the Navy
is gonna show up
in your living room.
I'm glad you had fun.
Well, um...
Good-bye.
I thought I was staying
the night.
Maggie I told me I could
have the couch...
But if that's a problem...
N-no. No problem at all.
Ohh.
Hello.
Richard,
he's leaving Thursday.
Kate?
They're recalling him back
to Yugoslavia... for good.
You have to do something.
Hello?
Hello, Richard?
You're with Lonza now?
He's in my apartment.
I told him
I was going out for champagne.
You'd better get back.
Sit tight.
We'll figure something out.
Mind if I leave this open?
I kinda miss
the taste of fresh air.
Of course not.
Uh, it might get chilly.
Here's hopin'.
No such thing as chilly
on a submarine.
At least let me get you
another blanket. This... this...
Oh, no. This will do fine.
If I start freezing to death,
I'll come find you.
For... another blanket.
Right. Yes. Please do.
If you're freezing to death.
Laura, thank you
for letting me stay.
I'm grateful.
Good night.
Your drink.
I can't believe you made it
back here in one piece.
Everything all right?
How do you mean?
You've got a pretty healthy grip
on that armrest.
Flying makes me
a little queasy.
I'm not sure
rum is the remedy for that.
I'm in the Navy, ma'am.
Rum is the remedy to everything.
You don't have
to call me "ma'am."
I'm... my name is Laura.
Can't you just close your eyes
and pretend this is a submarine?
That's what I do
when I get nervous.
You pretend you're
in a submarine?
I pretend
I'm somewhere else,
somewhere I feel safe.
Can I ask you somethin'...
Private?
Sure.
Say you and I were close,
and I did somethin'
to make you mad at me,
and we didn't talk
for a long time.
You think maybe this
would make it go easier
when I saw you again?
It's beautiful.
Yeah, but is it enough?
In this scenario,
am I your girlfriend?
Uh, no, sorry.
You're my mama.
I'm your mama?
See, we've always been close...
Real close,
but when I decided to join
the Navy, she didn't understand,
took it personal, thought
my leavin' was somehow sayin',
Redwater, Mississippi,
wasn't good enough,
that she wasn't good enough,
only that wasn't it.
You just wanted to see
the world.
Yeah. Seemed like
too big a place
not to go wanderin' in it,
but she ain't spoke to me since.
I send her postcards,
but... nothin'.
I think the hummingbird
is beautiful,
but I'll bet
what she really wants
is to know
that wherever you go,
you still need her,
just like before.
You don't know my mama.
Oh, I think I do.
- That so?
- I'm pretty sure
my mother could give your mama
a run for her money.
Uh, my mama
don't run nowhere.
She just commands
from right where she is.
My mother ambushed me...
Ooh.
- Uh...
- Mm.
Can I help you?
I got a little
top secret business to discuss.
Here? Now?
Yeah, we don't have much time.
We got a friend over there
who is about to
surrender himself to the enemy.
A defector?
Uh, in a manner
of speaking.
Listen, this is
our last chance to give him
the send-off he deserves,
and, uh...
Boy-o,
does he love the redheads.
Wait. What?
Yeah, I ain't askin'
for the full gypsy Rose Lee.
Just, you know, toss the hat,
drop the jacket,
do a little shimmy.
Uh, you... come on.
I got a sailor over there
who's getting married.
He needs a stag party.
You want a stripper so badly,
you can do it yourself.
And we're out there
every day protecting you
from the dirty communists,
and we...
You're not a dirty communist
lover, are ya?
Snow.
Well, definitely snow. What's...
What's Christmas without snow?
And a Douglas fir.
Or, um, how do you
call it... spruce?
Very well, a spruce,
but with colored lights.
Or maybe only white.
Hey, I'm giving in
on the spruce.
Yeah, 6 or 7 feet tall,
which I will cut down myself.
From the forest
behind the house?
Mm-hmm.
Are you expecting someone?
At 1:00 in the morning?
Ohh. It could be
the neighbors.
The wife
kicks him out a lot.
Kate, get on
your fire escape.
What? We don't even know
who it is.
Exactly.
Niko, it's raining outside.
Okay,
before I get drenched,
can I at least check
the peephole?
Mrs. Luckovich?
I saw your light on,
or I wouldn't bother you.
Is something wrong?
Do you have a hot water bottle
I can borrow?
My arthritis is acting up.
Of course. Come in.
It's my nosy neighbor.
Do you still want me
out the window?
There's
a first time for everything.
- It's all right.
- No.
We're here to pick up your package.
Is he armed?
No, you don't need to.
You don't need to.
Kate!
Hello, Mr. Lonza.
Kate, do you know these men?
No.
Not exactly.
I think it's time
you made some new friends.
I have all the friends
I need.
You never know.
Let's take a ride,
get acquainted.
I don't like to go out in rain.
Well, you're gonna have
to get over that.
- Hey. Hey!
- Wait.
No! No, wait!
Let me...
- Aah!
- No!
No, wait!
Trust me.
We're your only way out.
Get off me!
Niko, please. Go with them.
They want to help.
Who are you?
Who are you?!
No!
Morning.
You cleaned up.
And you put a roof
over my head.
Hangover?
Got just the thing.
You like eggs?
Hot sauce?
Orange juice? Molasses?
Sounds delicious.
I call it
the Redwater special.
After your hometown.
No, 'cause it looks like
red water.
Straight from the mighty banks
of the Mississippi
to cure what ails you.
Down the hatch?
I should get that.
Where's Maggie Ryan?
Depends.
Can I help you?
I'm the super. You responsible
for last night's little shindig?
That also depends.
On what?
On how mad you are
about it.
You living here?
No. Yes. No.
Well, temporarily.
Uh, at least
it was temporary,
but it's actually been
working out very well, so...
And who is he?
Joe? Um, he's a guest.
Your guest?
Sort of.
Kick him out.
- Excuse me?
- You're not on the lease,
and I don't like
your guest.
Kick him out,
or I kick you out,
and no more parties.
You understand?
I'll ask him to leave.
You're not gonna drink that,
are you?
I'm not that hungry.
What time is your train?
Not until 6:00.
What do you say
we go buy your ticket
and then wander the city
a little?
Oh, you don't need to do
that for me.
Listen, I know you were trying
to avoid me last night...
Avoid? No.
And I deserve it
for what I did on the plane.
I was a little drunk,
and I forgot,
for a moment,
how things are.
Joe, I would...
I would really like
to spend the day with you.
I'd like that, too.
Coffee, please.
I've been here 45 minutes.
I've had a busy morning.
I can't always drop everything
when you call.
Well, you managed
to rustle a lynch mob
last night when I called.
He's safe. You did your job.
What's the emergency?
Why didn't you tell me
that you were pulling him
out of my apartment?
Have you forgotten the concept
of "need to know"?
I could have talked him
into a meeting.
Turning a diplomat is
a delicate procedure.
Yes, you were real delicate
last night.
The last thing I need is
your personal attachment
complicating matters.
My personal attachment?
The only shot you have at this
is my personal attachment.
No. We have more than that.
What?
Don't you have
an around-the-world flight
coming up?
Go. Enjoy yourself.
Richard, I want to see him.
- You've done your part.
- Forget about Niko Lonza.
We've got it from here.
- Richard, no. No, no.
- Take me with you.
I need to explain my side
of things.
- No, you don't.
- Please. I can help.
Richard, I need to talk
to him!
"Under the yum yum tree."
No.
You don't even know
what it's about.
I know what it's called.
Well, are you sure you want
to see a movie?
Uh, we could go to central park,
the statue of liberty.
My mama would call you happy
as a dead pig in the sun.
- That's not very nice.
- It means you don't know any better
than to smile.
It's a good thing.
I tell you what.
Why don't you wait here?
I'll go grab my ticket,
and then we'll see
the tasty tree movie.
"Yum yum."
Don't remind me.
You're beautiful,
you know that?
Thank you.
$19, sir.
What do you say
I buy you lunch?
Um, I'm fine. Thank you.
Oh, come on.
I'm a nice guy.
Laura, let's go.
Now what makes you think you can
order a lady around like that?
Oh, h-he wasn't ordering me.
It's okay, Laura.
No, it's not okay. This...
This is not okay at all.
Come on.
Joe. Joe!
Joe! Joe!
Yes, Crown Heights. I got it.
Richard, is he all right?
- Oh, thank goodness you're home.
- Oh, my God.
I-I... we...
we were a few blocks away,
and I didn't know where else to go.
- What happened?
- For the record,
a couple of them look
worse than me.
Them? You got in a fight
with multiple people?
It's all my fault.
Stop that. It's only mostly
your fault.
Kate.
I don't have any bandages
or tincture of iodine.
Can you run to the drugstore?
- No.
- Laura, I have to go.
Go where?
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- I'll explain later.
Ohh!
Unh. Right there.
Unh. Lookin' at you.
Where is he?
Ohh.
Oh, yeah, baby.
What the hell is going on
out there?
I don't even want to know.
Oh, it is nothing.
Kate's taking off her clothes
to entertain the men.
And why would she do that?
Feeling patriotic, I guess.
What does a guy gotta do
to get a decent cup
of coffee around here?
- Oh, but it's just...
- Oh, don't bother, Colette.
- I'll get my own.
- Okay.
I like coffee, too.
Mm.
Sure. Yeah.
Run along, boys.
I'll stay, fly the plane.
Oh, no need to be jealous.
I said Kate was taking
her clothes off,
but I didn't say
who was putting them on.
- Ohh.  Sailors.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh, if you want a quick look,
I'd be happy to take over.
No, thank you. I'm...
I'm happy right where I am.
Too bad. It's always been
a dream of mine to fly.
Excuse me,
first officer Valois,
could you please take
your seat?
Mm.
You know, there's actually
some gray area here.
Uh, the... the singing guardians
of democracy back there
are not technically
paying passengers...
And they're sworn to protect
your right to the pursuit
of happiness.
Oh, this would make me
very happy.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Uh, both hands on the yoke.
The yoke?
Yeah, the steering wheel.
Roger that, captain.
Mm.
I'm flying?
And a dream comes true.
I'm flying.
Guys, guys. Hey.
Oh.
Ensign will finely is gonna
get himself married.
To Will!
My mama always says,
you carry your first impression
of a person
for the rest of your days.
It becomes a part of you,
like...
A photograph in your pocket...
Which is why I deeply regret,
the first time I met
Will Finely, he had dysentery.
Aw, Will!
Now that's
a hell of a photograph
to be stuck with forever.
To Will.
You're missing
a pretty good speech.
Uh, you could use
a lecture.
Oh, you're a lifesaver.
I am starving.
What?
Nude photographs?
I don't plan on showing anyone.
Doesn't matter. They exist.
Do you have the negatives?
I thought you, of all people,
would understand.
Have you not read
the Pan Am code of ethics?
And every practical reason
aside,
you're not the kind of girl
who does that.
Well, I must be,
because I did,
and I'm not going
to apologize for it.
And quite frankly,
that sounds like something
mother would say.
Nude photos it is.
What's going on, Kate?
For a while you seemed
so happy,
but lately you're...
On edge.
Boy trouble.
Since when have you had
a boy?
Since Monte Carlo.
No. No.
The one you stole from Maggie?
Please.
Maggie never stood
a chance.
Wh-what's he like?
He's sweet
and funny, kind and...
He's noble.
Oh, my God.
You're in love.
I'm in over my head
is what I am.
My boyfriend's
a Yugoslavian communist.
He's a communist?
Now who sounds like mother?
You're right.
Who cares?
The free world.
But you're in love.
Nothing else matters.
Hey, don't let that go.
It's complicated.
No, it's simple.
It's a dime, a phone booth,
and a handful of words.
Call him
as soon as we touch down,
and tell him that
love trumps everything.
I-I can't.
No arguing.
Laura.
Kate, no arguing.
Apparently
your personal attachment
is stronger
than we thought.
He won't talk any more
until he sees you.
You have him here?
We use an insurance office
as a front.
It actually turns a profit.
Be careful.
It's not going well.
What a surprise.
He's through here.
I don't suppose you could
offer me any privacy?
I can offer you this...
He's angry, you're angry,
but what he wants
for his country
and what we want from him
do, indeed, run parallel.
You need to make him
believe that.
Kate.
I've misled you.
I've withheld from you,
but I haven't lied to you.
Is Kate your real name?
Yes.
Is anything else
about you real?
I started as a courier.
This is beyond anything
that I ever thought
that I would be doing
for them.
Oh, clearly they can
spot talent.
You had me convinced.
Niko, you and I...
That part was real.
Niko, are you in danger?
Tito has put
an entire nation in danger.
"Chief architect
of the second Yugoslavia,"
and yet his dreams are not
for his people.
I was going
to try to help my cousin.
This might be the last time
I'll ever see him again.
Niko?
My mind is full
of you, too.
Very convincing.
I meant it.
But it wasn't just
between us.
I didn't know.
Did you record everything?
Congratulations.
You are now a professional.
Don't be cruel.
My new friends here... they have
a terrific proposition.
I return back to Yugoslavia
as a double agent
or explain this tape,
made in the bed
of an American agent,
to our secret police.
But I thought...
I thought when they told me
that they wanted you to help us
that that meant that
you would stay in New York...
At your current job.
Doing what?!
Passing information,
but here,
where you could be
protected!
No, sweetheart, it means
being sent back to spy
on a government that... that is
already suspicious of me.
I'm so sorry.
I thought I was helping.
This is helping?
I thought you meant the things
that you said on that tape,
that you wished your country had
the same freedoms as America.
Well, it's still my country!
And it needs to change.
You believe that!
If you could work...
If you could work with us...
This is not "working with."
This is a death sentence.
Niko.
Niko, please.
Hear them out.
I do not like
what they've done,
but I believe that
you want the same...
things.
I-I honestly can't tell.
Are you... are you just
a silly, naive girl or...
Or... or a master liar?
Both.
I'm both...
But I am also yours.
This is getting out of hand.
It's like feeding time
at the zoo.
Can you imagine being trapped
underwater with them
for six months?
I'd load myself into
a torpedo tube and launch.
That bad?
My kingdom for a sedative.
How snockered are they?
What are you thinking?
Nifty little pilot trick.
I'm gonna decrease
the cabin pressure
by manually raising
the cabin altitude.
I love Greek.
Beautiful language.
It makes boozy passengers
fall asleep.
You're kidding.
Oh.
No. That's why test pilots
don't drink on game day.
Pilots and their secrets.
Well, what are you
waiting for?
Joe, we're asking everybody
to return to their seats.
Is it okay
if I stay back here?
Sure, as long
as you buckle up.
Still unsettled?
You could say that.
- I liked your toast.
- Where's the wedding?
Alabama.
Oh, that's convenient.
Right on the way home.
Yes, it is.
Is it a church wedding?
It's a... country club.
Well, that will be nice.
Exclusive country club.
Oh.
But thanks to you,
I've got a secret weapon.
Gonna close my eyes and pretend
my ass right into the front row.
Upset all those old ladies.
Get those fans going.
I, um...
I should probably take
the bottle
before Maggie catches you.
It's against the rules.
I need to, uh, prepare
for landing.
Does it hurt?
You want the truth
or the tough guy answer?
I am so sorry.
Hey. It was hardly
a tussle.
I knew hittin' the town
with you would draw some eyes.
That's on me.
I'm sorry because...
Because it isn't right.
It isn't right that...
When you tried to kiss me,
I cared what other people
would think.
It isn't right that
when I went to bed last night,
I locked my door.
It isn't right that
when the super told me
to kick you out, I did it.
You took my hand
in front of those men
at the train station...
And you brought me back here
to take care of me.
That counts for something.
That mean old man really
told you to kick me out?
Don't worry. I plan
on flooding the bathtub.
Isn't it
Maggie's apartment?
Where I work, we call that
a command decision.
Why are you being nice
to me?
Same reason I tried
to kiss you.
Same reason
I told Maggie I had
nowhere else
to stay last night.
That was a lie?
That was a desperate attempt
to keep your company
a little longer.
Why?
You ever been
on a submarine?
There's a lot of gray.
Gray pumps,
gray engines,
gray gauges,
gray steel...
A big gray ocean tryin'
to crush you like a tin can...
So you can imagine
what it's like to come up
from all that gray
and see...
You.
Laura, what are you doing?
Making
another command decision.
Is something funny?
You're the guy...
And the next time I have
to close my eyes to feel safe...
I'm gonna pretend
I'm right here.
I remember my first trip
around the world.
I took a little spoonful
of dirt
from every place we landed
as a souvenir.
You must be excited.
Beyond.
Oh, I have bills to mail.
I'll be right down.
Okay, make it snappy.
It's time to board.
Kate. Where on Earth
have you been?
I know. I haven't
returned your calls.
Is everything all right?
The way you ran out
on Joe and I...
Kate Cameron? Phone call.
I need to mail these...
Kate speaking.
Kate?
Kate, what is it?
Excuse me. Are you lost?
I, uh, seem
to have found my way.
Which flight is yours?
Pan Am 2.
Around the world.
I'd like to do that.
Mine is leaving in, um,
two hours.
Flight 22.
London.
And then on to Yugoslavia.
I was supposed to be leaving,
uh, two days ago,
but then I got delayed.
Job interview.
I thought you weren't
interested in a new job.
I didn't care
for the interview.
But then we, uh...
resolved our differences.
There are people...
who need me in Yugoslavia,
and it's time.
So this is your choice.
Things rarely happen
the way we expect.
I'm beginning
to understand that.
So you'll... let me know
when you book a return?
It's likely to be
a long trip.
Well, the only thing left
to do is, um,
to say good-bye
to my American girlfriend.
She'll be devastated.
At first. Maybe.
But then she'll understand
that I'm doing what I must...
That I'm, uh,
I'm "Walking like a man."
I hope she'll be proud
of me.
She already is.
Laura?
Um, you go.
Good-bye, Kate.
Your layover in London...
There's... a great pub
in cadogan square.
Oh, it's a... it's a good spot
for billiards.
I'll...
I'll try to remember that.
Hey, Kate.
Me, too.
No plants, no animals, no men.
If I'm gonna be circling
the globe for three weeks,
the last thing I need to worry
about is home maintenance.
Who wants economy
with me on the first leg?
Somebody's got to do it.
I'll do it.
Just smile through it,
dear.
Oh. Here they come.
Are you ready, Kate?
Mm-hmm.
Welcome to Pan Am.
- Good morning.