There you are.
Enjoy your flight.
"Jet clipper service is unique.
"Upon boarding
an around-the-world flight,
"passengers are greeted
"by the international beauty
and grace
known
as the Pan Am stewardess."
"All college-educated,
girls can fly until they are
married or turn 32."
Hands.
Excuse me.
Can you help me?
That's quite a picture.
Thank you. Uh, I have a bit
of a problem, miss...
Over a million copies sold,
and your hat is askew.
Oh, I didn't pose for it.
I was only leaving the building.
Are you wearing your girdle?
Yes, ma'am.
- Oh.  Uh...
- Is that...
Is that necessary?
A girdle doesn't stand up
and announce itself.
There's a rip
in your stocking.
Yes. I know.
Can you help me?
My flight leaves
in less than an hour.
How long
have you been flying?
Three weeks and two days.
I have an extra pair.
We're on the same crew.
Follow me, beaute.
Not too dark, miss Valois.
This isn't a cabaret.
Yes, miss Havemeyer.
Next.
She likes the girdle.
So... congratulations.
When did they pick you
for it?
Just last week.
I was on the San Juan leg.
No, no. Not the flight.
The magazine.
How did it happen?
I'm not sure exactly.
Um...
Ah, pas mal.
Saviez-vous etudier a Paris?
A l'universite de Baltimore.
Make way
for the face of Pan Am.
No, don't.
Don't say that.
- Nylon emergency.
- Don't say that. I'm not.
Don't apologize. You're on
the cover of "life" magazine.
Yes,
with a face like that,
you'll find a husband
in a couple of months.
Oh, I'm... I'm not looking
for a husband.
I hope not.
You're famous now.
No, trust her.
She's not.
Looking for a husband, that is.
Kate, I-I tried
to telephone last night.
A man just took a picture.
I-I didn't ask for it.
Of course you didn't.
I need gum.
Does anyone want anything?
Oh, hi, Kate.
Can you chew gum
in uniform?
Clipper 22 cabin crew.
Oui?
Have any of you ladies s
your purser... Bridget Pierce?
The departure gate
for Pan Am flight 3-1-0
has been changed.
The new departure gate is...
And the magazine?
Oh, no. I'm just looking.
Are you sure? We'll sell out
in a couple hours.
I'll take one.
Here.  Take mine.
Uh, a pack of Wilmingtons
and the young lady's
chewing gum.
68 cents.
Keep the change.
Thank you.
Pretty girl.
Very.
Are you ready
for your first assignment?
Now?
Seat 3D.
We need to detain him
at customs in Heathrow.
Replace the British visa
in his passport
with this expired one.
Without him knowing?
I'll take that
as rhetorical.
- You forgot your gum.
- Oh.
Sure. Let me get it.
Oh. Does the marxist dialectic
account for a dual thesis?
That's Hegel, not Marx.
Hello.
Maggie? This is Bill
from Pan Am scheduling.
Can you volunteer for
a special flight last-minute?
I think you're working off
the wrong list.
We're missing
our lead stewardess
on our New York to London.
Can you come and be
our purser?
Today?
8:30 departure.
Margaret,
this is Paul Gilbert.
Pan Am is launching a new clipper jet...
And I cannot let it fly
without a purser.
Did you know I was grounded,
Paul Gilbert?
Uniform violation.
Not if you can get here
in 35 minutes.
I wish I could.
I'm in the city.
Get your Fanny to midtown.
I'll have a helicopter waiting
for you at headquarters,
and, sweetheart,
wear the girdle.
Helicopter?
An extraordinary gesture
on my part
to get your purser here
on time.
What,
Bridget's not here yet?
Not your problem.
"Clipper Majestic"
departs on schedule.
Write her first chapter,
captain.
Yeah.
Your attention, please.
This is the last boarding call
for flight 2701...
John?
To Sao Paulo, Brazil.
Hey, John!
Hey, was that your...
The one from Rome?
Oui.
Well, he's about to be
the one from London, huh?
Did you know
he was on this flight?
I love surprises.
Just smile through it,
dear.
Listen,
you can crash here,
but lock the door
when you leave.
Maggie.
You dropped
your silly blue hat.
Look, I get
to see the world, Sam.
When was the last time
you left the village?
I don't need to see
the world to change it.
Well, I do.
Taxi! Taxi! Taxi!
I'm going to 200 Park Avenue,
the Pan Am building.
Wow. It's beautiful.
Brand-new.
Never been flown.
What do you think, ladies?
Can we make this work?
Are you our pilot?
One of 'em.
No, he's our co-pilot.
Well, uh, first officer.
First officer.
Are you okay, miss?
Eyes forward.
Fuel quantity checked.
Flight controls
free and correct.
Are we ready, boys?
Hey. Are you nervous?
'Cause I could take that seat,
if you're nervous.
Thanks, Ted,
but Pan Am wants actual pilots
in the left seat.
Ha ha.
Welcome aboard, Mr. Sabel.
Right this way.
3d is the aisle.
May I take your coat?
I wear coat when it's cold.
Your briefcase?
Gin with bitters, please.
Colette.
Bonjour.
Welcome aboard, monsieur.
May I take your coat?
John, please slow down.
Tommy slipped.
Oh. Are you all right, buddy?
Uh, Evelyn, coat?
If you don't mind, I'd love to
get our son settled in first.
Certainly. Yeah.
Clipper 22, tower.
Your special delivery
just landed. Over.
Roger that, tower.
That's our girl.
The captain will give
you a report on our flight plan
just as soon
as his duties permits.
We're happy to have you
with us this morning.
Well, thanks, Kate.
Hey.
Maggie, you're our purser?
Best they could manage
on short notice.
Can we roll out, gentlemen?
I'm getting tired of waiting.
Maggie?
Dean?
You're a captain now?
Did you just fly in
on a helicopter?
Oh, well, I like to make
an entrance.
Uh, where's...
Where's Bridget?
I don't know. They just
called me to fill in.
Yeah? Who's filling in
the rest of her?
He won't be doing
any actual flying, will he?
Well, welcome aboard,
Maggie.
Thanks.
So...
Who else do we have?
A new hire. She's in back.
"Laura... Cameron"?
My sister.
I can't seem to escape her.
They put you two
on the same flight?
Mm.
Well, isn't that something?
Clipper 22, idlewild tower.
Cleared for takeoff,
runway 3-1-left.
3-1-left.
Clipper 2-2 on the roll.
So how new are you, Laura?
Is it that obvious?
Better buckle up.
Adventure calls.
Oh.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Go ahead.
Say it.
Welcome,
ladies and gentlemen.
This is
your... captain speaking.
Today you get to share
a bit of history
with us here at Pan American.
This is the maiden voyage
of the newest clipper jet
in the Pan Am fleet.
If you've never flown
on a jet to Europe before,
you're in for a real treat.
Our flight will only take
six and a half hours...
Oh, thank you.
With no vibrations
or outside noise
in our air-conditioned cabin.
We're traveling at a speed
of 575 miles an hour.
In addition, we'll benefit
from a substantial tailwind,
courtesy of the jet stream...
Mm.
So our ground speed could reach
over 650 miles per hour.
Thirsty?
An American man would say
something, no?
Depends on the subject.
The family in row 5 and 6.
He's married.
Oh. Well, did you ask?
Oh, no. I don't care.
I was only surprised.
Oh. Well, good. Okay.
That's very French of you.
Should we spike his food
or his drink?
Both.
Relax, and enjoy your
clipper jet service to Europe.
What?
I don't think
I can call you "captain."
You gonna be able to
call him "captain," Sanjeev?
35,000 feet, captain.
I don't think I can do it.
Maybe I'll start in Spanish,
work my way up to it.
Boston center,
clipper 2-2 with you.
Flight level 3-5-0
heading 0-1-niner degrees.
Roger, clipper 22.
Hey, Boston, uh, could you
contact Pan Am operations,
see if they could secure
a location on a Bridget Pierce?
Come again, clipper 22.
Check on our missing stewardess,
will ya?
Whoa. Bailing out already?
Permission to christen
the John, el capitan?
No. Still sounds weird.
Maybe in Italian.
Well, Bridget must have
called somebody.
She'll turn up.
She always does.
Hey, Maggie.
Heard you got grounded.
Somebody caught you
out of your girdle?
It won't be the last time.
Let me know
if you need help
with that
uniform inspection, hmm?
Oh, thanks,
but I think I'll leave that
to more experienced hands.
Ohh.
Mm.
E-excuse me.
Pardon me.
Oh. Oh.
Oh.
Lunch menu?
- Oh, would you take our picture for us?
- Yes, thank you.
Oh. I've never seen one
like that.
Yeah, it takes a special film.
The photos develop right inside.
It was a wedding present
from my parents.
Yeah. It's all set up.
Just, uh, press the top there.
Are you on your honeymoon?
Oh, finally.
I knew in the seventh grade.
It just took him
ten years to ask.
Excuse me, miss.
Is this you?
Uh... no.
We are so excited
to be going to London.
We were gonna go to Paris,
but my friend sue Ellen
just went to Paris,
and we didn't want to come home
with all the same stories, so...
Ohh! Lovely. Absolutely lovely.
Greg is a very lucky man.
Your father saw him eyeing
this house on Asher
near the elementary school.
We should really try
the other necklace again.
Perhaps just
a bit more Rouge.
Kate, does it fit?
We considered
basting the hem, but...
Don't concern yourself,
sweetheart.
If your sister cared how
her dress looked,
she would have flown in
for the fitting.
Oh, I'm sure you guessed
perfectly, mother.
Well, I had to, didn't I?
You're still not changed?
I had to mend the veil.
What? What did you do to it?
I didn't do anything to it.
It just tore a little bit.
Kate, stop.
Just stop. Get dressed.
I'll tell Greg we need
a few more minutes.
Whew.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
It's just nerves, I guess.
I can't seem to stop shaking.
Well, you look beautiful,
so just enjoy it.
Can I get you anything?
Could you get me some water?
Yeah. Of course.
I'll be right back.
Congratulations.
I traveled
for 36 hours straight,
but I got here.
And still you couldn't
manage the time
to change out
of that costume.
I am proud of my uniform.
Do you know
what we get to do?
You made it clear you don't care
what I think of what you do.
Go ahead. Gallivant around
the world if you like,
but don't use
your sister's special day...
Oh, this isn't Laura's
special day. This is yours,
because Laura hasn't made
a decision for herself
her whole life.
Laura? Laura, what happened?
Did you faint?
- I can't...
Has she eaten this morning?
I can't...
Shh. It's nerves.
Just smile through it, dear.
Mother.
I can't...
Shh. I'll get a sedative.
I don't think that's...
I can't go through it.
Kate, not now.
I-I don't want...
I don't want to get... do you
want me to open the window?
- I don't... I don't want to do this.
- Okay, sweetheart,
- just breathe. -  I don't want to do this.
I don't want to do this.
Just breathe.
You're all right.
I don't want to do this.
Okay, do what? Marry Greg?
It's too... it's too late.
No, no, no.
No, it's not too late.
I don't want to do...
I don't want to do any of it,
but everyone's already here.
Then we'll leave. They can all
have a party without us.
But... mother...
Laura, listen to me.
You need to decide
right now,
because this is your life.
What do you want to do
with it?
Does daddy still keep
his keys in the visor?
Oh!
I can't believe we're doing this.
Laura.
Oh!
- Oh, you look beautiful. Congratulations.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- I-I-I have to go.
- Laura!
I have to go!
Where are we going?
I have a week. I'll take you
anywhere you want to go,
anything you want to see.
I want to see the world.
I love that plan.
Yeah, you can show it to me.
I'll become a Pan Am stewardess.
Girls, what do you think
you're doing?
Go. Go, go, go!
Where are you going?
- Get back in the house!
- We are lining up!
Aah!
No! The prelude is starting!
Ladies and gentlemen,
for those of you on
the left side of the airplane,
as promised,
you can see the Southern coast
of Greenland.
Colette.
I'm sorry.
Uh, I didn't know
you would be on this flight.
What a coincidence.
I didn't know
you were married.
I thought you understood.
Understood what?
I'm your mistress?
No...
Colette.
I just need a little time.
I-I didn't plan for this.
What was your plan,
Mr. Stanton?
Believe me, when we met,
I didn't expect...
Now, daddy?
It's a long flight, buddy.
Um, he wants to see
the cockpit.
Well, we can do that
right now, okay?
Come on.
A long flight?
Bridget!
It's a motorbike now?
I talked the salesman
into letting me take her out
for the day.
With your stellar Italian?
That and the americano dollar.
Who's that?
Lost tourist
in need of direction.
Good.
I need directions
to Tivoli.
Oh, I-I can't.
I-I promised Kate
I'd meet her for lunch.
So tell her
you got rerouted.
Well, can you wait?
Not my specialty.
I'll, uh, save room
for dessert.
Come and find me.
See you soon.
Taxi!
Guardi dove va!
No. Community service.
The 4-H club.
My sister was
the beauty queen.
Well, then somebody got
something backwards.
You'd really have to see her.
Oh, I don't need to.
You found the place?
Oh, yes. They had
a table waiting for us.
And your friend?
Oh, um, this is...
I'm sorry.
I didn't catch your name.
Richard. Richard Parks.
Bridget Pierce.
She came to my rescue.
My translation book
was failing me.
A yank?
He's, uh, hopelessly lost,
I'm afraid.
Sit down.
- I can't. I'm sorry.
- Oh.
I just didn't want you
to be waiting.
They need a purser
on the evening flight to Berlin.
Ma rimani. Lui e carino.
Uh... Forse un pochino.
- Ci vediamo a New York.
- Okay.
- Ciao.
- Ciao, Bridget.
I take it
that wasn't your sister.
Oh. No, no. We fly together.
I'm a Pan Am stewardess.
Oh, well, that's
my favorite kind of stewardess.
So what do you do
for a living, Mr. Parks?
I work
for the U.S. government.
Intelligence.
Hard to believe?
No trench coat?
Mm. I didn't say
I was any good at it.
You, on the other hand,
fit the profile perfectly...
Beautiful, well-educated,
trilingual.
And I have
the perfect cover.
Exactly.
A Pan Am stewardess can
travel all around the world
without suspicion.
Wait. How did you know
I was trilingual?
No, thank you.
Can I get you
anything else?
Uh, yes. Some peace.
Maggie.
Sir, would you like
some caviar?
From where?
Flown in daily
from the Caspian Sea.
Perhaps later.
Wait. Wait!
That is
my "life" magazine.
No, I believe yours is
in your briefcase.
Can I steal a cup?
Help yourself.
Hi. I'm Ted.
The first officer.
That's right.
What's your name?
Laura.
Is this, uh, your first,
uh, intercontinental?
- Oh, no.
- It is.
Nope. Not this one.
I'm just being hospitable.
Consider her
restricted airspace.
I'm just helping you girls out,
pouring myself some coffee.
You know, for a co-pilot,
you spend a lot of time
out of the cockpit.
Great.
If you need anything,
Laura, you let me know.
I almost called home
last night.
Did you finally tell
mom and dad
- that you followed me into the uniform?
- I wrote a letter.
You better hope it gets
there before "Life" magazine.
Miss?
Um, excuse me.
Can you help me?
Have you seen my glasses?
I think I left them in my coat.
Yes, I'll take a look.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're hitting a patch
of rough air,
so for your safety,
I'm gonna ask you to please
return to your seat.
I've got it. I've got it.
I'm sorry. I couldn't...
I thought you trained
for this.
Kate, I just started.
This is hard for me.
Hard for you, Laura?
Nothing is hard for you.
You're perfect.
Is that what you think?
Just get out of my way.
I do not need a lost puppy.
That's good, baby.
Excuse me, miss?
Yes?
I'm sorry.
I didn't catch your name.
Colette.
Colette. Thank you so much for
taking Tommy up to the cockpit.
Oh, it was our pleasure.
He's a very sweet boy.
Could you sit for a moment?
Is that allowed,
visiting with the passengers?
Yes.
I can't imagine what it's like
to be on your feet for so long.
You get accustomed to it.
I wanted to ask you where
you get your eyelashes.
They look so natural.
No. No, they are natural.
They're mine.
Darn.
I was hoping they were Parisian,
and I could pick up a pair.
You're blessed.
I'm jealous.
What are you drawing, Tommy?
Oh, last month
it was space rockets.
This month it's airplanes.
Lovely. You're an artist.
Miss, could I have
another Martini, please?
John, don't drive her off.
No, not at all.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Clipper 22, Gander Oceanic.
Gander Oceanic, clipper 2-2.
Go ahead.
Pan Am operations asked us
to relay a response.
Your missing stewardess resigned
from the London office.
They don't mean Bridget,
do they?
Do you copy, clipper 22?
Uh, Roger, Gander Oceanic.
Clipper 2-2.
Thanks for passing
that along. Over.
Bridget loves Pan Am.
She wouldn't quit.
Never trust a radio.
They once lost track of me
for three weeks in Brazil.
Unless...
What?
She'd have to quit
if she got married.
Uh, who? What, Bridget?
Oh, Dean. The whole company
knows about you two.
I didn't know.
Everybody but Sanjeev
knows about you two.
Did you get engaged?
Ahh! You son of a bitch!
Congratulations.
If you're engaged,
why is she in London?
Oh, who knows where
that woman ever is?
She barely made it
on the plane in Cuba.
She was in Cuba?
We all were.
Flew out the last DC-6
full of released
Bay of Pigs prisoners
for Uncle Sam.
Plane with a mutiny?
Ah, it wasn't a mutiny.
¿Esta bien?
Rapido, rapido.
- Is this the last of 'em?
- You're asking me?
I thought Pan Am was just
flying out some freed prisoners.
You didn't say we'd have
to leave the plane.
Let's get off the ground before
someone changes their mind.
Por favor, sigan moviendose.
- Hey, get on!
- We're wheels up in ten!
At least they don't have
any luggage, huh?
Where's the state department?
I thought they were supposed
to be organizing this.
Organized the Bays of Pigs.
I'd rather they just pay Castro
his ransom. Come on!
We did try to invade
his country.
- His country?
- Whose country is it?
Castro's never gonna be able
to hold on to it. Come on!
Vamonos, Maggie.
Let's get outta here.
Where's Bridget?
Number four fuel boost
pump off.
Check. Pump off.
All engines stabilized
at 1,000 R.P.M.
Let's get the hell
outta here.
Cabin secured?
We don't have Bridget.
Well, where is she?
She's not on the plane.
I didn't see her outside.
Captain, you're gonna
have to kill the engines.
No, no, no.
I have a mission
and a plane full of people
I'm responsible for.
You can't leave
without your crew.
We finally have clearance now.
We're leaving.
Yeah, not without her,
you're not.
I'm not gonna get stuck in Cuba.
Dean!
I swear to God,
I will take off without you!
Hey! Move! Move!
Maggie, tell these people
we're taking off in one minute.
We're getting outta here, and do
not let him close this door!
No pasa nada.
No, no, no, no, no.
Go, go, go, go.
What are you doing out here?
Looking for you.
We forgot one.
We almost forgot you!
You're always
disappearing on me.
I always come back.
Then good. Promise.
Marry me.
What?!
You heard me!
You're asking me now?
Well, I just decided now!
On a tarmac in Cuba
with a plane full of exiles?
Are you mad?
Say "yes" now!
It'll make a great story!
Dean, I...
I-I can't say "yes" now.
Then say "yes" later.
Arriba!
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're beginning our descent
into London Heathrow airport,
where the local time
is approximately 8:05.
My newlyweds want a bottle
of champagne to take with them.
Do we do that?
Uh, sometimes, if they're nice.
They're certainly nice
to each other.
Thanks.
Kate, I never wanted
to be a burden to you.
I will ask
to get reassigned.
Laura, I'm sorry. It's not
that I don't want you here.
But you ran away from home
for a reason.
I liked knowing you were there
to come home to.
- Oh, this is fine.
- I'll take that from you.
Wait. Hold on.
Ladies and gentlemen,
in honor of this jet clipper's
inaugural flight,
by a random selection,
we'd like to offer
the passenger in 3D
a bottle of champagne.
Please, give him
a round of applause.
Here you are, sir.
Compliments of Pan Am.
No, thank you.
Oh. All right.
Wait.
Is this you?
Yes.
I thought these
were models, no?
Well, I just graduated
from stewardess school,
and I was crossing the street
to go call my sister.
I hardly remember
the photographer.
I was just... happy.
I guess it made a good picture.
Have a good evening.
Welcome to London.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Stay dry.
- Have a good evening.
- Thanks.
Welcome to London.
- Thank you, ladies.
- Welcome to London.
Welcome to London.
Thank you again.
- Our pleasure.
- Thank you.
Have a wonderful trip.
You still love surprises?
Only the good ones.
Oh, so sorry.
I forgot my purse.
I'll get it for you.
Thank you for flying
with Pan Am.
Here it is.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Tommy's drawing.
No, keep that.
I want you to have it.
Put it on your refrigerator
to help remind you
not to sleep
with other women's husbands.
You're going to be great
at this.
Excuse me.
Would you, uh, would you
place a local call for me?
Bridget Pierce.
Certainly, sir.
I'll patch it
through to the house phone.
Great. Thank you.
Very dramatic.
Is that my "yes"?
Hello?
Bridget.
This is the operator, sir.
I'm sorry. This number for this
residence has been disconnected.
Eventful flight?
You're late.
You're... British.
Keen Powers of perception.
Give it a moment.
You'll catch up.
I take it you weren't
detained at customs.
Roger Anderson, MI6.
I'll be one
of your London contacts.
The passport?
One of many.
You didn't think we'd
throw you into the field
without a test,
now, did you?
You passed, by the way...
Barely.
You walked out with it,
didn't you?
No matter.
We were testing mind-set.
We were testing will.
Your real assignments
might, in fact, be easier.
Almost all foreign diplomats
and businessmen,
persons posing as such
fly Pan Am.
You'll be expected to keep
your eyes and ears open
and communicate back to us.
Sometimes you'll function
as a courier.
Bridget?
But you must use discretion
at all times.
Make no mistake. We call it
a cold war for a reason.
I understand.
I certainly
hope that you do.
Mr. Anderson,
people have underestimated me
my entire life,
and they've been wrong.
Yes, well,
we'll see if you...
Live up
to your recommendation.
Wait. It was Bridget,
wasn't it?
Bridget arranged that meeting
with Richard in Rome.
She had an eye for talent.
"Had"?
Am I her replacement?
I have great hopes
for you, Kate.
I think I like debriefing.
It's unofficial,
but mandatory.
Yep. Yep.
Tomorrow another plane takes off
to someplace new.
Vanished... today's mistakes.
Their only trace...
A touch more wisdom.
I think I understand you
better in French.
Is that
the British edition?
Oh, no.
Well, I had to get my own copy.
Another continent?
I can't get away from it.
Why would you want to?
Hmm. I'm not that picture.
I...
I could never live up
to that.
Because it's not you.
It is the promise of you.
This is all of us.
Face it. If Bridget
were predictable,
you would eventually
lose interest.
I've hit on enough
of these girls to know
that they're not like
normal women.
They're... blah.
I don't know.
They're... mutations.
I think I know where you're
going wrong there, ace.
Well, I mean that
as a compliment.
You think the first man to crawl
out of the primordial ooze
knew he was different? No.
He just had an impulse
that there was more to life
than primordial ooze.
Is this you trying
to make me feel better?
Uh...
See... you see that table
over there?
That is natural selection
at work, my friend.
They don't know
that they're a new breed
of woman.
They just had an impulse
to... take flight.
So don't try and ground 'em.
That was
a tricky approach tonight.
Hell of a landing...
Captain.
Appreciate that.
It's the only time
you're ever gonna hear it.
Mm?
You got it.
Take two more, please.
Yeah, I heard Mickey
down at baggage...
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com