Previously on "Pan Am"...
Let's keep it in New York,
Ginny. Monte Carlo was a lark.
It's likely to be
a long trip.
I'm doing what I must.
Good-bye, Kate.
How old were you
when the Nazis occupied France?
I was 3.
I'm flying.
I am in charge in the air,
and what I say
and what I do is the law.
And a sky God is born!
Hey, call it
whatever you want.
You either accept it
or you need to get another jet.
Attention passengers
of Flight 296 to London, Heathrow.
That hurricane's stepping
on everything heading South.
It hasn't stepped
on us yet.
Well...
Well... Hello.
Hello.
Laura,
this is Charles Moore.
He's gonna be navigating us
down to Venezuela today.
My friends call me Chuck.
I'll let you know
when you can call me Chuck.
Okay.
What happened to Sanjeev?
Vacation. Bombay.
There's an oxymoron.
Excuse me.
Colette!
Put your eyes
back in their sockets.
She's a waste of your time.
Valuables under
lock and key?
She's waiting for Mr. Right.
She's very patient.
Hey, Bob, do you have
the latest weather maps?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Are we in
for some bad weather?
Well, it's October.
'tis the season.
Well, if you need any help
in the cockpit,
I do have experience.
Yeah, so one lesson.
Now you're the expert?
Experts don't appreciate it
as much as amateurs.
It loses its thrill.
Big storm brewing between us
and Caracas. Massive even.
Have they given this one a name yet?
We should probably
discuss this later.
Depends on the weather.
Uh, I-I'm forgetting
my meteorology,
but what is the technical term
for a destructive squall
with wind speeds exceeding
73 miles per hour?
It's not a tropical storm
but a...  Oh...
- Hurricane!
- That's what it is.
Well, they must have named
it something.
Uh, it's Ginny.
Hurricane Ginny!
Oh! What are the odds?
- What?
- Captain.
Why did the gives
hurricans names anyway?
And the girls name.
Of all the female names
that start with a "G"...
Georgia,
uh, Geraldine, Gina...
And we're flying
right into it.
Have you checked
the returns on the radar?
Ohh.
Recommend we change heading
to... 10 miles right of track.
Mm. 5 should do it.
You're ignoring
the cosmic, uh, signals here.
It's... it's like the universe is
giving you a second chance
to avoid Ginny, and you're
still not taking it.
Where do I get her number?
God. See, I wish I had
an ejector seat.
Gerda. 1961 was Gerda.
Right.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're about to experience
some rough weather.
I'm gonna ask you to keep
your seat belts fastened.
Here comes Ginny. I wonder which
one will be more destructive.
Landing card?
Thank you.
- Landing card.
- Thank you so much.
Sorry it's such
a full flight, Miguel.
We won't have a chance
to catch up.
Mm.
A situation
which must be remedied.
Mm. I'm having a small gathering
on my boat in the Gulf
tomorrow evening.
Will you and your girlfriends
still be on layover?
Absolutely.
Then it's a date.
He keeps
his boat out at night?
Sweetie, when Miguel says
"boat," he's referring
to his 80-foot yacht,
and a "small gathering"
is a hundred of
his most glamorous friends.
Good evening, Mr. Belson.
How can I help you?
I was hoping I'd get
the pretty one.
Must be my lucky day.
Are you a diplomat
or a playboy, Mr. Belson?
Please, dear,
call me Henry.
Oh, well, only if
you call me Kate.
Is this normal, Kate?
I mean, you know,
feeling like
you're in a,
washing machine?
It's as normal
as snow at Christmas.
The air we're flying through
just changed directions,
that's all.
Let me get you some water.
No. Oh, no.
All this shaking?
I'm... you know, I might take
my second bath today.
Is this your first time
flying, Henry?
Yeah. This trip was,
uh, 40 years in the making.
Lot of Mason jars filled up
with spare change in that time.
Well, as a seasoned traveler,
let me give you my cure
for turbulence.
Staying home?
Distraction.
Uh, well, I knew this was
my lucky day.
You got a fella?
Oh, not anymore.
Ohh.
A beautiful redhead
broke my heart once, too.
Henry,
I wasn't the heartbreaker.
Well,
that's hard to believe.
I guess grief is the price
we pay for love, huh?
See that? A quick conversation,
and the worst is over.
Well, we're still 30,000 feet
above the Earth.
What brings you
all the way up here
after 40 years?
Uh...
Henry?
- Henry?
- Ohh.
Oh. Henry, what's...
What's wrong?
I can't breathe.
Uh, has this happened
before?
No?
Never.
- Aah!
- Oh! Henry.
Uh...
Aah.
Fuel at 19 North will be
48,000 pounds.
I've got a heart attack.
You look okay to me.
Maggie's checking for a doctor,
but he needs a hospital.
Well, it can't be Miami.
The hurricane just hit the Florida coast.
Find somewhere!
If we don't land now,
this man is going to die!
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Where is
the nearest airport?
Are we really doing this?
He needs a doctor.
Grab the notams.
Uh, Port-au-Prince is
the closest.
Uh, the Dominican Republic
is friendlier.
No, the runway's still ripped up
from the last hurricane.
Haiti's clear.
You realize voodoo is an
acceptable form of medicine there.
Port-au-Prince tower,
Clipper 203.
I think you need
to elevate his legs.
That's for back pain.
We appreciate your concern,
but we need to keep
this area clear,
so if you could please
return to your seats?
I found
the flight service manual.
Oh, that's useless.
Uh, "treatment is
absolute rest."
"Make comfortable.
If breathing is difficult,
prop up pillows."
That's it? That's all
they expect us to do?
Told you. Useless.
Thank you.
Ohh.
You're gonna be all right,
Henry.
The captain is working on
how to get you more help.
Why aren't they answering?
We should be in range by now.
Nature's way of telling you
you're making a mistake.
Port-au-Prince tower,
Clipper 203 is a Boeing 707.
Requesting to make
an unscheduled landing
for a medical emergency.
L'aéroport est fermé.
What the hell is that?
Are you on the right channel?
Port-au-Prince tower,
Clipper 203. Do you read me?
Nous ne pouvons pas...
Why is he speaking French?
Miss, a refill?
We're not serving drinks, sir.
Sorry.
I had a minor collision.
Well, we, uh, we have
to land in Port-au-Prince,
but they're only responding in French.
Don't air traffic controllers
have to speak English?
Yeah. Here. Talk to 'em.
I want you to tell
the Port-au-Prince tower
we have a passenger onboard
that will die
if we don't get him
on the ground.
Port-au-Prince,
nous avons un passager mourant.
You're letting a stewardess talk
to the control tower.
Do you speak French?
Vous n'avez pas l'autorisation.
What are you looking for?
Uh, a plan "B."
The Haitians kicked out
the American military in July.
I-I l... I laid eyes
on the poor bastard.
He doesn't have time for plan "A".
- Shh. - L'aéroport est
fermé pour la nuit.
- Here. You know what?
- Il n'y a personne
à la tour de contrôle
pour vous guider.
Il doit y avoir quelqu'un!
C'est une urgence.
What is it?
The airport is closed.
There is no one in the tower
to help you land.
I... we don't need anyone.
No air traffic controller?
Shouldn't we be aborting
this landing?
Tell him that
we're starting our descent.
Request visual
for Runway 10.
Visuelle pour la piste dix.
We're doing a visual?
If you can't handle it, then tell me now.
Chuck can handle it.
Can't you, Chuck?
Ladies and gentlemen,
due to a medical emergency,
we're going to make
an unscheduled landing
in Port-au-Prince, Haiti.
We anticipate only
a short stop.
We'll be back
on our way to Caracas.
Cabin crew, please prepare
for landing.
Uh, I'm sorry. I'm going
to need that back.
When do you think
we'll be in Caracas?
I have family meeting me
at the airport.
Everyone, please buckle in.
Let me know if you need help.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Descending to 3,000 feet.
Still total darkness.
Let's go ahead and get
our lights on.
It's gonna be like landing
in a black hole.
Still not helping, Chuck.
We need runway lights.
They haven't come on yet?
No.
Let's go flaps 30,
gear down
before landing checks.
Flaps at 30. Gear down.
In Haiti, that could mean
they're looking for flashlights.
They're working on it.
Is everyone strapped in
back there?
Kate's on top of it.
Hold on.
Ohh.
Descend to 1,000 feet.
Descending to 1,000 feet.
Colette, tell them
we're landing now.
If they don't want me
to hit the tower,
they can give me lights.
Nous allon d'atterrir.
Ou sont les lumieres?
We may have to go around.
We'll lose
at least 20 minutes.
Captain, you're out
of limits.
Descending to 500 feet.
Stay with me, Henry.
You can do it.
We're almost there.
200 feet.
Ah, is that the runway?
Oh, the son of a bitch
snuck up on us.
We're coming in too fast.
Runway in sight. Full flaps.
- Confirm runway in sight.
- Full flaps.
Aircraft at 40 feet.
20 feet.
10 feet.
Okay.
Ohh.
I've seen friendlier-looking
ground crews.
What if they try to board
the plane?
Well, then I'll take
the one on the right.
Do you want some water,
Henry?
Henry? Water?
No.
There's nothing to see.
Just relax.
We'll be taking off soon.
Where's the doctor?
Docteur?
Les lignes sont coupees.
Il n'y a plus d'electricite
sur l'ile.
What's he saying?
There's no phone, no doctor.
Nous avons un homme tres malade
a bord. Ou trouver un docteur?
Petionville est le village
le plus pres avec un docteur,
mais les routes
sont trop dangereuses.
C'est une tuerie.
There's a village not too far
with a doctor.
We can bring Mr. Belson there.
I don't think
he can travel.
We'll have to bring
the doctor to him. I'll go.
No, no. A captain can't.
You must stay with your plane.
Um, j'ai besoin de votre jeep.
No. No jeep. Killing.
Okay. Give me
all the money you have.
Did he just say "killing"?
One of
us is gonna have to go.
It must be me. The doctor
might only speak French.
I might need directions.
No. No, no, no.
Colette, you don't have
to do this.
This is why we landed,
isn't it? Quickly.
All right. Ted, you drive.
That's what you're worried
about, my driving?
He's driven
in Haiti before.
Been driven. In a taxi.
Ted! You don't stop
for anything.
Sound advice, captain.
I used to like coming
to Haiti. Loved lake Sumatra.
See the flamingos
and the man-eating crocodiles,
but I tell you,
you put one lunatic in charge,
and the whole country turns
into crazyland.
Instead of leaving,
the American military
should have crushed Papa Doc
and his merry men
and taken over.
Mm. The whole country would
be better off.
We'd be feeding flamingos
right now.
Uh, I mean,
that probably sounds
a little imperialistic
to the French, right?
Am I right?
Do you always talk
this much?
Yeah, when I'm nervous.
A bit.
You always talk
this little?
What's that?
What?
It looks familiar.
Well, uh, a hurricane
just hit.
I'm sure there's more
than one downed tree.
No, we are going circles.
Not according to the North star,
which is directly behind us.
I used to be a navigator,
you know?
Flamingos bite. They do.
I-I mean, they... they're...
They're very pretty
a-and... and pink
and very quiet,
but they bite.
They break the flesh.
You know, as a child,
when there was danger,
I was taught not to speak,
not to make a sound.
Really? Why?
Ted. Just...
Whoa.
Are they dead?
There's nothing we can do
for them. Just keep driving.
Wait!
Americains?
What did she say,
and why is she getting in?
She will show us the way.
Lucille Ball?
Oh.
I thought you were gonna
say... Rita Hayworth.
Oh, well, I like funny.
But with nice legs.
I bet you had your choice.
Oh, but there's always
that one, right?
That one you let in all the way
ends up breaking your heart.
Well, she didn't mean to.
Yeah, she fought hard,
but the cancer won,
and she left.
Blanca... my redhead.
The redhead who broke
your heart was your wife?
Married 40 years.
Going to Venezuela
to celebrate.
That's where she was born.
We always meant to go
together one day,
but, you know, things...
Things.
Blanca?
Yeah.
It's a funny name for a redhead,
isn't it?
Oh, it's beautiful.
Oh.
It was not just
on the outside.
You know, she, uh, cared
about people.
She was always volunteering
for things. Too much, I thought.
I-I wanted her with me,
you know? Selfish.
Mm-hmm.
Very selfish.
I'm gonna make up for that
when I get back...
Try to be more like her,
make some kind of...
impact.
Mm. I've been trying
to make an impact myself.
Keep trying.
She says the killings have
been going on for weeks now.
The secret police suspect
everyone to be a rebel.
The rebels
suspect everyone
of working
for the dictator Papa Doc.
And here we are, two foreigners
in a government vehicle. Swell.
Perhaps they'll be too busy
shooting at each other
to bother with us.
What about
our planeload of passengers?
Doctor?
Does it look like I can go anywhere?
It's just a few miles.
We'll bring you right back.
And how many die here
before I get back?
We got money. Back at the plane.
Enough to save a lot of lives.
What makes your passenger
more important
than these people?
Nitroglycerin.
Put it under his tongue. It can
sometimes stop the attack.
Now go before
anyone sees you here.
Merci.
No, no, no, no. Ride's over.
Tell her to get out.
No. I can't.
Why?
I already told her
she could come with us.
No. No way. Not unless
she's got a medical degree.
Her entire family
was butchered.
Ted!
Those gunshots
are coming from the North.
- We have to go North.
- Lay down.
Get back. Don't get up,
no matter what. You, too.
We might be... we might be driving
right through the middle of it.
Stay down!
You're counting.
Why are you counting?
The runway...
It's too short?
That stays out here.
How could it be too short?
Pan Am used to land here
all the time.
Hurricane left some scars.
How much is gone?
Too much for a loaded 707.
So we can't take off?
Maybe the cavalry's
on their way.
Oh, if they're the cavalry,
we're the Indians.
How short is it?
About 500 feet
shy of liftoff.
So we're grounded.
You think "grounded's"
a viable option?
According to that manual,
it's the only option.
These manuals are written
by engineers, not pilots.
These planes will do a lot more
than they say they can.
They build in a pad
for a reason.
Well, we can't afford
that reason.
What's the outside
temperature?
78 degrees.
Gotta love the tropics.
But the wind speed
is 12 knots at our tail,
which negates
the temperature advantage.
I m... I mentioned
I was a pilot, right?
Current fuel level and cargo,
we weigh in
at 237,000 pounds.
Gonna have to
lose some weight.
Starting in 6A...
185, 140, 133.
Why are you asking
our weights?
The plane is too heavy
to take off.
I just saw the pilot
measuring the runway.
Now they're concerned
about weight?
How long have you
been flying 707s?
How long has your captain?
He looks like he just
got out of the service.
He does look very young.
Youngest captain
at Pan Am.
Well, he is.
So ask yourselves,
why would Pan Am,
the best airline in the world,
promote someone so young?
Well, looking around,
I can only assume
it's because
he looks good in his uniform.
May we help you?
Avez-vous
de la nourriture?
N'avons pas mange
depuis deux jours.
Bien sur.
They're just hungry.
They want some food.
How did Hemingway
describe fear, Mr. Ortiz?
Was it
"Grace under pressure"?
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
That's how he described courage.
So while she takes care
of the men with the guns,
why don't you sit down...
and I'll make you
a nice, hot cup of tea.
- Where are they?
- I don't know.
Henry? You awake?
Oh.
Still here.
What, uh...
What part of Venezuela
is Blanca from?
Oh...
Chuao.
Very small.
By the water.
She said e-everybody there
just wanted to feed you.
I've been to Venezuela
several times, but never there.
I'd love to see it
with you, Henry.
You may have to carry me.
Oh, come on. We'll celebrate
your anniversary together.
We'll dance the joropo.
Well, you're...
You're very lucky to...
Have gone to so many places.
35 countries and counting.
Best part of my job.
Which was your favorite?
Croatia.
Ahh.
Yugoslavia.
It was just supposed
to be a short layover.
It was part of my job. I didn't
even want to go there, but...
From the moment I arrived...
I felt like I was home.
Was it...
Was it beautiful?
It was gorgeous.
Strong, safe...
With this romantic side
that surprised me...
Devastated me.
Who was he?
He was my redhead.
Henry?
Okay, ladies. Let's go.
Where's the doctor?
You're looking at 'em.
- He's not coming?
- He sent medicine.
Dean.
No. Absolutely not.
Dean, we can't.
We can't leave her here.
She barely escaped
with her life.
And I'm sympathetic to that,
Colette, I am,
but taking her
is not an option.
Are you hearing me?
She could be killed.
Yeah, along with
a thousand other villagers.
So let's go out...
we'll round them up,
we'll lock the doors, and wait
for someone to take us hostage.
I'm not asking
for thousands of villagers.
I'm asking for one girl.
And I'm asking you
to put yourself in my shoes.
I just landed a plane
full of passengers
who are my responsibility
on a runway that is too short
in a country
that's about to explode.
And between you and me?
The only way
that we are taking off
is if we lose
a few thousand pounds
and there's a passenger
on this plane
that's got a guardian angel that
feels like doing extra credit.
She doesn't weigh much.
Oh, damn it, Colette.
I don't have the time,
the space, or the luxury
to take on strays right now.
"Strays"?
That's how you see orphans?
Oh, don't do that.
Don't make this about you.
How is she...
what is she? She 17?
I didn't realize
there was an expiration date.
Even if we take her,
immigration will immediately
kick her right back.
We have to try.
Pan Am has...
has strict guidelines
against bringing
stowaways on board.
I'm the captain
of this aircraft.
I believe in you,
I believe
this plane will take off,
and I believe that
once we're safely in the air,
you will regret
leaving that girl behind.
I landed here for nothing,
put all these people's lives
in danger for a dead man.
You landed here
to save a life.
There is still
the possibility of that.
She's standing right there.
- The man is dead.
- Why are we still here?
We'll be leaving
very soon.
What are we doing now?
Refugees?
She doesn't belong
on this plane.
She's seen much worse.
Is she coming with us?
She lost all her family.
Nothing's left for her here.
Here. You may need this.
It gets cold up there.
What is with this guy?
You don't suppose he could be
delivering good news, do you?
The good humor man's
coming?
- Or the rebels.
- Any one of 'em would love
a planeload of American hostages
to parade around like poodles.
So that hurricane should
have cleared Miami by now.
Yeah?
It's closer. We can lighten
the load by burning more fuel.
We're diverting.
How overweight are we?
You know how ostriches
are birds but they can't fly?
Well, this one's going to.
I want you to start
the before start checklist,
then start the engines.
Copy that.
Why is she being given
a seat?
Well, she's the only
Haitian passenger
that was brave enough
to show up.
First you land us
in this hellhole
just to watch a man die, and now
you want to smuggle refugees?
We choose who flies
on this aircraft.
What if you were sick?
Wouldn't you want
us to land for you?
I don't deal with conjecture.
I deal in facts.
And the fact is
she is a stowaway.
She is a guest of Pan Am.
And you are
an ignorant young girl.
Go back to your seat
and shut up.
Who is
the paying passenger here?
If you promise to go mute
for the rest of this trip,
I will see about
getting you a refund.
Okay, everybody calm down.
You hear that?
So those are our engines.
We're burning off some fuel
so we can lighten our load,
and then we'll be leaving.
Oh!
But I need everybody's help.
Do you want us
to get out and push?
I may take you up on that,
but right now
I'm gonna need all your personal
items removed from the plane.
That includes your luggage.
Every pound counts.
We burn 50 pounds in minute
with all 4 engines running.
Yeah, we need a lot more minutes
and we don't have 'em.
You want me to change
the laws of physics?
Oh! Hey! Stop!
Don't take another step.
I paid to have my luggage
arrive with me in Venezuela,
and that's where it's going.
Let me help you
with that.
You idiot.
Ah... ah... hey.
You touch that suitcase,
you're gonna be
keeping it company on the tarmac
when we take off.
You and Papa Doc
can have a party without us.
When I report this, you'll be
lucky to fly crop dusters.
Nothing wrong with crop dusters.
That's how I learned to fly.
Go.
Thank you
for flying Pan Am.
If this plane
is too heavy for luggage,
it is too heavy
for that Haitian.
He's right.
This isn't luggage.
She's a person
who needs our help.
This redhead needs a favor.
We need to leave her here.
If she stays here,
she'll be killed.
We might die
if she doesn't.
If the girl stays,
somebody goes.
Are you volunteering?
No.
Henry is.
He wanted to help people.
Tonight he gets to do that.
We leave the body,
and the girl stays.
You made that impact, Henry.
Safe travels.
That can't be good.
Ready or not,
we're leaving right now.
I'll start preflight.
- Kate! Let's go!
- Prepare for takeoff!
Come on. Let's go.
The wind has increased on our tail
and the temperature has dropped.
We can't take off.
Cut the pep talk, Chuck.
Where's our fuel?
We've lost 6,000 pounds.
Add that
to our garage sale,
and we're down
to about 200,000 pounds.
Still not enough
to fit into our prom dress.
We need to burn more fuel,
a lot more.
Well, there's no time.
Setting brakes.
Setting takeoff thrust.
Takeoff thrust set.
Captain,
it's my duty to tell you
that based on F.A.A.
rules and regulations,
it is too dangerous
to take off.
Yeah, noted.
We've taken off from aircraft
carriers shorter than this.
In a fighter jet. A 707 isn't
designed to take off like this.
'Cause fighter jets
don't veve four engines.
If you don't
blow an engine first.
You need me to change
your diaper, Chuck?
I mean, you're embarrassing
the Navy here.
Ted, I'm just
trying to tell you...
It's not Ted,
it's first officer Vanderway,
and sitting next to me
is captain Lowrey.
He makes the decisions
on this aircraft
without any interference
from you. Am I understood?
Yes, sir.
Seats in
the upright position.
Make sure your belts
are nice and tight.
Flaps at 20.
Flaps 20.
Engine 2, oil pressure 80.
Engine 3, 82.
- We can't sustain this thrust forever.
- Just another minute.
Smell that?
That's the brakes burning up.
I can fly without brakes.
Just a little while longer.
Another 30 seconds,
they're gonna be on our tail.
Thank you for Henry.
I hope immigration
doesn't send her back.
Cabin crew,
prepare for immediate takeoff.
I may have a friend
who can help.
It's now or never.
Do it.
Releasing brakes.
Pull up. Pull up!
I see it.
Oh...
Damaged runway cleared.
- Take gear up.
- Oh, way ahead of you.
Flaps up.
Flaps...
Up.
Nice job, captain.
You may
have to land again.
I think I'm having
a heart attack.
Your controls.
Ladies and gentlemen,
that was rougher than expected...
My apologies...
But we are climbing normally.
We should be reaching
cruising altitude shortly.
- Yay!
- Whoo!
Don't worry.
Kate is going to help you.
Miss Benoit?
Please give us
a few more minutes. Please.
I need you to do this,
Richard.
I can always count on
you for the unorthodox.
Can you do it or not?
We do have some experience
with green cards.
Please, I understand,
but we might
be able to fix this.
I'm in no mood
for one of your little games.
Just do it.
Give me a couple of hours.
No. Not hours. Minutes.
I guess I will have to
go over a few heads.
And a faster family.
A nice one.
She can't be here alone.
I will interrogate them
myself.
Thank you, Richard.
I owed you one...
Or several.
Yes, good bye.
You land
in a hostile country,
you leave the dead body
of a Pan Am passenger,
and you come back
with a 17-year-old refugee.
Which one of you
is responsible
for bringing a stowaway
on board a Pan Am aircraft?
Miss...
Valois.
Miss Valois, come with me.
Colette, I can't let you take
the blame for this.
I brought the girl on board.
Is this true?
They're both
covering for me.
Ask anyone in our New York
office. I'm the troublemaker.
Maggie, you are such a liar.
It was my idea, and you know it.
Laura, stop protecting me.
You know this was my idea.
They're all lying.
I already confessed.
Okay.
I think I get the picture.
Thank you, ladies.
There you are, girls.
Power in numbers.
- Debriefing?
- I'm buying.
So how long are we
stranded here for?
Stranded?
Have you been to Palm Beach?
Colette?
Are you coming?
Right behind you.
Okay.
Just consider
yourself fortunate
that Mr. Trippe seems
to hold you in such high regard,
because if it was up to me,
you would be out of here.
Quite an evening.
Really?
Did I miss something?
Some bad weather.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com