Previously on "Pan Am"...
There's a dealer in London
who's gotten hold
of a list of CIA assets.
- Who's on that list?
- Bridget Pierce.
I've fallen in love with you,
and I will do whatever it takes.
Dean, I need to move on.
I beg you to see
the Trevi Fountain with me.
You don't know a thing
about this guy.
You're a prince?
- You're a smuggler?
- I need a partner, Maggie,
someone
to share in the rewards.
I am more comfortable
with women.
I want to be married
to you.
- How?
- It'll be perfect.
You can see whoever you want.
I can see who I want.
You can even have Laura.
Please.
Madam, now...
- That feels nice.
- It's nice.
How is your flight so far?
- Very good.
- I don't like too much sugar.
- Light sugar.
Omar seems very down-to-earth.
You know, for a future king.
Despite buying out
the entire first class
for himself and his entourage.
That wasn't his idea.
It was his parents'.
I dated a prince once.
You did?
Johnny Esposito.
His father was the muffler king
of Clatsop County.
Every time we pulled
into a filling station,
we were royalty.
That's not exactly
the stuff of fairy tales.
I'm done with fairy tales.
Who needs 'em?
I do.
Well, look who's beaming.
I feel like I'm floating
on air.
We all are.
We're at 30,000 feet.
Okay.
Where did I leave off?
It seems strange,
doesn't it,
not calling it
"idlewild" anymore?
Airports are supposed to be
named after places, not people.
Yeah,
but it's Jack Kennedy.
What did Jackie say?
"There will be other presidents,
but there will never be
another time quite like that."
Yeah, for
"one brief, shining moment"...
"Known as Camelot."
Excuse me while I go jump
out of this plane.
And yet they had
a very unconventional marriage.
How do you mean?
Well, he was known
to entertain
a stewardess or two,
and they still made
it work.
What, you're not thinking
about messing around already?
You're not even
married yet.
Amanda sort of
gave me permission.
Seriously?
Well,
she's a very modern girl.
It could be a test.
I definitely feel tested.
Well, as your captain
and your friend,
I will just tell you
to think about it
before you do
anything stupid.
I didn't.
Now the woman I want to be with
is back there in first class
getting fitted
for a glass slipper.
All I've been doing
is thinking.
I thought you said
she was perfect.
She is. She is.
Well, almost. I mean,
nobody's perfect, right?
Yeah. For me...
Colette comes close.
I guess
if you really love someone,
that makes 'em perfect,
even if they don't necessarily
feel the same way about you.
Coffee, gentlemen?
Yes, please.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
You're welcome.
The lounge is reserved
for first-class passengers only.
Shut the curtain.
I need you to
walk something through customs.
What is it this time?
Antique jewelry.
Berber pendants.
More art than sparkle,
but collectors pay top dollar.
Smuggling jewelry
into the United States
is a little more serious
than sneaking cigarettes
into North Africa.
Yeah, so is the money...
Money you're gonna need
for your future plans.
My future died last month
in Dallas.
Well, I guess
I'm your future now.
How depressing.
Yeah, but lucrative.
"Clipper Majestic,"
welcome home to
John F. Kennedy International.
So new year's Eve at my place.
We'll help cook?
Well, you can see Times Square
from Ted's apartment.
We could watch the ball drop
without being trampled.
I don't cook.
I don't help cook.
We'll do everything...
And everyone can get
to know Amanda better.
And Omar.
I can't remember being
this excited about a new year.
1963 was pretty eventful.
1964 will be even better.
We'll make it better.
What now?
Juan Trippe offering you
the moon route?
What is it?
Says I've been grounded.
For what?
"Pilot's license has
been suspended
pending the outcome
of a hearing."
Well, that Haiti business
was months ago. Why now?
It doesn't say...
But I think I got
a pretty good idea.
What took you so long?
I always flirt
with the customs agents.
You wouldn't want me to change
my routine now, would you?
You know, you're getting
to be a real pro at this.
Save the sweet talk.
What's next?
So...
I'm meeting the buyers
tomorrow night.
I'll make the deal.
You'll get your cut after that.
Unh-unh. Not so fast.
I'm coming with you.
Yeah, that's gonna be
a problem.
These guys aren't gonna want to make
a deal with a woman in the room.
Well, it's almost 1964.
They better get used
to women with opinions.
Maggie, let me handle this.
You can't even handle me.
Let me make this
perfectly clear.
Where the jewels go, I go.
So I got no choice.
You never did.
PAN AM
Sadly, Series finale - 1964
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Pop.
Edward.
I called your apartment.
- You didn't answer.
- I was out walking.
Important lunch popped up.
We gotta do ours next week.
Bring Amanda along.
Okay.
Did she tell you?
The Governor has agreed
to preside over your wedding.
Amanda's father is
one of his poker buddies.
Your mother says
this is shaping up to be
the social event
of the year,
and guess who else
is coming.
Juan Trippe.
Those captain wings
are in the bag.
- I'd like to earn 'em on my own.
- Nonsense.
All this is damn exciting,
if you ask me.
- What about asking me?
- Well, isn't it?
Everything's moving
kinda fast.
Maybe we should
slow it down.
I'm afraid the women
on both sides of the aisle
won't stand for that.
Hell, the Normandy invasion
had less planning.
I mean, uh,
e-everything's okay, right?
Look, I-I don't want
to make a mistake.
Some of the best marriages
are not about love.
They're great partnerships.
Yeah, so whatever
you're going through,
you know, you'll...
You'll get
through it, right?
Attaboy. Okay.
I'm late, so I'll talk
to you next week.
Richard? What's wrong?
I've been shot.
This looks bad, Richard.
You should go to a hospital.
No.
Hospital's the first place they'd look.
"They"? You don't know
who did this?
It was dark.
I was on my way back
to CIA Headquarters...
To deliver the microfilm.
Okay.
We should call someone.
Don't you understand?
It was somebody on the inside.
Nobody else knew
about the drop.
A double agent.
Listen to me, Kate.
This has to be delivered
to the CIA by noon tomorrow.
You're gonna have
to take it in for me.
Okay.
Nobody knows I'm missing,
and if anybody
from the agency contacts you,
if they ask about me,
that person is
the double agent.
Understand?
This can't all be for us.
No. For me, so I can learn
all your favorite foods.
I could have just told you.
What's the fun in that?
I hope you don't mind.
I flew in the chef
from, uh, that restaurant
you like in Paris.
Le Dome?
Omar, that's too much.
We could take the subway
to Brooklyn
for brick-oven pizza.
No, no.
This is wonderful.
Please.
Colette.
May I have your permission
to court you?
Isn't this what you have
been doing?
For me, yes,
but for my parents
and the royal family rules, no.
There are rules?
I'm afraid so.
A formal courtship is
a minimum of six months.
You'll have your own wing
in the palace,
your own staff,
an unlimited clothing allowance.
You want me to move
to Wahran?
So my family can get to know
you as a real person
and not the fantasy
I've made you out to be.
Our personal physician
will make sure
you are not made
from fairy dust,
and... and others will be, uh,
dispatched to investigate
what magical land
you are from.
And what about my job
with Pan Am?
You could take a leave
of absence,
but only if you wanted to,
of course.
Please tell me you'll
at least think about it.
I'll think about it.
Another camera?
We can't let
the communists win.
No, I can't.
It's... it's too expensive.
It's on Pan Am.
I-I told 'em what happened
in Moscow,
and they sprang
for a new one.
That is very sweet.
Thank you.
I want to show you
something.
Okay.
That was after I told you
that I...
Yeah. Right. I remember.
I look like I'm sitting
on the hot seat
and the warden just pulled
the switch.
When did you realize
Greg wasn't the one?
I mean, you almost married
the guy, right?
I think I always knew...
But my parents loved him.
Everyone said we were perfect together.
Honestly, I...
I couldn't think
of a reason to say no.
Except you wanted more.
Not wanted.
Needed.
This one was
Andy Warhol's favorite.
You showed me
to Andy Warhol?
He said that you looked
like you were being hunted
by the FBI.
What does he know?
The guy paints soup cans.
I think he's a genius.
Plus he said that you were
a fascinating subject
and that I had a very good eye
for choosing you.
Yeah? Maybe he is a genius
after all.
And this one...
Is my favorite.
I look like a goofball.
I like the man
in that picture.
Amanda's probably waiting.
You're probably right.
Yeah.
You must be lost, monsieur.
I know.
I started walking.
Guess my inner guidance system
brought me here.
So how's, uh...
How's prince charming
treating you?
He wants me
to move to Wahran
to begin
a formal courtship.
You think
it's a little, uh...
A little fast?
The purpose
of a courtship is time.
Everything is moving
so quickly,
it will be nice
to slow it down.
You're in love with him?
Love is not something I care
to discuss with you.
Look, I-I just...
I-I don't want you
to get swept up
in some fantasy.
Well, I'm beginning to believe
that love is a fantasy...
One day there...
and the next, gone.
Look, Colette...
Good luck
with the hearing, Dean.
The microfilm should be
safe inside the lining,
even if someone
searches you.
Walk straight
into CIA Headquarters.
Alan O'Neill is
on the 14th floor,
last office on the left.
Don't stop.
Don't say anything
except the password.
"Albatross."
Alan will know what to do.
Kate.
Sorry. I frightened you.
Anderson.
What are you doing
in New York?
Little trouble with Richard,
I'm afraid.
You haven't heard from him,
have you?
Has Richard been
in contact with you?
No.
Not since Rome. Why?
Well, he's disappeared.
No one at MI6 or the CIA
has heard from him.
He has in his possession
a very valuable microfilm.
If it were to fall
into the wrong hands,
it would be devastating
to both our countries.
Well, do you think
he's all right?
Well, our fear is
that he's gone rogue
and is arranging a sale
to the Russians.
If you hear from him,
call me immediately.
Where?
I'm staying
at the Plaza Hotel.
Either there
or CIA Headquarters.
Richard?
I couldn't make it to the CIA.
I got stopped by someone,
just like you said.
Teddy.
Hi, Amanda.
Did you hear about
the Governor?
Do you know how many people
he's married?
None.
We're the first.
Amanda, just, um...
Let me talk.
This isn't easy to say.
Then don't say it.
Come upstairs.
I missed you.
No.
"No"?
I don't understand.
I can't share my wife.
I still want
an old-fashioned marriage.
Fine.
Then I will be
your devoted, faithful wife.
But every morning you'll wake up
wishing I was someone else.
Isn't it
the other way around?
This is about Laura,
isn't it?
What? No.
- Amanda, I'm sorry. I-I'm sorry.
- Look, Teddy, don't do this.
I...
I can't marry you.
Why are you taking
your Pan Am bag?
Gets me the best table
in town.
Amanda.
Maggie.
Darn.
I was just on my way out.
We'll have
to catch up later.
Actually, I wanted
to talk to Laura.
Amanda, hi.
This is a nice surprise.
I made an investment
in a friendship.
I hope it's about to pay off
in the form of a favor.
Yeah. Of course.
Anything.
I'd like you to be
Ted's mistress.
That's...
The funniest thing
I've ever heard. You...
I'm serious.
You can't be.
That's... that's...
I-I don't want to be
anyone's mistress.
I've noticed the way you two
look at each other.
There's definitely
an attraction.
No. No.
Ted is in love with you.
You're about
to get married.
Look, he's running away
from our wedding.
I think the main reason
is you...
So if it will get
Ted to marry me...
I'm willing to share him.
If Ted's getting cold feet,
this is not the way
to get him back.
No, it'll be perfect.
While I'm home
enjoying the things
that you ran away from,
you and Teddy can be off
circling the globe together.
Those things I ran away from
I still want,
just at the right time
with the right guy.
Well, it won't be
with Teddy.
Fine.
My parents' names were
Oscar and Rachel Valois.
They were
in the French resistance,
killed while fighting
the Nazis.
And you were raised
in an orphanage?
By Ursuline nuns
in Le Chambord.
And you remained in Le Chambord
until you were 23?
Yes.
Too long...
Because the one thing I
remembered was my mother saying,
"if you are lost,
stay where you are.
We will find you."
So I stayed,
hoping one day
I would cross the street
and see my mother
buying bread
or pass a cafe where my father
was reading the paper...
Even though I was told
they were dead
and I no longer remembered
what they looked like.
I think that's
enough questions for today.
There's a bar
around the corner.
Maybe your girlfriend
would be more comfortable
waiting there.
I'm fine right here.
She gets emotional.
You know how women are.
Once they get their claws in,
you're hooked for life.
Onde eles estao?
Fique tranquilo.
Eles estao aqui.
Deal's off.
What the hell are
you doing?
Wait. Wait.
We want to make an offer.
Let's go. Now.
I-I'm sorry.
She's crazy.
I'll be right back.
What the hell are
you doing?
It's a rip-off.
How the hell
do you know that?
They were speaking in Portuguese
about stealing the jewels.
That's ridiculous.
Nice people you deal with.
I've never dealt
with 'em before.
- It was set up through a friend.
- Now you tell me.
Look, I didn't want you
to be nervous.
You could have
gotten us killed.
It won't happen again,
all right?
Just give me the bag.
I'll come up with another plan.
You do that,
but the jewels stay with me.
Safety tip... don't leave
a key lying around
with a tag
that says "spare key."
Where did you go?
Let me sit first.
The room is spinning.
I followed you to make sure
you were safe.
I needed to be sure
Anderson didn't double back.
Where's the microfilm,
Richard?
Right here.
Sorry. I had to be sure.
So you were testing me?
Well, that bottle
in your hand says
you don't completely trust me,
either.
So you knew about Anderson?
Suspected.
Ever since the two of you had
that little escapade in London.
He was after the list
for himself.
The Soviets put a premium on it.
Anderson decided to cash in.
Anderson told me that
you're the double agent.
Classic spycraft.
Accuse your accuser.
I came here because I wanted
to trust you, Kate.
Now you have to decide
who you trust.
What am I supposed to do
with this?
Do with what?
Amanda
and her ridiculous offer...
Marry her and get me
in the bargain?
I'm sorry. She's just used
to getting her way all the time,
but d-do you really think
that I'd ever accept that
or... or think for a second
that you would?
Why did you call off
the wedding?
To tell the truth,
Amanda is great...
On paper,
a-and I've always...
Wanted someone like her,
o-only not her.
Why not?
Well... well, to be perfectly
honest, there's someone else.
There is?
Yeah.
Someone I've, uh, come
to know quite well,
a-and I think I've fallen
in love with her.
And wh-when did this... happen?
I-I don't really know.
She just sorta grew
on me...
Holding a TV antenna out
a window in Jakarta,
watching Jack Kennedy
speak in Berlin.
It's always been
you, Laura,
ever since that first flight
in London.
Ted.
I know.
Do you?
Don't I?
During a medical emergency,
I am required to land
at the nearest airport.
In a country hostile
to Americans?
This was
a life-or-death situation.
Not for long.
The passenger died.
Yeah, despite the heroic efforts
of my crew to find a doctor.
You were informed
the airport was closed.
Did they give you
a reason?
I landed without incident,
and I got my passengers
and my aircraft home safely.
We have an affidavit
from a Pan Am passenger,
Miguel Ortiz.
He claims
you threatened him
and that your decision
to take the refugee was based
on a personal relationship
with one of your crew...
Colette Valois.
In the end,
I made the decision
that I felt was right.
Sorry I didn't call first.
I was trying to avoid
another setup.
What are you doing here?
Where is captain Broyles?
He gets so emotional.
You know how men are.
Women are much more practical,
don't you think?
I'm willing to forgive
and forget.
What are you proposing?
Well, you still want to buy
the jewels, don't you?
Very much.
Vamos fazer negocios.
How?
Surprise is
a great negotiator.
Isn't it beautiful?
Even more so
with you on top of it.
That painting is beautiful.
The background investigation
has revealed something.
Am I an escaped murderer?
Your name is not the same
as your parents.
How could that be?
No, your investigators
made a mistake.
No mistake.
The nuns changed your name
to protect you and themselves.
But why?
Because they would have been
killed for sheltering
a child
with the name Halevy.
It is a Jewish name.
My parents were Jewish?
Yes.
They weren't
part of the resistance?
Maybe. I don't know,
but that is not how they died.
How?
Does it matter?
How did they die?
Dachau.
I stayed awake all night
wondering how I would tell you.
All my life,
I've only known lies...
Even my own name.
This doesn't change
who you are now.
No, but it changes us,
doesn't it?
Here.
Look at this.
- Is this...
- Your family.
It was taken by the friends
who gave you to the orphanage.
But there's a baby.
A boy.
He was adopted
from the orphanage
a few days
after you both arrived.
We tried to locate him,
but couldn't.
I had a brother.
You still have a brother.
As far as we know,
he survived.
One of the conditions
to settle the lawsuit
with Mr. Belson's family is
that you be terminated.
Although you were acting
under extreme circumstances...
Permission to speak.
Of course, captain Broyles.
On the subject of Haiti,
captain Lowrey left that body
behind to ensure the safety
of his passengers,
by the book.
Not Pan Am's book.
Then I suggest an addendum.
But he took on a stowaway.
Once she was on board,
she was his passenger, too.
It was his duty to protect her.
And I talked to his navigator.
That takeoff
out of Port-au-Prince was
a thing of beauty.
Instead of standing here
being judged,
captain Lowrey ought to be showing
other Pan Am pilots how it's done.
At a party in Rome,
didn't captain Lowrey
assault you?
Justified.
I would have hit me, too,
and harder.
That's all I have to say.
Thank you, captain Broyles,
for your... testimony.
If that's all...
It's not.
Addressed to you,
from Juan Trippe.
You may want to read that now.
That's from Maggie,
and I want a rematch.
You're on.
Well, you're very fortunate,
captain Lowrey.
It seems that Mr. Trippe has made
an investment in your future,
and taking this
and captain Broyles' testimony
into consideration,
you will not be terminated
at this time.
Thank you.
However,
your flying privileges
will be suspended
for six months.
There'll be a plane
waiting for you in June.
Consider yourself
very lucky, Captain.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
You pulled me out of a meeting.
I called off the wedding.
Amanda wasn't the right woman,
so it's over.
What are you talking about?
She's perfect for you.
No, she's perfect for... for
that plan you have for me,
but I don't need that plan.
I've got Laura.
Who's... who's Laura?
The woman I love,
and it turns out, she loves
your huge disappointment
of a son, too.
I never said you were
a disappointment.
You didn't have to.
Just wait. Think about it.
I'll come by the house.
Let's talk.
Tell mom I'm sorry.
Happy New Year, pop.
Edward, we're not done here.
Edward.
I talked to Richard.
Where is he?
My apartment,
asleep on my couch.
He trusts me.
Good. All right. Stay here.
I've got to get to him
before he contacts the Soviets.
Anderson, it doesn't matter
if he does.
I have the microfilm.
I lifted it
from his pocket.
Good girl.
I knew I could count
on you.
Give it to me.
I'll keep it safe.
Just one thing.
The mission in London...
Why me
and not a female MI6 agent?
We can talk about that later.
Just give me the microfilm.
They're trained agents.
I'm a stewardess.
Don't undervalue
your abilities.
A worldwide
intelligence agency
is looking
for that microfilm,
and you were the one
to retrieve it.
Now I must insist
that you give it to me.
Let's take it
to CIA Headquarters...
Together.
Kate, this is not a game.
Are you sure?
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna shoot me
in front of all these people?
It's easily explained.
The Soviets turned you
when you were in Moscow.
You shot Richard.
You stole the microfilm.
I caught you.
Unfortunately, you resisted.
All right. Let's go.
A little unfinished business.
Get on the ground!
I'm a special agent for MI6!
I'm arresting that woman
for espionage! She's a spy!
I hate to break it to you.
We're all spies.
This is how I always
want to remember you, Anderson.
Get up.
Amanda.
You know,
at my summer home...
I used to push you
off the dock
just to see you cry.
I'm a better swimmer now.
I'm the one being thrown
in the deep end.
Amanda.
We talked about this.
There's been
a slight detour.
I've just come
from the doctor.
I'm pregnant, Teddy.
Well, don't just
stand there.
You're... you're gonna be
a father.
Hug me.
We'll get married right away.
You'll see.
This is the best thing
that could have happened.
What are you doing here?
It's New Year's Eve.
Don't you have a party
to run off to?
I do.
I couldn't leave you here
all alone.
Well, for people
in our business,
alone is our natural state.
You have come a long way
from the stewardess
who didn't think
she could switch a passport.
That was a lifetime ago.
My biggest problem was my sister
on the cover of a magazine,
my parents were the enemy...
And this country
was Camelot.
The world has changed.
It's getting more dangerous
every day.
That's why we need
people like you.
You have me.
Right now, like most women
who work for us,
you're just an asset,
but that is about
to change.
We want you to become
a real agent, Kate.
You'll have to go
through training at Langley.
A new class starts
next month.
What about Pan Am?
Life is all about
making choices.
Happy New Year, Richard.
As we speak, little Teddy Jr.
is growing inside of her.
A-a guy has gotta do
the right thing, right?
Yeah, absolutely.
Man.
What am I gonna do
in that right seat
for six months
without you in the left?
What's your gut
telling you?
That I've had too many
of those.
Yeah?
Good. Have another.
Boy.
What does the gut know
anyway?
It keeps changing its mind.
Until Colette.
Yeah. Until Colette.
You're gonna get her back.
No. She's gonna be
a princess.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
The royal courtship
is kaput.
- It's what?
- It's over.
- When?
- Last night. Laura told me.
The runway's clear,
my friend.
Yeah, but, see, she'd still
have to forgive me.
- Right.
- That's highly doubtful.
At least you have a chance.
I'm gonna be a father
and lose Laura forever.
Hell.
It's New Year's Eve.
Tomorrow's a new year.
Yeah.
He's 21.
He might in college.
He might be married.
I might be an aunt.
You lose a prince.
You gain a brother.
Without knowing it,
I think all my life
I've been looking for him,
but all I seemed to find were
the men I shouldn't have.
Those kind are
easier to find.
Yes. You know, sometimes
the right one's right there
under your nose,
and you just don't know it.
Until he's gone.
Or you wish they were.-
Where's Ted and Dean?
The ball's gonna drop in a minute.
Who needs more champagne?
Me.
Maggie.
Did you pilfer all
those bottles from Pan Am?
No!
This is legitimate cargo.
Really?
I recently came
into a little money.
Thank you.
- A toast.
- Yeah, yeah.
To Pan Am,
for bringing us all together.
Pan Am.
- Hey.
- They're here!
- Voila.
-  Traffic was crazy.
Hi.
Hey.
When did that happen?
Isn't he engaged
to somebody else?
To Amanda. She kissed me.
- What?
On the mouth.
It wasn't half bad.
Congratulations.
I hear you're still
a Pan Am pilot.
Yeah...
With a 6-month suspension.
Well, still better
than being fired.
Sorry about...
you and the prince.
Don't be.
I'm not.
That's my family.
That's me standing in front
of my father.
Well, who's, uh,
who's the boy?
That's my brother.
Tomorrow I start looking
for him.
Let me help you.
- Dean.
-  Come on.
Hey,
it just so happens
that I have six
months off of work.
Come on. Please.
I missed you.
Listen, uh,
Laura, I have to tell you
something.
Hey, everybody!
The countdown's about to begin.
Tell me next year.
- Let's watch the ball drop.
- All right. Okay.
Thank you.
Good-bye, 1963.
- It was the best of times.
- It was the worst of times.
I loved
every minute of it.
I love us.
And this. I love this.
I hope that ball never lands.
Happy new year.
Happy New Year, everybody.
A very Happy New Year.
Sync, corr. with pleasure by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Isn't THAT better looking than
some creepy vampires or walking deads?