Previously on "Pan Am".
We'd like to move you up.
From courier to agent.
I'm George Broyles.
Who is that?
Oh, that's a sky God.
- What are you doing with all this?
- Diplomatic relations.
And you brought this
all on our flight?
I don't wanna lie to you.
Then don't.
I wanna feel how liberating
anonymous can be.
This is
about self-expression.
- Will you marry me?
- Yes.
I wish I could be more
like you.
Oh!
I'm so sorry.
My mistake.
It certainly was.
Okay, let's try it again
from the beginning.
I'll get it.
But you still haven't told me
why I'm doing this, Richard.
- What is my mission?
- First things first.
The key to pickpocketing
for a woman
is not to do it like a man.
For a woman,
it's all about distraction...
Touch, kiss, the foreplay
before the lift.
Make men fantasize
so their minds are elsewhere.
In other words,
seduce them.
In other words...
Put a little Pan Am
into it?
You surprise me more
every day.
Mm.
But you still need
more practice.
I'll get the practice in.
What's my mission?
You leave for Rome
tomorrow.
We've arranged entry
for your Pan Am crew
to a party following
an international conference
on the space race.
Kennedy's goal
to reach the moon first
has everyone scrambling.
Alessandro D'Arco.
Used to work S. I.O.S...
Italian intelligence.
Now he's a freelance courier.
He'll be carrying
a microfilm case.
Inside are stolen
American rocket plans.
And I have to pick them
out of his pocket?
Before he's able to pass them
on to the Soviets
that same night.
You won't be alone.
There'll be s.I.O.S. Agents
at the party.
As backup?
More like observers.
The Italians
have granted us access,
but that's as far
as they're willing to go.
And what if I fail?
At least you'll have
a new career as a thief
to fall back on.
All right,
let's try it again.
Amanda.
Maggie.
Do you have a minute?
I was actually in the middle
of something, but...
Oh. The Kennedy campaign.
- Did you work on it?
- I was a volunteer,
went from city to city,
house to house.
Changing the world
one doorbell at a time.
Look, Amanda, I...
No, Maggie, please.
Let me explain.
What happened
the other night...
I just... got caught up
in all the evening's emotions,
what with Teddy proposing
and all the celebration.
It just happened, okay?
Honestly,
it's no big deal.
I didn't know, so...
It's not even the first time
that's happened to me.
I must be sending out some kind
of signal or something.
A girl signal.
Must be it.
Who knew?
Look...
I just wanna make sure,
you know, Teddy doesn't...
Oh, no, no.
Your secret is safe with me.
Thank you, Maggie.
You're a true friend.
Look all you want,
you won't find it.
My name. I'm sitting
the next flight out.
Turns out you can't just
have a wedding.
You gotta spend months
planning the damn thing.
Yeah, well, at least
you two are still talking.
More than I can say.
Oh, Colette.
Won't return my calls.
Won't even speak to me.
Ouch. Bridget thing?
She says I'm in love
with two women.
I don't even think
that's possible.
Well, technically
it's possible to love three,
but... although I'm not gonna
go into specifics.
- The point is, it's the...
- The sex.
It ruins everything.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
It makes certain relationships
more fun,
but the "fun" ones are not
the ones you wanna marry.
By the way,
so you're telling me
that you and Amanda, you
haven't... we haven't.
- Oh, come on.
- We haven't.
And I'm glad. It's made me
take things more seriously.
Painfully,
painfully seriously.
Look, if it's real,
you know it,
so just figure out a way
to prove that to Colette
and never, ever give up.
See, now that's the only
rational thing
- you've said all day.
- Good.
Then I've met my quota.
Hey, do I know you?
I don't think so.
Sorry.
I know I've seen you
somewhere.
The photos, right?
Oh, right, yes.
You and everyone else,
unfortunately.
That's some
ground-breaking stuff.
It's really bold, electric.
You're very far ahead
of your time.
All that from a magazine cover?
Thank you.
Magazine?
"Life" magazine. I'm the Pan Am
stewardess on the cover.
I don't think "life" would
ever publish those photos.
Wait. What... what photos
are you talking about?
The nudes.
Where did... where...
Where did you see them?
Gallery in the village.
Uh, van something.
I need to know the name.
Van Amberg gallery, I think.
Excuse me.
Hey, Maggie.
I've been meaning to ask you
if you liked Amanda.
I did, and I think
she liked me.
Oh, I figured you two
would hit it off.
She's been bringing up
your name a lot.
- Oh. Has she now?
- Uh-huh.
You know, you two
should get together,
once we get through
all this wedding stuff.
Oh, I don't know, Ted.
The first few months
of married life,
the lovebirds should really
feather the nest alone.
Don't you think?
We're feathering the nest.
We're not building the Cage.
Yeah.
What's going on with you?
Nothing.
I just think the two of you
should...
Really, really
get to know each other.
Wait. Maggie...
Are you jealous?
What?! No.
I mean, I get it.
You're at the age
where you probably wanna
feather your own nest,
and hearing about us...
Ted, stop talking.
I just don't want you
to make a mistake.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
At the fund-raiser, uh,
Amanda and I were alone,
and... well, she was trying
to make me feel better,
and, uh...
She might have kissed me.
And...
Wait. What?
It wasn't a big deal,
but I thought
maybe you should know.
You're joking, right?
I mean, this is ridiculous.
This is the woman
I'm about to marry,
and you're trying to...
what are you trying to do?
No, no, I'm not trying to do anything.
I just...
Just because I can see
my future
and you've never been able to
get a grip on your own
- doesn't mean you can start a rumor.
- You... you know what?
You're right. I'm joking.
It never happened.
And I hope you have
a long and happy married life.
And we will never
discuss this again.
PAN AM
Ep.12 - New Frontiers
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
What are you doing
in my cubby?
Learning more
about my favorite stewardess.
Why do they call 'em
"cubbies" anyway?
Makes you seem like
a bunch of kindergartners.
Funny. I thought
you were the kindergartner.
All right, all right,
cool your jets.
Let me make it up to you.
Lunch?
Nice try,
but last I checked,
I'm on a flight to Rome,
and you are not.
Check again.
I know this little place
on the Via di Monte.
It's Jack Kennedy's
favorite restaurant in Rome.
I'm really not interested
in dating you.
I'm not interested
in dating you either.
Then why?
Come to lunch and find out.
Ooh! Ooh. I'm so sorry.
That man is infuriating.
Did you do something
to your hair?
What?
I like it.
It's so soft.
It's the signal.
I'm giving off the...
The girl signal?
Hmm?
Oh. Look at that.
Your wallet.
Is it my posture?
So...
Do you have any, uh, plans
when we get to Rome?
'Cause I was hoping
for a public flogging
in the Colosseum.
Colette, we're never gonna
talk about this
if you just keep avoiding me.
We can't talk about this
because there is nothing
left to say.
Actually,
I have plenty to say.
I know.
I know you still care
about me.
I know you wish you
could change the past.
Okay, but you... you're...
You're forgetting
the most important part.
It's the part where I tell you
that I have...
I've fallen in love with you
and I will do whatever it takes
to prove that to you.
But you can't.
Dean, I need to move on.
Just give me a chance.
I put in for a transfer
to the Hong Kong base.
Hold on. We have a last-minute
passenger addition.
They found him wandering
around the cargo area.
I'm afraid I made a wrong turn.
Luckily, they found me, or I
would be riding on the wing.
Well, we stopped boarding
ten minutes ago,
so you almost
missed your flight.
Must be my lucky day.
Did they manage to check
your luggage, mister...
No luggage.
Friends call me Omar.
Omar it is, then.
How about we find a seat
for, uh, Omar, shall we?
When registering
for housewares,
sometimes it's better to bring
gimbels to your actual house.
Mm.
What do you think, Teddy?
Ivory lace or Dover fog?
Mm, the white one.
Neither of them is white.
They look the same to me.
Indulge me, Teddy.
I am a woman of eclectic tastes.
Eclectic tastes.
Yeah, I've been wondering
about something.
We're gonna spend
a long life together, right?
You forgot "rewarding."
A long, rewarding life?
Oh, right.
Which glass?
Uh, whichever one
holds more booze.
Uh, but for a life
to be rewarding, um...
It needs to be built
on honesty, don't you think?
Hold that thought.
Okay.
Now...
What were you
gonna ask me?
Nothing.
Is everything okay?
I've often wondered
where these come from.
Perhaps a tiny bartender.
But you only get
a tiny hangover.
Have you been to Rome?
Yes, but, uh,
I have to confess I haven't
done much sightseeing.
Only from the backseat
of a car.
Well, then you haven't
really seen anything.
You have to stroll down
the Spanish steps,
visit Trevi fountain
at sunset.
- Sounds lovely.
- Mm-hmm.
And better if you have
someone to share it with.
But you are traveling alone,
no?
No companions. No luggage.
Awoke this morning
and booked a flight to Rome.
Sometimes we need
a change in pace
to see life
as it really is.
I couldn't agree more,
Omar.
You know my name,
but I don't know yours.
My name is Colette.
Pleased to make
your acquaintance, Colette.
The pleasure is all mine,
Omar.
Oh, no.
Hey, hey,
what are you doing?
I want them down.
Oh, you're her...
The model.
These photos need to come down
right now.
Stop. I can't.
I have a contract.
Look, I don't...
I don't understand.
Okay? You must have willingly
posed for Graham.
He never said
he would sell them.
They're supposed to be private,
not on display
for the world to see.
He sold them to me
along with the negatives.
I had no idea.
All I knew was this was
the most beautiful model
I'd ever seen.
I am through
being that person...
Just a woman on the cover
of a magazine,
being judged
by how she looks.
I don't judge a photograph...
A good one, anyway...
On how the model looks.
It's, you know, it's how
the picture makes you feel.
I only know how
they make me feel,
and I just want them down,
please.
Look,
I have an important buyer
who's willing to take them
from me
for quite a bit of money.
But...
I'll sell them to you
for my cost
if you can get me the money
by closing today.
Really?
Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
How much do you need?
I will get it to you.
$500, and they're yours.
$500?
I thought maybe
you were thirsty.
Unfortunately, I spent
my last dollar on the ticket.
You are going to Rome
with no money?
Ah, I guess I'm not one
for planning.
Hmm. Well, lucky for you,
refreshments are courtesy
of Pan Am.
I cannot say Rome
will feel the same way.
Then I'll have to think
of something before we land.
What do you suggest?
Stealing?
Begging.
Okay.
We'll try it your way.
I beg you to see
the trevi fountain with me
at sunset.
Between you and me,
it's not really the fountain
I'm interested in.
Well, I'm not much interested
in dating these days.
But good company
is always worth the time.
There? You see?
Begging works.
Hey, Kate.
Is it just me, or is there
something off about this guy?
Dean, she's just doing
her job.
Yeah, but does she
have to do it so well?
Here.
Do you think she's serious
about this transfer?
What transfer?
She said she put in
for Hong Kong.
Is this my wallet?
Well...
Here you go.
What's all this?
I was hoping you could tell me,
capitano.
This, uh, is your signature.
This is my name.
I didn't sign this.
Well, this is the cargo manifest
you filed with Italian customs.
Are you aware
of the 400,000 lire
worth of American cigarettes
hidden in your cargo hold?
The captain of any vessel has
an ultimate responsibility for...
For any cargo he's carrying.
I-I understand that.
And can lose his license
and face criminal charges
for smuggling.
I don't know anything
about this,
but I swear to you
we'll get to the bottom of it.
Any suspicious passengers
onboard?
Often they travel alone,
no luggage,
pay for everything in cash.
I-I think I might know someone
who fits that description.
Laura. You okay?
- I don't know.
I... oh. I'm so sorry.
- I didn't mean to interrupt.
- That's okay.
We could use
a woman's opinion.
- Um...
- Sorry.
I-I'm sorry.
I'll just be a second.
The thing
men don't understand...
Is that the patterns
you choose
announce to everyone
who you are.
Colorful or monochromatic?
Timid or bold?
Teddy tells me
you were engaged once?
Afraid so, yes.
It was a case of...
Traditional and modern.
And which one were you?
I would like to think
I'm a modern girl.
Me, too, Laura. Me, too.
But I'm betting
that's not why you're here.
No. I, um...
I need to borrow some money,
and...
I really don't wanna ask Ted,
but... it's a lot of money.
Well, how much do you need?
Oh, no.
No, not you. I...
I couldn't.
But I could.
Us modern girls
have to stick together.
How much?
$500.
On one condition.
This is not a loan.
It's... an investment
in friendship.
Um, okay.
Thank you.
- Very nice to see you.
- Excuse me.
- A great pleasure.
-Perfecto.
Grazie. Ciao.
What finally convinced you?
Was it the invite
or my charming personality?
Neither. I wanna tell
Jack Kennedy one day
that I dined at
his favorite restaurant in Rome.
Right, after you two
become best friends
and your kids start playing
backyard football
in Hyannis port.
You act like that
isn't going to happen.
In politics,
everyone knows everyone.
Buon giorno, signore.
Hey, ciao, ragazzo,
molto tempo. Ciao.
So is that your plan, then...
Long-term politics?
'Cause you and I both know
what the odds are for that.
I don't remember
asking for your opinion.
Oh, which is why you should
value it. It's unsolicited.
I made a mistake
coming here.
The truth is,
you're a Pan Am stewardess.
And for some women, that would
be the ultimate accomplishment.
But sooner or later,
you turn 32,
they turn you out,
retire you.
Of course, I've read
your personnel file.
You won't make it that far.
You know how many women
serve in congress?
20.
Which translates
to around 3%.
All of them got into politics
at an earlier age than you
or married into it
or got a college degree for it.
I have a degree.
A real one.
Not a fake one.
Do you know what it is
that I do?
Besides treat every airplane
like your personal limousine
and every stewardess
like your personal...
I don't treat planes
like limousines, Maggie.
I treat them like trucks...
Specifically, cargo trucks.
I use them to transport goods
from people who don't need them
to people who do.
You're a smuggler?
I'm a provider.
Now sometimes that means
providing food to the hungry,
clothing to the impoverished,
medicine to the sick.
Cigarettes to the needy,
vodka to the thirsty.
I won't deny that there's
a profit to be made,
but...
It's getting harder.
I need someone inside
to help me with, uh,
with routes, restrictions,
cargo manifests.
And who better to get
through customs,
no questions asked,
than a stewardess?
Oh, not just any stewardess.
You made it to purser.
You have more access
and experience
on a flight crew than
just about anybody else.
What are you asking me?
I need a partner, Maggie...
Someone to share in the risks
and rewards,
and I think that someone...
Is you.
Oh, and I thought
I was a fast driver.
It's not every day
I get to ride on one of these.
Speaking of,
what do you do every day?
I am in the service industry.
I, uh, smile,
greet people,
make them feel welcome.
So you're
a Pan Am stewardess.
Perhaps I have found my true calling.
Thank you.
If I tried more begging,
would you join me
for dinner tonight?
Other plans?
We have an official Pan Am
appearance at a party tonight...
- An ambassador's residence.
- Which you're gonna be late for
if you don't hurry up
and get a move on.
Dean, this is Omar. He was
a passenger on our flight.
Oh, yeah,
the man with no luggage.
I remember.
How are you finding Rome?
The sights are quite beautiful.
I'm sure no more beautiful
than wherever it is you're from.
Where are you from?
- Dean.
- What, Colette?
You don't know a thing
about this guy.
Don't you wanna find out
a little more
about your friend?
You like cigarettes?
What is this?
I'll tell you about it
on the way to the party.
Well, I'm not going to the
party with you, Dean.
I believe the lady
wants you to leave her alone.
I don't think this is
any of your business.
Oh, yes, it is,
because he's coming to the party
with me tonight.
Meet me here at 7:00?
I'd be delighted.
Great.
Could you
get me a negroni at the bar?
I'll let him get that
for you.
Ohh! Ohh!
- Ahh.
- Hello.
You saved me.
You come to Rome,
you get a pair of shoes,
and... look what happens.
You wind up
in the arms of a stranger.
I am Alessandro D'Arco.
I'm at your service now.
Let me get you a drink.
Yeah, I might take you up
on that a little bit later,
but first I'm...
Just off to the powder room.
Oh, please.
Shoot.
Scusi.
Thirsty? I'm told they have
an excellent bellini here.
You just don't give up,
do you?
Well, you still haven't
given me an answer.
I said I'd have
to think about it.
There are two Maggie Ryans...
One who thinks about herself
and one who thinks
about others.
You're having a problem
with the second one.
I'm pretty sure
neither Maggie
wants to profit
off the misery of others.
Well, you'd be turning
that misery into happiness,
making a profit
at the same time.
Come on, Maggie.
Don't let me down.
I've had my eye on you
since that incident with Dean.
What incident?
Don't play dumb.
You saved your job
by exposing his fling
with a certain
Pan Am V.P.'s mistress.
That showed moxie.
I was afraid I'd have to
threaten to tell Dean,
but... I'm pretty sure I know
what your answer's gonna be.
And how do you know that?
Because, Maggie, you and I...
We're the same.
Care for that bellini now?
The modern kitchen is
a fully automated kitchen.
Don't you think?
Teddy?
Hmm?
What's wrong?
You've been so...
Distracted.
Well, I don't care about China
or highball glasses
or... or toast.
I care about you.
Here... here you are,
getting to know my friends.
I've never met
any of yours.
I hardly know
anything about you.
Okay, Teddy.
Ask away.
Anything you want.
Okay. Okay, good.
Um...
Let's catch up
on the last 15 years.
Are there, um,
any old boyfriends I need
to worry about?
No one who compares
to you.
I'm beginning to believe
that's actually true.
What is that
supposed to mean?
Um...
When I saw you today...
With Laura,
you looked happier with her
than you've ever been with me.
No. I am happier with you
than I have ever been
in my life.
Come with me.
What are you doing?
I can't wait any longer.
So do you want to dance?
Where did you learn
to dance like this?
- Here and there.
- Oh.
I am well trained.
Clearly.
I ask you questions.
You dance around them.
Your friend, the captain,
has made you
more curious about me.
He was right.
We've spent the day together,
but I know next to nothing
about you.
I am a man who cannot enjoy
the same freedom as you.
And yet you woke up
this morning,
hopped on a plane to Rome
with no luggage or money,
and you are now wearing
an expensive new suit.
I am not without friends in Rome.
Dancing again.
Today has been
a fantasy for me.
I suppose I wanted to enjoy it
for a little while longer.
And just like that,
our dance must come to an end.
Right. That's him.
Dean, what are you doing?
He's a smuggler, Colette.
No, he's not.
That's not possible.
Oh, then let's let
the carabinieri decide
whether or not
he's a wanted man.
Oh, he's most definitely
a wanted man.
Your family's been very worried
about you, your highness.
"Your highness"?
This is prince Omar III
of the Kingdom of Wahran.
You're a prince?
A prince?
You're absolutely certain?
Interpol has been circulating
his photo for days.
Dean, could you give us
a minute?
I apologize
for my deception.
I needed to escape
my life...
Obligations.
You smile, greet people,
make them feel welcome?
There. You see?
My life is not so different
than yours.
Well, there is the royal palace.
A palace can be a prison
as well.
Omar, why didn't you say...
Tell you sooner?
Would you have treated me
the same if I had?
Your highness,
we have a police escort waiting
to take you to the airport.
What are you doing
a week from this Friday?
I am to dine
at the White House,
and it occurs to me
I have no one to bring.
You won't make me beg,
will you?
No more begging.
I would love to.
You again.
You're following me,
Alessandro?
Martini. Due olive.
Well, I suppose
I cannot help myself.
How are those new shoes?
Oh, it's nothing a Martini
can't fix.
You're a friend
of the ambassador?
I'm a Pan Am stewardess.
We're friends to the world.
That must include me, then.
Well...
A few more drinks, and...
Maybe you'll find out.
Grazie.
Shoot!
It's my fault.
No. Teddy, it was... nice.
It'll... it'll get better.
Of course it will.
My first time
was with Theresa Miller
in our boathouse,
in a rowboat, no less,
which is much more difficult
than it sounds.
There were oars everywhere...
My point is, is everybody
has a story
about their first time,
and this will be ours.
I really should go.
Why?
Well, we're not married yet.
People will talk.
Who cares what people say?
I do, Ted.
Can you...
Turn around?
Yeah.
Oh, wow. It's you.
You're the model.
No, no, you must have
the wrong person.
No, it's... it's you.
How cool.
You must be so proud.
I could never be this brave.
It was nothing, really.
Nothing?
These are empowering.
Thank you.
You know, the art critic
from the "Village voice"
said these photos
are transcendent.
Really? Are you sure?
Very sure.
That critic was me.
How does it feel to be
a pioneer?
Uh...
When the buyer heard that
you wanted the prints back,
he asked to meet you.
Who's the buyer?
Local artist.
Maybe you've heard of him.
Andy Warhol.
So I figure
we start in Vienna.
Work our way East.
The Soviet bloc... they're crazy
for American whiskey.
Broyles...
We trade for beluga
caviar and vodka.
We make a profit
coming and going.
Then we can open up
a new South American route.
I can't do this.
Go ahead and tell Dean.
Tell him everything.
Maggie,
let's not get crazy.
What's the worst
that can happen?
You lose Pan Am.
You lose everything.
I'll take that risk.
And why would you do that?
Because you got
the wrong Maggie.
Because I can always go back
to changing the world,
one doorbell at a time,
and because most of all,
I'm nothing like you.
You're leaving so soon?
I was having such
a good time.
I almost forgot
I have an early flight.
Let me at least
walk you out.
Where is that ticket?
Oh, uh, is this...
Is this yours?
Oh, yes, 47. It's mine.
Are you sure it's yours?
You wouldn't be trying to swipe
some poor stranger's jacket.
I would never do that.
Oh, here.
Please, allow me to help?
Oh.
Are all American women
this accommodating?
Oh, well, you'll have to come
to America to find out.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Where is your coat?
You know, I think I left
my ticket in the powder room.
I guess this is good-bye.
In Rome, we never say good-bye.
Arrivederci.
Until we meet again.
Gotcha.
The guy was a prince.
That's just my luck.
He fit a profile.
Now it's back to me.
You fit another profile.
Many of these smugglers
work from the inside.
Who has better access
to the cargo hold than a pilot?
If you really want to catch
this guy,
I would look
within your company.
Excuse me.
Ah, captain Lowrey,
just the man I'm looking for.
Uhh!
Find another ride home.
Colette.
Hey,
would you hear me out?
I don't want
another discussion.
I was wrong. Okay?
I was wrong about Omar,
and I've been wrong about a lot
of things, and I'm sorry.
I thought that I could
protect you,
but I understand that
I can't do that anymore, so...
I'm gonna respect your wishes,
and I'll leave you alone.
I'm sorry. These are
already spoken for.
I can see why.
She looks so brave.
A pioneer.
I think she has
a pretty bright future.
- Can I take your coat?
- Thank you.
So are you ready
to meet Andy?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
Good, good,
'cause word on the street
is he's looking
for a new model...
Someone brave,
you know, a pioneer.
He wants me?
We'll see.
He'll be here in a minute.
- Hi.
- Do you wanna sit down?
- Sure.
Teddy, I've been
thinking about last night.
So have I.
And I think you were right.
It gets better.
And that's marriage, right?
You start with something,
and you build on it,
grow it.
No, that's not marriage.
You can't... build on something
if there's no honesty.
Okay.
You want honesty.
Yeah.
Yes.
I am... more comfortable
with women than men.
And I don't know why...
Or how it happened.
It's something
I always felt.
But what I do know,
Teddy...
Is that I love you,
and I want to be married
to you.
How?
Don't you see?
It'll be perfect.
You can...
see whoever you want,
and... I can see who I want.
But we'll still have us...
Our life, our family,
the house
and the white picket fence.
We can still have everything.
You can even have Laura.
Laura?
I see the way
you look at each other.
A woman knows.
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, no!
What are they saying?
What's going on?
- What's wrong?
- For Juan Trippe, right away.
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
No!
We interrupt this program
for a CBS news
emergency bulletin.
This is Walter Cronkite
in our newsroom.
There has been an attempt,
as perhaps you know now,
on the life
of President Kennedy.
He was wounded in an automobile
driving from Dallas airport
into downtown Dallas,
along with governor Connally
of Texas.
They've been taken
to Parkland Hospital there,
where their condition
is as yet unknown.
He was cut down by bullets
as his motorcade
approached downtown Dallas.
He is now in the emergency room
of Parkland Hospital.
He is remaining
in the emergency room
because, uh,
secret service aides
say that the facilities there
are as good as elsewhere.
As of ten minutes ago,
a White House aide
says that the President
was still alive.
The extent of his injury,
whether it is
indeed critical or not,
is not... has not been officially
confirmed by...
He'll be fine.
He has to be fine.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com