Previously on "Pan Am"...
I bet you've got a few surprises
under that cute blue hat.
Is that smoke? That speech
is government property.
Not anymore.
Marry me!
I-I can't say yes now.
Teddy? Look at you.
I'm not going to let myself
get hurt again.
This is real.
A Pan Am stewardess can travel
all around the world
without suspicion.
And what if I refuse?
We can make this your last
mission and your last flight.
Uhh!
Aah!
That was never
supposed to happen.
But now that it has,
there are certain protocols
we have to follow,
do you understand?
You'll need an alibi
in case anyone saw you
follow him here tonight.
Kate, I need you to focus.
Think.
Did anyone see you
follow him here tonight?
I don't know.
Scotland Yard will investigate,
and MI6 will want answers.
Kate...
Look at me.
Right now you have to run.
Bridget?
Kate. I'm back.
Back from the dead.
Where have you been?
What are you doing here?
Well, I was hoping
you could tell me that.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Well, according to my horoscope,
I can expect a great opportunity
to present itself.
Let's hope that means
Mike Ruskin
is going to help me
publish my article.
I didn't even know
you wanted to be a journalist.
What I want
is for the entire world
to hate
congressman Christopher Rawlings
and his nuclear
death monger agenda.
If I happen to become
a world-famous journalist
in the process, so be it.
He didn't seem like
a death monger.
Looks can be deceiving.
Stay there.
My teacher said lighting
is the key
to revelatory photography.
I'm forgetting why
I volunteered for this.
Because this week's assignment
is portraits,
and I told you that I needed
somebody with a beautiful face.
Ah. Now I remember.
Oh, fudge.
Lightbulbs...
Kitchen, second drawer.
Ooh! Your horoscope says
that you'll meet
a tall, handsome man.
Hi.
Was that congressman Rawlings?
No.
Don't!
Maggie, you're acting crazy.
He might be here to arrest me.
Arrest you? For what?
I-I might have
set his hotel room on fire.
London? That was you?
Well,
I can't actually arrest you.
I'm not
a law enforcement official.
Plus I forgot my handcuffs.
But something tells me
you might have your own set.
I heard you could
strangle Republicans with them,
so I thought I should
invest in a pair.
Hmm.
Nice hair.
Why are you here?
Specifically, you haven't
been returning my calls,
and I'd like to have lunch
with you tomorrow.
More generally,
I think you might be insane,
but you intrigue me.
Lunch? With you?
I'd rather chew off my own leg.
Fair enough.
Just one question...
If you hate me so much,
why do you care
what you look like right now?
It's a good question.
Call me.
I'm staying at the Ritz.
Oh, and, uh,
nice to see you again,
Maggie's blonde
stewardess friend.
Oh. You, too...
Mr. congressman... sir.
Sometimes opposites attract.
More like out of sight,
out of mind.
I think that you two
would make a perfect couple.
- Me and Charles Talcott?
- Yes.
You can't be serious.
I'd have to fight that awful
bulldog of his for attention.
I don't know.
He's very fancy.
Oh, and fancy
is perfect for me?
What was the name
of your horse again?
Which one?
Exactly.
Okay. Maybe I grew up fancy.
But that's not
what I'm looking for.
Then what? Snooty?
Stuffy?
Well, after four
marvelous days in London
and three in New York,
I suspect all this time
I was looking for you.
Mmm.
Teddy, it's getting late.
Uh, I haven't seen the inside
of your place yet, though.
The inside of my place
is being
very diligently preserved
for one very special man.
That's me. I'm special.
Not if you don't
get some sleep.
Big day tomorrow.
Lunch with your father,
the ever-imposing
Mr. Vanderway.
And the mood is killed.
Good night, Teddy.
Good night, Amanda.
Hmm.
- What was his name?
- No, no, no, no.
Bedford... Bed... Bedford?
I doubt he's even
that handsome offstage.
But they wear makeup, you know?
Redford. Robert Redford.
Fine. See? Even the name...
He just sounds like
a prima donna.
It might be worth it
to wake up to that face.
Aw. "Take me to go see 'Barefoot
in the park, '" she says.
"It'll be romantic."
Aw. I'm teasing you.
It was a wonderful night.
Yeah.
And if I squint my eyes...
Yes, you do look like him.
And the French don't have
a sense of humor, they say.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anybody.
It'll be our little secret.
Oh, I thought
you didn't like secrets.
Well, depends who's keeping it.
Well, then,
I might have one for you.
-Really?
- When we get to London.
Really? What is it?
Animal? Vegetable?
- Oh...
- Mineral?
- I can't tell you.
- Come on.
No, it's a secret.
I have ways of making you talk.
- Oh, yes?
- Mm-hmm.
How?
Oh, I admit it will be difficult
to make it all the way to London
without spilling
this little secret of us.
Who said that us
has to be a secret?
Apparently, it all came
to a head in London.
What did you hear?
That there was a mission
last week...
To swap out a list of names...
Compromised agents, assets...
And I was on it.
But now, with that list
off the market, I can come home.
I can get my life back.
That's wonderful, Bridget.
Really.
What is the first thing
you're going to do?
Get my job back
at Pan Am, of course.
And Dean.
I've come back for Dean.
I hear you have a houseguest.
Yes. Thank you
for the heads up.
We thought you could be useful
in helping Bridget
with her... transition.
The thing is, Richard,
I'm tired of being useful,
and I'm tired of being
at your beck and call.
I want out.
You've made your wishes known.
It's all been arranged.
You'll be debriefed by MI6
when you get to London,
polygraph,
then you're on your way.
Polygraph?
I have to take
a lie detector test?
It's standard
in cases like this.
You were a witness
to a shooting, after all.
Witness.
MI6 will want to make sure
all the I's are dotted
and the T's are crossed.
We do have a dead body
on our hands, Kate.
Yes, of course.
No worries.
Just tell the truth,
and you'll be free and clear.
And you and I
can bid each other adieu.
You done good, kid.
- Really, Mike?
- I pegged you as tidy.
Is there a secret password?
Uh, "abracadabra," maybe?
"Open sesame"?
Maggie, thanks for coming.
I was so excited
to get your call.
I'm ready.
Ready for what?
Uh, my meeting with your editor.
About my article?
Uh... No.
I actually called you
down here to, uh,
give you, uh...
These.
Uh, I don't understand.
What are these?
Political articles.
- And I should read them because?
- They're very well written.
- And my article was...
- Not so well written.
Wow. Mike, I don't know
what to say about that.
Maggie, listen... you're
passionate. That's a good thing.
And you're smart.
That's even better.
A-and you spell really well,
which is pretty much crucial
to the whole process.
So it's just
the words you hated.
You're the one who's doing
the hating. That's the problem.
Your article
was an angry diatribe.
Uh, so the folks
who agree with you
are going to get a kick
out of it,
but so what?
They already agree with you.
You have to find an angle...
Why does he believe
what he believes?
Uh, where's he coming from?
You have to lead the reader in
and convince them that
you're right with the facts.
I thought I did that.
You led the reader in and beat
them with a baseball bat.
Maggie, you're capable of it.
Y-you just gotta dig deeper.
Ruskin?!
Oh, I've got to run
to an editorial meeting.
Do you, uh,
you wanna do chumley's
next week?
Oh, sure. Of course.
The Ritz, please.
Oh! Edward Vanderway.
Lieutenant, U.S. Navy.
- Serial number 653...
- Knock it off.
I'm never going to
figure out lighting.
Sure you will.
You're just not gonna get
any good pictures
with this old thing.
But I'm a beginner, Ted.
My sister gave it to me.
If you don't want to be here...
I'm just teasing. Jeez.
So what's the assignment?
Men of great character?
Most eligible bachelors?
I have to photograph one beautiful face...
And one unusual one.
What, seriously?
Who... who's your other subject?
- Maggie.
- Oh, okay.
For a second there, I thought
I was the weirdo face.
Yeah.
- Okay. I think I've got it.
- Good.
Hey, can I ask you,
um, something?
Did you and, uh, Craig,
you know, uh, do it?
That is none of your business,
and for the last time,
my fiance's name was Greg.
-Greg.
- Right.
Right. Greg.
Um, so I'm guessing everything's
still in the lockbox?
Stop talking.
Is there anything
that Greg could... Craig...
Greg... could have done,
uh, different
uh, to, uh, you know,
make things... unlocked?
If you think for one moment
that I'm going to coach you
on how to get into
some poor girl's pants...
Don't smile.
She's not a poor girl.
She's a very, very rich girl
who I spent
the entire week with.
Nonstop. Except for when
things do stop...
Abruptly, because of
her strict pants-on policy.
- Amanda? From London?
- Yeah.
Turns out she's better
than advertised.
But I saw her
come out of your room.
We were necking like
a couple puppy dogs
with peanut butter,
but that is it.
- Hmm.
- What "huh"?
Ted Vanderway finds a girl
he's willing to wait for.
I'm not willing to wait.
That... that's my point.
I mean, sure,
a-Amanda I-is smart and funny
a-and beautiful,
but seriously, what is
the point of boiling water
if you're not gonna make
the hot toddy?
Well, I think falling in love
may suit you.
No, we're having lunch later
today with my father,
so I-I think after that,
I'm gonna have to
put the brakes on this one.
- Ted?
- Hmm?
I want to respect you right now,
but you don't make it easy.
And you look like a statue.
I-I thought you'd respect me
if I was honest.
All I'm saying is
there are some girls
who are saving themselves
for marriage, and I admire that.
I'm just not one of them.
Wait. What?
Ha.
Did you see this?
2,000 screaming Beatles fans
showed up at Heathrow
last night.
Yeah, apparently,
"the fab four" were
- returning from Sweden...
- And word got out.
Well, I hear
they're very popular.
You know...
They have girl hair. Right?
Well, it doesn't
seem to bother their fans.
Um, can I cash this check,
please?
British pounds.
Uh, you can go ahead
and make that dollars.
I need money for London.
Pounds sterling.
Thank you.
For what? Five-star dinner
in Balentine?
Tickets to the ballet,
then darts and drinks
at the squid and wiggle?
Yeah, we're doing all of that,
and you're not paying
for anything.
No?
Dean.
What?
You don't like the ballet?
Dean.
Hello, Dean.
Colette...
May we have a moment?
Of course.
I'll be on the plane.
I've spent every night for
months imagining our reunion
and... and what I'd say to you
when I saw you.
Look...
I can't, for the life of me,
remember what I said.
What did I say?
When?
Every night.
Every night,
when you imagined this moment,
what did I say?
That you were angry,
betrayed, confused.
The list was fairly extensive,
and you have all the right
to be all those things.
I-I can't imagine
what you're feeling right now.
Why are you even here, Bridget?
I've been reinstated
back at Pan Am.
They're flying me to London
on the 2:00.
You're a passenger?
On my flight?
I-I was hoping
that when we touch down,
we could have dinner, and I
could explain what happened
and where I've been.
All those nights...
You imagining what I would say
in this moment,
and it never
even occurred to you
that I might just do
exactly what you did...
Leave.
Oh. I'm so clumsy.
Oh, let me help you.
I got it.
Colette, what's wrong?
Bridget is back.
I know.
I saw her this morning.
Hey, Kate.
Could you give us a minute?
Yes, of course.
You okay?
I don't know.
Are you?
Yeah. Fine.
We can talk about this later.
There is nothing to talk about.
Okay, nothing's changed.
It is you and me, Colette.
That's all that matters.
You hear me?
I hear you.
Okay.
Something you wanna tell me?
I was waiting
for the right moment.
I guess I waited too long.
Welcome to Pan Am.
Kate.
Welcome.
Colette.
Welcome to Pan Am.
I haven't had a chance
to say a proper hello.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Is this where all
the congressmen hang out?
Well, only if they love
a good burger.
Can I get some vinegar
with those fries? Vinegar?
It's a nasty habit I picked up
from the brits.
They keep a bottle
behind the counter here.
You must come here a lot.
Actually, I used to work here.
That's how I put myself
through law school.
I have two older sisters.
Dad was a longshoreman.
I played trumpet
in high school.
And, um, I wet the bed
till I was 11.
Why are
you telling me all this?
In the desperate hope
that who I am as a person
is more interesting to you
than who I am as a politician.
Ohh.
You're trying to distract me.
I'm trying to tell you...
I like you.
Scotch, please.
Make it a quadruple.
And then pour half of that
into a second glass.
Add two cubes of ice to each,
and deliver them
with water backs.
You want me to get through lunch
with my dad?
I'm protecting you
from yourself.
It's what friends do.
Friends?
I don't need any more friends.
But only one girlfriend...
I hope?
Amanda, um, look,
we need to talk.
- Edward.
- Hey, pop.
- Mr. Vanderway.
- Amanda.
I just finished the back nine
at winged foot with your dad.
Since when are
you desperate enough
to spend time with my son?
Ah. Thank you.
Colette.
Do you have a moment?
Of course.
It must be strange,
me turning up like this.
It is a little odd.
We heard you were married.
What?
No.
Nothing could be further
from the truth, Colette.
Then what is the truth,
Bridget?
I was sick.
Very, very sick.
I didn't want to burden anyone,
most of all, Dean.
I'm so sorry.
I never stopped loving him.
I know he doesn't want
to talk to me and I...
I don't blame him.
But you two are friends.
Can you ask him
to give me a chance?
Just to explain myself.
Please, Colette?
Yes.
Excuse me, miss, uh,
I need another Tom Collins,
please.
Scotland yard is none too happy
about the jeweler's murder,
nor are they convinced
it was a simple robbery.
You made it look like
a break-in, you took jewels...
Well, not enough,
it would seem.
But it was a mission.
- He was selling...
- It was a botched mission.
The man in question
may have been a traitor,
but for various reasons,
Scotland yard
can't know about that.
Richard thinks
you pulled the trigger.
Yes, of course he does.
That's what I told him.
Why?
To avoid further speculation,
MI6 would love to give
Scotland Yard
somebody's head on a platter,
which is why I have sworn
up and down
that i was the shooter.
You were merely
an unfortunate witness.
You lie to protect me.
MI6 won't hand me over
to Scotland yard,
but they might sacrifice you.
Unfortunately,
they don't entirely believe
my story.
Why not?
That is irrelevant.
The point is,
you have to take that polygraph
and you have to lie...
For both of our sakes.
How do I do that?
Don't worry.
I'll teach you how.
Little known secret...
When Edward was a little boy,
he refused to finger paint.
- Really?
- I didn't see the point.
It's not like we couldn't afford
the brushes.
Alice used to sit
next to his high chair
with a wet towel
because he wanted
to be cleaned off
every time he touched the food.
I'm sure this is all
very fascinating for Amanda,
but maybe we could talk
about something else.
The point is, Edward never liked
to get his hands dirty.
Still doesn't.
I live in Manhattan. It's not
like I got a back 40 to plow.
Figure of speech, son.
It means
you don't apply yourself.
Maybe if you did,
you'd be captain
instead of just first officer.
Hey, you know what?
You know, speaking
of little-known secrets,
Mr. Vanderway,
daddy told me that
your freshman year at Warwick,
you were part
of the theater club's
annual light opera.
I don't remember that.
- No. No.
- I'm certain it was you.
Teddy, I bet you didn't know
your father was an actor.
No, I didn't, Amanda.
Daddy said you were desperate
to join the club,
but there weren't
any male roles left,
so you volunteered to play
one of the female roles.
You played a girl?
It was "the mikado,"
if I remember correctly.
The female parts
were traditionally played
by the girls
at miss Fielding's school,
but when your father approached
the director and begged...
Oh, it sounds like you
really applied yourself, pop.
I was a damn good yum-yum,
if I do say so myself.
Hi.
I didn't hear you come in.
How long have you been here?
Long enough to know
that I'm in trouble.
Oh. You're falling
for the death monger.
We spent the day together.
It was... he was...
Amazing.
Would it really be
the worst thing in the world,
falling for the congressman?
I mean, for goodness sakes,
he's not a criminal, Maggie.
Oh, no.
No, that would be me.
Maggie the arsonist.
Hello? Hi, Mike.
What good news?
No. No, you can't...
Stay there.
Don't move.
I'll be right there.
Maggie, what's the matter?
Everything.
You worked up an appetite?
I got those, uh,
reservations at Balentine
and then
your mysterious secret.
Dean, I was thinking,
maybe you should hear
what Bridget has to say.
I... why... why
the hell would I do that?
Well, because you...
We can't move forward
until you put this behind you.
I... it is behind me.
But now it's in front of you,
Dean, again.
Colette.
This is a conversation
you have to have.
Better you do it now.
So how sick... were you?
Y-y-you couldn't even call?
The prognosis wasn't good.
I didn't want to saddle you
with an ailing bride.
Oh, so... so you were
doing me a favor,
disappearing,
not telling me where you were?
Now... you're better.
It's good news.
Did you know that the screams
of 10,000 Beatles fans
makes more noise than
a jet aircraft taking off?
What all the fuss is,
I don't know.
Rumor is they're staying
in the hotel,
and that's all it is...
A rumor.
You give me Sinatra any day.
Times are changing.
Not for the better,
if you ask me.
Not for the better at all.
Well, congratulations
on your clean bill of health.
Your husband must be thrilled.
I'm not married.
That was a lie...
An atrocious lie, Dean.
What about the other men?
Are they all an atrocious lie?
There were never any other men.
No. No. There were
always other men...
In bars, in elevators,
in hotel lobbies.
- No, Dean...
- No, I saw that, Bridget.
I saw the nods,
the glances, the smiles.
- I just never let myself believe it.
- Dean, no.
So you cheated on me,
you lied, you left,
- and now I'm done.
- Dean, I never wanted to lie to you.
The trick
to a successful lie is
to believe that
you're telling the truth.
If you know
that something is false,
how can you trick yourself
into believing it isn't?
Simply make the false answer
another question's truth.
Look, if I ask you,
"did you shoot Mr. Bolger?"
You simply fashion,
in your mind,
a question which
the truthful answer is "no,"
something like, uh...
"Am I a secretary?"
Then you simply speak
the answer... no.
This is ridiculous.
It is one lie, Kate.
It is one lie.
You can tell the truth
about everything else
that happened that night...
How you were pulled
into the mission,
how you ended up
at the jeweler's,
the race to get there.
You need only lie
about one thing,
and you're free and clear
of this forever.
Okay, now...
Relax.
Let's try this again.
Shall we?
On Saturday last,
were you engaged
by your superior...
Block it out, Kate.
Shut it down.
If you need to make peace
with what you've done,
now is not the time.
I don't want to shut it down.
I have been trying to forget...
Pretending like
it didn't happen,
like it was a bad dream,
but it doesn't matter.
I killed a man, Anderson.
Okay.
I've never seen pop
at a loss for words.
Well, I grew up with boys
in the family.
I couldn't beat them up,
so I learned to compensate.
With charm, wit,
and a razor-sharp sense
o-of how to bring a grown man
to his knees.
Oh, and which grown man
are we referring to now?
Good night.
You're not begging
to come upstairs?
Let's just say some things
are worth waiting for.
What happened to
"it's not so well written"?
Well, we were short a column
at deadline,
so I goosed yours and sent it
off to the presses.
But I... there weren't
enough facts.
It's a... it's a baseball bat.
You said it wasn't ready yet.
It wasn't, but you can't run
blank space in a newspaper.
You have to stop this, Mike.
Don't worry.
I did some quick research
and I rounded it out a bit.
You know, we're not gonna
win over the opposition,
but at least every
liberal reader in Manhattan
is gonna know what a jackass
Rawlings is.
Congratulations, Mags.
You're gonna be published.
Looked like you could use
the company.
I'm guessing we both could.
How did you handle it, Bridget?
The lying? The deception?
It was hard at first...
But I got caught up
in the rush of it,
convinced myself it was
for a good cause,
and...
For a while, that worked.
Have you ever had
to take a polygraph?
A lie detector? No.
Have you ever...
Done something...
In this job that's haunted you?
Yes,
and it still does.
What's wrong, Kate?
I'm sorry.
I should not have asked.
I suppose this is what it's like
being on the outside.
Everything I thought
I understood about this world
is...
It's been turned upside down.
If I don't pass this
polygraph, I lose everything.
Whatever's happened,
it's in the past.
One thing I've learned
about this nasty business
is whatever it takes
to save yourself...
You do it.
I know that this is
none of my business...
But you've been gone
a long time.
If Dean has started over,
maybe you should, too.
So I guess we're not going
to make
that dinner reservation
after all.
Sorry.
I needed to walk,
you know, clear my head.
You're confused,
as you should be.
I'm not confused.
I know exactly what I want...
You.
You can't force this decision,
Dean.
There is no decision.
Of course there is.
So you're the one that told me
to talk to her,
and now you're gonna hold that
against me?
No, I'm not holding anything
against you.
I've been trying to tell myself
nothing has changed.
Hey, look at me.
What has really changed
since yesterday?
Huh?
I mean, I'm still
not half as handsome as...
Is it Bedford?
It's Redford.
Not half as popular
as the Beatles.
You were in love with her,
Dean.
She broke your heart.
Now she's back. I can't be
in the middle of that.
Colette...
Please don't make this
any harder.
Just go.
Once you were upstairs,
did you see Mr. Anderson
engaged in a fight
with Mr. Cyrus Bolger?
Yes.
Did Mr. Anderson see you?
I don't... I don't think so.
No.
Did Mr. Bolger see you?
Very good, miss Cameron.
Now...
Miss Cameron, did Mr. Anderson
shoot Mr. Bolger?
Answer the question,
miss Cameron.
I thought you'd be gone.
By "thought," I mean hoped.
You were right earlier.
I was lying.
Gold star for me.
But I never cheated on you.
There were never any other men.
I was not married.
All I ever wanted was to be
your wife, Dean. I love you.
But I had to leave.
Okay, so you give me
one good reason
why you would have to disappear
without a call,
without a trace, a note,
anything.
It was life or death...
My life and the lives
of others around me.
I was in real danger.
Why the hell would anyone
want to hurt you, Bridget?
Because I worked
for British Intelligence.
MI6.
I was a spy, Dean.
I was a spy.
Dean, you've got to believe me.
Those other men...
They were contacts.
They were not lovers.
- I don't want to hear this.
- Dean.
They told me I had to disappear.
I had no choice.
I wanted to tell you everything,
but I couldn't.
It was for your own safety
and mine.
Wh-what do you want me to do
with this information, Bridget?
Say, "gee, thanks
for the explanation.
Let's get married now"?
The whole relationship
has been a series of lies,
and whether you... whether
you lied for your country
or for the hell of it,
it makes no difference to me.
I've moved on.
Dean, one thing
I never lied about was you.
I've always loved you.
- I love you still.
- No, it's... it's too late for that now.
Dean, look at me.
Look at me and tell me you still
don't have feelings for me.
Tell me that you don't love me.
If you can do that,
I'll walk down that corridor
and I'll disappear.
- Ted.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
Hope you don't mind me
dropping by.
Actually, I was just leaving.
Oh.
Headed to your boyfriend's?
Maggie is expecting...
Company.
Kate's in London,
so I'm staying at her house.
I don't have a boyfriend.
I thought because you said, uh,
you know, you lost
your, uh, the lockbox.
Good night, Ted.
Wait. Forget that.
I-I, uh,
I have something for you.
Ted.
It's the real deal,
all the bells and whistles
and everything.
Oh.
It's... beautiful.
And expensive.
Why?
Because you talked
a lot of sense into me.
You bought me
a professional camera
because I talked
a lot of sense?
And because you're
an excellent photographer...
Probably.
You're
a real talent, Laura,
and it'd be a shame
for the world not to see that.
But that's not all?
No. Um, I need to ask you
a favor. I need your help...
Shopping for an engagement ring.
I'm gonna ask Amanda
to marry me.
Oh.
Yeah.
Come on. I'll call you a cab.
I'll tell you all about it.
Okay.
I don't agree
with any of your ideas.
I'm never going to.
Whoa. Is that why
you summoned me down here?
To tell me
you disagree with me?
I thought we covered
that territory.
No. I, uh,
I have to talk to you.
Haven't you done enough
talking for one day?
Chris, I need to tell you...
Can it wait?
Till the morning?
Mm.
It can wait till morning.
Good.
Kate.
Kate, you did well.
I did what you told me.
Did you ask yourself
an internal question?
Yes.
"Will I ever forgive myself?"
No.
Good-bye, Anderson.
You saved my life, Kate.
You saved the lives
of every agent on that list.
And now you've passed
the polygraph
under conditions which would've
made most good agents crumble.
Despite your protestations...
You're very good at this.
You're free to go, as promised.
Anderson, wait.
Wait.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com