Previously on "Pan Am"...
What do you think
you're doing?
I ran away from my own wedding.
Bon voyage, Laura.
Safe journey.
- Marry me.
- I can't say "yes" now.
Bridget?
Fit the profile perfectly.
A Pan Am stewardess can travel
all around the world
without suspicion.
I have no idea
what you've done
nor what it takes
to keep a cold war cold.
- Do you think you're special?
- You think you're in the wrong seat.
Yeah, I am!
Well, you either
need to let it go
or you need to call your daddy
to get you one of your own.
You don't understand.
Maybe if you whine at me
another 20 minutes...
It was my engagement ring.
How could you just sell it?
Same way you pawned it.
I needed the money.
Who pays my bills...
Rockefeller?
Guy comes in, likes the ring.
You left it over 60 days.
I sell it.
But... but...
Don't spit all that out
again.
I get sob stories in this shop.
I get sob stories at home.
But here, this sidewalk... mine.
No sobbing.
Greg deserves
to have it back.
He saved up all his money
to buy me a ring.
For him,
that meant everything.
Oh, yeah? But for you,
not so much, huh?
Ah, crap. Freakin' hot.
I hate summer in New York.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
...Flight 270 arriving from...
Thank you,
miss Cameron.
Next in line.
- Laura, hi.
- Hey, hi.
How is the new arrangement,
staying at Maggie's?
Fine.
And did you, uh,
did you settle things
last night?
Kate, why must you
interrogate me about this?
Maggie offered. You were more
than happy to have me gone.
No, I meant last night
with Greg.
You know, the man
whose engagement ring
you're returning?
Had to cancel.
He couldn't make it to New York?
I didn't say that.
I came down with the sniffles,
some congestion,
and we had this early flight
this morning.
Really?
What are you saying, Kate?
You don't consider this early?
Oh, cookies.
Can I help?
No. No help. I don't want
any more of your help.
- Good morning, Ted.
- Yuck.
So do you wanna at least talk
about what happened last night?
This is all your fault.
Am I chewing gum? No, I'm not.
Gumdrop, Laura. Drop.
I never miss it.
This Grand Prix?
Every year?
My boyhood dream
was to be a racer...
The Monaco circuit.
Now all I can do is watch.
Season after season.
Quite sad, huh?
Oh, yes,
Monte Carlo, the beach,
the water, the sun,
every single year. Mm.
I feel badly for you,
Mr. Lonza.
Niko, please.
Feel badly for Niko.
Roger, Gander.
We have our oceanic clearance.
- Clipper 2-2.
- It's all about speed.
The Grand Prix is a race.
It's not a beauty pageant.
Through the streets
of Monaco?
My dime's still
on the Cooper-Climax.
I like the Citroen.
Now that's an automobile.
Not a formula one, Sanjeev.
Cooper-Climax won it last year.
Thank you, miss.
And that's my point exactly.
Do you boys always
leave this door open?
Sometimes we get lonely.
That is one heck of a dashboard
you've got there.
It does the trick.
Can I help anyone in here?
Do you have any jujubes?
Airport gift shop was out.
Jujubes. No.
But if you return to your seat,
I can get you some pate.
Oh, too pasty for me.
And those poor little geese.
But chewy gumdrops...
Pure heaven.
So you're going
with the Cooper, yeah?
I will if you will.
Dean Lowrey, your captain.
Ginny Saddler,
your interloper.
You were mentioning a pub, Niko?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Great spot.
Excuse me.
Oh. Yugoslavian, I think.
Who?
4C. Are you blind?
No. Just slower on the draw.
I'm curious
about the mink coat lady.
A mink coat? In July?
She's not V.I.P.
there's nothing here.
Where is she sitting?
With our captain.
And then the engines
started up.
Vroom, vroom, vroom, and go!
- Really?
- Like "Rebel without a cause"?
Fred and his Desoto,
Lenny in his Buick,
and me and my handkerchief.
"Miss Drag Race,"
Appanoose County, Iowa,
1955.
Ah, so you were listening.
Captive audience.
Oh, my favorite kind.
Was there a cliff?
This wasn't a chicken run.
Oh, there was a thing
with chickens,
but it was only the one night,
and no one meant to...
Well,
no sense revisiting that now.
Anyone for a cup of tea?
- No.
- No, thank you.
Love one, but I'm gonna
head back to my seat.
These boys need to fly a plane.
Yes, boys,
why don't you fly a plane?
Jujubes?
That's your first thought?
- Well...
- Pathetic.
Yes, I stocked up,
and yes, that's pathetic,
but this woman...
This vivacious,
voluptuous woman...
Barely out the door,
and your mind goes to jujubes.
Among other places.
Well, hallelujah,
because sad to say,
she took a liking to you,
captain.
Yeah, maybe.
Not maybe.
Get out there.
Pal, jump off the ledge.
Sign that dance card
and tiptoe yourself
into a little
corporeal distraction.
And at great personal sacrifice,
to myself...
I offer you these.
He's not dead, I hope.
Dead.
Eight letters,
starts with "M".
"Moribund." It's a good thing
you came along.
See, I thought you'd be up
in first.
Oh, I like it back here.
Who's
your traveling companion?
Oh, not one of mine.
Just cold and tired,
so I tucked him in.
Sweet gent.
Oh, it's a lucky gent.
It's my coat.
I'm the lucky one.
See, people think that I wear it
because I'm rich, which I'm not,
or because I'm snobby,
which I could learn to be.
Truth is, someone's always cold
on an airplane, even in July.
I have a surprise for you.
I love surprises.
Uh, private supplier.
Excuse me.
How you feeling?
Your sniffles
and congestion?
Oh, yes. Much better.
False alarm.
Just enough to cancel
with Greg?
I didn't wanna
make him sick.
Maybe you didn't really
want to end it?
Oh, I did. I do.
Well, I have.
I'm trying.
You have to talk to him.
And give the ring back.
I'm trying.
I don't remember this weather.
In London?
- In July.
- Oh.
I like it.
But it's chilly.
Couldn't we find a closer
pub to debrief at?
Yes, but this is the one that...
Mr. Lonza's going to?
There will be
race car drivers.
By all means, then,
let's dash.
Laura, you're right.
It is chilly. I'm gonna run back
for my jacket.
I'll meet you guys there?
You want us to wait?
No, go on. I'll be fine.
A bench in the fog,
Mr. Anderson?
Fog? Really?
I hadn't noticed.
But then again,
I'm British.
It's lovely to see you again,
Kate.
That was quick thinking,
about your jacket.
Yep. I am worth every penny.
Wait.
I don't get any pennies.
Shall we discuss your salary
or lack thereof?
No.
I think not.
There'll be a man
on your next flight...
Niko Lonza, U.N. attache,
designation of no importance
in this particular assignment.
I've met him. He was
on our flight from New York.
Well, no matter.
We're not interested in him.
However, Monte Carlo,
casino, V.I.P. room.
Mr. Lonza will be gambling
with a friend of his...
A friend who is currently
seeing an Italian woman
who goes by the name
of Lena Bracca.
She's a Soviet agent.
We'll need her fingerprints.
How do I do that?
Well, I suspect that you'll
need to arrange for Mr. Lonza
to bring you with him
to the casino
so that you can meet
this Lena Bracca.
That may not be so easy.
He's already interested
in another stewardess.
Well...
Un-interest him.
So I said, "you have 21.
You don't need another card."
But he blurts right out,
"hit me."
That sounds like something
my super would do.
The man doesn't know
a mailbox from a flower box.
Disastrous for
the chrysanthemums.
The table has opened up.
Shall we?
- Oh, I don't know.
- You won't accept my challenge?
Well, if you can teach me.
I've never actually played.
I have.
I'll take your challenge.
And I'll win.
Your friend sounds
like she means it.
Well, she can be competitive.
Uh, 8-ball? 9-ball?
Bank?
It's your choice,
Mr. Lonza.
Please, call me Niko.
That's a good shot.
Nice.
Think you're gonna
make that one?
Absolutely.
Clearly,
I underestimated you.
Clearly.
Let's try darts.
Oh, after a rematch.
Really? I mean, is that okay
with people waiting
for the table?
She's right.
I hate to be a pool hog.
You won't allow me
to even the score?
I'm sorry.
There was a chance at that?
Rack 'em up.
Lovely.
Good evening, sir.
You're almost right on time.
You can't mean me.
Pan Am has the best
on-time schedule in the world.
That's a heck
of a dashboard.
No driver?
He's at lunch.
Very generous of you.
Mm, I'm a giver.
Got a, uh, crossword puzzle
in there anywhere?
Five letters,
starts with "W,"
rhymes with "song."
Why don't you come in
out of the fog, captain?
Is this how you reel
all your men in?
No. Some of them can
open a door.
- Ah, poor frogs.
- Can't get the language down,
much less drive.
Where's Niko?
Where's your evil twin?
Billiards... busywork for
the unemployed, if you ask me.
Now darts...
That's a proper pub game.
There's a word
from the bird.
Crickets then?
I'll spot you the 20.
Hey.
Didn't see you much
during the flight.
Not at all
Am I avoiding you,
or are you avoiding me?
Ted, this...
really isn't the time.
Thank you.
- Ohh!
- Oh.
Where are you headed?
Besides into a wall if you
don't lower that thing.
What are you doing here
on your day off?
Just trying to stay
out of trouble.
Cashing my check.
Where are you...
Where are you headed?
133rd and 7th.
- Harlem.
- Business.
You're kidding, right?
I can't have business
in Harlem?
Should you?
I learned the subway system.
I can find my way down there.
It's not down.
It's up, and I'd hate to
see you lose all this.
Oh.
Okay. Up?
Nighttime in Harlem... I'm sure
you'll blend in beautifully.
That's not
a very nice attitude.
It's exactly what
you're gonna need up there.
Ted... it's personal.
- You mean a female thing?
- No.
Well, then what the hell?
I'll come along.
I haven't been to Harlem
in days.
Fine.
But I really don't wanna
talk about it. Understood?
Understood.
We've flown
Pan Am brass before,
but never
a senior vice president.
Yeah, that's a very nice
lapel pin there, Mr. Henson.
Consolation prize
for the Pan Am executives.
We wanted wings.
Just kidding.
I'm sorry she's so late.
Not a good sign
in a secretary.
She has many
positive attributes,
promptness not
being one of them.
What time do you have?
Uh, sorry, I'm not
wearing my watch.
What, you don't
have your rolex on?
- I thought you slept in that thing.
- Well, I stopped wearing mine, too.
Much easier to ask someone.
Ah, she deigns to join us.
Oh. Sorry.
So sorry.
Do we have enough room here?
Yes, of course.
Okay.
Okay, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go warm things up.
Secretary, my ass.
No, it's possible.
Lot of businessmen
travel with their secretaries.
First class ticket?
Mink coat?
The shopping bags?
No steno pads.
She's not his secretary.
She's his mistress.
Yeah, I guess most secretaries
don't drive around in Bentleys.
Oh, my God. You cashed in on the jujubes.
You know, I would never
encourage you to...
With...
- It's the vice president.
- I don't plan on telling him.
Could be worse.
You could have jujubed his wife.
That is not worse.
A wife is the block
he grew up on.
A mistress is where
he's living now.
Well...
You want the left seat, Ted.
This could be your chance.
Oh, I've been
to a casino before,
- just not one in Monte Carlo.
- Really? What's your game?
I don't know. Something where
I won't lose a lot of money.
Oh, in that case,
I have the perfect system.
You'll never lose.
Mm. And you'll, uh, teach me
this perfect system.
It's very simple.
Stay out of the casino.
Sorry, Kate. There's been
a slight change of plans.
Laura's moving up
to first,
so you'll be covering
economy today.
Hmm.
You've been called up
to the big leagues.
Odd that Maggie
reassigned you.
Oh, yes, it's very odd.
A woman scorned.
Sends the other one
to the kitchen.
Laura, I know you'll do
the right thing with Greg.
Whoa!
Right then and there
with the groom standing
outside in a penguin suit?
That lady looks like
she's about to fall.
- Should we wake her up?
- Oh, God, no.
Second rule of the subway...
Never wake anybody up.
What's the first rule?
Take a cab.
- What a wuss.
- Who?
Craig. You never let
the bride bolt on you.
You bolt on the bride.
- 72nd street.
- Greg. Anyway...
Next stop, 145th street.
I moved in with Kate that same night.
I didn't have any money...
So I pawned
the engagement ring.
Ohh. That's a dagger
through a fella's heart.
Thank you, Ted. I already know
I'm a horrible person.
I could just kick myself.
Well, you had to eat, right?
I'm sure at the time,
a short-term pawn seemed
like a pretty good idea.
Well, that's what I thought until
they sold it to a man in Harlem.
I mean, they can just do that?
It's in
the "how to pawn" manual.
See,
now they didn't give me a...
Oh.
Anyway, Greg's coming
to New York,
and I want things
definitively over.
I need to give
the ring back.
He didn't hear "definitive"
when you hurdled
yourself off that altar?
Yes, but when he came
to Paris...
He followed you to Paris?
Pathetic. Craig is Bambi.
It's Greg,
and he's not pathetic.
He's actually
quite romantic.
Well, see, that was
his first mistake.
I mean, look at history.
Antony and Cleopatra,
Samson and Delilah,
Pepe le Pew...
All of them brought down
by romance.
Well, he was really
very sweet.
You know, he saved up,
bought the ring,
found the right moment.
Oh, God, I really am
a horrible person.
Oh!
Was your whole relationship
this much fun?
Can I help you,
Mr. Henson?
A blanket, please.
She doesn't like to share.
Thank you.
There'll be a man
on your next flight...
Niko Lonza, U.N. attache.
Mr. Lonza will be gambling
with a friend of his...
A friend who is currently
seeing an Italian woman
who goes by the name
of Lena Bracca.
She's a Soviet agent.
We'll need her fingerprints.
Where am I
going to find shoes?
Does he know
all the games?
Well, I... he must.
I mean, he gambles here ever
year with a friend.
He won $2,000 at roulette
last year.
So you can only imagine.
I was shocked when he asked me.
Le casino Cote d'Azur...
Magnifique.
Want to go for a ride?
I think I've already been
taken for one.
Well, maybe this one
will be better.
It's hard to see
that happening.
Unless, of course,
uh... I drive.
I'm in your hands, captain.
Have Ted and Dean
even checked in yet?
I think they're still
drooling over those sports cars.
Boys and their toys...
a timeless love story.
- Colette.
- There you are.
Anyone for a guilty pleasure?
How guilty?
700 francs.
No pleasure in that.
No kidding.
I'm off to saner pastures.
I do like that hat
in the corner.
Oh, and that bag.
The bag and the hat.
- The cat in the hat?
- Ted.
Do you have time
to talk?
I have plans with Kate.
Does she know that?
Ted, it's fine.
You don't need to apologize.
Who's apologizing?
You ought to be.
You just said
I didn't have to.
Because I assumed
you knew you should.
For trying to protect you?
Which is not at all
what you did, is it?
Y...
I can't explain myself.
I was drawn to the man.
You never said a word to Niko
before the pub in London.
It was sudden.
I didn't really speak to him
on that first flight.
Let's talk about flights.
I've never been a big fan
of breakfast...
All those first class eggs
made to order.
All right.
You cancel your date with Niko,
and those eggs go away.
- For a month.
- A week.
- Three.
- Week and a half.
Two and a half,
and we're done.
Done.
Excellent.
Quick whiz,
then a few more shots,
and I'm off to get gorgeous.
Don't wear yourself out.
I'm Irish.
I'll pick you up at 8:00.
That's your date?
Smile. Niko's worth it.
Too bad we don't have
a camera.
Oh, but we do.
I was a girl scout.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
As in "be prepared"?
Yep.
Yes, I would say
that you are prepared...
For everything except say...
Telling me about a man
named Everett Henson
or his profession, which is...
Oh, yeah, airline executive.
I had the impression you liked
the element of surprise.
You could've filled me in
a bit more on your life
beyond "Miss Drag Race."
I suppose.
On the other hand,
"hey, Ginny, you said
you weren't rich.
"Didn't mention a job,
"yet you wear a mink coat,
fly to London, Monte Carlo,
"shop at Harrods.
You inherit a ton of money?"
See, I always figure
that when someone doesn't ask
you anything about your life,
anything about what's
staring them right in the face,
they don't really
wanna know.
That wouldn't be you,
would it?
Oh. Masterpiece.
It's museum quality.
Don't show it to Everett.
He doesn't like anyone
touching the car.
You mean like this?
You know,
I do accept payment.
This, however,
will not be enough.
No?
Still here.
You're not getting
rid of me, Philippe.
Miss Cameron, I reiterate...
We cannot release information
about our guests.
And I cannot be ready
to go to the casino
if I don't know what time
Mr. Lonza's car is arriving.
Perhaps you should ask him.
Philippe, it's a surprise.
He doesn't know
that I've flown in.
I'm sure he doesn't.
A tear? Hmm?
Would that help?
Because I can do that.
Please, no, do not.
Christophe? Christophe?
...Que monsieur Lonza
besoins sa voiture
a vingt heures precises.
Maintenant, s'il vous plait.
Parlez-vous francais?
8:00.
What ever
are you talking about?
Ah, Phillipe, merci, merci.
Je suis...
Oh, it's 7:15.
Thank you so much.
Well, thanks a lot, Kate.
You just left me here
talking to myself
like a lunatic right in this
very spot, as a matter of fact.
Laura, Laura, focus.
Can you do that?
I'm not 12.
How much money
do you have on you?
As you can see, Mr. Bodine,
I have your receipt
of purchase.
Call me "shoot man."
Uh... sh-shoot man?
Come on now.
Don't shy away from it.
- Shoot man.
- Shoot man!
- There it is.
- Thank you.
As I was saying,
I'm prepared to offer you $50
more than you originally
paid for the ring...
"Tasty pudding."
Track two, side "B,"
"tasty pudding."
White boy blows so smooth,
you got to dig it.
You certainly do. I wish
I'd seen him jam with Mulligan.
I'm sorry. Mr. Bodine...
Ah, Shoot man.
- Shoot man...
- Do you dig "tasty pudding"?
I, uh, yes, I do.
I-I dig the... tasty pudding.
But what I would really, really
like to discuss is the ring...
The ring ain't for sale.
Excuse me?
Man buys a ring,
he means business.
Well, there's business,
and there's business,
couple extra C-notes.
I don't have that much on me
today, but I can...
No way.
Well, I guess it ain't
that important.
Ted, hush.
Shoot man is
taking advantage of you.
Some people might call it
supply and demand,
but if that's how he feel,
then...
Sorry, little lady.
Deal's off.
I can't leave empty-handed.
In all fairness,
you... you did say that
you liked the tasty pudding.
Downtown 2 train approaching.
What?
Downtown number 2 train
approaching.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Wait! Knock it off!
What is your problem?
You!
You... usurped me.
I usurped you?
I was this close to getting
the ring back.
You were this close
to being played.
It wasn't about the money!
I was trying to make things
right with Greg
so he could move on,
so I could move on.
And you messed it all up.
You are...
a horrible person.
I thought you were
the horrible person.
Fine. Sure.
Run away.
Where are you going?
First rule of the subway,
Ted.
Taxi? Taxi!
Where have you been?
Sightseeing.
Ho ho.
I don't want to know.
Oh. Oh. Wrong door, huh?
Hate that.
Your fly's open.
Keys. Keys.
Oh, no.
Hey! Hey, you! W...
- Mr. Henson.
- Captain Lowrey?
You're out of uniform,
Captain.
What are you doing
down here?
Oh, just dropping off
a car for a friend,
and, I, uh, I noticed
this beauty. You?
Well, this beauty is mine.
- Oh, yeah?
- I'm sorry about yelling.
I didn't know who was
doing what over here.
No, I don't blame you.
Don't blame you.
Wow. These doors...
Solid, huh?
Your hand, Captain.
You're like me, huh?
Keep your greasy fingers
off my car.
Annoying as hell, isn't it?
Yeah, I'd love to...
love to take it for a spin.
Sure. We'll get on that.
Tomorrow.
Ginny.
Dean.
- Key.
- From the front desk.
Key.
From under the front seat.
Allow me.
How did you find it?
Well, I told you.
I pay attention.
When did you find it?
Before Everett could.
You know, you were right.
He doesn't like
people touching his car.
You look ready
for a night on the town.
You, too.
All dressed up,
and nowhere to go.
My friends' car
broke down in Nice.
Well, and that's not
Monte Carlo's fault.
Hmm.
I'm so sorry, caro.
Cars, taxi, tourists...
Everywhere.
O gli americani che non sanno
leggere i segnali stradali.
Voglio da bere.
This must be Lena?
Niko, at last. I have heard
so much about you.
And I've heard
about you.
This is Kate from New York.
Oh, I love Manhattan...
The shopping,
almost as good as Roma.
Lena, it's so nice to meet you.
I'm sorry. There was traffic?
All is fine, thank you.
Remy, is there only champagne?
Is there no Chardonnay?
Non c'e Moscato?
A quanto pare lasciano entrare
chiunque di questi tempi.
I think we're just gonna have
some champagne. That's fine.
Oh, uh, I think Lena has
the right idea.
I-I'd love wine, too.
Chardonnay?
Sauvignon Blanc?
Oh, I'd prefer something red.
Lena, I am so sorry.
I can be such a klutz sometimes.
Oh, no, no, don't do that.
Hot water will set the stain.
I have club soda.
It's a-a gift from the gods.
It's like an eraser.
We use it all the time
for our passengers.
- I'm a stewardess...
- for Pan Am.
If I can't make those
look brand-spanking new,
I'll get you a new pair...
From New York.
Please.
Let me make up for it.
Schifosa.
Excuse me, bartender?
Yes, sir. May I help you?
I would like to have a glass
of something red, I think.
Perhaps
the '57 Chateau Capet-Guillier.
Oh, that's
an excellent Bordeaux, sir.
And also,
instead of having a glass,
I would like to have
a bottle,
if you will join me.
I think I will save
this bottle as a...
What do you call it?
A keepsake?
Memento?
Both.
It was an accident.
Accident, blessing,
good fortune.
You know what?
I think Remy will thank us.
Thank you.
I could see it
from the beginning.
Not a good match.
You just met her.
Well, I have a good eye
for people.
Oof.
No, he'll never make his 11.
Not impossible.
Mmm, he can't thread.
He can't kiss.
Nothing worse
than a bad kisser.
What do you wanna bet that not
a single one of those men
have ever played
against a girl?
I would take that bet.
What'd you wish for?
Do-over.
Oh, power over time and space.
Quite a penny.
10 francs.
Well, I-in that case,
uh...
My engagement ring?
You have another 10 francs?
I'll go for world peace.
You've had it
this whole time?
- I tried to get your attention.
- This whole time?
A guy's gotta pick the right
moment to give a girl a ring.
Wow.
That might have been
the worst thing
I could have possibly
said right now.
Maybe I am
a horrible person.
Just thoughtless sometimes.
Getting into it
was so easy...
Flower arrangements,
bridesmaids dresses.
Getting out?
That part
I really messed up.
The suspense is over.
You're not perfect.
How did you talk Shoot man
into it?
Oh.
The thing with musicians
is you gotta start off
on the right foot,
which, in this case, was, uh,
"what time you got?"
Oh, God. Your Rolex?
Thank you
for choosing Pan Am. Good night.
Bye-bye.
- Ladies.
- Captain.
Good to be back in New York.
Yeah.
Did you lose something?
I thought I had
a tin of aspirin.
Monte Carlo,
always too much of a party.
It's too much of something.
High wire, perhaps.
Always loved
walking it myself.
Although sometimes...
It's helpful
to have a net.
Now where's the fun
in that?
Captain, there you are.
I thought we missed you.
Ah, I got you this far.
You'll have to do the rest
on your own.
If you ever need anything...
From the inside.
Yeah. And...
If you ever need anything
from 35,000 feet...
Okay.
Should probably keep one
of these on hand, too.
Yes. I definitely will.
Thank you.
Absolutely.
Keep it running.
- I'll only be a few minutes.
- Yes, ma'am.
- For me?
- Well, it's the least we can do.
Apparently,
we don't pay you.
Can't tell that Mr. Anderson
anything.
Ah, the lovely Lena.
She was blonde
last I saw her.
She mention
anything about Gdansk?
Poland?
Site of this year's
world fencing championship.
Interesting cover
for a spy convention.
I'm pretty sure Lena's already
been to fencing school.
The fingerprints
should prove helpful.
We'll be able to zero in
on the nine aliases
she's used
over the last two years.
Nice work.
An 8-year-old
could have done it.
Did you get an invitation
to a casino?
Good-looking guy.
I take what you give me.
Hey. You can get these
right here on the street.
You've gotta love New York.
How was your, uh,
insurance... official?
- Agent.
- We call them agents.
I, uh, I couldn't
get out of there fast enough.
So where are we going?
Oh, just down the street.
I'm betting we can find
a few men
who've never played pool
against a girl.
I'll take that bet.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com