Previously on "Pan Am"...
Look, I get to see the world,
Sam.
When was the last time
you left the village?
I don't need to see the world
to change it.
- Marry me!
- I can't say yes now.
Pan Am stewardess can travell all
around the world without suspicion.
You volunteered for this.
They will let you out.
Are you going my way?
Sometimes the stars align.
You're different
from other girls.
Thank you.
And democracy is not perfect.
You're casting a shadow,
Kate.
I take it you missed
the signal?
- Stood me up at the park.
- I didn't miss it.
- Are you gonna invite me in?
- We had our exit interview.
Well, it doesn't work
that way, Kate.
It's like a marriage.
Saying "yes" is the easy part.
Now would be a good time
to invite me in.
Nosy neighbors.
I have a job for you.
No.
No more jobs,
no more mysterious packages,
no more betrayals.
I'm going to London.
Just hear me out, Kate.
And if I don't, what?
This time I get dragged away
by the men in trench coats?
There's a dealer in London who's
gotten ahold of a list of names.
CIA assets.
He's selling that list
to the Soviets.
I told you, no.
All you need to do is deliver
this to your contact in London.
Inside is
a counterfeit list.
Anderson will take care
of the rest.
Anderson.
And what if I refuse?
I'm gonna make this plain
for you, Kate.
Your exit from the agency
can go a few different ways...
A simple matter of a little
paperwork and a handshake,
or we can make this
your last mission...
And your last flight.
You would really cost me
my job at Pan Am?
I'll do whatever I have to,
to get this done.
Just like you did
with Bridget?
- Here.
- Oh, thank you.
Sam?
Hey, Mags, sorry I'm late.
Late for what?
You know, hitting
the Wild Blue Yonder,
crossing the pond.
Chip chip cheerio
and all that rot.
Sam, what are you doing here?
I'm leaving for London
in two hours.
I know. I'm going with you.
Remember?
Oh! Hi, Sam.
Laura. Good look.
Think you can
sneak me into first class?
Sam, I...
Do not do this to me,
Maggie.
You promised you'd get me
to London.
What's in London?
The World Atomic Symposium...
Biggest gathering of
death merchants on the planet.
Ban the bomb uk is gonna crash
their little war fest,
and I've got a spot
on the front lines.
How long have...
How long have you been part
of the ban the bomb movement?
Since saving mankind
from extinction
became a moral imperative.
I think that is very noble.
I mean, what could be more
important than saving the world?
- How about saving my job?
- Won't be any job left
when the world winds up
in a pile of radioactive ash.
Come on, Maggie.
You owe me.
Dean?
You better get a move on.
We're flying in two hours.
Is this how it works,
you kiss a girl once
and you become her chauffer?
Actually, it was you
who kissed me.
Oh, then maybe I should
drive you,
which will give you a chance
to put on your uniform.
I said we're flying,
not flying Pan Am.
Well, you said you wanted
to learn.
With these?
Yeah. It's a Stearman PT-17.
Crop duster. Same plane
I learned to fly on.
A crop duster?
You are getting your wings
today.
PAN AM
Ep. 09 - Kiss Kiss Bang Bang
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Who's in first class today?
Earl of Halifax,
two movie stars,
and a United States
congressman.
A congressman? Who?
Oh. Christopher Rawlings.
I hear he's very handsome.
I'm not worried
about how he looks.
You mean Sam?
No, the Earl.
I'm sure he'll be on
his best behavior.
Then you don't know Sam.
Listen, you've gotta help me
keep an eye on him.
If anyone finds out
about this...
Find out about what?
Uh, V.I.P. on our London
flight... a congressman Rawlings.
Oh, great man. Met him
at a fund-raiser last year.
Let me guess.
Fat cats for progress?
Hysterical.
Let's just make sure
the congressman gets
the V.I.P. treatment today,
okay?
Emphasis on the "V".
Aye aye, captain.
Oh, no,
you're not our captain.
Where is Dean?
Called in sick.
Huh. Must be something
going around.
Colette's sick, too.
Mm.
Who's Dean's replacement?
Captain Thornton.
Dennis Thornton?
You know him?
Captain on my very first
round-the-world.
Two weeks of war stories
and wandering hands.
Steer clear.
Ladies.
Captain.
I'm sorry,
but, uh,
your hat is where?
Oh. The hat pin broke.
I was just trying
to fix it.
I don't care about your excuses,
miss...
Cameron.
Laura Cameron.
Next time I see you
out of uniform,
you'll be written up.
He always does that.
Don't let it get to you.
How? That man is awful.
Ugh. Tell me about it.
Six hours of World War II
stories to look forward to.
Remind me to kill Dean
next time I see him.
You're jeopardizing
the life of every living being
on this planet!
Whoa.
It's murder
on a worldwide scale!
I mean, when are you people
gonna realize
that nuclear weapons are
nothing but a death sentence
for the human race?!
Sir! You need to calm down.
You need to get your hands
off me, flyboy!
Sorry about this,
congressman.
We're gonna take care
of this right away.
It's okay, captain.
Let him talk.
It's a free country.
Well, actually,
I'm the first officer.
Uh, Ted Vanderway. We met
at, uh, midtown fund-raiser.
Of course.
Good to see you again.
Yes.
What are you, the President
of his fan club?
Sir, you need to take
your seat.
Hey, Maggie,
get this guy off of me.
Wait, you know this guy?
Stay here and don't move,
don't talk,
and if possible,
don't even breathe.
Mags, come on.
Do you know who that was?
You're talking
and breathing.
Christopher Rawlings...
Congressman warmonger himself.
So?
So he's probably on his way
to the symposium.
This is our big chance.
Your chance to be
the nice, respectful passenger
you promised to be.
- But I d...
- No "buts."
For once in your life, Sam,
just try to fit in.
You mean like you?
I am my principles, Maggie.
I can't separate that
from who I am.
Yep.  That was
my 44th mission
in my P-38 Lightning.
That little gem of a plane
was practically a part of me.
They don't make 'em like that
anymore.
All this... clutter.
No maneuverability.
Anyway, the frogs were
hunkered down outside of Bayeux,
and only the jerries
were on the road.
So... if something moves, we're
supposed to just light it up.
Coffee, gentlemen?
Oh, bless you.
I'll let you know when
coffee is served. Dismissed.
Um...
Scoot, missy.
That'll be all.
So anyway, I spotted
this convoy of Jerry trucks,
and I'm thinking to myself,
hey, this is my lucky day.
I'm gonna take 'em all out.
I can't believe
we're hooking.
We're not...
We're not "hooking."
W...
Playing hooky.
What you just said
means something else entirely.
What did I say?
It involves
charging by the hour.
Oh! Uh, no.
Ahem. The apples
look beautiful.
Yeah. Mcintosh.
My mom's favorite.
We'll bring her a dozen.
- Your mother?
- Yeah.
No, I thought
we were going flying.
We are.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Crop duster belongs
to my father.
He keeps it behind the barn.
I'm going to meet
your parents?
It's no big deal.
We always had people
stopping by...
Friends, neighbors.
My high school baseball team
practically lived there.
Oh, Dean, I'm not sure.
Isn't this
a little different?
It'll be fun.
You know, we'll have lunch,
exchange pleasantries.
And then...
We'll fly.
Congressman Rawlings,
I am so sorry about
what happened with that man.
Oh, it's okay. Everyone's
entitled to an opinion,
even if
it's completely wrong.
Well, please allow me
to offer you a free drink,
courtesy of Pan Am.
I thought
they were already free.
But this one's
coming from me.
Well, I wish I could, but, uh,
it'll put me right to sleep.
Big speech tomorrow.
The World Atomic Symposium?
You've heard of it?
You'd be surprised
at the things I've heard of.
Well, I don't doubt that.
I bet you've got a few surprises
under that cute blue hat.
I'll get it.
This is Laura.
Right away, captain.
Captain Bligh wants his coffee.
Do you want me
to bring it?
No, thank you.
I can do it.
You wanted coffee, captain?
Oh, thank you, Lori.
It's Laura, sir.
Uh, would you
do me a favor, honey?
Uh, this damn air speed gauge
is fogged up.
Uh, would you mind
cleaning it for me?
Of course not.
Aah!
God! What the hell?!
Oh! I-I am so sorry.
It... it must be the turbulence.
You get her off
of my flight deck right now,
Vanderway.
You should probably, um...
What an idiot.
Laura, why are you hiding
back here?
We're ready to go.
Me? I'm... I'm not hiding.
Miss Cameron!
You think
you're pretty clever
with that little coffee stunt,
huh?
No, sir, I didn't...
Well, I hope
the London base manager
appreciates
your sense of humor
because I'm filing paperwork
for disciplinary action.
Captain, I'm sorry if I...
Oh, you'll be sorry,
all right.
Captain.
Can I speak to you
for a moment?
Not now.
Well, actually, sir,
it has to be right now.
Please tell me
it was piping hot.
Oh, you're my hero.
Shh!
What is Ted doing?
Oh, probably making it worse.
What happened?
What did you say to him?
Oh, I told him he could
take that paperwork
and shove it right up
his cargo hold.
You didn't.
No,
but it's taken care of.
Ted, thank you.
No, thank you.
After that little trick
you pulled,
that blowhard didn't say a word
for the last thousand miles.
No, I really owe you.
Well, that's good to hear, uh,
'cause I'm ready to collect.
Oh, please.
I'm not a total cad
all the time.
Then what is it?
It's not a what, it's a who...
Amanda Hartford Mason.
You want my help
with a girl?
Uh-huh.
Let's move a little faster,
ladies.
This place is crawling
with lobby lizards.
I've never seen so many
in one place.
It's the uniform.
It turns grown men to mush.
Seems to cause
memory problems, too.
They all forget
they're married.
Laura, grab my key for me.
I need to make a call.
Pardon me.
Would you happen to have
a cigarette?
I seem to have left mine
in the other jacket.
Yes, of course.
Very good. Thank you.
Okay. I've done my job.
Hold on, Kate.
What?
Richard said I give you
the case and I'm through.
I'm through.
Hardly.
The mission's changed.
You're just getting started.
There's been a hitch, Kate.
I did what I was asked.
Whatever the hitch is,
it's not my problem.
You don't understand.
This is an urgent situation.
The list was to be delivered to
the Soviets three days from now.
Instead, they're coming for it
tonight.
I've had to improvise.
I need you to be my decoy.
Decoy for what?
A certain jeweler.
Cyrus Bolger.
In his possession
is the actual list,
not this fake
that you've supplied to us.
Our people are going to
break into his safe
and switch the two.
And how exactly do you suppose
I decoy this...
Mr. Bolger?
Simply by being yourself...
A Pan Am stewardess.
I, however...
Will be Mr. Caldwell
down from Liverpool...
Here to close
a business deal...
And get reacquainted
with my favorite stewardess.
Well, at least
I'm your favorite.
Caldwell likes
to buy expensive baubles
for his paramour.
That's our entree
to the jeweler.
I told you,
I'm not interested.
Understood,
but you may be familiar with
some of the names on that list.
Do I have your interest now?
Who's on that list?
Bridget Pierce.
Among others.
And Niko Lonza?
He's at the top.
Let me walk you
through the mission.
This is it.
Don't worry.
You look great.
Nobody looks great
after a hundred miles
in a convertible.
They are gonna love you.
- I just wasn't expecting to...
- Hey...
I didn't tell you
because I didn't want
to make a big deal out of it.
Okay?
Dean!
Bill, it's Dean!
Hiya, mom. Hi.
Oh. Oh.
Mm.
Bill, they're here.
I can see 'em, Marjorie.
I've got eyes.
Ohh.
And this must be Bridget.
No.
N...
Uh...  Mom, pop,
this is, uh, this is Colette.
Oh, dear. Colette.
Well...
Mr. and Mrs. Lowrey, it's
a pleasure to meet you both.
You're French?
Oui.
Ohh.
Colette and I work
together.
She's, uh,
she's a Pan Am stewardess.
Oh.
So what happened
to Bridget?
Well, come on in, you two.
Let's have some lunch.
Yes.
Ohh. Amanda Mason was
the bane of my adolescence.
This girl was a cross
between Grace Kelly
and... and an ice cube.
She wouldn't give you
the time of day?
She wouldn't give me
the month.
She wouldn't give me the year,
for that matter.
A-anyway, our
parents are best friends,
weekends in East Hampton
a-and all that,
and Amanda, ohh,
went out of her way
to make my life
absolutely miserable.
She was mean to you?
No, worse. She ignored me.
And you're going out
with this girl why?
Sneak attack
from the parents.
"Oh, Edward. You're going to be
in London at the same time."
Blah, blah, blah.
"Oh, what
a wonderful coincidence."
Your parents call you
Edward?
When they're trying
to ruin my life,
which is always.
- Okay.
- What do you want me to do?
I want you to be
my girlfriend.
I made a reservation at 7:30
at the hotel dining room.
At 8:00, you come over to
our table, steaming mad at me,
which shouldn't be much
of a stretch for you,
but you gotta come at me
with both barrels, you know?
Hey, you can wear
that little black number,
the one
that shows off your...
O-okay, Ted, I agreed
to this favor reluctantly.
You can't tell me
what to wear.
Fair enough.
You could just tell
your parents no.
Way too complicated.
But having me pretend to be your
deranged girlfriend makes sense?
Yeah.
Glad you see it my way.
Sam, what are you
doing here?
I thought you'd be filling
Molotov cocktails by now.
No, the only cocktail
I'm filling...
Emptying...
Is right here.
What happened
to ban the bomb UK?
Ohh. Arrested.
Locked up.
Thrown in the pokey.
Ohh. Sam, I'm so sorry.
Well, it's a good thing
you weren't with them.
How can you say that?
I should have been with them.
You wanted to get arrested?
If that's
what was necessary.
You can't effect change
without personal sacrifice.
How is going to jail
the answer?
You talk about seeing
the world to change it, Maggie,
but you're
just another tourist.
I am not.
You meet important people
in your job.
When was the last time
you talked to them...
Really talked to them?
I talk to people all the time.
Sure,
to take a lunch order.
You have a captive audience
at 35,000 feet,
and you won't take
advantage of it.
You could make a difference...
But you don't.
Paris must be the most
beautiful city in the world.
What was it like
growing up there?
Well, actually, mom,
she's, uh,
she's from
the countryside, so...
So, yeah, not so
different from here.
Oh.
Yeah.
And how long have you two
been flying together?
Well, we've been on
the same crew for a few months.
Yeah.
She... she speaks
four different languages...
Ohh.
And she makes, uh,
this, um, it's a tart...
Tarte tatin?
Tarte tatin.
- It's, uh...
- French.
It's... yeah. I-it tastes exactly
like your apple cobbler.
So good.
Uh, h-hold on here.
I don't want to point out
the elephant in the room,
but I have to ask.
What the hell happened
to Bridget?
- Bill.
- Dad.
Nothing personal,
Colette...
But the last time my son was here,
he told us he was getting
engaged to a girl named Bridget.
Hey, dad. Can we talk
about this later?
It's always later with you.
You didn't call us
when you left the Air Force.
You didn't tell us
when you took the Pan Am job,
and now you're jetting around
God-knows-where.
H-how are we supposed to know
what's going on with you?
I'm here now.
Isn't that good enough?
On what occasion?
You two getting engaged?
Bill, please.
Mnh. No. Wh...
Are you expecting?
- No.
- Bill!
- Come on.
- As I live and breathe!
I'm sorry.
Would you excuse me?
Oh.
What are you thinking?
Colette, listen.
You gotta...
understand about my parents.
Take me home, Dean.
Come on. I thought you wanted
to learn how to fly.
I think I've learned enough
for one day.
I'm sorry. I'm...
You know, I never really
expected today
to go like this.
Well, how did you think
it would go?
You would pretend
I was Bridget
until your parents
figured it out?
No, I-I figured
they'd meet you,
and... and they'd think
you're fantastic,
like I do, and...
And the embarrassment
of breaking up
with your fiancee
would be ignored?
Okay. I messed up.
I'm sorry.
Can we start over?
No. It's not that simple.
Look, I realize how awkward
that was back there,
but you gotta understand that
that has nothing to do with us.
Us?  I don't think
there is an "us," Dean.
- You're still in love with Bridget.
- No.
- Yes.
Yes. That's why you didn't
tell your parents.
You still imagine
she'll show up one day
like nothing happened,
like she never left you.
And you're so sure that
every guy that you fall for
is gonna up and leave you
for another woman.
I'm not going to let
myself get hurt again.
So then why would you
kiss me in Miami?
Honestly, I don't know.
Just take me home.
- No. No.
- Please take me home.
- No.
- Why... why not?
Because you're asking...
Let me go.
You're asking
the wrong damn question.
You want to know why
I never told my parents
that I broke up
with Bridget.
Well, for the same reason that
I never brought her up here
to meet them.
There's just something
about her that wasn't real,
but after two weeks,
I brought you.
So I'm real?
Yeah.
No, Dean.
This is real.
Dean.
They're beautiful.
Yes.
Well, just last week,
the duchess of argyll was in,
admiring
the very same pieces.
- The duchess?
- See, I do have good taste.
Well, it might be
a little excessive, though.
Oh.
Darling, after all I do
for you, aren't I worth it?
Well, I suppose they do go
with your eyes.
Can I try
the diamond chips again?
Of course, madam.
There we are.
Ohh.
Oh, it's perfect.
Of course, it'll have
to be sized for me.
Oh, we can do that for you.
It... it will be ready
tomorrow morning.
Oh, no.
I'm a stewardess for Pan Am,
and our flight leaves
early tomorrow.
Perhaps you could bring it
by our hotel
later this evening,
say, 8:00?
If it wouldn't be
too much of an imposition.
Of course not.
Ohh!
You are so good to me.
Mm.
Wow. Laura, you look...
Wait. You can't meet
the ice princess
with your tie all cockeyed.
Thanks.
Now don't forget... 8:00.
You come marching in,
and you make a scene.
Give me full-on Liz Taylor.
"Cleopatra"
or "Butterfield 8"?
Whatever's crazier.
I could throw a drink on you.
Pretty good at that.
I don't know why
I'm so nervous about this.
I'm a Pan Am pilot,
for God sake.
If I can make 200,000 pounds
of metal fly,
I can handle a half-hour
of misery, right?
For the record,
you're not just a pilot.
You're a decent man,
and she is going to regret
the day she ever let you
get away.
You should go.
Congressman Rawlings?
I'm Maggie Ryan,
your Pan Am stewardess.
Of course.
How could I forget?
Well, I wanted
to apologize again
for the trouble
on the flight.
That's not necessary,
miss Ryan.
Maggie.
Maggie. It comes
with the territory.
Can't have a circus
without a clown or two.
Congressman, if you don't
mind my saying so,
your position
on nuclear weapons...
It's wrongheaded.
We need a testing ban.
Well, that's an awfully
simplistic view of things.
So you're saying that 11 of
our greatest atomic scientists,
including Einstein,
are simplistic?
Einstein didn't have to man
a sentry post in Korea
and stare down
the Chinese army.
And you did?
Yes.
Look, I support regulation,
but banning
nuclear weapons testing
is just plain naive.
Well, I bet I can change
your mind.
No, you can't...
But I'll give you
three flights of stairs to try.
Okay. Every
industrialized nation known...
Take the Cuban missile crisis.
Take it where?
The perfect example of the need
for better dialogue
between the superpowers.
Dialogue?
Have you met Khrushchev?
No.
Arrogant. Lots of ear hair.
Right. Of course.
You know Khrushchev.
Well... my point was... is...
You realize
you're in my room.
Well, that's 'cause I haven't
finished yet.
What's this?
Cognac. V.S.O.P.
I know what it is.
I'm not here
for a nightcap.
Indulge me.
You're not going to make
your argument with this.
And you're not going
to make yours without it.
Enough of my job.
Tell me about traveling
the world.
You must have seen
some pretty exotic places.
Sure. Potsdam, Yalta,
Hiroshima...
- What was that?
- What?
You snorted.
No, I didn't.
That was definitely
a snort.
Uh...  A-a chortle.
Maybe a chuckle.
You're not taking me
seriously, are you?
You've made it this far,
and I haven't called security.
Teddy?
Teddy.
Uh...
Oh, it's been...
Ooh. Years.
Forever.
Uh, yeah.
Look at you.
Huh?
You've got shoulders.
Oh, yeah.
Well, once I learned
scrawny was no longer
in style.
It's so good
to see you, Teddy.
Yeah.
You always were so funny.
Oh.  Yeah.
Well...
Now I'm funny with shoulders,
apparently.
Yeah.
Um, uh, please.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
- We've been over this.
- I know what to do.
A half-hour. That's all the time
I need to switch the lists.
And this is it for me?
I do this, and I'm out?
Yes. Yes, you are out.
There he is, right on time.
He's on his way up to you.
- Kate.
-  What?
Stick to the mission.
I know how to be
a stewardess.
I mean about us, our story.
Don't worry, Spencer.
I'll be fine.
Spencer?
I gave you a first name.
Hello?
Be careful, Kate.
He's here. Go.
Good evening.
I have the bracelet.
Oh, come in. It's so kind
of you to bring it here.
Diamonds are expensive,
but service is priceless.
I can't wait to try it on.
Well, the sizing was
a little more difficult
than I thought, but I think
you will like it.
Oh, very nice accommodations
for a stewardess.
Yes. I don't usually have
a room this big,
but Mr. Caldwell...
Well, he insists on the best.
And you deserve it, right?
Where is your Mr. Caldwell?
Oh, he called.
He's running late.
Oh.
Well, don't worry.
He's coming with a checkbook.
Yes, well, I don't have
much time myself.
Uh, let me show you.
Kennedy said the test-ban treaty
was only a first step.
First step to surrender.
- You're a cynic.
- Lighter?
If anyone's a cynic,
it's Kennedy,
placating the left for '64.
Well, at least J.F.K. has
the right idea.
And that is?
Relaxation of tensions.
Mutual disarmament?
A truce.
What did you think
of the flight?
Takeoff was good...
But the landing was better.
You were right, you know?
About what?
Back when we were
on the ground in Haiti...
I felt like I was coming
apart at the seams.
You were wonderful.
I didn't think we were gonna
make it out of there.
But we did.
Well, you were right
about rescuing the girl.
I never would have
forgiven myself.
You don't need to say this.
You saved us.
Yeah, but you saved me.
Does this mean I earned
my wings?
Not yet.
Do you remember
that summer?
Ohh. Pfft.
Block island...
And your dad's crazy clambake?
Oh, yeah. You used to wear that,
um, uh, flowery headband.
- Yeah.
- How do you remember that?
Wow. You were right about the lobster.
I think I have order envy.
We can share.
No. No, no, no.
I'll suffer through
my bad decision.
If I can make it
through that clambake,
I-I can survive this.
Well, if you do, I think
you might deserve a reward.
- Oh. Oh, yeah?
- What kind of reward?
The kind that comes wrapped
in a flowery headband.
Really?
Well, well, well.
Look what the cat dragged in.
Captain Thornton.
Oh. Dennis, okay?
So you
and, uh, Vanderway, huh?
Me and Vanderway what?
Oh. You don't have
to hide it.
He told me all about
you two.
Oh, he did?
I'd say
you're pretty lucky.
Not every fella talks
that way about their girl.
Really? Um...
What did he... say?
That you were wonderful,
smart, funny, kindhearted.
He said that you were
the best thing
that's ever happened
to him,
and he didn't want to see
you get into trouble.
Ted said all that about me?
Yep.
Like I said, lucky girl.
Oh, cookies.
You know, my flight back
isn't for a few days.
There's a lot we could do
between now and then.
Yeah, if I didn't have
a date with a bunch
of stuffy nuclear scientists.
I'd love to see you
in action.
Well, haven't you already?
- Ooh! Come on.
- I want to see your speech.
No. No, no. You don't...
You don't want to do that.
Oh, sure I do. Where is it?
Maggie, wait.
Chris, you can't say all this.
Well, I told you
you weren't going to like it.
You don't honestly believe
all this?
You're damn right, I do.
Give... come on.
It's practically fascism!
Mussolini was
a childhood hero.
Give me the... give me the sp...
What are you doing?
Saving you from yourself.
Maggie!
Come on.
Open the door.
Almost there.
Is that smoke?
Maggie, that speech is
government property.
Not anymore.
This is the right thing
to do, Chris. Believe me.
In a couple of years,
you will thank me for it.
Yeah? Well, I don't need
those pages.
I have a photographic memory.
It's all up here.
Oh, my God!
Yeah, I know.
It's a real gift.
Oh, my God.
It's lovely.
Uh, we'll have to go back to the shop.
We'll have Mr. Caldwell meet us
there to pay for the bracelet.
The shop? No, wait. Uh, he's
going to be here any minute.
You do hear the fire alarm,
don't you?
Uh, it's probably a false alarm.
It happens here all the time.
Nevertheless, I'm going
to need that bracelet back.
Hold on.
You can't expect me
to leave it with you.
It's my bracelet!
- Not until it's been paid for!
- I...
I... no. Please.
No, please.
Mr. Bolger, wait.
What? No.
- Uh... no.
- Please, Mr. Bolger!
Ohh.
Mr. Bolger, please wait!
Ted! I am so sorry.
Laura.
What... what happened to you
downstairs?
Um, nothing.
I-I didn't even make it
to the table,
and both of you were gone.
- Well...
- Teddy, what's going on?
Um, I-it, uh,
it's a fire alarm, I think.
Um, we should...
We should get downstairs.
Uh, excuse me. Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Kate?
Oh.
Maggie. Maggie, wait.
Chris, can we just forget
this ever happened?
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
Because you are,
without a doubt,
the most reckless, pigheaded,
craziest person I've ever met.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
I, uh, I kinda like it.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com