Finland 1944
He's my son!
- Erik!
- Mommy!
Westchester, NY 1944
Mother?
What were you...
I thought you're a burglar.
I didn't meant to scare you, darling.
I was just getting a snack.
Go back to bed.
What's the matter?
Go on, back to bed.
I'll make you hot chocolate.
Who are you?
And what have you done
with my mother?
My mother has never set
her foot in the kitchen in her life.
And she certainly,
never made me hot chocolate.
Unless you can order me, made to do it.
You're not..
Scared of me?
I was believed I can't be
the only one in the world.
The only pass I used..
Different.
And here you are!
Charles Xavier.
Raven.
You hungry?
And alone?
Take whatever you want.
We've got lot of foody.
You don't have to steal.
In fact..
You'll never have to steal again.
You most understand, Erik...
These Nazis, I do not like them.
Genes, the most important thing, right?
But thier chains?
Blue eyes? Blonde hair?
Sounds silly.
Taste the chocolate.
Delicious.
Would you?
I want to see my mother.
Genes are the key to the door
leading into a new era, Erik.
A new future for humanity.
Evoulution.
You know what I mean?
I'm not asking for much.
A small coin, it's nothing
compared to the huge gates.
Right?
Yeah!
I've tried.
Sorry doctor.
I can not..
I do not..
It's impossible.
The only thing I can say in favor of the Nazis,
is that thier methods are producing results.
I'm sorry, Erik.
Mommy!
My darling..
How are you?
Not this is what we will do.
I count to 3..
And you'll move the coin.
If you don't move the coin,
I'll pull the trigger.
Do you understand?
One..
- Mommy?
- You can do it.
Two..
It's okay.
Three!
Excellent!
Great!
Unbelievable, Erik!
We have opened your gift with anger.
Anger.
Pain.
You and I..
Are going to have a lot of fun.
X-men: First Class
Subtitle by: Ballen Abdulkarim
Geneva, Switzerland, 1961
Oxford University, England
Heterochromia.
A gentleman would at least
offer finest drink first.
Norman!
My habitual beer for me,
and a Brandy for the lady, please.
How did you know that?
Lucky guess.
Name is Xavier..
Charles Xavier.
- How about you?
- Emmy.
Heterochromia, is a reference to your eyes,
which I have to say...
Astounding!
One green, one blue...
It's a mutation.
It's a very groovy a mutation,
I've could use it for you, Emmy.
You are a mutated.
First you're proposing a girl,
and then you go to deform it.
How is that seduction
technique working for you?
I'll tell you tomorrow morning.
No, no.. Seriously, you must've knocked it.
Mutation tooks us from
a single cell's organisms,
to be leaded down former
to reproductive life on this planet.
Infinite form of variation
with each generation..
All through mutation.
Then, let's revel with that one.
Mutions and proud.
Cin-cin, hey!
Hi, I guess I have
to buy my own drink.
I'm sorry.
One Cola!
Charles was just telling me that, I'm like one of
the first sea-creatures with one increased leg.
And kinda bit sexy.
I'm sorry.
This is my sister, Raven.
Hi, Emmy.
And, what do you studding?
Waitressing.
Oh, look!
You have heterochromia too!
- She what?
- Look at here eye!
Right!
Raven, get your coat, please!
Don't talk to me!
You did that on purpose.
I did not!
Why would I do it on purpose?
You know I can't control it some times.
If I was stressed or tired...
It's been a qutie good job, right now!
Mutions and proud!
As not like a pretty mutation
or invisible ones, like yours.
If you're a freak,
you better hide!
You are being ridiculous.
I didn't meant to sound like an old faulter.
Which you are.
Sometimes.
But we talked about this, Raven.
Small slate postpone is nothing,
a big one does not barred thinking about.
Mutate and proud.
Mutate and proud?!
If only..
Would you date me?
Of course, I would.
Any young man
will be lucky to have you.
You're astounding.
Looking like this?
I... You.. What?
Blue?
You're my oldest friend.
I'm your only friend.
Thank you for that!
Well?
I incapable thinking of you as like that.
I feel responsible for you.
Anything else would just feel wrong.
- And.. But, if you did not know?
- Unfortunately, I do know you.
God! What's got into you?
You got something with your look!
I'm sleepy.
Would you read for me?
No! I have my tests coming.
I have to study.
To Homo Neanderthalensis,
has mutant cousin, Homo Sapiens..
It wasn't an aberration.
Peacful cohabitation, if ever existed.
Was short lived.
Homo Schmidt, without an exception,
the arrival of the mutation
human species in their regions,
was followed by an immediate
extinction of the less evolved kill.
Possession of this gold is illegal.
- Do you want me to call the police?
- Let's not play this game.
So, where did you get it from?
From the others.
They recommended I come to your bank.
Understood.
You know our terms, sir?
Yes.
And you should know mine.
This gold is all that is left of my people.
It was thier property.
Taken out of thier teeth.
This is blood money.
And you can help me find the
bastards responsible for it.
Don't touch the button.
I need Schmidt.
Klaus Schmidt.
Where is he?
Our clients leave no addresses.
- We don't..
- Not a bank?
Metal fillings, huh?
Not gold.
Worried that someone might steal them?
Argentina..
Schmidt is in Argentina!
Villa Gesell!
I beg you!
Thank you.
I'm pleased to kill you.
So, remember..
If you warn him about me..
I will find you.
Las Vegas, Nevada
Another day at the office.
Is that Colonel Hendry?
You mean our guy?
Yeah.
Yes it is!
And those are three Mafia bosses, the Italian
Ambassador and the senior of Lockheed.
They're may be a Communists?
What's that club?
There must be something else.
Do you see that?
Hello, girls!
Wow! Yeah!
Nice!
What.. What're you doing?
Using some equipment,
that CIA didn't give me.
Saty close.
- Are you Hendry?
- Yes, ma'am!
Emma Frost,
Sebastian Shaw's associater.
And where is Mr. Shaw?
We're having a party.
And amusing entertainment.
Come with me.
Hoo-hoo!
- Hello, beautiful. How're you?
- Hi, baby? You wanna have fun in quiet place?
I'm so sorry!
I've been booked by Colonel Hendry.
Excuse me!
Make sure, we can't get you a refill, Bob?
No.
So, I heard you blocked a proposal
to possession the Jupiter missiles in Turkey.
I expected you reconsider.
We've have this conversation.
You'll put our missiles in Turkey,
or anywhere that close to Russia.
And you're looking at war.
Nuclear war!
I do not ask for favors, Colonel.
I express my expectations.
So..
Let me say it again..
I expect you reconsider.
The only thing I will reconsider..
Is having another glass of
that delicious Champagne.
What the hell did you put in my drink?
You think you would running?
Hiding?
We've found you, Hendry.
There is not a fortress in the world,
that could keep us out.
Isn't she, Bob?
Genetic mutation.
The evolution of the human gene!
Where is Azazel?
We do not want the colonel to delay.
Forward.
Missiles in Turkey
send a very clear message.
We ever decide to fire them, the Russianly
warning system will not have time to kick in!
It's better be important, MacTaggert.
Wow, wow, wow.. Slow down!
Have you smoked any funny cigarettes?
People do not disappear!
Colonel Hendry was there.
He was there Micon.
In the Hellfire Club.
Colonel Hendry?
I agree with you general!
I reconsidered by possession, and know
I believe we should put Jupiter missiles in Turkey
Colonel Hendry is here.
So unless he naturaly traveled
3000 miles in the last 10 minutes.
So, listen to me..
I suggest, that you stop wasting my time.
Looks like Hendry wants
to start World War III.
I have better things to do right now, MacTaggert!
Sarge, I..
God!
You lost your mind?
So, now what?
We'll find an expert in genetics mutations.
Professor of genetic,
Charles Francis Xavier.
So, how is your feels to be a Professor?
No, don't call me that.
You don't get to be cool as professor,
until you have the teaching possession
I know, but..
No, don't say that!
You say Let's go and have a drink
- Let's go and have a drink
- One little.
Villa Gesell, Argentina
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
Wow, the heat!
Beer, please.
CASPARTINA
Dutchest beer.
Of course.
Yes, it's Bitburger.
Like it?
Could not be better.
What brought you to Argentina?
Climate.
I live the weather.
I am a tailor.
Have been my whole life.
My father sewed the best
costumes in Dusseldorf.
My parents are from Dusseldorf.
What are their names?
They had not names.
Their names were selected..
Breeders..
And tailors.
Blood and honor.
Why prefer to lose again?
We carried out the orders..
Hence and blood.
Don't move, freak!
Come on, shoot!
Who are you?
Let's just say,
I'm Frankenstein's monster.
And I'm looking for my creator.
Drink. Drink. Drink!
Yeah!
Come on.
So proud of you!
I need another drink.
And you need another Cola.
Congratulations, Professor!
Thank you very much.
It's much harder than it looks like.
No! I mean on your presentation.
Were you in my presentation?
How nice of you!
Thank you very much!
- Moira MacTaggert.
- Charles Xavier.
Do you have minute?
For a pretty little beenig,
MCI-1 gene, I have 5.
I say, MCI-1.
You would say, golden hair!
It's a mutation.
It's very groovy mutation.
Mutation, right?
Two kinds from single cell organisms,
to the dominant form..
You know, this routine make
over greate with colleges..
But, I'm here on business.
What?
I really need your help!
Wa..
The kind of mutations that you
were talking about in your dissert..
I need to know if they
maight've already happened.
On people live today.
Professor?
I think we should just talk
when you're foresighted.
Do you have any time tomorrow?
Something tells me, you already
know the answer of your question.
This is very important to me.
If I can help you, I will do my all best.
Thank you!
Miami, Florida
Still drinking Champagne, Bob?
I will pass.
Okay, will.. So much for the pleasantries.
I was wondering..
Who you told about our
little arrangement?
No one.
He's telling the truth.
Good!
Well, I guess we done here.
Let's rap things up, shall we?
Oh, I knew better than to trust you!
You let me walk out of here,
with my money.
Or I will pull this pin,
and we all die!
Go ahead.
Pull it!
I'll do it, I swear the God!
No, you won't.
But I will!
You're one of them?
Very astound of you Colonel Hendry.
You wanna guess what I can do?
I've got the power to absorb energy..
Keeps me young.
That's the boring part.
The fun stuff is what I can do
with your absorb, got it?
- CIA headquarters, Langley, Virginia
- The advance of nuclear age..
Might have accelerated
mutation's progress.
in the vigils with extraordinary
abilities may already be among us.
Thank you very much!
MacTaggert, you really think that
some crack points of scientists...
Is gonna make me believe in
sparkly dames and vanishing men?
You just bought yourself one-way
ticket back to the tipping cool.
This meeting is over.
Uh.. Please, sit down,
Agent MacTaggert
Hasn't really expected you to believe me.
Even that all you think about in
regarding the presentation,
what thought of it as a pie in
serving at the cafeteria.
It's apple and pecans.
I have been entirely honest with you enough,
I'm sorry.
You see...
One of the many spectacular things
that mind mutation allows me to do..
Is that I can read your mind!
I've seen this before in a magic show.
Are you gonna ask us to think of
a number between 1 and 10, now?
No, Mr. Stryker. It's old.
I could ask you about your son, William.
That you're thinking about.
Which is very nice.
But, I think I would to ask you
about the Jupiter missiles..
That America currently placing it, in Turkey.
He's a goddamn spy!
You brought a goddmaned spy!
I will not.. I would never do that!
How is that for a magic trick?
Best than I ever seen!
I want them out of here.
And lock down,
untile I can figure out what to do.
My facility has a space.
I take them.
I can't believe this.
I didn't thought the director
of CIA having a commissar.
We sould be going after Shaw, right now!
But instead that up there, worring
about the wrong mutions.
What we gonna do, Loaven?
Loaven?
Loaven, what's wrong with you?
Absolutely nothing. I'm just frozen him for
a moment, because I'd like to talk to you.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm as interested in this
Sebastian Shaw as you are.
And if you still want my help, meet me
in the third floor, at the parking garage.
I've always known adoring people like you out there.
I've been the laughing stop in
this agency for years, but I knew it
- You're gonna love my consultancy...
- That's gonna have to wait.
Why?
Agent MacTaggert doesn't leave
Sebastian Shaw, if we don't move now!
Parley, we're gonna lose it.
What?
Not only can he read minds,
he can commudicate as well.
Moira and I just had
a loving conversation.
Yes, we did!
That's incredible!
But, but.. I can not take you anywhere else
without the permissions from upstairs.
Would you like to see one more magic show?
- Okay!
- Get in the car.
Good idea!
Subtitle by; Ballen Abdulkarim
He's here to kill you.
What kind of greeting is this..
After so many years?!
Emma...
We won't harm our kind.
Uh..
Now it's a party!
This is the U.S. Coast Guard.
Do not attempt to move your ambassador!
Stay where you are!
Thay have a telepath!
I've lost Shaw!
I've lo.. I've lost Shaw!
There's something blocked me.
This never happened to me before.
I think, there is someone
like me on that ship!
Like you?
I.. I'm sorry.
A telepath.
This is incredible.
I can actually feel that inside my mind!
I'm very sorry, but I don't think I would be so
much helpful tonight. Here you're on your own.
- Oh, my God!
- Jesus!
Get inside!
Wait, stop, stop..
What?
God!
Charles!
You okay?
There's someone else there!
There!
Time to go.
Let go!
You've to let 'em go!
You could have to kill him, there's
someone else in the water! help him!
Let it go!
You have to let is go!
I know what this means to you,
but you're going to die!
Please, Erik!
Calm your mind.
Get of me!
Calm down!
Just breathe!
We're here!
Who are you?
My name is Charles Xavier.
You were in my head..
How did you do that?
You have your tricks,
I have mine.
I'm like you.
Just calm your mind!
I thought I was alone.
You're not alone.
Erik...
Secret CIA base
Welcome to my facility.
My mission has been to
investigate the application..
Of paranormal powers
in military defense.
Or offence.
This guy, Shaw.. Schmidt..
Whatever you want to call him..
He's working with the Russians.
We might need your help to stop him.
Fabulous!
So we would to be the CIA's
new mutation vision, yes?
Something like that.
So super sonic!
Most advance plane ever built.
You should see it in real life.
It's incredible!
Hank, these are the special new crew,
that I was telling you about.
This is Hank McCoy.
The one of our most
talented young researchers.
How wonderful!
Another mutate, already here!
Why didn't you say?
Say what?
Because you don't know.
I am so sorry!
Terribly sorry!
Hank?
You didn't ask,
so I didn't tell.
So, your mutation is what?
You're super smart?
I'll say, Hank graduated Harvard at age 15.
I wish that to tell it was.
You're among friends now, Hank.
You can show of.
Splendid!
Sorry!
You're amazing!
Really?
The presence of U.S. missiles in Turkey..
represents an unprecedented threat
to the people of Soviet union.
Warn of Russian for Minister in Gromyko,
Earlier today.
But he was quick to insiste..
the Russians will not be the first
to initiate any military action.
Yeah, we'll fix that soon
as we get to Russia.
Unless the CIA finds us first.
I'll take care of them too.
If that telepath inside your head,
it wouldn't be much fun as I am.
Already here, my love!
Russians..
Made me this!
So..
What am I thinking?
I don't know!
I was thinking that you're the most
exquisite thing I ever seen in my life!
And this needs ice.
Bring me some.
I.. I promised myself, I'll find the cure.
Ever since I was a little boy.
You have no idea what I give to feel..
- Normal.
Charles, has never understood.
He's different, but..
He's never had to hide.
Hey, this serum that you're making,
it doesn't affect abilities, right?
Just the appearance.
Normalize, is it?
Yeah.
Do you think, it would work on me?
I can look into it, of you like?
It's the least I can do, after asking you to
come down here was such a wierd request.
I've to admit, usually some guys
ask me out, they don't after my blood!
Sorry!
I didn't attend to be forward,
I was just.. I was excited!
You know, the nature of your mutation..
If any genes hold the key
to change you appearance..
It's yours.
Hank, you're being forward,
That's kindda what I meant.
No!
I'm just, sorry if I was.
And I'm sorry that you are.
Go ahead,
take the blood!
Sorry!
Does that hurt you?
Kinky!
By the way..
If I ever liked you,
I wouldn't change a thing!
What I know about you,
I'm surprised to you stay this low!
What you know about me?
Everything!
Then you know to
stay out of my head!
I'm sorry, Erik.
But I've seen what Shaw did to you.
I felt your agony.
I can help you.
I don't need your help.
Don't kid yourself.
You needed my help last night
It's not just me you walking away from.
Here you have the chance to be part of
something much bigger than yourself.
I won't stop of knowing.
I could.
But I won't.
Shaw has got firends.
He could do use some.
Hank turned that radar
installation into a transmitter.
It's designed to amplify brain waves,
So it could hands your telepathic powers.
Help us find other mutate
for our division.
What if they don't
wanna be found by you?
Erik!
You decided to stay!
If new a species has
been discoverd...
That would be bought by your kind.
Charles and I find the mutations.
No suits.
Firstable, that's my machine out there.
Secondable, it's much importantly,
this is Charles's decision
Charles's find the CIA being
involved, ain't that right?
No!
I'm sorry, but..
I'm with Erik.
We'll find them alone!
What if I say no?
Then good luck using your
installations without me!
- I.. Call it Cerebro.
- You..?
- Is it in the spanish for Brain?
- Yes.
Okay, so, the electrodes connect
Charles the transmitter on the roof.
When he picks up a, mutant..
His brain sends a signal for the relay.
And then the..
Coordinates in the locations will appear out here.
You designed this?
Yeah!
- What an adorable land rates, Charles!
- Do not spoil the moment, Erik.
I've been in liberate,
and I know one when I see one.
Okay, great!
Are you sure we can't
change shave your hair?
Don't touch my hair!
It's working!
That daddy O,
you'll get a private dance!
You guys know it's
double for both, right?
Will, that won't be necessary.
While I'm sure it will be magical..
We were thinking,
and we will show you ours.
If you show us yours.
Baby, that is not the way
it works around here!
More to you vicar?
I verify that for you!
Mu turn!
How would you like a job
when you get your clothes on?
Where to, fellas?
Richmond, Virginia.
Right! So you want, airport,
to station, what?
We were hoping you take us all the way!
That's a 6 hours drive!
That will give us much time to talk!
What the hell the government
wants from a guy like Alex Summers?
hope you not planning on
putting him with others.
First guy I ever meet when
actually prefer solitary can find.
Crazy, huh?
What?
You like fish, I like fish, too!
I wish I could buy sometime
to talk about it.
I'd like to go out with the fish.
This fish?
- Excuse me, I'm Erik Lehnsherr.
- Charles Xavier.
Go fuck yourself!
- There's nothing on radar?
- Nothing!
- Sonar?
- Neither!
Then we have a problem!
Beautiful.
Isn't it?
The reason we exist..
We are the children of the atom, my love!
We have a situation.
The telepath..
I shouldn't be able to feel no matter distances.
It's like he reaches..
Amplified.
They're recruiting.
You go on to Russia,
And I'll handle them.
There's so many other out there.
One hundred minds that I touched.
I could feel them.
Their isolations..
Their hops..
And ambitions.
I'll tell you, we'll start
something incredible thing, Erik.
We can help them.
Can we?
Identification, that's how it dones.
And ends will be rounded us.
Experiments of them,
are limited.
Not this time!
We have common enemies.
Shaw, the Russians...
- They need us.
- For now.
We should think of code names.
We are goverment agents now,
we should have secret code names.
I wanna be called Mystique.
Damn, I wanted to be called Mystique!
That's up, I called it!
Wow!
And I'm more mysterious than you!
Darwin, what about you?
Will, Darwin is already my nickname.
And you know..
Sort of fits.
Check this out!
Thank you.
Thank you!
What about you?
I'm going to be..
Banshee.
Why want be named after a willing spirit?
You might wanna cover your ears!
Your turn!
My, uhh...
Stage name is Angel.
Kindda fits.
You can fly?
Uh-Ha
And, uh..
Disgusting!
What's your name?
How about, Big Foot?
You know, they say
about guy, Big Feet..
And, uh..
Your too kindda small!
Okay, now!
Alex, what's your gift?
What can you do?
It's not the...
I just can't do it.
I can't to it in here.
Can you do it out there?
Would you do it there?
- Come on!
- Alex!
This is spirit!
Get down, when I tell you.
Get back!
Whatever!
You're kidding!
We've got in tell that Shaw is meeting
the Russian defense chief in Moscow.
Go ahead, say it!
I'm not here to say 'I told you so'.
You know why I'm here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Clearings to bring all new units.
Fight fire with fire.
Make sense.
Wait!
You're okay with this?
Sending a bunch of untraind,
unauthorized freaks?
These 'Freaks' are dedicated,
hard-working people!
Plane flies to Russia in a hour.
Telling you, these kids
are not ready for Shaw.
I think it's gonna surprise you,
an exceptional of bunch of young people.
What the hell?
Harder!
What are you doing?
Who destroyed the statue?
It was Alex!
No, Havok..
We've to call him Havok.
That's his name now.
And we were thinking,
you should be Professor X..
And you should be Magneto.
Exceptional!
I expect more from you.
Country House Military Office of the
Union of Soviet Socialist Republics aka USSR.
- We've got a problem.
- What?
I'm so sorry!
It's jsut wasn't on the map.
No matter what happens, act normally.
I'll take care of this, alright?
Now listen to me.
- To where?
- To the other side.
- Can you show me the back?
- Sure, sure!
- What's in there?
- Nothing!
- So, we're finished here?
- Yeah.
- Where's Shaw?
- I don't know!
If she is telepath and if I read her,
She'll now we're here.
I'll try something else.
Shaw has send his apologize.
But he's in dispose.
He asked me to come in his place.
Between you and me,
I'm a lot better company.
Please, come here!
He's not coming.
So now what, boss?
Now, nothing.
We're here for Shaw,
mission aborted.
What the hell is this?
- Erik!
- She's his right hand woman!
That's good enough for me.
The CIA invading a home
senior Soviet officer..
Are you crazy?
I'm not in CIA.
Erik?!
So, you be busy,
planning your next move.
But what if the American refusing
transmute missiles to Turkey?
You know, I can't talk
about those things, Mrs. Frost.
Emma!
And don't worry..
You don't have to say a word!
He's gonna start World War III,
ain't he?
- Then, do somthing!
- Like what?
We're moving out!
You can't!
I'm sorry..
I can't leave him!
You calm!
You speak English?
You are so beautiful!
Yes, yes!
Pathetic!
Yes!
Nice trick!
Cine esti tu?
Go to sleep!
You can stop to read my mind, suger!
You're never going to get anything
from me, while I'm like this.
So you can just tell us!
Where's Shaw?
Erik?
Erik, that's enough.
Erik, that's enough!
All yours!
She wouldn't be shooting at
the diamond from again.
If she does..
Give here a gentle touch.
Untied States of American
*USA*
Russia
We are the children of the atom.
Radiation gave birth to mutations.
What will kill the humans..
Will only make us stronger.
Beautiful, isn't it?
This is worst than we previously imagined!
We're taking you with us.
CIA will want to
question you themselves.
I doubt it.
They've bigger things, than
you're worry about right now.
Wow!
Alright!
Jesus, man..
You are killing me!
Don't beat yourselfe up,
we've lot of spare time.
Oh, I didn't know, the circus was in town!
Ow, come on honey!
Give us some of..
Will!
Go on, let's see the foot!
Here he is!
Come big foot, let's go!
Hey, hey..
Come on! Hey!
They're just guys,
being stupid!
guys being stupid, I can handle!
Okay, I handled them all my life!
But, rather bunch of guys stare of me, with
my clothes off, and when they were staring me!
And us!
What was that?
I don't know.
There's something I don't feel right!
No word of Shaw?
Not a peep!
Not even through
that back channel?
What is that?
We have an intruder in the main atrium.
Where are the mutates?
You take another step,
I'm gonna put you down!
Of course you will! but where do
I find more of evolute people?
Send backup,
now!
Get back, Get back!
You don't leave that room!
We're under attack!
Shoot..
Shoot him!
Where are the mutates?
Put that man down,
or we will open fire!
Stay behind me ass!
Let's go!
Get back!
We need help!
This way!
If you need the mutates,
they're right through that door!
Just let us normal people go!
Or no way....
Where's the telepath?
Not here!
Too bad!
Oh, let's take this silly thing off.
Good evening.
My name is Sebastian Shaw.
And I'm no here to hurt you.
Freeze!
Azazel!
My friends..
There's a revolution coming..
When man kind dicovers, who we are!
What we can do!
Each of us will face a choice.
Be in slaved...
Or rise up to rule!
Choose freely, but know
that if you are not with us,
By definition, you are..
Against us!
So..
You can stay...
And fight for the people
who hate and fear you.
Or you can join me,
And live like kings!
And queens!
You kidding me?
Come on!
We don't belong here.
And that's nothing to be ashamed of.
We have to do something!
Stop!
I'm coming with you.
Good choice!
So, tell me about your mutation.
Will, I adapted to survive!
So, I guess I'm coming with you.
I like that!
- Alex!
- Get out!
Do it!
Checking your fallow mutants...
It's a noble gesture.
Feels good!
Adapt to this!
Moscow, Russia
Welcome.
Again, I'm sorry about intelligences
treatment for you.
The American are merciless.
And know, they put rockets in Turkey.
And I guess, you look for a place
to put your own rockets.
Somewhere, that the American defense
system will be useless.
You will put them in Cuba.
And very close to Florida.
Rockets in Cuba?
Are you serious?
That way, we will announce the war!
Maybe, I wasn't clear enough.
You will make this happen!
Sure!
Let's see what KGB
think about this!
Hello?
General Armifilkov.
Yes?
No thing.
Raven!
We'll made the arrangement
for you to be taken to home immediately.
- We're not going home!
- What?
He's not going back to prison.
It killed Darwin!
I hold one more reason
for you to leave.
This is over!
Darwin's dead, Charles!
And we can't even bury him.
We can avenge him!
Erik, a word please.
- They're just kids!
- No, they were kids!
Shaw has is army,
we need ours.
We'll have to train.
All of us!
Yes?
Yeah!
We can't stay here.
Even if you reopen the department,
It's not safe!
We got no where to go.
Yes, we do!
The law says we've
got to turn it over.
The law, applies to human beings.
The same law doesn't apply on mutions.
They're too dangerous!
Turns like this!
Security is more important than liberty!
There's a war coming, John.
Yes.
But a war, with who?
Excellent question!
Although I do not call it war exactly.
That's suggest both sides standing
an equal chance of winning.
The Russians have send
their war-head to Cuba.
We have a week bofore
the ship hits the coast.
Our fleet can be on this line,
when the Russian missile ship arrives.
If that ship crosses the line..
They'll have declared a war,
against the United States.
We will have no choice, but the
retaliate of the full nuclear response.
Who is with me?
Despotic to seventh fleet.
This is yours?
No..
It's ours!
Honestly, Charles..
I do not know how you survived.
Living in such harshness.
Will, it was a harshness softed by me!
Come on, time to the tour.
Moscow, Russia
Dear, firends..
The USA has sent a warship to Cuba.
And that..
Will leave only one choice..
Mr. First Secretary,
we have to send a fleet marine.
Send the fleet!
President Kennedy has
signed a formal proclamation.
Setting up a blockade of all missiles,
come from Cuba.
The Soviet Union reacted by terminate a step
along the road to initiate a formal nuclear war.
You sure?
I'm sure.
Well.
No. No, I can't. I'm sorry!
I can't shoot anybody pop like this.
Like my friend!
Oh, come on!
You know I can deflect it!
You always tell me,
I should push myself.
You know you can deflect it,
and you're not challenging yourself.
What if that happened to the man
who is tring to resubmarining?
Well, I can't!
Something that big, I need a situation of anger.
The anger is not enough!
That has got my job done all this time!
And you got in your kill all this time!
Okay..
Let's try something more challenging!
My step-father, took a possibility
of nuclear war, quite seriously!
This way.
That's why he had this
bunker build, down here.
So we can use it as a practice
range in our source.
Don't you think I'm gonna blow up the walls?
Ha-ha!
He had this place built with
stone of nuclear bomb.
I think it'll handle you out.
You know, when I do this,
bad things can happen!
It's because you
can't control it..
It, controls you.
That's why we're here, Alex.
That's why we're training.
What you're doing is incredible.
You're hitting the pitch of sound ways,
as the same resonates frequency of the glass.
That's why it shatterd!
But this, is like any other muscle in the body.
You can control it!
In each of us,
two natures are in war.
Robert Louis Stevenson,
Dr Jekyll and Mr. Hyde.
10 marks.
So you mustn't really like or can
believe in that, wouldn't you?
It's about, mans animal nature.
His struggle, so he can control it.
To conform.
And that struggle was just holing you back.
Jekyll was afraid of what
would he be capable of.
You are, too.
If you serious about that,
there's no way to get back.
Looks nice.
Have I shut the door?
Yeah.
When you be ready.
My God!
I will teach you to
control this, Alex.
Are you sure, this will work?
Anything is possible.
- I based the design...
- Stop talking!
Come on!
Now, remember..
Scream as hard as you can!
We need the sound wave
to be the supersonic.
Catch in the right angel,
you should continue!
I should continue?
Encouragingly!
Good luck!
And don't forget to scream!
If you want to beat me this time,
you have to send the beast free!
On your marks.
Get set.
Go!
Oh.. Congratulations, my friend!
Robert Louis Stevenson
would have been proud.
Impressive, Hank!
You like those,
Ain't that like a red nose?
Right, Bozo?
I'm done here!
Thank you, Alex!
Come on, Hank!
If you're using half of
concentration to look normal..
Then you're only half-paid
attention do whatever else you do.
Just calm down..
So point to something could save your life!
You want consorter to accept you.
And you can't even accept yourself!
Sexy!
We can pull off this, it's just in producible.
The real one will look consider be better!
The whole suit.
See? These, sensors measured energy.
I'll put this panel.
Focuse is in the access of the absorbent.
Well, we'll try having one in the middle.
Just one in the middle, alright?
Good luck!
God! You must see this!
Your genes are extraordinary, you know that?
Your cells age, have
the rate of normal female.
When you're 40 you'll still have a look like of teenager.
You have the most incredible
cellular structure, I ever seen!
Would you believe, I'll fly this time?
Unreasonably!
I trust you.
- I'm touched.
- I don't trust him.
Say nothing!
I'm gonna die!
Erik!
Wow!
What?
You know we were thinking at same!
What a work have you done!
Thank you very much!
Alright, Alex..
I want you to hit the X.
And try not to hit me,
that's good, champ!
You serious?
I'm very serious!
I've complete an ample faith in you!
I'm still a Bozo?
Yes, Hank.
You still a Bozo.
But, nice job!
See that?
Try to turn it face us.
You know..
I believe, the true force is lies somewhere,
between rage, and surreality.
Would you mind, if I..
What did you just do to me?
I accessed the brightest corner
of your memory system.
Very beautiful memory, Erik.
Thank you!
I didn't know, I still have brightness.
There's so much more,
than you think know.
Not just pain..
And anger.
It's good into you,
I felt it.
When you can access whole over..
You'll possess a power,
no one can imagine.
Not even me!
So, come on!
Try again.
- Hey!
- Well done!
The President on television taking a speech.
It shall be the policy of this nation...
To regard any nuclear missle,
crossing the embargo line..
That surrounds Cuba.
As an attack by the Soviet
Union on the United States.
Requiring a fully terrorist response,
upon the Soviet Union..
That's how we gonna find Shaw.
How do you know?
Two superpowers facing of.
He wants to stop, World War III.
He want leave as to take a chance.
So much for the diplomacy.
I suggest you all get a good night sleep.
...All eventually, leads to war.
..As the missel ship, nears Cuba.
All diplomatic efforts to avoidance nuclear war.
That gaves wrong damage.
As the American people ready themselves
for the mightly war of an atomic attack.
There are reproducible reports of panicking.
Supermarkets cleared.
As shelves unused since the Second World War,
are started for what may had.
In all its history, America has
never faced a greater threat.
The world is brace for war.
And there is no one to stop me!
Come in!
Hi!
Hava surprise for you!
I isolated the right marker in
your DNA example..
The serum works like an antibiotic.
Attacking the cells that
causes the physical mutation.
It won't effect our abilities,
just our appearance.
Do you still wanna do this?
Should we have to hide?
You're already do!
You're hiding right now,
like I hide my whole life.
I don't wanna feel like a freak.
All the time, I just wanted look..
Normal.
Yeah!
Hank, don't!
You are beautiful, Hank!
Every thing you are,
you are perfect!
Look at all of us.
Look at all what have we achieve this week!
All we will achieve..
We are different,
but we shouldn't be
trying to fit in the society.
Society should inspire
to be more like us.
Mutant, and proud!
But whose wanna tell you?
And even, if we save the world, tomorrow..
And mutions are accepted into the society..
My feet, and your natural form..
Never been that beautiful.
You look beautiful now!
We need, this cure!
Cuba, Russia, America.
Makes no difference.
Shaw's declared war
on mankind, and all of us!
He has to be stopped.
I'm not gonna stop Shaw.
I'm gonna kill him!
Do you have any tallow then?
You've no longer know why I was here, Charles.
The things have changed.
What's starts as uncoverd mission,
tomorrow, mankind will know that mution's exist.
They fear us.
That fear will turn out to hating.
No if we stopped the World War.
No if we can proved Shaw.
Not if we rescue or life doing so.
They'll do the same for us.
- We're having to be the better man.
- We already are!
We're the next age of human evolution.
- You said it yourself..
- No, we don't.
Are you really so naive,
as to think they won't battle their own extinction?
Or it's arrogants?
I'm sorry?
After tomorrow, they're gonna terminate us.
Are you blinded?
Because you believe they're more like Moira.
You believe, they're all Shaw.
Listen to me, very
carefully, my friend.
Killing Shaw, will not bring you peace!
Peace, weren't ever an option!
No!
No..
No.
Wow!
That's a surprise!
The nice kind?
Get out, Raven.
I wanna go to bed.
Maybe in a few years!
How about now?
I prefer the real Raven.
I said, the real Raven!
Perfection!
Could you pass me my robe?
You don't have to hide.
Have you ever looked at a tiger,
thought you had to cover up?
No, but..
You're an exquisite creature, Raven.
All your life,
the world has tried to tain you.
It's time for you to be free.
Now, sometimes I wonder what
my life what have been like..
What?
Oh God!
For God sake, Raven.
Wear your clothes.
That's not what you said,
when you first saw me.
I guess pets always cuter,
when they're little, right?
Raven, I don't know what's got into you.
I saw you been in good mood.
Hank..
He tells me, he has found the
answer to your cosmetic problem.
You gonna tell me what's the matter,
or I will have to read your mind?
You promised me,
you would never do that!
Until recently..
I never had to use my power, to know
what you're thinking about, Raven.
You know, Charles..
I used to think, it's gonna be me and you,
against he world!
But no matter how the bad world gets,
you don't want to be against. Do you?
You wanna be a part of it!
What the hell happened here?
Hank has been busy.
Do we really have to wear these?
There's none of us mutated to enjoy
extreme G force, or be immune by bullets.
I suggest we suit up.
Airbase
Where is Hank?
I'm here.
Hank?
It didn't attacked the cells.
Didn't handle them.
It didn't work.
Yes, it did, Hank.
Don't you see?
This is, who you meant to be.
This is you!
No more hiding.
You're like a bad-ass!
Hank?
Don't mock me!
Hank, put him down immediately, please!
Hank, Hank!
I wasn't!
Even I got to admit you look pretty bad-ass!
I think, I gotta new name for you..
Beast!
You sure, you can fly this thing?
Of course, I can!
I designed it!
Cuba
Porterage in the target?
Rect 1-8-0,
12 knots.
3 minutes to the embargoed, sir.
God help 'em, if they crossed it.
God help us all.
Send to general quarters.
General quarters,
General quarters!
- All plants been back to station?
- Aye, sir!
State condition, zero.
General quarter, back to station.
Captain, sir.
We've our commands.
Why you need other commands?
I've been in a war, my friend.
I don't want another one.
Get your positions!
Yes, sir!
Rects are,
in the coordinate of 1-8-0.
Missiles are ready.
There's commands
from the Palace, sir!
Commands for a bearer of the missiles,
And change it's destination
to the Odesa harbor.
To the Arrel prow, over.
There's no any respond, sir.
It's not changing it's destination.
You have your commands to change your destination,
and go back. Do not cross the line!
Target ready to be fired, sir.
- Sand by to fire.
- Standing by, sir.
Wow!
Looks pretty nasty, out there.
To the Arrel prow, over.
To the Arrel prow..
We command you to
change the destination.
He still here, somewhere!
That ship is on the coast of embargo line.
That ship corsses the line,
our boys are gonna blow it up!
And the war begins.
Unless they're not, our boys.
USA Independence,
this is Alexander Nevsky.
We've lost control of our cargo ship.
We've commanded to stop.
Do not fire!
We repeat,
do not fire!
The signal of cargo ship
is turning around, sir.
It's a ruse.
Stay know of it.
Stand by to fire.
Standing by to fire, sir!
On my count..
Five..
Four..
Hold on!
No!
What was that?
The Russians..
They've fired on their own ship!
Allow warning next time, Professor?
Sorry about that!
Are you alright?
Yeah!
Son of..
Give me commander on the line.
I need to know new orders.
Congratulations, my friend.
You have just avoided us a nuclear war.
What?
Arrest him, and put him in the cell.
What? Why?
What happened?
They say, their comrade has lost his mind!
Americans are applauding.
They're here!
That telepath is powerful!
I'm going to the backup plan.
- That was inspired, Charles.
- Thank you very much.
But I still can't locate Shaw.
He's down there.
we need to find him, now!
Hank?
Is there anything unusual
on the radio or scanners?
No.
Nothing.
Will, then he must be under water.
And obviously, we don't have sonar.
Yes, we do!
Yes, we do.
They are ready for war.
We just need to scratch another
matches to let the fuse.
And we still have the most
powerful weapon available.
Me!
Turn the nuclear reactor to %100 output.
And make sure,
I'm not disturbed.
Hank!
Steady the bloody plane!
Hey!
You're right back off!
Beast, open the back plane door!
Remember..
It's the muscle!
You control it.
You'll be with me, entire time!
Hope see you soon!
On my mark!
Three.. Two.. One!
Go!
Let the fleet,
their men is in down!
Banshee has got the location of Shaw.
- You ready for this?
- Let's find out!
Come on!
Remember, the point between
rage, and surreality.
Erik, take my hand!
Uhh...
Hold on guys!
It's gonna get uncomfortable.
Erik, take my hand!
Damn!
Moira?
Moira, are you alright?
Yeah, I'm okay!
I read the teleporter's mind.
Shaw's absorbing all the
power out of his submarine.
He's turning himself to
somekind of nuclear bomb.
We've got no time, we have to got it,
before it gonna out of control.
Alright, Moira.
This is what we going to do.
Get the radio, tell the camp boat
leave out, immediately.
I'm going in!
Beast! Havok!
Back them up!
Erik, I can guid you to be sure in.
But, I need you to shut down
whatever it is, that blocks me.
And then we just have to hope to God,
it's not too late to stop him.
- Got it!
- Good luck!
Raven, stop!
I'm going to help them!
We don't have time to this.
Anything comes in to enter,
you've got to take care of it.
- Yes?
- Fine!
If we go,
you go!
We think that Shaw, is tring to
create somekind of bomb!
Erik..
Go to the middle of the submarine.
That's the point, my mind
can't telepath.
We have to assume,
that's where Shaw is!
Stay there,
Stay there!
That's a nuclear reactor!
Disable it!
Stop!
Don't move!
Get down!
Erik, you're there
have reached void.
He's not here, Charles.
Shaw's not here!
He's left the sub!
What? He's got to be there. He has to be.
There's no where else he can be in. Keep looking!
But I'm telling you, he's not!
He's not here, goddamn it!
Erik!
What a pleasant surprise.
Erik?
So good to see you, again!
Might I ask you something?
Why are you in their side?
- He's gone!
- What?
He's gone into the void.
I can't communicate with him there.
Why fight for a doomed race,
they'll hunt us down..
As soon as they realize,
their race is coming to an end!
Yeah!
I really am!
He's back!
Erik, whatever you do, keep doing it.
It's going to work!
But, every thing I did..
I did for you!
To unlock you power.
To make you impressed!
It's working!
I've got started to see him,
but I can't yet touch his mind.
Come along way,
from banding gates.
I'm so proud of you!
And you just started
to scratch the surface.
Look how much we can order if worked together!
Stop, Azazel!
I don't want to hurt you, Erik.
I never did.
I wanna help you.
This is our time..
Our age.
We are the future..
Of the human race.
You and me, son.
This world, could be ours!
Everything you did..
Made me stronger.
Made me the what I am today!
That's the truth.
I've known my all life.
You are my creator!
No, Charles!
Na!
Are you okay?
Moira, if you qiut.
I can not control this man for so long!
Sorry, Charles.
Erik, please..
be the better man!
But I don't trust you.
Erik, there will be no turning back!
No!
Don't do this, Erik!
If you are in there..
I would like you to know,
that I agree with every word you said.
We are the future..
But..
Unfortunately, you killed my mother.
This is what we going to do..
No!
Please, Erik.. No!
I'm going to count to 3.
And I'm going to move the coin.
One..
Please, Erik!
Two..
Three!
No...
no...
The Russians, share our concerns.
And will join us to strike
on all the mutions.
We can end this threat for good.
We'll never have an opportunity like this.
We have an agent
on that beach.
One agent!
She's a good agent!
She is a collateral damage.
Today, our fighting stops.
Take off your blinders, brothers ans sisters.
The real enemy is out there.
I feel their guns moving in the water.
Their metal targeting us.
Americans, Soviets, human..
Uniting their fear in unknown.
And the under fellas running scared,
my fellow mutions.
Go ahead, Charles.
Tell me, I'm wrong.
Fleer commander,
this is agent XB-70.
Respond, over!
The beach is securite,
call off the attack!
The beach is targeted in,
and ready to be fired upon, sir!
- Stand by.
- Standing by, sir!
Do you hear me?
Stand by to fire the missiles!
Hello?
- Fire!
Erik, you said yourself,
We're the better man.
This is the time to prove it!
There's the thousands of
men on those ships.
Good, honest, innocnet men.
They're just following orders!
I've been in the mercy of the
man, just following orders.
Never again!
Erik, release them!
Don't!
- Don't wanna hurt you!
- Go hurt me!
Stay back!
Erik, stop!
Gentlmen, I was honored
by serving with you.
I'm so sorry!
I said, back off!
You..
You did this!
Erik, please..
She didn't do this, Erik.
You did!
Let's not turn on each other,
that's what they want!
I tried to warn you, Charles!
I want you by my side!
Like brothers, as you and I.
All of us, together.
protecting each other!
We want the same thing.
My friend..
I'm sorry..
But we do not!
Charles, I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry, Charles!
It's alright..
It's alright!
God..!
This society won't accept us.
We form our own.
The humans who have played their hand...
Now we get ready to play ours.
Who's with me?
No more hiding!
You..
You should go with him.
It's what you want.
You promised me never read my mind!
I don't..
I promised you I won't try anything I'm afraid.
I'm sorry!
Take care of him!
And, Beast..
Never forget..
Mutions, and proud.
- Help me up, come on!
- He's..
I'm gonna get yout hospital.
Wait, don't, don't!
Charles, don't move.
Okay?
Actually, I can't..
I can'...
I can't feel my legs.
I can't feel my legs!
And this day of Thanks giving...
There's much we can be grateful.
As you look back,
to where we stood..
Only 4 weeks ago..
The unity of this hemisphere...
has supported our allies,
and calmed determination of the American people.
These qualities maybe tested
many more times, in this decade.
So, how many students
do you think you'll have there?
Once you get the academy running?
As many, as I can manage.
Possibly, more
You know..
One day the government is gonna
realize how lucky they were..
To have the Professor X on their side!
As I suppose I'm a real professor now, am I not?
Last thing you know,
I'm gonna be bald!
We still in the government side, Moira.
We still the G men, just without the G.
No. You're on your team now.
It's better.
You're X-man.
Yeah..
I like th sound of that.
Moira..
For us..
Anonymity will be the line of defense.
I know!
They can threaten me,
all they want, Charles!
I'll never tell them, where you are.
Ever!
I know you won't.
I know..
I remember they attacked on H.Q.
Leaving and go somewhere else.
And then, this morning..
I woke up in home.
That's it!
All that time wipe
clean on your mind.
Just gone!
He can do that,
you don't remember anything?
Sometimes I get fragments.
Like..
Trees..
Sun light...
A kiss!
Oh, Jesus!
Gentlemen, that's why the CIA
has no place for a women.
What the hell was that?!
I know, we've our differences.
Where's your telepath friend?
Gone!
And I have a little up of void in my life,
if I'd be honest.
I was hoping you could
take that void and fill it.
Join us!
Erik, I believe!
I prefer..
Magneto!