Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Pinto!
You're covered on all sides.
Raise your hands.
He's still alive.
Let's get him
into the old jail.
Well, they did it.
They shot him down.
I never thought
they'd do that-
not to pinto sykes-
not that easy.
He's ain't got more
than a few minutes
left to live, johnny rob.
You go fetch
his paw and sister.
All right,
mothershed.
Yes, sir.
That's the end of that!
Normally, the old man
would be correct-
this would be the end
of the story.
We've had the traditional
shootout on the street,
and the badman
will soon be dead,
but some men of legend
and folktale have been known
to continue having their way
even after death.
The outlaw and killer
pinto sykes was such a person.
And, shortly, we'll see
how he introduces the town-
and a man named conny miller,
in particular-
to the twilight zone.
Who's that?
It's me, conny. Jasen.
Why'd they fence off that
piece of street down there?
It's his blood.
If you could see down
under all that dust,
you could see
his blood down there.
Whose blood?
Pinto sykes'.
They shot
and killed him
day before
yesterday.
Well, well. Lookee what
the wind blowed in.
Hello, conny.
Jim.
Same, conny?
That's... that's
all for me.
Did you notice our little fence
out in the street, conny?
That i did...
and i know
what's in it, too.
The blood
of pinto sykes.
Who shot him?
We did.
Who is "we,"
mothershed?
Us. The whole town.
Not me.
I don't believe
in gunfire myself.
Only eight of us
actually fired,
but the whole town
was behind it.
We'll have to admit
the whole town ain't
much of a marksman.
Out of eight shots fired,
only one of them hit him.
We don't even
know who it was
that got him.
Bullet passed right through him.
No one's bragging
that they did it.
No, sir.
No one's
taking credit
for that piece
of gunplay.
You know something,
mr. Mothershed?
Maybe, by now,
pinto knows
who it was
that killed him.
Reckon you're some
disappointed, conny,
being as how you
spent so much time
trying to find him
for yourself.
That i am, ira.
Four months wasted
looking for him,
and i could have
found him here.
That ain't the way
pinto tells it.
He claimed you didn't
even try to catch up to him.
Hello, johnny rob.
Still as big a blabbermouth
as ever, i find.
You do spout off
a lot, johnny rob.
But no need to get
riled, conny.
Us here ain't saying
that you didn't actually
try to catch him,
but it is a fact
that pinto claimed
that on his deathbed.
He talked
before he died?
He lived
a half hour
after he
was shot.
Talked
a blue streak
right up to
the very end.
What did he say about me?
I reckon that
conny deserves
to hear it all.
We got a new
circuit judge, conny-
a young fellow
named ed thackeray.
He was through
here last week,
and we went to him
with our complaints.
We told him
how one pinto sykes
is wanted by the law
in three states,
but treats this town
like it was his
personal property
just because he was
born and raised here.
And we tell how we hired you-
conny miller-
to track him down,
but we ain't had much results.
Well, sir...
this thackeray
gets mad at us-
tells us to grow up
and act like men,
or else leave town
and move to where
men can protect us.
He gets us
kind of fired up.
So we hold a meeting,
and we all agree
to work as one
so that the next time
pinto rode in
we all join in,
and we take him.
Day before yesterday,
he rode in.
Now, do you want
to tell it, ira?
That's about all
there is to tell.
He rode in.
Eight of the town
gunned him down
out in the street.
That's all there is.
No, that is not
all there is.
All right,
you tell it.
We sent for
his paw- dan sykes-
and for his
sister ione...
i know the names
of his family.
I was born here, too.
He spent the last
few minutes
talking to them.
He told his paw
how sorry he was
that he hadn't
turned out better,
and his paw allowed
as to how he'd
turned out right well.
He told ione
how he wished
she'd marry a fine
man and move away.
Asked to be buried near his maw,
only 20 feet away,
as she's too true a woman
to have the likes
of him any closer.
What did he say
about me?
He got real riled
when he mentioned you.
He said, the slower
he ran away,
the slower
you chased him.
He said he waited
for you in albuquerque.
Even sent word
where he was.
You never showed up.
He said you
ought to be able
to catch him now
but, that if
you ever come
anyways close
to his grave,
he'll reach up and grab you.
He lied... even
on his deathbed.
I searched
all over albuquerque-
every saloon, hotel.
He wasn't even in
that town long enough
to rent himself a room
for the night.
Hello, ione.
Give me a bottle
of rye, mr. Bodley.
Seems your paw is
hitting the drinking
a might heavy, ione.
Maybe you ought
to try to get him
to tone it down.
He's a fine man.
Now, the folks
here in town,
they don't hold
it against him
that he's pinto's paw.
This ain't for my paw,
mr. Bodley.
It's for me.
Well, look what
the wind blew in.
Hello, ione.
And how are you?
Fine. Just fine.
How's yourself?
Just tolerable.
You know,
my brother and i
were just
talking about you
just the day
before yesterday.
He's real sorry
he's been missing you.
We told him, ione.
Even about how
pinto's going
to reach up
and grab him?
We told him that, too.
You been chasing him
for so long, conny,
you ought to feel lucky tonight.
You know right
where he is.
All you got to do
is walk out there.
Isn't that nice?
That whole sykes family-
they never was real bright.
Tell me something,
conny.
Are you afraid
of pinto's grave?
The rest of us are.
Now, how about you?
Are you afraid?
No.
I'm going to tell you
something, johnny rob.
I was never afraid of pinto
when he was alive,
and i sure ain't afraid of him
now that he's dead.
I don't believe that.
I ain't armed!
Hold it,
conny.
Let's not
have any
bloodshed.
Nobody calls
me a coward.
Now, you didn't
let me finish
what i was going
to say, conny.
I don't think
you're a coward.
Leastwise,
i don't think
you're afraid of
anybody in this room.
Especially not me.
I'm just
a poor old boy.
I work hard
for not too much.
But dogs and
kids like me.
They follow me around
all the time.
Sure is windy
tonight, ain't it?
No, sir,
i don't think
there's anybody
afraid of me.
Whether you were
afraid of pinto alive-
only you know that.
But what i was
going to say
before you hit me
and hurt me
was... well, now,
i'll bet-
i'm not accusing,
you understand-
but i'll bet
that you won't call
on pinto tonight.
Why don't you shut up
before you really get hurt?
It's almost midnight.
Now, i'll bet you
you won't walk
out of here
at midnight sharp...
and visit
pinto's grave.
Now, i got
a $20 gold piece.
Now, i'll bet you...
i'll bet you this $20 gold piece
it took me 20 weeks to save
that you won't do
what i just said.
I'm going to tell
you something, boy.
I don't like you.
I never have,
and i never will.
So old blabbermouth
got hisself
a $20 gold piece, huh?
Well, i just happen
to have one, too
and it just
covers yours.
I guess,
in a little while,
one of us will have
$40 instead of $20.
That's right.
And, when i get back,
i don't want you
hanging around here
where i can see you.
You understand?
Conny.
You don't want to put up
another $20, do you?
Are you saying
that you want
to bet against me,
too, steinhart?
Betting's my
business, conny.
You don't think i got the nerve?
I didn't say that.
I just said i'd bet
$20 you don't go.
There.
Keep an eye
on the bets, ira.
Sure, conny.
I still got some
betting money left.
I can't afford
to bet tonight.
Steinhart just took all
i can afford to lose.
Well, if steinhart hadn't
hadn't taken all your money,
whose side
would you be on?
I reckon i'd bet
agin you, conny.
What's wrong with you?
You people know me.
How come now
you think i'm afraid?
Because we'd
be afraid.
You can draw
your gun
real fast,
conny.
We've seen you.
But, out in
that graveyard,
that gun won't be
worth a copper cent.
I don't get my nerve
from this gun, mothershed.
I had it long before i could
pick one of them up.
Conny...
before you go,
we've got to work out
a little detail.
Since you're doing
this job by yourself,
how will we be sure
you've done it?
What do you mean?
What's to keep you
from going
to the edge
of the graveyard,
then telling us
you've gone all the way?
You saying you don't
trust me, steinhart?
Business is
business, conny.
And, with me,
this is business.
Then, in that case,
i guess you'll have
to keep me company
so you can protect
your own interests.
I have another way.
Give me your
bowie knife, ira.
What's that for?
When you arrive
at your destination,
simply stick it
into the grave.
Then, at daylight
tomorrow,
we'll see the proof
of your visit.
If we see it
within five feet
of the fresh earth,
we'll concede
the wager.
One thing,
conny.
Won't nobody
go up there
and steal
that knife
once you've
planted it.
Keep the bottle
on the bar, ira.
I won't be long.
Conny.
Hello, ione.
Come to see pinto?
Maybe.
You're braver
than i thought.
Hmm... here.
Maybe a good
belt of red-eye
will make it
all easier.
I don't get my nerve
out of a bottle, ione.
You go on up there
and see pinto.
I just came
from there.
He's waiting for you.
I don't
understand it.
It's morning,
he ain't back yet.
Maybe he didn't
have the nerve
to come back
and face us
when he didn't have
the nerve to do it.
Not likely.
His horse is
still here.
I just can't
help feeling
somehow i got
a man killed.
Now, it's full
daylight, johnny rob
and we can all think
with clear heads.
Deep down,
we all know
that the dead can't
really hurt nobody.
Morning!
Good morning, ione.
What are you doing
with that plate?
This is his.
He used to eat
out of it
when he was
a little boy.
I'm going to put it
on his grave.
I'll go with you.
I got to see what
happened out there.
Well, i reckon
we can't spend
the rest of our days
being afraid
of a dead man.
I'll come with you.
I knowed it!
I got a man killed.
Cut it out,
johnny rob.
You're acting
like a baby.
It's not your
fault, boy.
What do you mean?
What happened?
The whole story
is right there.
Look at him.
He came up here.
He had more courage
than i thought.
There's his knee prints.
He knelt by the grave.
He pulled his knife
from his belt
and plunged it into the grave,
but the wind was strong,
and it blew his coattail
over the grave.
Being dark,
he didn't notice
he'd put his knife
through his own coattail,
pinioning it
to the grave.
Then he started to rise.
As he did so,
perhaps halfway up
he felt a sudden tug-
the knife holding his coattail.
But, in his own mind, pinto
reached out and grabbed him.
He was already
scared half to death,
and that
finished him.
His heart gave way,
that's all.
There you are, bud.
So you think conny's death
was an accident?
That he stuck
the knife
in his own
coattail?
Yes, ma'am.
How did his coattail
get over the grave?
For some reason,
he had it unbuttoned.
The wind must have
done the rest.
What direction was the wind
from last night?
The south. Why?
The south...
same as now.
Look at
my cloak.
I'm standing in the
same spot conny was.
Look at my cloak.
Is the wind blowing it
across the grave?
You take this
with a grain of salt
or a shovelful of earth,
as shadow or as substance.
We leave it up to you.
And, for any further research,
check under "g" for "ghosts"...
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, we borrow
from the exceptional talent
of author jerome bixby.
It's an adaptation
of what has been called
one of the most terrifying
modern fantasies ever written.
What you'll see is, in a sense,
a portrait of a monster
as a young boy.
Next week's very special
excursion into the twilight zone
is called "it's a good life."
I hope we see you then.
This is james arness.
You know, it's only a short hop
fromthe twilight zone
to dodge city andgunsmoke-
saturday nights
over most of these stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org