Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Whoa!
This is the 11th day
of fever, christian
11 days of fever.
He just can't take
much more.
You said that
after the third day
and the fourth, martha.
He'll take more,
just as we all have.
How's the boy, mrs. Horn?
Oh, about the same,
thank you, charlie.
You figure that apache country
is just due south.
That's what
you said
we were looking for, isn't it?
That's what
we're looking for.
It's, uh, it's this way, chris:
We've been doing a lot of
talking and a lot of thinking...
and?
We figure we ought to turn back.
Turn back.
Is that what you figure?
Is that what you want?
Chris, we're about
at the end of our rope.
We're hungry and we're sick.
We figure if we don't do it now,
we're going to die out here.
If you try to go the 1,500
miles back to st. Louis
i'll guarantee you'll leave your
bones bleached on some desert
or lose your scalps,
or freeze in a mountain pass.
What about water, chris?
We're almost out of water.
I'll find us water.
I'll get water.
How, chris-
with a divining rod?
I don't know,
but i'll find water.
And food, chris,
and medicine for your own child?
I'll take a look at
that rim over there.
Chris, you might... you might
look for some shady spot...
a pretty spot where we might...
we'll not talk about burying our son now
not while there's
breath in him.
Stay close
to the wagons.
Keep them bunched up.
Chris, how far you going?
Just over that rim
there about 100 yards.
Maybe there's a stream,
or game or something.
You never can tell.
Never can tell, chris.
You hold on...
hold on, all of you.
I'll be right back.
The year is 1847, the place
is the territory of new mexico.
The people are a tiny handful
of men and women with a dream.
11 months ago, they started
out from ohio and headed west.
Someone told them about
a place called california
about a warm sun and a blue sky,
about rich land and fresh air
and at this moment,
almost a year later
they've seen nothing
but cold, heat, exhaustion
hunger and sickness.
This man's name
is christian horn.
He has a dying
eight-year-old son
and a heartsick wife
and he's the only one remaining
who has even a fragment
of the dream left-
mr. Chris horn, who is going
over the top of a rim
to look for water
and sustenance
and in a moment will move
into the twilight zone.
Martha!
Charlie!
Where'd they go?
What's going on here?
Howdy.
Did you see it?
See what?
That thing... that monsterlike
thing that came at me.
Monster?
Yeah, it almost...
almost hit me.
Well, mister,
i never saw anything.
If there was anything,
it never got to here.
Oh, no, but it was just
a mile or two down the road.
You mean the truck?
The truck?
Are you
all right?
I mean, uh... how long you
been out there in the desert?
Oh, well, almost a year.
That is, almost a year
since we left ohio.
One of the wagons was burned
by the indians
and the other two
went back.
Yeah, well, uh...
well, why don't you come on
inside for awhile, huh?
Let me take a look
at that arm, too.
Yes, the gun went off
when that... when
that monster came at me.
Yeah, you let mary lou
take a look at it.
She used to be
a nurse's aide.
Mary lou
is my wife.
Come on.
Mary lou!
Uh... this, uh,
fellow shot himself
in the arm by accident.
You want to take
a look at him?
Why, sure.
You sit down
over there, mister
and i'll get
some bandages out.
Yeah, uh, go ahead.
Sit down.
Have a glass of water.
Go ahead.
Obliged.
Well, now, there's
an old-timer.
It, uh... must be
a real antique, huh?
It's been used a lot.
Well, it isn't hunting
season around here.
What about indians?
Indians?
Well, we don't have any indians.
Well, leastways
not hostile ones, huh?
How long have you been here?
Uh... a couple of years.
See, we lived over in phoenix.
Phoenix.
Yeah,
phoenix.
You see, uh, mary lou's folks
are from there.
And, uh...
first married, i worked for her old man.
And then we, uh
we bought this place here, and, uh...
of course, i admit
the restaurant
isn't doing too good right now, but, uh...
trucks are beginning
to stop now.
This, uh, is a jukebox.
It's a jukebox.
Hey, mister
where are you from?
I mean, really.
Where are you from?
From?
Yeah.
I'm from ohio.
Ohio!
I left the wagons on
the other side of the rim.
I came to look for water.
Well, there's
a natural spring
just west of here.
Spring?
Yeah.
And game?
Well, uh...
i guess so.
Here, you... you take two of these
and drink some water with them.
What do you have there?
Well, it's penicillin.
It'll keep away any infection.
Where did you get it?
At the
drugstore.
You feel all right?
Do you say this is good
for a sickness?
Well, sometimes, depending on what it is.
I've got a real sick boy
back in the wagon.
You mean, you brought
your family with you?
There were three wagons...
and i... i looked around
and i...
what is that?
It looks just like...
oh, god in heaven,
how could that be?
That says
"september, 1961"
when it's...
eighteen hundred
and forty-seven!
Who are you?
Who are you and where am i?
Where is
this place?
Where am i?
Thank you.
Come again.
Well, doc, what do you think?
If you had some bourbon,
mary lou,
i'd prefer that
at the moment, but...
coffee'll do
for second best.
Having coffee, huh?
Did you take a look
at him, doc?
I did, indeed.
Malnutrition, that's
his major problem
although he's not
a bad specimen of a man
i'll say that.
You were right, joe
he's an interesting
customer.
Must have been
the heat, huh?
Or something.
Well, i mean, doc,
he's just not rational.
Now, i'm not
a psychiatrist, joe.
I'm just an
old-fashioned g.p.
But freud himself
would have something
to gnaw on here.
Oh, he happens
to seem very rational.
Oh, doc, come on!
He can trace his
imaginary life
a whole lot clearer than
any of us can our own.
His seeming recall
is amazing.
But what does that mean?
And one other thing.
A little parenthetic
aside, let's call it.
The fillings
in his teeth-
there are
two of them.
No modern-day dentist ever drilled them.
And you saw his gun, joe.
Sure, but it's an antique.
An antique that isn't
more than a year old!
A 100-year-old gun, joe
and you said yourself it looked
like it was manufactured
less than a year ago.
Okay, now, doc
you're not trying
to tell us...
i'm not trying to
tell you anything, joe.
That is, i'm not
trying to make a point.
All i'm giving you
is the benefit
of some observation.
He's suffering a delusion of some kind
but it's a delusion
of the purest form.
The way he describes
those wagons, his wife
the other people, his son.
He said his son was sick.
Yes, he told me
his boy was dying
and from the way
he described the symptoms
i'd call it pneumonia.
Well, i sure don't
understand it.
I don't
either.
So, doc...
what are we going
to do with him?
I want the
sheriff's office, please.
Precisely what i'm doing now.
I'm getting the authorities
in here to take care of him.
Hello, is the
sheriff there?
Oh, well, that's even better.
Can you radio to him
to get over to joe's diner
as fast as he can?
There's a man here
who needs looking after.
My son.
I read this in the book.
The encyclopedia.
"Horn, christian,
junior, m.d.
"Famous for his early work
in childhood diseases
"pioneer in
vaccine research.
Meladin,
ohio, 1839.
Santa barbara,
california, 1914."
That's my son- that's chris.
I may be crazy, or the world
may be turned upside down
but i know that i've been
put here for a reason.
A reason.
Thank you.
You've been kind and gracious
and i appreciate it
and i've got
to get back.
Horn, we want
to help you
but help means rest
and medical attention.
I've sent for
the authorities.
I want you to come
over here and sit down.
Authorities- i have
no idea who they may be
but i have not the time
to wait and find out.
Horn, please!
Martha.
Did you forget
something, christian?
Where did you go?
Where did we go?
What do you mean, chris?
Where could
we have gone?
Well... all this time.
Allwhattime?
Chris, honey, you just
left a few seconds ago.
What did you forget?
What's that?
Here. Give him
two of these tablets.
I think it may
save his life.
Short trip, chris.
Nothing much on the
other side, was there?
You'd be surprised,
charlie.
There's a whole lot
on the other side of that rim.
For there'll be highways
and many new things-
a whole new land.
You know what, charlie?
It was people like us.
We made it happen.
I wouldn't
worry none, joe.
He can't get far.
We'll be
finding him soon.
Okay. Thanks, sheriff.
Joe, what happened?
Mary lou...
this is horn's rifle.
Why...
i picked it up just
where he dropped it,
and look at it.
Just look at it.
It looks like
it's been lying
out in the desert
for 100 years.
Yeah.
Hey, joe.
Who was he?
Where did he come from?
I think he went back
to wherever it was
he did come from
because, when we got
to the top of the hill,
he... just disappeared.
Where, joe?
All right, boys,
there's water up ahead,
and we're going to california.
And my son has got
a whole lot to accomplish there.
A whole lot.
Giddyap!
Mr. Christian horn-
one of the hearty breed
of men who headed west
during a time when there were
no concrete highways
or the solace of civilization.
Mr. Christian horn, family
and party heading west
after a brief detour
to the twilight zone.
Be sure and watchgunsmoke,
starring james arness,
saturday nights over most
of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org