Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
I thought you made
an appointment.
I did.
Oh, come on, alan.
You're not in that much
of a hurry, are you?
Yes.
Oh.
Well, in that case,
you tell them.
You tell them
they're keeping the head
of the mcclellan enterprises
waiting. Tell them.
All right, all right.
Do you want to forget
the whole thing?
No, i don't want to
forget the whole thing.
I just want to get this
foolishness over with.
Can i have one?
Why, thank you.
Come on.
Hello.
May i help you?
My name
is ransome.
I believe my wife made
an appointment with you.
Oh, yes.
I am mr. Spiereto.
Now, exactly where do we
intend to go?
We intend to go to london.
Splendid.
Of course, you've been.
No.
Well, it's a charming place,
utterly charming.
Of course, you
picked a rather bad
time of the year...
excuse me, mr. Spiereto,
but we're kind of rushed,
and i'd
appreciate it...
well, we all are.
Now...
have you decided
on an airline?
No.
Well, then, if i may,
i'd like to suggest...
oh, we're not going by plane.
I beg your pardon?
I say we're not going by plane.
Oh, but you must.
That is, unless
you're planning this
for some time
in the future.
No, no, we're leaving
right away.
Then i'm afraid a ship
is out of the question.
You see, this is
the off season,
and all the ships
have been booked;
they're taken off
their regular schedules.
All of them?
All the acceptable
ones, yes.
I hope you won't mind
my saying this, mrs. Ransome,
but you know,
airplanes are
perfectly safe nowadays.
Why, i realize
a few people
experience a certain...
trepidation, shall we say,
but there's absolutely
no reason...
you don't have to tell me
about airplanes.
I used to be a stewardess.
It just happens that
we don't want to fly.
Eileen, for heaven's sake,
if it's the only way,
it's the only way.
Could i see a list of the boats
thatarerunning?
As you wish.
Alan, you promised.
I know i promised.
It really is
very important.
Now, we agreed
on that, right?
I'm afraid...
theseare the only
passenger-carrying vessels
leaving for england
in the next 30 days.
Themintrelis a freighter
but i understand
the accommodations
are quite adequate.
Oh, excuse me.
What about this one?
Thelady anne?
Oh, i don't think so.
Why not?
Well, for one thing,
it's very nearly
the oldest boat
in the water
and it's certainly
the slowest.
13 days to le havre,
another half day
to southampton...
ifthere are
favorable winds.
Well, forget it.
Oh, no, no, wait a minute.
It leaves on thursday.
That's less
than a week.
Please, mrs. Ransome,
forget it,
take your husband's advice.
Thelady anneis an antique,
a relic.
Look we can relax
when we get there
if that's what you want.
Don't make such a
big deal out of it.
Well, itis
a big deal to me,
a very big deal.
Give us two tickets.
For this?
Yeah, that's, that's right,
thelady anne.
Very well.
A few extra days
won't matter, will they?
No.
I don't have anything
better to do.
Portrait of a honeymoon couple
getting ready for a journey
with a difference:
These newlyweds have been
married for six years
and they're not taking
this honeymoon
to start their life
but rather to save it.
Or so eileen ransome thinks.
She doesn't know why
she insisted on a ship
for this voyage
except that it would
give them some time
and she'd never been
on one before,
certainly never one like
thelady anne.
The tickets read
"new york to southampton",
but this old liner
is going somewhere else.
The twilight zone.
Oh, alan, alan,
it's beautiful.
It's urgent that schwimmer
get these reports tonight
or, at the latest,
early tomorrow morning
before the office opens.
I'll call you
when i get to london.
What?
Well, it's beautiful.
Uh-uh, not it, madam,
she.
This ship happens
to be a lady.
Oh, of course.
Well, she's
beautiful.
I'd say she's
From the
descriptions,
we'd expected
a cross between
a kayak and
theflying dutchman.
You two seeing
somebody off?
No, we're
passengers.
What's that?
What?
What-what
did you say?
We're
passengers.
Oh, i hardly think so.
I don't think that...
this is, this is
thelady anne.
There must be a mistake.
Toby, please,
i haven't kept you
waiting long enough
to raise
your temper.
Come along.
Be quiet, millie.
You look at your tickets,
and you'll find there's
been an error. I repeat,
this is
thelady anne.
And i repeat,
we're passengers.
Let me have a look
at your tickets.
Show me your tickets.
Why should i do that?
I beg your pardon.
I'm sorry.
Call it curiosity.
Please, please,
let me have a look at them.
Go on.
All right.
Thank you.
"Mr. And mrs. Alan ransome,"
is that what it says?
"New york, southampton."
"Two one-way..."
toby, toby, you're not gonna
reading the small print.
These seem to be
in order, millie.
Thank you. I'm glad
to know that.
No, but i tell you,
there's a mistake.
There's a mistake.
This is what you might
call a private party,
a private...
an excursion.
A mistake.
A terrible mistake.
Millie, millie,
come along, come along.
I guess that
means welcome
aboard in british.
Well, don't let him
get your back up.
You'll be twice as cranky
when you're his age.
You can still
turn back, you know.
Just think of being cooped up
with me for 14 days.
I made a promise,
i'm going to go
through with it.
Isn't that
good enough?
Sure, sure, sure.
At leasttry
to enjoy yourself.
One moment, please.
Your names?
Ransome.
You want to see
our tickets, too?
No, sir, that's quite
all right. Thank you.
State room 24
is down that flight
of stairs there
and to your left.
You're not going
to let him do this?
I'm afraid it's out
of my hands, sir.
Come on, come on.
Let's check the room,
see if they got
the luggage in.
We're due to take off
in ten minutes.
Take off?
Leave, sail.
Depart.
Depart, depart.
I don't believe it.
Oh, alan!
Alan, isn't it marvelous?
Oh, alan, the bed!
Oh, isn't it wonderful?
Oh, and stairs! Look, you have
to go up and down to get in.
This is probably the
most ridiculous room
in the whole world.
Probably? Probably?!
It is!
And you
like it, huh?
Oh, yes, yes,
i like it!
Don't you?
No kidding.
Can we even take this
for two whole weeks?
I mean...
alan, alan, the whistle!
Come on, come on,
let's go up on deck.
Why?
Because that's
what people do.
Haven't you ever
seen any movies?
Here they are.
Those are
the ones i mean-
they're coming with us.
Nonsense.
It's obviously
a silly blunder.
I tell you, i've
seen their tickets.
All right,
keep calm.
There's plenty
of time.
I want
to see it
from the
top deck.
You young people
are probably
unaware of the fact
that this is
a sort of, uh,
private cruise.
Yes.
Quite... there must be
a slip-up somewhere.
Oh, no.
There hasn't been
any slip-up.
This is our ship
and we're sailing
to europe on it.
Her.
Oh, her.
There you are, you see.
Oh, dear.
This is very bad news indeed.
Oh, really?
This may sound
odd to you,
but, really, we
want to help you.
Exactly. You see,
there are certain things
you don't know about the ship.
Now, what does that mean?
Well, for instance,
it isn't generally known...
no, no, no, careful, careful.
No, no, no.
No, no, my dear gentleman,
i must tell them.
The ship is over 50 years old.
Oh, we knew that.
Oh, well, then, uh,
possibly one or two things
you don't know
because you haven't looked.
She's falling apart.
Even the chairs...
they wouldn't bear
the weight of a baby.
And the staircase, the
staircase- look at it-
likely to collapse
any moment.
And the food- you
won't be able to eat it.
It'll poison you,
you get to main.
So you can see how impractical
the whole idea is, can't you?
Uh-huh.
Uh, there's just one thing.
Huh?
If this is such an awfully
dangerous boat,
what are you two doing on it?
Uh, uh... oh, well, we're old
and eccentric.
We're... young
We like
impractical things.
And besides,
we think
that this is
an absolutely
darling little boat.
That's the
last warning.
They'll be taking the
gangplank down any moment.
You'll get seasick,
you know.
No stabilizers.
She rolls like an
old washing machine.
Well, it sounds
like fun!
For pete's sake,
will you two gentlemen...
just a moment, please.
Now, what's that for?
I'm prepared to pay you double
the amount of your tickets
if you'll abandon
your plans.
Well?
Not a chance.
All right, then i'll
triple the amount.
No.
Mrs. Ransome, you're
driving me to extremes.
However, if you leave
thelady annenow,
i'll give you
the equivalent
of 5,000
american dollars.
And i'll
match that.
Making it a total
of 10,000.
Well, now you gentlemen
are talking my language.
Shall we make it
an even 100,000?
Good gracious, we don't
have that sort of money.
Sorry, no deal.
Oh, no, no,
please reconsider.
You don't understand.
Now look,
my dear sir,
ever since we
picked this tub,
people have been
trying their best
to discourage us.
I don't know why
and i don't care.
But if you're worried
that the brash americans
are going to try to crash
your cozy little tea party,
forget it.
No, laddie,
it isn't that at all.
Forget it.
And leave us alone.
You thought i'd take
the money, didn't you?
I honestly
didn't know.
Oh, look, alan!
We're off
to a great start.
Well...
we tried.
We should have
tried harder.
kept them off
this ship.
Alan?
Oh, alan.
What are you
doing up so early, hmm?
It's almost 11:00.
So...?
Good morning.
All right.
You're not getting nervous
already, are you?
No.
Come on, alan,
let's not let
two cranky old men
spoil our honeymoon.
How many?
Hmm?
Get dressed.
Fire drill's
in 15 minutes.
Oh, alan, i wish
you would tell me
what this is all about.
I feel as though i'm
climbing the scaffold
on my way to my execut...
all right, pay attention,
please.
Call for fire
drill practice.
Oh, alan.
Now, see to it
that your straps
are firmly pulled
across the chest and tied.
And that the jackets
fit snugly across your body.
Alan, you don't suppose
that everybody...
everybody.
I checked
this morning.
I didn't see
a person under 75.
Oh, that's silly.
It must just be the
first class section.
There's only one section,
it's all first class.
Do you mean that...
that they're the only...
now, then...
in the event
that the balloon
should go up,
the alarm will sound.
In a calm
and orderly fashion,
you will don your belts-
over there, please-
and assemble here,
"b" deck,
where you will await
further instructions.
Groups will be divided up
in the following manner:
Group "a,"
mr. And mrs. Hunter small,
mr. And mrs. Mckenzie,
mr. And mrs. Scott esprey...
now, remember,
dear,
getting there
is half the fun.
Looks like we're
on time for the orgy.
Shh.
This isn't a boat,
it's a floating rest home.
Alan.
Bartender.
Could you fix us up
with a couple of
double martinis, very dry?
Could i have one?
Alan?
Hmm?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it
was going to be like...
like this.
Yeah.
No, i really
mean it.
I am sorry.
Listen, you know,
it really doesn't make
that much difference.
I mean, we really
didn't want to
meet anyone anyway.
What we really wanted...
stop saying "we,"
will you?
If you'd listened to me,
we'd be in london
right now.
Yeah, and you'd be at
a business conference.
No.
Yes.
Thank you.
And you would be
there the next day
and the day after.
Oh, alan, that's what
this trip is all about.
Don't you see that?
Look, i know you've
been unhappy.
But do you think i enjoy
working 28 hours a day?
Well, it comes to
the same thing, doesn't it?
We never see each other,
we never talk,
we never...
look, i told you before
right after
i put this deal across,
i'm going to start
taking it easy.
Oh, sure, sure.
That's what you said
two years ago.
And you put the deal across and
it didn't make any difference
because there are always
more deals
and there will always
be more deals
because that's all that matters
to you anymore, isn't it?
Isn't it?!
Could i have
another drink, please?
You're supposed
to sip those things,
not guzzle them down.
I'll tell you something,
i am so tired of begging
for a little bit
of your time.
You're not interested
in me anyway.
You are interested
in success.
You have to fight
to get to the top,
and then you have to
fight to stay there.
And you just fight,
fight, fight.
Stop making a scene.
Why?
Does it take your mind off
mergers and board meetings?
No, it takes my mind
off the fact
that i was supposed to be
taking a trip
and having a good time.
Oh, come on, alan,
you took me on this trip
because i asked to be taken,
that's all.
Otherwise, you would
have gone alone.
Now, isn't that right?
I want you to admit that.
Isn't that right?
Isn't that the truth?
I cannot talk to you
when you act like this.
I cannot talk to you.
You don't care about me anymore.
Oh, i was really stupid
to think that, uh,
that a few days alone
was going to make
any difference.
Oh, you are
a flaming success now.
Alan ransome,
the successful financier.
And i am your nagging wife
who doesn't understand.
Oh, what's the matter, alan?
Don't get nervous.
You think they're
going to catch on?
They'll be like
everyone else.
They'll think that we're
a happily married couple
just made for each...
just shut up, just shut up!
Oh, yes, sir,
yes, sir, yes, sir!
Well...
you can stop worrying
because when this tub
finally gets there...
you can relax...
because i'm going to leave.
That might be a good idea.
Well, it is.
It is a good idea.
And then you'll have
all your business deals
to keep you warm
and you won't have any
silly woman picking at you.
Now, won't that
be marvelous, huh?
Yes.
Yes, it will be.
Mr. Ransome...
excuse me.
What for this time?
Oh, millie...
oh, mrs. Ransome,
i didn't see you.
We were wondering
whether you cared to join us
for a cup of tea
this afternoon
and a chat, perhaps.
No, uh, i don't
think so.
Yes, yes,
of course, we'd be delighted.
It's at 4:00, isn't it?
Yes, 4:00
at the imperial lounge.
All right,
we'll see you then.
Good, good.
Come along,
millie.
Why did you do that?
Because you and i have nothing
more to say to each other,
and you said it yourself,
we're gonna be stuck together
for a whole week,
so we might as well call a truce
and make the best of it.
Okay?
Okay.
"Housey housey."
Sounds funsy-wunsy,
doesn't it?
Oh, here they are, millie.
Come on,
mr. And mrs. Ransome.
Tea's ready,
the kettle's boiling.
Come and sit down.
Thank you.
So glad you could
make it.
It's nice of you
to have tea with us.
Well, it's
our pleasure.
I don't know if you've really
met my wife, have you?
Millie,
mr. And mrs. Ransome.
Hello.
I'll have another cup of tea,
old girl, if i may.
Nasty day, i'm afraid.
Now, then, the reason why
we asked you to have
a cup of tea with us
apart, of course, from having
the pleasure of your company
was because...
millie- mrs. Mckenzie-
thought we'd been
a little inhospitable,
a little standoffish,
rude, rude...
so, i expect i ought
to apologize.
Do you, mr. Mckenzie?
I beg your pardon,
do i...?
Apologize? Yes, of course,
most sincerely.
Now, another thing-
great news, great news.
Very important,
since we've been
talking it over
millie and old burgess
and the rest of us
and we've come to the conclusion
that you won't have to leave
the ship after all.
Oh, we won't have...
oh, say, that is
good news.
We were afraid
we'd have to swim back
and that had us
sick with worry.
Oh, my dear fel...
he thought he'd got to swim.
Oh, we'd never allow that.
Of course we wouldn't.
But we were a little bit
embarrassed, you know,
because it never entered
our heads
that any stranger- outsider-
would want to travel
on thelady anne.
You see, primarily
she's a cruise ship,
and last time she picked up
a new passenger
was, according
to captain protheroe...
have you met
the captain?
According to him,
the last time they picked up
a new passenger
was the summer of '48.
So, you see...
well, no need
to fuss, is there?
Because everything's
settled now.
What's all settled?
What my husband is trying to say
is that you won't
have to die, after all.
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
What did you say?
I said you won't
have to die after all.
Of boredom, millie means.
Don't you, dear?
Oh!
Yes, of course. Yes.
I'm afraid we haven't been
very good company so far.
Well, no. No, frankly...
frankly, you haven't.
Oh, please
forgive us.
You see, the fact is
that old millie and i
have spent many fine hours
on this old scow.
Hours one can't
forget easily.
When we heard
they were going
to retire her,
we joined her
for her last
two-way sailing.
It's true
of the others.
That's why there's so many
old parties on board.
Oh.
Well, we didn't
understand.
And they still
don't understand.
Some more tea?
It's very refreshing.
Yes, thank you.
One thing
hasn't changed:
It's still the best
cup of tea in the world.
What about
all the others?
Well, as i said
same reason
as ourselves, really.
Sentiment, you know.
Of course they know.
Why should they choose
thelady anne?
Blessed if i know.
Well, it isn't really
such a different story.
Sentiment.
There are different
kinds of sentiment.
Partly, it was because
alan i haven't really
been alone in six years.
Excuse me. I'm going
to get us a drink.
Good idea.
Scotch all around?
No, not for me, thank you.
Excuse me.
He's embarrassed,
isn't he?
I'm doing that to him
all the time lately.
You said that you two
hadn't been alone.
No, no, uh...
alan is a very busy man.
Anyway, when he told me
he was going to england
on business,
i made him promise
to take me,
whichever way
i decided to go.
But why did you choose
thelady anne?
Well, uh, i guess
it was time, really.
You know, more time
to be alone together.
I don't know.
It just seemed... special.
Oh, my dear,
she is special.
Much more special
than you and your husband
could ever imagine.
Well, for one thing,
toby and i sailed on her
when we got married.
That was, um,
52 years ago.
53, as a matter
of fact.
Oh, you should have
seen her then-
splendid specimen, she was.
The ship i mean,
not old...
oh, toby, really.
I thought you told me
it was an old rust bucket.
Not it, dear.
She, she, she.
Did i say that?
I should have been
struck by lightning
for such a fearful lie.
Do you know thelady anne
was the fairest boat
that ever crossed the seas?
Queen of the fleet,
she was.
Is, old boy.
Is.
No other ship
can touch her.
I beg your pardon.
Quite right.
Oh, this
is old ian burgess.
You haven't met
him properly.
Mrs. Ransome.
How do you do?
Well, don't stand there
like a ninny.
Sit yourself down.
Please go on.
You were telling me
how special she is.
"She," she said.
Did you hear?
Good show.
Congratulations.
She was the only one,
mrs. Ransome.
She specialized...
oh, no
existedfor
honeymooners.
Her cargo:
Young people in love.
Yes. Your presence...
oh, here he is.
Come and sit around here.
Can you manage?
Mm-hmm.
Your presence on board
is so ironic.
No, that's not the word.
Not ironic. What's the word?
Sweet.
No, that isn't it.
Doesn't matter.
The fact is
this ship was a regular
floating wedding barge.
No one on board except
young married couples
full of juice,
and the moon in their eyes.
Oh, dear me,
you'd have laughed.
It was funny
to see them
pretending they'd
been married for years,
acting as if
they were grown up,
and all the time
nervous as kittens.
Remember, burgess?
Of course i do.
But all the nervousness
vanished
once thelady anne
had given them enough time
to know each other.
She was such
a wise lady.
She understood
these things.
Everything was done
for young people.
I expect,
to the others,
the ship seemed
a bit ridiculous.
Love has its own
particular
point of view.
It sees everything
larger than life.
Nothing is too ornate,
too fanciful, too dramatic.
Love demands the theatrical.
And then transfigures it.
It turns the grotesque
into the lovely,
as a child does.
With it, we can see
what we wish to see
in other people.
Without it, we can't see
anything at all.
We can search forever
and never find.
How a shipping company ever had
that particular point of view
i cannot imagine.
But they turned thelady anne
into an enchanted gondola
and took
that moment of happiness
and made it live for two
unspeakably wonderful weeks.
They get the drift, millie.
No need to go all sticky on us.
I feel sticky.
Yes, we all
love this ship.
When we heard she was
going to be retired,
we thought it
only right
to join her on
her last journey.
Most people are here
for the same reason.
Major jones
is just behind me-
the bald man-
with his wife.
He was an engineer
and a very good one,
in his day.
And the couple
on the left there-
the whiteaways-
charming couple.
They were married
on the ship
41 years ago
tomorrow.
Oh.
The chap sitting
over there alone
is otto champion,
the writer.
Surely you've heard
about him?
We used to call him
otto of roses.
Such a one with the ladies.
You wouldn't think so
to look at the old chap now,
would you?
He's a widower.
His wife died in '28
uh, no, '29.
'29, that's right.
The day trigo
won the derby.
What are you talking about?
She died in '33,
the year hyperion
won the derby.
Oh, anyway, it was
round about that time.
Good heavens, look.
There's old lord bristol.
He can hardly walk.
Is he alone?
Decent sort
of fellow.
Yes, i'm afraid
he is. Yes.
What about you,
mr. Burgess?
The same.
She's lovely.
We intended to do
this trip together
but, uh...
oh, no, my dear.
Please.
I'm so sorry.
No, i'm sorry.
We'll be together
again soon.
I'm sorry.
It's all right,
my dear.
Nothing matters
if you're in love.
You are in love,
aren't you?
Yes... of course.
Well, that's all
that matters.
Are you better now, dear?
Yes, yes, i'm...
i'm sorry.
It's quite
all right.
I cry myself
sometimes,
don't i, toby?
Sometimes?
All the time.
Oh, no.
Well, i don't.
It depresses me.
I say, why don't you two
go get some fresh air?
It'll do you good.
Thank you
so much.
Now what's going on?
Hmm?
The, uh, sun.
Well, what about it?
It's, uh... behind us.
So... it's behind us.
Well, it was
over there yesterday.
That means
we're heading north.
So we're heading north.
We should be
heading east.
Blame it on me.
I'm responsible
for everything else.
Why not this?
I don't know what i'm doing
on this crazy boat.
Really, eileen,
this is ridiculous.
Eileen?
Where are you, eileen?
Oh, for pete's sake.
Oh, i'm sorry.
Something wrong?
Have you seen eileen?
I can't find her.
No. Haven't you?
No. We were...
we were
standing over here
and, uh, uh, she...
she was right behind me,
and i...
you don't think anything
happened to her?
I doubt it. It's not
easy to fall overboard.
She may be looking
for you even now.
Have you seen her?
Sorry, sir, but
i wouldn't worry
if i were you.
Where's the captain?
I want to have
this ship searched.
Captain protheroe
is extremely
busy, sir.
I've already taken
the liberty of
alerting the crew.
Have you tried
the library?
Eileen!
Have you found her?
Beg pardon, sir?
My wife. Have
you found her?
You were searching.
No, sir.
Not turned up yet?
In that case,
why not...
why not let's go
and have a drink, eh?
Come along, my boy.
Two whiskeys, please.
Better make 'em
large ones.
Thank you.
Now, then...
ah!
She's gone.
No, she hasn't really.
It just seems like that.
But you've missed her.
That's all, my boy.
A toast...
to thelady anne.
The finest and loveliest ship
that ever sailed the seas.
Thelady anne.
It's a pity what's
going to happen.
It isn't a pity.
It's a crime!
A crime perpetrated
by stupid men in bow ties.
Now, now,
easy, burgess.
Nothing to get
overheated about.
Nothing?
Are you so...
so feebleminded
that you can't see the truth?
Don't you realize
why they're going to
scrap thelady anne?
Outlived her usefulness,
i suppose.
Oh, nonsense.
She's the finest
ship afloat.
You deny it?
Certainly not.
Oh.
She may be
a little slow, perhaps,
but... 13 or 14 days
ought to be quite fast enough
for anyone in their right minds.
That's just it.
People aren't in
their right minds anymore.
They sacrifice leisure
for speed.
And speed's the only thing
that matters.
Come, quick,
hurry, hurry, hurry.
Fast, faster, faster.
Get it over with.
Why the rush?
Don't get so querulous,
old man.
It's bad for you.
I am not querulous.
I am merely trying
to point out
the true reason
for this disgraceful
decision.
Which is?
A plot...
obviously
of communistic origin.
They're going to condemn
thelady anne
because she represents
a way of life.
The old way.
She has grace, manners,
tradition.
And now they're going
to scrap her.
Oh, i say!
Somebody turn
him off.
Nothing is sacred anymore.
The beasts are at the gates,
but we're too old to fight,
so we have to stand around
like pathetic statues,
with our medals tarnished
and our swords broken,
while the vandals turn
our castles into sideshows
and stick up nasty
little advertisements for soap
all along the roadside.
And now they're going
to scrap thelady anne.
But i warn you,
how are we going to stop them
from scrapping the whole world?
Poor old boy.
You mustn't blame him.
He'd planned to make
this trip with his wife.
And then, a few weeks ago,
she had to go
and die on him,
poor old boy.
Well, we'll have
the party tomorrow night.
Yes.
He may feel
better then.
Another drink,
mr. Ransome?
No? All right.
Drinking alone?
Where have you been?
I've been looking
all over for you.
I've been here, alan.
But i look...
oh, alan.
Alan, you must be drunk.
No.
I'm not drunk.
Where did this
come from?
Mrs. Mckenzie
gave it to me.
She wore it
on her honeymoon.
Do you like it?
It's beautiful.
And you're beautiful.
Oh, alan
alan, what happened?
I don't know
what happened.
But i'm going
to try very hard
not to forget it.
See that?
What have you
got there, dear?
Don't you remember?
They're your letters.
I've had them
how long a time?
What are you going
to do with them, eh?
Bury them.
I don't need them anymore.
It won't be
very long now.
Here they are.
Come along,
mr. And mrs. Ransome.
Champagne's
getting warm.
You know my wife,
don't you?
That's the captain.
Have you met
captain protheroe?
No.
There he is,
mr. And mrs. Ransome.
Sit down. Make
yourselves comfortable.
I'm very happy
to meet you.
We're happy
to meet you, sir.
You've had a pleasant voyage?
Oh, yes,
sir. We're...
we're grateful to
have been part of it.
Indeed?
Well, that's very nice.
I suppose you've packed
your things?
Hmm?
They don't know yet.
Oh?
Well... i suppose
it's all the same.
Don't know what, sir?
Oh, nothing.
We thought it would be
better this way,
captain.
You know, your presence
aboard has been rather-
how shall i say? -
symbolic.
Us ending, as it were,
and you beginning.
Our captain's quite
a romantic, isn't he?
Extraordinary man.
Well, if you'll
excuse me,
i have some business
to attend to.
You'll be back?
Very shortly. Yes.
Well, look at me.
That's cute.
I see thelady anne
has worked her magic on you.
Oh, yes. She andyou-
all of you.
I can't tell you
how grateful we are.
See, we'd forgotten
so many things.
As mr. Burgess said,
people don't know
how to relax.
Rush, rush, rush.
I guess i was rushing.
I forgot the most important
things in my life.
But i won't lose sight
of them again.
I say, let's drink
to that, shall we?
Yes, here we are.
Cheers.
Thank you.
What's that?
What's what?
The engines. They've stopped.
Some slight difficulty.
Nothing, nothing, nothing.
Mrs. Ransome,
may i have the pleasure
of this dance?
Oh, i was hoping
you'd ask me.
Thank you.
Mrs. Mckenzie
i'm not
very good, but, uh...
delighted,
mr. Ransome.
Good old millie.
Got your hands full.
Not so much
of the "old," dear.
Had enough
of it, did you?
Thank you.
I see they haven't
got them fixed.
What fixed?
The engines.
Oh?
No.
Your things have been
gathered together.
What things?
Why, your luggage.
Really, mckenzie,
i'd have thought
you'd have told them by now.
Yes...
well, we're all having
such a fine time
i didn't want
to spoil the fun.
Excuse me,
but what are you talking about?
Why should we gather
our things together?
Because, my friends,
we're putting you off the ship.
You're what?
Putting you
off the ship.
What do you mean?
Just that.
Why? Are we in trouble?
No, no...
well, then why?
There's no time
for explanations.
If mr. Mckenzie had done
as he promised,
they wouldn't
even be necessary.
Skip the explanation.
They'll understand eventually.
Maybe, but we're not
going anywhere
until we understand why.
I'm afraid
you haven't any choice.
Follow me, please.
No.
Unless this is
some sort of gag.
Oh, it is, isn't it?
I mean, you don't just
put passengers off a ship
in mid-ocean.
He's kidding, isn't he?
Follow the captain,
please.
We'll come
along with you.
A bit of
the way, anyhow.
Better bring
your coat, millie.
My boy,
mustn't worry too much.
Your exact position's
been radioed.
Even now,
help's on the way.
Your luggage is
in the boat, you see.
Biscuits, flares...
and some champagne,
i saw to that.
Coats and provisions
are in the boat.
Oh, and it sends out
an automatic signal.
Really...
everything
you need.
Except a reason.
I'm sorry.
It's time we were off.
Into the boat,
please.
But why?
Is it something we've done?
No, not a bit of it.
Then for heaven's sake, why?
Tell us.
You can't just put someone
off a ship
in the middle of the ocean
without a reason.
There's a reason, my boy.
We like you people.
We thought you liked us.
They do.
Lower away!
Better put on those coats.
You'll get cold.
Wrap up warm.
Yes, wrap up warm.
Good-bye! Bye-bye!
Stiff upper lip! Keep it up!
Cheers!
Cold?
I've never felt so warm
in my whole life.
Thelady anne
never reached port.
After they were picked up
by a cutter
a few hours later,
as captain protheroe
had promised,
the ransomes searched
the newspapers for news,
but there wasn't any news.
Thelady anne, with all her
crew and all her passengers,
vanished without a trace.
But the ransomes knew
what had happened.
They knew that the ship had
sailed off to a better port-
a place called
the twilight zone.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org