Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Mr. Mulligan, a rather
dour critic of his times,
is shortly to discover
the import of that old phrase,
"out of the frying pan,
into the fire"-
said fire burning brightly
at all times
in the twilight zone.
You better move,
mister.
Get out of the street.
You want
to get yourself killed?!
Hey, get out of there.
Harmony?
Hey!
Hey! That's mine!
There's nothing going on
around here, sergeant.
Everything's as quiet as a...
mouse!
Hey, you!
Call you back, sergeant.
Hey!
Stop in the name of the law!
Oh!
You juvenile delinquent, you!
Oh, no!
It's broken.
How am i going
to get back now?
I only got 15 minutes.
Let me try to
understand this, sir.
You have this
funny-looking hat, no pants,
and you've got to get
back to somewhere
within 15 minutes?
Right.
This is a time helmet.
I'm from 1890.
That's where i've
got to get back to.
And your trousers?
I hung them up
to dry in 1890.
You're from 1890?
What proof have you?
Proof?
Yes. Ah! That watch.
Those clothes.
Where did
you get them?
They're mine.
Is it possible?!
Quickly- who
is the president?
You mean
benjamin harrison?
Benjamin harrison.
And before him?
Grover cleveland.
But what's that...?
By george!
I believe you, sir!
You are from 1890!
Well, that's
no news to me.
How to get back
would be news.
And this is
the device, eh?
How does it work?
Well, you...
well, i don't know!
See, i'm only
the janitor.
Janitor, hmm?
Hmm. Primitive,
but functional.
Yes, yes, yes.
Fascinating.
Oh! Where are
you going?
Proprietor!
Propri...
yeah?
Would you come here
a moment, please?
Yes, please.
What is it?
Can you fix it?
We can fix anything.
Good.
Thursday,
about 2:00.
Thursday?!
You don't understand.
This man must
get back to 1890.
Oh, you're in
the wrong block.
This is
only 1600.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's a time helmet.
And this man
is from the year 1890.
What are you,
some kind of nut?
I'm an electronic
scientist.
Now, just lend me
those tools...
don't touch!
But this is...
don't touch...
don't touch
the tools!
Listen to me.
Howdy.
I'm going to tell you something.
Yeah.
That man doesn't
have all his buttons.
Oh, you don't believe me, huh?
Well, i'll prove it to you.
Look at these papers.
We barely have
15 minutes
to get back to his
time continuum.
If you'll repair...
excuse me.
This feller says
he hasn't got
all his buttons.
What's he mean,
he has no buttons?
Means he has no mental
facilities, yes?
Who said that?
This feller here
in the window.
That's tv!
Who's tv?
Tv- television.
Oh, you wouldn't
understand if i told...
what on earth are you
doing, young man?
Don't do that
to me, pal.
Look, look, look.
All we want
is this soldered
to that.
Don't touch the
tools, will you?
You don't
understand.
D-d-don't touch my tools,
if you don't mind.
Look, allow me to
show this to you.
Don't touch
the tools!
What did you say?
I'm trying
to explain to you...
don't holler.
Don't holler!
You don't...
just a moment, please.
Now...
help!
Help!
H-h-help!
H-h-he...
what are you
doing in here?!
Now, look, we want to get
this thing finished in time.
Just sit down
quietly, please.
Now.
You sure this isn't
some kind of
a coffee maker?
No, sir, that's a
very scientific
piece of equipment.
Five dollars, please.
What is that little
thing in there?
Oh, well,
that, you see...
that is a transitron.
Don't... don't
touch my tools,
if you don't mind.
I'm merely trying
to point out to you that,
in order to
facilitate that...
don't point with
my tools, please.
Would you allow me
to please make this
clear to you?
Don't you understa...?
That's mine!
Oh, just a moment!
Now where has he gone?
Come on out.
Will you come out?!
Just keep working.
Keep working!
Hey...
what's the idea
of running around
the street
with no pants on?
Alley... oop!
Well, is it ready?
Couple of small,
minor adjustments,
you'll
be all set.
I envy you
your trip, sir.
1890 is a
wonderful period.
Mmm. For instance,
no income tax.
Income tax?
I am a scholar
of that period, sir.
It has a charm- nay,
a fascination- for me.
The very thought
of having lived
in those halcyon days...
i'll sure be glad
to get back.
If i ever do.
How much time
is there left?
Oh...
we got less than
five minutes!
Mmm. Tell me
about your town, sir.
Where, for instance,
might a scientist
find employment?
You a scientist?
Yes. Are there any
in your town?
Well, professor gilbert.
I work for him.
There you are, gentlemen.
All fixed.
Good. What
do we do now?
Uh... pay me.
Hmm?
Pay the man,
pay the man.
Ah! That's just
the right amount.
Thank you.
Uh... how does
it work?
Oh, you just
set this dial.
Good!
Hey, what are
you doing?
I intend to
use it myself
in exactly
three minutes.
You can't do that!
But iam
doing it, sir.
I'm returning to
that time of bliss
and simple pleasures!
And leaving me here?
Your fate is
unimportant, sir.
You are a janitor.
I am a scientist!
Why, i...
stand back!
In less than
three minutes,
i shall have escaped
this age of madness!
Look, look.
I brought a chicken
with me
all the way from 1890.
All i did was hold it.
We can go back together.
You're lying, sir.
I am not.
Hey, look out!
Get that nut
out of here.
1890, here i come.
"To each his own."
So goes another old phrase
to which mr. Woodrow mulligan
would heartily subscribe.
For he has learned,
definitely the hard way,
that there is much wisdom
in a third old phrase
which goes as follows:
"Stay in your own backyard."
To which it might be added,
"and, if possible, assist
others to stay in theirs."
Via, of course,
the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, onthe twilight zone,
you'll find yourself
inexplicably entangled
in this dark dungeon.
You'll meet an incredible
group of people who, like you,
will be quite unable to explain
how they got there,
why they got there,
or how they're going to get out.
And, at the end,
we're going to belt you
with one of the most surprising
endings we've ever had.
Next week, "five characters
in search of an exit"
onthe twilight zone.
Seat belts can reduce
serious injury by one-third.
Does your family have
the security of seat belts?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org