Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Help!
Please help!
Who is it?
Go away.
I've been shot.
I need help.
Who are you?
An... officer.
Police.
Please,
open the door.
I need help.
You're lying to me.
I know you.
You can't fool me.
Help.
You're lying.
You're no policeman.
Why can't you
leave me alone?
I know who you are.
I knowwhatyou are.
An old woman
living in a nightmare.
An old woman who has fought
a thousand battles with death
and always won.
Now she's faced
with a grim decision:
Whether or not to open a door.
And in some strange
and frightening way,
she knows that this
seemingly ordinary door
leads to the twilight zone.
Won't somebody help?
Unless you help me,
i'm going to die.
I...
i don't think
i can move.
Don't say that,
it isn't fair.
You're trying
to trick me.
Don't move.
L-l-i'll close the door.
What?
I've been shot.
I'm bleeding to death.
Please.
My name is harold... beldon.
I need a doctor.
Please, call the hospital.
I haven't got a telephone.
I'd have to unlock the door.
You can't ask me to do that.
I don't want to die.
You understand.
I know who you are.
You're not going to help me?
You're going to let me die?
I don't understand.
But... it hurts.
Oh, it hurts.
Stop. Stop.
Why do you torture me?
It isn't fair.
I... i can't move.
I...
ooh, it hurts.
It isn't fair.
I'm still alive.
Now, listen, you should
try and get some rest.
Really, i feel much better.
When the doctor gets here,
he'll take me off your hands.
You didn't call the doctor.
Why not?
I haven't got
a telephone.
But couldn't you go
to one of the neighbors?
There aren't any,
they've all moved away.
Trucks came and took
away their furniture.
First one and
then another.
And...
even-even if i could
call a doctor somehow,
i couldn't take a chance
and let him in.
Don't you see?
He might behim.
Him?
Mr. Death.
I know he's out there.
He's trying to get in.
He comes to the door
and knocks.
He begs me to let him in.
Last week he said
he came from the gas company.
Oh, he's clever.
After that, he claimed to be
a contractor hired by the city.
I knew who he was.
He said this building
was condemned
that i'd have to leave.
I kept the door locked,
and he went away.
He knows i'm onto him.
Mr. Death?
Is this a person,
like you or me?
I know it sounds crazy,
but it's true.
I know it's true.
But
people die
all over
the world.
Now how could one man
be in all those places
at once?
I don't know.
Don't ask me that.
Maybe there is more than one.
Maybe...
please don't cry, i...
i don't want
to hurt you.
Please, i'm sorry.
There.
At first,
i couldn't be sure.
It was a long time ago.
I was on a bus.
There was
an old woman
sitting in front
of me knitting.
Socks, i think.
There was something
about her face.
I thought i knew her.
Then this
young man got on.
There were empty seats,
but he sat down beside her.
He didn't say
anything, but...
his being there upset her.
He seemed a nice young man.
When she dropped her yarn,
he picked it up,
right in front of me.
He held it out to her.
I saw their fingers touch.
He got out at the next stop.
When the bus reached
the end of the line...
she was dead.
Hmm.
But you said yourself
she was an old woman.
But i've seen him since,
several times.
I've seen him in crowds,
i've watched for him.
Every time someone i knew died,
he was there.
Once he was a young soldier,
a salesman, a taxi driver-
someone you wouldn't notice
unless you
were watching.
I wondered why
i could see him
and that no one
else could.
Then i knew.
It was because
i was getting older
and my time was coming.
I could see clearer than
younger people could.
All right.
But if you knew what he
looked like, why be afraid?
You could avoid him.
Because his face is always
different, i couldn't be sure.
How about when you go out?
Couldn't he touch you then
if he wanted to?
I never go out.
Never?
I haven't been
out for years.
Well, what do you do about food?
A boy delivers it.
I leave him money and a list.
And i always wait
until he's gone away
before i unlock the door.
How can you live like this?
If i don't live like this,
i won't live at all.
If i don't watch out,
if i let down
even for a moment,
he'll get in.
I know he will.
I haven't always
lived like this.
I was young once.
People said i was pretty.
I lived out in the sunlight.
People said i'd spoil
my fine complexion.
I didn't care.
I loved outdoor things.
I lived out in the sunlight.
I've always hated
the dark and the cold.
I'm old.
I've lived a long time.
But i don't want to die.
I'd rather live in the dark
than not live at all.
Here.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
We're alone here.
And there's nobody at the door.
You need some rest...
and i need help.
No.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
You better answer it.
Go on.
That's right.
Go ahead.
Go ahead,
answer it.
I'm sorry, lady,
but i've got my orders.
I can't fool around any longer.
Easy, lady.
Just lie quiet
till you get
your strength back.
You gave me quite a scare
when you caved in like that.
And still i live.
You got to understand,
ma'am, i...
i don't get no pleasure
out of busting in doors.
You don't seem
to realize
how important
this is.
I've got a-a crew and
equipment coming in an hour
to pull this tenement down.
Begging your pardon, ma'am,
but it's long overdue.
I'm surprised
it's still standing.
And you're really...
not mr. Death?
Well...
i don't know what
you're talking about.
All i know is
i got a contract to demolish
this row of buildings.
Everybody else
moved out long ago.
Until the other day,
i thought this building
was deserted.
I seen them windows boarded up,
and i figured you moved, too.
You want me to go outside?
You want me to leave here?
I can't.
You were notified months ago,
right?
I'm just trying to do my job.
These buildings
were condemned by the city,
and i'm the one
who's got
to tear them down.
How can you.
This building has had it.
It's worn out,
used up.
All these buildings
have got to come down.
I ain't a monster, lady.
I... i've got a heart
just like anybody else,
but, uh...
i can see how you
could get attached to a place
and not want
to see it wrecked,
but when a building is old,
it's dangerous.
It's got to come down
to make room for a new one.
That's life, lady.
Old make room for the new.
Well, people get the idea
that i'm kind of destroyer,
but...
they think i get kicks
out of tearing stuff down.
That ain't the way it is.
I... i just clear the ground
so other people can build.
In a way,
i help them do it.
Look around-
it's the way things are.
A big tree falls,
and a new one
grow right out
of the same ground.
Old animals die and...
young ones
take their places.
Even people step aside
when it's time.
I won't.
The door.
There's no need
in that.
Now, what's the sense
of locking a door
that won't even
be here in an hour?
If you've got any
possessions you'd want to keep,
i'd move them out.
I'll help you.
Now, look, i've been
trying to go easy,
but if you insist
on staying here,
i'll have to call a cop.
Please cooperate, lady.
Of course.
Explain to him.
Tell him the reason
i can't go out there.
You'll help me,
won't you?
What are you doing?
Who are you talking to?
Mr. Beldon
is a policeman.
Please tell him.
I'm sorry, but if
you're still here
when the crew arrives,
i'll have to call a cop.
Why didn't you help me?
I thought you understood.
You.
He looked right at you
and didn't see you.
No!
Look in the mirror, wanda.
You tricked me.
It was you
all the time.
Yes.
I tricked you.
But why?
The moment i let you inside,
you could have taken me
anytime.
But you were nice.
You made me trust you.
But i had
to make you understand.
Am i really so bad?
Am i really so frightening?
You've talked to me,
you've confided in me.
Have i tried to hurt you?
It isn't me you're afraid of.
You understand me.
What you're afraid of
is the unknown.
Don't...
don't be afraid.
But i am afraid.
The running's over.
It's time to rest.
Give me
your hand.
But i don't want to die.
Trust me.
No.
Mother,
give me your hand.
You see,
no shock.
No engulfment.
No tearing
asunder.
What you feared would
come like an explosion
is like a whisper.
What you thought
was the end
is the beginning.
When will it happen?
When will we go?
Go?
Look.
We have
already begun.
There was an old woman
who lived in a room
and, like all of us,
was frightened of the dark,
but who discovered in a minute
last fragment of her life
that there was nothing
in the dark that wasn't there
when the lights were on.
Object lesson for the more
frightened amongst us, in or out
of the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, onthe twilight zone,
we let you in on a... an
extravagant practical joke.
A man who wants
to convey an illusion
that the world
is coming to an end.
Now there are jokes
and there are jokes,
but this one
stands all by itself
as an exercise in the very
different and the very bizarre.
Our play is called
"one more pallbearer,"
and we commend it to you
as something quite special.
This is james arness.
You know, it's only a short hop
fromthe twilight zone
to dodge city ingunsmoke.
Saturday nights
over most of these stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org