Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Three glass
perfume bottles.
Threecrystalbottles.
To imprison the attar
of damask rose petals.
Two pottery jugs.
Pottery jugs?
Where's your
aesthetic sense, man?
You can't entice anyone
to buy "pottery jugs."
You think people buy something
'cause what you call it?
People don'tbuyanything
in a gift shop.
They come in because
they don't know what they want.
And then i...
sell them something.
Okay, what do you call
the pottery jugs?
We'll display those alongside
a couple of those silk pillows,
with a loaf of dark bread.
"A loaf of bread, a jug of wine,
and thou beside me
singing in the wilderness."
I'll unload them
in three days.
Okay, omar...
what do you call this?
Well...
when we buy
a shipment from morocco,
sight unseen,
we take what we get.
To sell this,
i'll have to high-pressure
some unsuspecting sucker.
Yes, sir, may i
help you, sir?
Well, i, i hope so.
I mean, i'm not sure.
I don't know what i want.
Well, suppose you
tell me the occasion
and for whom
it's intended,
and, uh...
leave it up to me.
Well, it's, it's got to be
something very special.
Yes.
A, um...
personal gift, sir?
Oh, not, not
toopersonal, no.
You see, there's this, uh,
girl at my office,
and she's...
she's like a goddess.
And i wouldn't want her to
think that i was implying...
i understand, sir.
Oh, i have it.
It's ideal, it's perfect,
it's marvelous.
It's romantic,
but not forward,
and yet, intime, in a subtle
sort of way, of course.
Voila.
That, that old...?
This magnificent
old antique-
a truly distinguished antique-
fit for a goddess.
A continual reminder
of your-your good taste,
your individuality,
your-your flair for romance.
Note the tarnished metal.
It testifies
to its true authenticity,
and only $20.
Here, put this
in a gift box
for a most discriminating
gentleman.
Thank you, sir.
And i trust that you will allow
me to serve you again
when it comes time
for the, uh...
engagement present?
Hmm.
Meet mr. George p. Hanley
a man life treats
without deference,
honor or success.
Waiters serve his soup cold.
Elevator operators close doors
in his face.
Mothers never bother to wait up
for the daughters he dates.
George is a creature
of humble habits
and tame dreams.
He's an ordinary man,
mr. Hanley,
but at this moment,
the accidental possessor
of a very special gift...
the kind of gift that measures
men against their dreams...
the kind of gift most of us
might ask for first
and possibly regret
to the last...
if we,
like mr. George p. Hanley,
were about to plunge headfirst
and unaware
into our own personal
twilight zone.
Hi, there,
georgie-porgie.
Where were
you for lunch?
Well, l-i had
a few errands.
Well, you missed
the world's champion
worst chili con carne
ever offered
for human consumption.
It set an historic new low
even for that greasy spoon
nick dares to call a diner.
I don't care much for chili.
Georgie, witness
a solemn vow for me, will you?
Right now? But i have to enter
these municipal bonds.
I, roger hackett,
do solemnly swear
never again to commit
gastronomic harl-kari at nick's,
beginning with the first day of
my promotion to head bookkeeper.
But mr. Watson said that
each of us with equal seniority
would have an equal chance.
That is true, georgie,
old porgie, we're all equal.
But some of us are just a teeny
bit more equal than others.
Especially me.
Now, mr. Watson
is fair, roger.
Now, don't-don't
don't be overconfident.
I'm sure he will
weigh carefully
our comparative
experience
in debit
financing
and in evaluating
liabilities.
That, old georgie,
is one reason
i am more equal than you.
W-what is?
You're always thinking
about debits and liabilities
when there are assets
like her around.
Guess who?
Roger?
Happy birthday...
oh!
...to the prettiest girl
in this entire office!
Happy birthday!
Many more.
No, but i'm theonlygirl.
And-and you would
remain the prettiest,
even if this office
were staffed with
the assembled
miss americas of
the past five years.
Now, stop fishing
for compliments and
open your present.
Well... i wonder
what it could be.
Oh, roger!
Hey, hey!
Oh, it's beautiful!
Ann, put it on.
Fellas, fellas...
can you just picture
old man watson's puss
when he calls her
in for dictation?
How 'bout that, huh?
Mr. Watson has a mind for
a different kind of figure, sam.
You, uh, really
like it, ann?
Oh, roger, i absolutelyloveit.
But, really, you shouldn't
have been so extravagant.
Well, after all, a girl
only has a birthday
once a year-
until she's 30, of course.
And then she has them
once every two years...
roger.
Come over here.
There.
Now, that's to show you
my appreciation.
And to show you
that i haven't even learned
how to count to 30 yet.
M-mr. Watson.
It... it's my birthday.
Oh.
Do any of you happen to be
aware of the annual statement
issued by this organization...
no, sir, no, sir.
...on miss lawson's birthday?
No, sir.
Then i'm sure it'll come
as an agreeable surprise
that this company
has just completed
the best year in its history.
And i believe that
this department
had no little part
in that success.
Oh!
Oh, that's
wonderful.
So, as a token of my
personal appreciation,
i think that this
is an appropriate time
to invite all of you
to be my guests
at a celebration party
beginning as soon
as we can meet
at the club tiki.
Oh, mr. Watson.
Mr. Watson?
Yes?
Mr. Watson,
you are a doll.
Ah. Thank you.
And as for you, young lady,
they're not the only ones
who appreciate you.
Uh, claudius?
Oh...
happy birthday
to the best-looking
and the hardest-working,
secretary i ever had.
Oh, mr. Watson,
they're just beautiful.
Yes.
Oh, thank you,
thank you so much.
Yes.
Hey, let's go, kid,
before the old man
discovers he's off his nut
and has himself committed.
I think he's a very
sweet, dear man.
Hap... happy
birthday, ann.
Oh, well,
thank you, george.
Aren't you coming?
Oh, yeah,
l-i'll be along.
We'll see you there.
Come along, roger.
Maybe i can use it
for an ashtray or something.
Hiya, buddy.
Hey, how are you, huh?
Come here, attila.
Come on, boy.
Here we go! Ha!
Come on, how was
your day, huh?
Here, look, hey!
Here you go, come on, beg.
Sit, sit, up, stand, sit.
Heel, fall, atta boy!
Oh, you ain't but
a good doggie.
Oh, boy, oh, i
love you, attila.
Okay, buddy, let's see
what's going on here, huh?
Go on, go sit.
Huh? There you go.
Ah, there.
Full moon, attila.
Ooh, how are the girls?
Here you go, there you are.
Did you have a good day, too?
Ah... boy.
Hmm.
Why does it always
happen to me, attila?
Come on, boy.
Hmm? Why does it
always happen to me?
S-sometimes i think some
people must have been born
with a-a silver spoon
in their mouths.
Me, i must have been born
with egg on my face.
Huh.
Now i didn't
give her any present.
You know, attila, i know
just what people think of me.
A patsy, a jerk.
Hmm, hmm...
especially that roger.
Sometimes i think
they're right.
George p. Hanley.
Jerk.
Hey, attila, what
are you barking at?
That box?
Well, come on, attila,
you can't
bark at the box
and hide in back of the
couch at the same time.
You'll give yourself
some kind of a trauma.
Be brave, boy,
be brave.
We're two of a kind, you and me.
Come on,
i'll show you.
Be brave, attila.
Be brave! Here, boy.
Come here. Come on, fella.
There you go.
Here, look, i'll show it to you.
Look, see?
It's just a box with a...
with a with a with
a beat-up old lamp in it.
That's all. There.
Probably came
from some junkyard.
See?
Magnificent old antique,
of rare distinction.
Boy, if being a jerk
is my vocation,
at least i'm good at it.
Gosh... it's so tarnished,
it almost looks black.
Hmm.
Hmm? What's the matter?
Eh, you tell 'em, attila.
Like me, a little late.
Well, let's clean it up.
Sure must be old,
if dirt's any sign.
Who... who... who...
who were you expectin'?
Who...?
I'm the genie in the lamp,
that's who.
Aladdin, magic, the whole bit.
Ge-genie.
G-genie?
Yeah.
You-you don't
look like a genie.
Well, what difference
does the wardrobe make?
The routine's the same.
You see, a couple
of thousand years ago,
i used to wear those crazy
silk balloon long johns
with the wild turban.
But let me tell
you something, jack.
George.
Jack, george,
as long as you're healthy.
Today, we dress
like the times.
Except for these.
Velveteen mukluks.
Mukluks.
Mm-hmm.
Genie.
If-if you
are the genie,
then i must be the
master of the lamp.
Big deal, master of the lamp.
All right,
you got yourself a free wish.
There's supposed
to be three wishes.
Ah, there's the rub.
There used to be three wishes.
But let me tell you
something, jack.
George.
You don't want
to change your name, huh?
Uh...
the scene used
to include three wishes,
but the recipients
were abusing the privilege,
so we had to cut down.
So, uh, give it
a little thought.
Give me a call.
But do me a favor, will you?
Sleep on it.
Sleep on it?
Yeah, you know
the routine.
Once you make the wish, that's
what you have to live with.
What do people
usually wish for?
Oh, let me tell
you something, jack-
george.
The wildest.
Oh, it's enough
to make you blush.
A fortune, they wish for.
Money, precious jewels...
that's not so bad.
It's not so bad, huh?
You see, you're
no different
from the rest.
All right, you get yourself
a lot of riches, a lot of dough.
Now you're in trouble
with the internal revenue.
You got a lot
of phony charities
come buggin' you.
Long-lost relatives come banging
at your door.
It's enough to make you
flip your gourd.
Not-not wealth, huh?
Forget the wealth.
Maybe... love.
Love?
That's what you'd wish for?
What are you,
some kind of a kook?
You call me back
from 2,000 years
to come and help you
and you wish for love?
You don't wish for love, jack,
you find it.
But i'm not really sure
what it is i want.
And if it isn't wealth or love,
i... i don't know.
Well, like i told you,
give it a little thought, huh?
Ponder, drop it down the well
a couple of times,
see if it splashes.
But don't go rubbing that lamp
every time you get a bug,
'cause that smoke is murder
on my sinus.
The next time i make
the scene, that's it.
Like, later...
george.
I can't believe it.
Anything i want
in the whole world.
Anything!
But only one wish.
Which one, attila?
Which one?
A million dollars.
No, he's right,
that's the 90% bracket.
Love?
Too risky.
George hanley...
first man on the moon.
scientist.
General george p. Hanley...
commander of the armies.
What if, what if
i were married to ann?
What if... what if she were
some kind of a...
some kind of a movie actress,
and i were her husband?
That would be killing two birds
with one stone.
George...
george hanley,
husband of-of ann...
ann alexandra.
America's sweethearts.
The perfect couple.
How about that?
Yeah...
yeah, how about that?
Remember, miss alexandra,
you love the guy so much
that you do
a loop-the-loop
as soon as you smell
his after-shave lotion.
I'll try.
Oh, darling.
Hello, dear.
Ooh, ooh, ooh-
makeup, georgie.
Oh...
you wouldn't want me
to play my final scene
with smeared
lipstick, would you?
No, i guess not.
Final scene?
Mm-hmm.
It's been a long grind.
They said you could have
a couple of weeks off,
but that was six months ago.
Well...
we could take
our honeymoon now.
If you want to, that is.
Want to?
Oh.
Ooh, georgie.
Makeup all day,
beauty creams all night.
Well, they don't pay a movie
star to look ugly, baby.
Besides...
don't you think i'm
worth waiting for?
Yeah, sure, but six months...
places, please!
Be right there.
I won't be long.
Oh, what a day!
Trying, endless day...
tonight, no... no
crawling into bed
right after dinner
to study your lines.
And tomorrow morning,
no getting up at 4:30 a.m.
To get to the
studio for makeup.
Oh, i like that face
just the way it is.
Oh, oh, i'm
sorry, darling.
It's just
that i'm worn out
from that ersatz d.w. Griffith
howling at me all day.
I thought you liked him.
Yes, i suppose.
But he is so noisy.
He always seems to measure
virility by decibels.
Well, i guess maybe
he'll be quieter
at the party tonight.
What party?
Oh, did you forget?
The celebration party
on the set tonight.
Oh, yeah.
We'll... leave
the party early.
Oh!
Oh, gee!
Oh, georgie.
Oh, dear.
Here, kiss me
right up there.
Oop! Be careful
of the hair, darling.
All right.
There'll be a million
photographers there tonight,
and andre will have a
convulsion if it's ruined.
There!
Andre should carry
medical insurance.
Now!
What i want
is a nice, hot bath
for about an hour.
Would you like me
to rub your back?
No, thank you, darling.
You know what
you could do for me?
You could take the dog
for a walk.
He's been cooped up all day.
Hi, boy, how are you?
There we go,
that's a good boy.
Come on, there
we go, attila.
That a boy.
Let's go for a
little walk, huh?
George! George boy!
Hi.
I want to talk to you.
Ann mentioned something
about you needing a vacation.
Oh, not me. Her.
Both of us together.
I'm not going
to mince words.
You got to say it's okay for ann
to do my next picturebeowulf.
Not a chance, eli.
It's our honeymoon.
Great. I'm shootingbeowulf
on location-
make a great honeymoon.
Some honeymoon, hmm?
Makeup call at 4:30 a.m.,
work all day,
study lines all night.
Do you know the last time i saw
her in the last six months
when she wasn't sleeping
she was getting herself swabbed
with makeup, beauty creams,
rinses or some junk like that.
She's a star.
You wouldn't want her
photographed
with bags under eyes
or wrinkles.
All i want is to see her alone
with bags or wrinkles.
You want the world's most
beautiful woman for a wife,
you got to share her
with the world.
I did for six months.
Now i want the world
to share her back.
Son... it's not for myself,
but no ann, nobeowulf.
But there are other stars.
Not like ann alexandra.
Millions of plain folks
all over the world
wait to see her.
Little kids count their pennies.
Mothers go without lunch.
And brave men sacrifice even
the tiny luxury of a cigarette
so they can buy a ticket
to a movie theater
and escape the drab
drudgery of an
uncaring world
watching their idol
ann alexandra.
Looking like a fairy tale,
doing all the things they dream
but never get to do.
I know.
Well, then, george,
couldn't you find it
in your heart
to make this
one little sacrifice?
You're right, mr. Watson.
I'll... i'll tell her
to do the picture.
We'll make the sacrifice
together.
Ann, darling, you
look magnificent!
You, too.
Well, please, please,
i'd like to make
an announcement.
Better yet, i'll
make it a toast.
Thanks, old man.
To the brightest star,
the most exciting
leading lady...
the loveliest
woman in the world.
Ann alexandra,
who has just agreed
to star with me
inbeowulf!
Congratulations.
Now, darling,
remember the makeup.
Besides, i'm not
as good in profile.
Hey, stop, thief!
Who's that?
Me, mister.
You hiding?
I snap something.
Nobody down
on this level yet.
Uh...
you make
your repairs?
Always i have
the accidents.
It is because i am-
how you say?
Too much prone?
Would you like
your drink now?
No, no, that
is just to hold.
I am under the age.
Under the age?
To drink.
I have this
terrible problem.
You see, in the
years, i am a child,
but i think i am mature.
Don't you think i am...
mature?
Yeah, i think you're mature.
You are producer, no?
Me? No.
Director?
Mm-mm.
Writer?
Sorry.
Then l-i cannot
guess who you are.
I'm george hanley.
Who?
Ann alexandra's husband.
Well, for pete's sake,
give me back my drink!
That's what you deserve
for wasting my time,
mr. Alexander.
Now, aren't you glad
you're here tonight?
Don't be egotistical.
I had to be here, anyway.
I don't understand you.
No man is supposed to.
That's the way
we little girls are.
Well, that part
i understand.
Mmm, i'll spoil
your makeup.
Who cares?
Ooh, oh.
Oh, boy.
Whew! I'm okay, boy.
Wow, what a dream.
You know something, attila?
The trouble for a guy like me
is that... when i want
something so much,
it would hurt that much more
to lose it.
Let's face it, l-i would
lose a wife like that.
But i still got you, huh, boy?
Yeah, you still love me.
Well, at least
it makes it easier to choose.
All i have to decide now
is between the two other things
i've always wanted.
Yeah. Hmm.
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
Good morning, george.
George?
Morning, rog.
Morning.
Well, today's
the day.
For what, rog?
What's got
into you?
Me?
All i said
was "morning, rog"
and "for
what, rog?"
I don't think
those are very
pregnant phrases.
You're real feisty
this morning, aren't you,
georgie, old porgie?
Hey, has watson said anything
to you about the promotion?
Oh, the promotion.
I forgot about that.
Huh, yeah, i'll bet.
Yes, sir.
Roger?
Hmm?
Mr. Watson wants you
in his office right away.
Oh, right away.
This could be it.
Well...
over the top.
They'd never pick him.
Never.
George? The old boy
wants another check
on all these entries.
For what?
A new account,
personal.
Hey, this guy is so
loaded, he could pay off
the national debt
out of petty cash.
But didn't you check those
entries after you made them?
Well, sure!
Well, then why do we
have to do it again?
That's not efficiency.
That's a waste of time.
George...
how much do you make a week?
Same as you, $98.50.
Well, this joker makes
so much dough
that he sweats more than $98.50
every time he ties
his shoelaces.
So, uh, waste
a little time, hmm?
What about this wealth bit?
I mean, even with
90% off for taxes,
there, there'd still be
something left over.
George hanley...
no, make it g. Peter hanley...
tycoon.
G. Peter hanley,
captain of industry.
Crown prince
of financial royalty.
G. Peter hanley, rich guy.
Beautiful day,
isn't it, sir?
It'll do, it'll do.
Will you be wanting me
for lunch, sir?
I can't say,
but you'd better
keep yourself available,
just in case...
roger.
Yes, sir.
No, no, we
can't play now, boy.
I'm so sorry, i couldn't
hold him, mr. Hanley.
Yes. Roger, you better take
attila over to "21"
and have the chef fix him up
a nice prime rib of beef, huh?
Yes.
Oh, and not too fatty.
Yes, sir.
Oh, also,
you better trot him
around the block
a couple of times.
His appetite's
a bit jaded.
Yes, sir.
Atta boy.
Come on, boy.
Paper, sir? Paper?
Son...
how old are you?
Nine, sir.
I see you here every morning.
Don't you miss school?
Oh, no, sir.
I wouldn't miss school.
I get up at 5:00 for my papers,
then i go to the afternoon
session at p.s. 31.
Incredible.
What do your parents say?
My mom is dead.
My old man had a store,
but it went broke.
I'm sorry, son.
I'll have that paper.
Yes, sir.
Gosh, i can't change $100 bill.
I didn't expect you to, son.
Good morning,
mr. Hanley.
Trl-electronics, up 7/8
on the morning ticker.
Glad to have
you back, sir.
Thank you,
thank you.
How was
the riviera, sir?
All right, i guess.
It's kind of like
a suburban tract,
only all castles.
Gay social whirl,
was it, sir?
I was about whirled out
after the first six parties.
They even gave one
to celebrate the
incoming of the tide.
Miss lawson, would
you take care of these?
They're a bit soiled.
Certainly, mr. Hanley.
Can't they
be cleaned?
We throw them away, sir.
In your tax bracket,
it's cheaper.
I suppose, i suppose.
Shall i start
the people in, sir?
Yes, you might as well.
Very good, sir.
Dr. Watson...
what brings you here, sir?
Begging again,
i'm afraid.
These days, a college
president is much
more concerned
with salesmanship
than scholarship.
Sit.
Thank you, george.
You've come
to the right man, sir.
George, you've already done
more for your alma mater
than we have a right to ask.
This is an emergency,
or i wouldn't be here.
How much, sir?
Too much, but i'm hoping
you'll be able
to start the ball rolling.
Don't be coy with me, sir.
How much?
All together, 1,200,000.
Now, if you could possibly
start us off
with, say, uh,
ten or 20,000...
you've got it.
You're a generous man, g.p.
We're all in your debt.
George...
you've made a mistake.
No, sir, i've always been
rather good with figures.
It's the entire sum,
1,200,000.
Deductible.
No, george, i can't take this.
But i want to give it.
So would others, george.
Thousands of alumni, not as
successful, not as fortunate.
But every bit as generous.
Giving, sharing the burden
and the satisfaction
is the cement which
binds their minds and hearts
to our beloved alma mater.
I can't let you
deprive them
of the great privilege
of giving.
I was only trying
to help, sir.
This isn't generosity, g.p.
It's ostentation.
I'm sorry.
What should i do?
Send me your check for
the 20,000 i asked for.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Well, sir, ready to see
how the old empire's faring?
I suppose so.
A few little
items here
i thought you wouldn't
want to miss, mr. Hanley.
I thought
i already owned one
of just about
everything ever made.
Ah, you can't keep up
with yankee
ingenuity and productivity.
We've got to buckle down
to some serious spending.
We can't let you have
too much cash available,
otherwise,
the government's liable
to invent a new tax bracket.
Now...
here we have
a handsome little yacht.
But i already own
a 94-footer docked
up at newport.
This one makes that
look like a dinghy.
Handsome, isn't it?
You know something,
masters?
Buying things isn't
any fun for me anymore.
Before i had money,
i, i used to look forward
to buying a secondhand car
like a... like a... kid
waiting for christmas.
Now there's no anticipation,
there's no hungering.
I... i just write checks.
Ah, you're feeling blue,
mr. Hanley.
I used to enjoy little things
like... an ice cream cone
when it was hot,
a ball game...
getting out of the apartment
for a walk in the park.
Now every time i go
for a walk in the park,
four people come up and ask me
when i'm going to subdivide it.
Masters, i'm going to quit
buying things.
That's subversive, sir.
I beg your pardon?
That's
un-american.
Salesmanship is our way of life.
Think of those men living
on blue sky and a prayer,
depending on you
for their daily commission.
They've got little ones,
mouths to feed.
No, mr. Hanley, you can't
stop buying, ever.
Buying is your destiny.
Don't waver now.
Do your duty, mr. Hanley.
Do your duty.
Congratulate me, george.
Hey, george, i said
congratulate me.
Con... congratulateyou?
Gentlemen,
you are now looking
at the new
head bookkeeper
of this entire
organization.
Congratulations.
Very nice.
Congratulations, roger.
Oh, thank you, thank
you, thank you.
But the first
thing i want to
tell you guys
is i intend to
keep my vow-
no more lousy
lunches at nick's.
Him...
they gave it to him.
He wasn't even a good chauffeur.
Well...
we're down to
the last wish, attila.
I'd never keep a beautiful wife.
And money... money's no fun
if you have everything.
You just sit around
and look at it.
Position.
Power, that's-that's what makes
the world go 'round these days.
Look at mr. Watson,
how he gave roger that job, huh?
Believe me, if-if i
had power, i'd be fair.
What do you think, attila?
Do we dare wish
that third thing?
Power.
Prerogative.
Push.
Why not?
George hanley, statesman.
G.p. Hanley,
controller of destinies.
George p. Hanley,
thegeorge p. Hanley.
Leader of men.
Oh, sir, you'll be exhausted.
Let me tell them
to hurry on to the airport.
Watson...
these people elected me.
They have placed
in these humble hands
their individual destinies.
I think it only fitting
that they see just what kind
of destiny they're getting.
They're getting the best,
mr. President.
Thank you, watson.
Thank you.
That means a great deal
to me, coming from you.
Very good, mr. Ambassador.
I agree.
No, there is nothing new
in our crisis.
Yes, sir.
Very good.
We are in agreement.
Yes, sir, very good.
Then go ahead, sir.
Mr. President,
this pension legislation
will tear the party in two.
If you let it come to the floor,
i for one won't get
a single vote in november from
anyone over the age of ten.
Have you checked
with the majority leader
to see if he can kill it
in committee?
No, i did not, sir.
Ask him. Tell him
the president said, "handle it."
Yes, sir.
Yes?
The situation is fraught with
tension in asia, mr. President.
We're not getting enough
intelligence down there.
Hold on.
Have the c.i.a. Prepare
a full staff study.
Tell bill you need it
right away.
Thank you, sir.
No.
Your appointment
schedule, mr. President.
Thank you, may.
Move the press conference
to after lunch;
i need a haircut.
Yes, sir.
I'll make the u.n. Speech.
Tell lorenson
to whip up a draft
and remind him- jokes.
Yes, mr. President.
Who are sonny and mickey?
Oh, they're the cub
scouts who wrote you
the letter
on citizenship.
You asked to
be reminded
when they came
into the capitol.
Aha.
Of course,
there's no time...
make time.
We'll have haircuts together.
Yes, sir. Oh, it's
almost 10:00.
Pardon me, murray.
20 million kilowatts
for the people of the southwest.
Too bad i can't make
all these dedications in person.
Miss may, pass this on
to the secretary of defense,
marked "expedite."
Yes, sir.
Save these for the cabinet
meeting, priority.
Yes, sir.
And get the economic advisory
council to dig in on this.
Right away, sir.
See me after lunch,
murray, won't you?
Hmm.
Come, boy.
Ah, come, attila.
How's my boy, eh?
Here we are.
Good boy.
Mmm.
Oh, mr. President,
i had to see you.
Who...
wh-what are you
doing there, woman?
L-i've been hiding
there all night, sir.
It was the only way.
They said you were
too busy.
Oh, please, please
listen to me, sir.
Don't send me away.
Oh, my good woman,
come, here you are.
Here you are.
Now, what, what can
i do for you, madam?
Mr. President, l-it's my son.
He's just a boy.
18.
He fell asleep on guard duty,
and they said it was treason.
They're going to hang
him, mr. President.
Hang him.
Easy now, easy.
He's in the service, your boy?
Yes, sir.
The army, special duty
at the missile base.
I see.
Falling asleep on duty
is very serious.
Oh, i know, sir.
Only a presidential
pardon can save him.
Oh, please, sir.
He's a good boy.
Just a little tired.
It could
happen to anyone.
Indeed it could, ma'am.
Then you'll do it?
You'll pardon him?
If freedom is our battle cry,
then justice and mercy
are our glory.
Ma'am... you tell your boy that
when you see him tomorrow.
Have the attorney general
prepare an order
for executive clemency
immediately.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you, thank
you, mr. President.
Mr. President,
you're a great man.
Bless you.
You see, attila?
Power is not
a difficult thing to handle.
All one has to know
is how to use it.
I couldn't wait,
mr. President.
Those blips on the radar screen
have just been identified-
spaceships.
From some
strange planet.
Spaceships from another planet?
Huge ones, hundreds of them.
Well, what'll we do?
We can't take chances.
Shoot them down!
You can't, mr. President.
There might be thousands
of innocent people aboard.
They're headed directly for us.
We signaled,
and they refused to answer.
It might be the
greatest breakthrough
of scientific investigation in
the history of the universe.
If they're advanced
enough to get here,
think of their weapons,
what they can do to us.
Our only chance is to
get them with missiles
before they arrive!
What if
they're friendly?
What if they aren't?
Let them land.
Counterattack before
it's too late.
The decision is up to
you, mr. President.
What about a staff study?
There isn't time!
Can we call the congress?
It's
too late!
The secretary of defense?
It's a matter of moments, sir.
It's up to you!
No, no, i can't decide!
I can't decide, no!
Not me! Not me! Not me!
Not me, not... not me.
Yeah, you, mac.
You and your mutt,
get off of my stoop.
Oh, okay, okay.
Come on, boy.
But you know something, attila?
No matter what i wished for,
it wouldn't change anything.
I'd still be me.
George p. Hanley.
Jerk.
What's the quotation?
"Men at some time
are masters of their fates."
"The fault," dear attila,
"is not in our stars,
but in ourselves."
Ourselves.
Get ready, you bored, old genie.
We're going to wish
for something... original!
Yes, master, i am the
genie of the lamp.
You may have three wishes.
But when you have made them,
you must return
the lamp to this alley
where others may find it.
At your service, sir.
Mr. George p. Hanley,
jerk.
Genie.
George p. Hanley,
a most ordinary man
whom life treated without
deference, honor, or success.
But a man wise enough to decide
on a most extraordinary wish
that makes him
the contented permanent master
of his own altruistic
twilight zone.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org