Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
He ain't here yet.
He'll be along.
He knows what's
waiting for him here.
He knows
he's going to get shot.
No question
about that.
I think i hear
him coming now.
Well, it's about time.
You're an hour and 15
minutes late, rance.
Sy, sy, sy,
don't start that.
You know how
emotional scenes
upset me before
we shoot. Ah!
Now, don't get
upset, rance...
what do you say
we get started?
All right, all right.
This is scene 71.
Got your script?
Read it to me.
Come on, tommy,
let's go.
Huh? Oh, sorry.
It's the interior,
saloon
cover shot of three
bad men at bar.
Rance mcgrew enters,
he walks to bar,
he glances sideways
left and right.
"Left and right."
You think my head
is on a swivel?
Listen, sy, when a
cowboy walks into a bar,
he walks straight to the
other end of the room,
then he takes his drink
and looks atthat,
then looks
straight ahead.
He doesn't look
left and right.
All right, rance,
we'll shoot it your way-
any way you want.
Now, can we begin?
In a minute,
in a minute.
My stomach is
killing me.
These scenes,
these miserable
emotional scenes.
All right, laddies,
let's get this one this time.
This is scene 71.
It's a cover shot
of rance entering the saloon.
Now, let's get with it,
fellas, please.
We're way behind.
Second team out.
The star is here.
Some 100-odd years ago,
a motley collection
of tough moustaches
galloped across the west
and left behind a raft
of legends and legerdemains.
And it seems
a reasonable conjecture
that if there are any television
sets up in cowboy heaven
any one of these rough
and woolly nail-eaters could see
with what careless abandon
their names and exploits
are being bandied about.
They're very likely turning over
in their graves-
or worse, getting out of them.
Which gives you a clue
as to the proceedings
that will begin in just a moment
when one mr. Rance mcgrew,
a 3,000-buck-a-week
phony baloney,
discovers that this week's
current edition of make-believe
is being shot on location
and that location
is the twilight zone.
Six-gun...
dress it up.
We'll wait
for the
new glass.
You win.
You ready out
there, rance?
Yes.
All right. Action.
Rotgut whiskey.
All right, wise guy.
Cut.
He put english on that
deliberately.
An english
on a bottle?
Guy needs a
catcher's mitt.
All right,
let's try it again.
From the bottle.
All right,
positions,
please.
Scene 71... again.
Action.
Guess you boys know
i'm the marshal.
We heard tell.
I guess you know that i know
jesse james is coming here
looking for me.
I know that, too.
Likewise.
There's something else i know
that you don't know-
that you don't know that i know
that you know jesse james.
You tell him i'm going
to be here waiting.
I'll be right here waiting.
Now, we hear the
horse ride up,
he stops, dismounts...
and he appears
on the porch.
Figured i'd bluffed you.
Here already, ain't he?
Marshal, marshal, please.
No killing in here.
Oh, i ain't aiming
to kill him.
Just going to maim
him a little bit.
Just going to pick
off his pinkie.
Jesse ain't going to
take kindly to that.
No.
Cut.
All right, we'll
bring in jesse here.
Ready, jesse?
Yes.
Action.
Marshal mcgrew, ain't it?
Yip.
You're about to breathe
your last, marshal.
Can't win 'em all.
All right, jesse,
this is it-
you and me,
man to man.
Stuntman!
Okay.
Stuntman! Stuntman!
Stuntman.
All right, cut and print it.
Good show,
really good show.
Thanks a lot,
mr. Mcgrew.
All right, boys, this
is the death scene.
Rance, in the bar.
Jesse lies
over there.
Rance thinks
that he's unconscious.
Jesse takes a gun
up off the floor
and fires
at rance's back.
At his back?
That's right.
Now, look, sy,
i don't want to fight you
but that's not
how jesse james used to operate.
He fought pretty fair.
Can't i yell
something?
Oh, that's thinking, that's
real creative thinking-
warn the fastest gun in the west
that he's about to be shot.
Look, when you're up
against rance mcgrew
you play it dirty,
or you play it dead.
Now, let's
get on with it.
This is cola.
I told you i wanted ginger ale.
It's got to look like whiskey.
Sy,
either straighten this oaf out
or fire him.
Mr. Mcgrew wants
ginger ale.
Okay, ginger ale.
Your head against the bar,
feet out here.
I don't care what he says.
Jesse james wouldn't shoot
anybody in the back.
Yeah,
but rance mcgrew would.
All right,
let's get with it.
Scene 93, take one.
And, rance, baby,
easy on the mirror.
Action!
Why, you stupid clod,
this is whiskey.
This is real whiskey!
Marshal, marshal-
jesse's gunning for you.
He's coming right now.
Why, you cementhead,
he already came in
in scene 73.
I'm going to call my agent,
and this time he'd better be in.
They call me
jesse james-
therealjesse james
not that side of pork
that's been playacting me.
Cut.
Cut!
Shouldn't we cut?
For pete's sake, somebody...
let's cut!
I'd be looking for the marshal.
Fella named mcgrew.
Rance mcgrew.
Thataway.
You wouldn't
be him, huh?
Where's the fella
who loaned me this vest?
Marshal, i think
maybe you and me
better have a little talk.
Maybe a long talk,
maybe a short talk,
but a talk.
You're supposed to be tough.
You don't look so tough to me.
You know what you look like?
Well, i haven't been
too well lately.
You look kind of
like a marshmallow.
Mm. Mm.
Don't that rile you none?
Come on, marshal.
First we'll have a drink.
Then we'll have a talk.
Then we'll have a showdown.
Two whiskeys...
just leave the bottles.
Marshmallow.
You don't do nothing very well,
do you, mr. Mcgrew?
Don't that rile you none?
No.
You're just about
the most even-tempered dude
i ever did meet.
However...
i got no time to be social,
marshal.
It's time we come
to a meeting of the minds.
Why do you suppose they're
all taking cover, marshal?
Closing time?
Yes... yes,
it's curfew.
Well, good-bye, jesse,
and it's been really
very nice meeting you.
Marshal!
Just hold it
right there.
Hmm?
You wasn't leavin',
was you, marshal?
I mean, you wasn't
just going to walk out,
was you?
No, no, no, i just, uh...
wanted to see if
it was going to rain.
No, not going to rain.
I thought
you was playing
some kind
of trick on me.
Like the time
that bad guy
had you covered
in the back
and you went through
the swinging doors
and swung
one door back
and knocked
the gun away.
That was the first show
last season.
Or those rustlers
waiting to bushwhack you.
Ten or 11, wasn't it?
Uh, 13.
I got nominated for an emmy
on that one.
Oh, i bet
you did.
I just bet you did.
Folks couldn't help but admire
a man of your talents.
You know,
the thing of it is, marshal,
thing of it is...
i don't believe you ever fired a
real gun in your life, did you?
Did you ever hit a man in anger
or get hit
in anger yourself?
Tell me, do you ever
ride a horse?
On... on occasion.
So you don't shoot, you don't
ride and you don't fight.
You just
strut around
going through
the motions
of killing off fellows like me.
Now, i wouldn't
say that.
Now, last... last year,
we had one script
in which one of the
dalton boys went free.
He told me about it.
He also told
how you captured him.
You jumped 800
feet off a cliff
and landed on the back of his
horse when he wasn't looking.
Now, marshal, did you ever
jump 800 feet off a cliff
and land on
a man's horse?
Heights... heights make me...
ill.
That figures.
We had a meeting up there-
me, my brother frank,
the dalton boys,
sam starr,
billy the kid,
quite a
few others.
And the consensus was
that you wasn't doing a thing
for our good names.
So they chose me
to come down here
and maybe take
a little of the shine
off your pants.
How's that?
Don't you get it?
We see you week after week
killing off this guy
and that guy,
capturing that bushwhacker
and that rustler.
But all the time winning.
Man, you just
don't lose.
You are the
winningest fellow
that ever come
down the pike.
So me and my friends,
we figured that maybe just once
you ought
to lose.
Mm-hmm, yes, yes,
that's a very good idea
and iwilltake that up
with the producer.
I don't think
there'll be time
to take it up
because mister,
you're going to
lose right now.
I'll tell you what:
I'm going to be
square with you-
a lot squarer than you
ever been with any of us.
Face-to-face,
and no, uh...
what do you call
them, stuntmen?
Out on the street,
you and me-
you coming down one
side of the street,
me coming
down the other.
But that...
that's been done.
Didn't you see
gunfight at red rock?
Lousy.
Didn't like it?
Let's go, marshal.
Now, you come
around this corner,
and i'll come around
that corner.
I'll let you make
the first move.
Nothing could be
fairer, could it?
Oh, my, no, no indeed.
Well, uh... shall we
say tomorrow afternoon?
This afternoon... now.
Why does it have to be
thisafternoon?
Could have been
tomorrow afternoon.
Rush, rush, rush.
Rush, rush, rush,
that's all anybody knows
is rush, rush, rush.
Marshal?
Where are you, marshal?
Come on out, marshal!
Come on out, marshal.
Marshal,
where are you?
Come on,
marshal.
Marshal,
i'm going to count to five,
then we're both going to draw.
One...
this is ridiculous-
it's never done this way.
Two...
i'm just doing this series
for the residuals.
Three...
and because they let me use
my own name as the character.
Four...
i suppose you
know i have an
aging mother
and millions of
fans all over
this country,
and they're going
to hate you for this.
And a lot of them
are just like my old mother.
You're killing
an american institution.
Five.
Stuntman! Stuntman!
Reach, marshal.
Just like i figured-
this guy couldn't
outdraw a crayon.
Give me a break,
will you, jesse?
Jesse, give me a break.
I'm too young to die.
I'll do anything you say, jesse,
just give me a break.
You say you got nominated
for an emmy?
Two, two.
You can't act
any better than
you can draw.
Jesse, jesse,
just give me a break.
I'll do anything you say,
you... you... you just name it.
Anything?
You just name it.
Marshal, maybe you and me ain't
too far away from a bargain.
I don't know exactly
what it is i want,
but i'll sure think
about it some.
You're not going
to shoot me down?
Nope.
Tell you what i will do.
I'm going to stick around
make sure that you have
to play it careful from now on.
We may be stiffs up there...
but we're sensitive.
Jesse?
It isn't whiskey,
mr. Mcgrew
it's ginger ale,
just like you ordered.
Are you all right,
rance?
Yes, yes, i'm...
i'm all right.
Where'd you all go?
Where'd we go?
We didn't go anywhere.
You sure
you're all right?
Yeah, yeah, i'm fine.
All right, now,
let's get this shot now.
Jesse's on
the floor.
You think
he's unconscious.
Somebody wants to talk to you,
mr. Mcgrew.
We're shooting
a scene.
He says he's rance's agent.
My agent?
Look, i don't know what
the chain of command is,
so go out
and talk to him.
Find out what
it ishewants
what it isyouwant
and what it is
we can shoot.
Howdy, marshal.
You said "anything,"
and "anything" is
the following:
I'm going to stick around
from picture to picture
to make sure you don't
hurt no more feelings.
Now, in this scene,
jesse don't shoot
you in the back.
He's lost blood,
he's weak as tea,
but he can still get up
knock you through
that window
and make his getaway.
Is that understood?
He knocked me,
rance mcgrew,
through a window?
Why, it's... it's...
sy?
Yeah?
Sy, uh, i have a great idea
for something
i think might be a fun shot.
Uh...
what?!
Are you out
of your mind?
Jesse does what?
Oh, rance...
all right.
Scene 93, take two.
Action.
Now, that was
just fine.
Now, about next
week's episode
the one where
you knock the gun
out of billy
the kid's hand
from a fourth-story window
a half a block away
with the base
of a lamp.
No good, huh?
It stinks.
The way i see
it is this:
Now, billy,
he hears you,
and he whirls around,
and he fires from the hip,
and he shoots the lamp
right out of your hand.
Now, in two weeks,
i think we ought to
give sam starr a break.
He's a real nice fella-
awful good to his mother.
Haw!
The evolution of the
so-called adult western
and the metamorphosis
of one rance mcgrew,
formerly phony baloney,
now upright citizen
with a preoccupation
with all things
involving tradition, truth
and cowpoke predecessors.
It's the way the cookie crumbles
and the six-gun shoots
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
For all of us,
even the most young at heart,
i suppose
there's a little kernel of want
having to do
with reliving childhood-
that grand and glorious
moment in time
when the biggest guy around
is the patrol boy.
Next week onthe twilight zone,
this moment is recaptured
in george clayton johnson's
exceptionally sensitive story
called "kick the can."
It costars mr. Ernest truex
and mr. Russell collins.
If the tobaccos in a cigarette
are good enough,
they alone
will give mellow richness
and satisfactory mildness.
Try chesterfields
and you'll discover
21 great tobaccos
make 20 wonderful smokes.
This is james arness.
You know, it's only a short hop
fromthe twilight zone
to dodge city ingunsmoke.
Saturday nights
over most of these stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org