Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Listen, horace...
now, why did
you do that?
Do what?
You know, with
the cap pistol.
Scared the pants
off of you, right?
Look, horace...
you do it almost
every day.
Boy, i love
cap pistols.
They got a great smell.
Smell that.
I know what it
smells like.
When i was a kid,
i always had a cap pistol.
Listen, leonard,
do you remember ken maynard
in the movies?
All the other kids
on the block
were tom mix,
except me.
I was ken maynard.
Me and my horse tarzan.
Look, horace,
i came in here
to talk to you
about your design
for the new
robot toy.
Now, there's
something out
of whack.
Listen, we used to gallop
out of the theater
and shoot up
the whole neighborhood.
Got you,
right in the heart.
Are you cuckoo?
You're cuckoo.
You missed me a mile.
Bing! Bing! Bing!
Horace, have you got
any idea
how loud you're yelling?
I'll bet you can hear that
al the way down
in mr. Judson's office.
How much? How much?
I'll bet you my ball
of silver paper.
You remember
that, leonard?
Remember when we used
to collect tin foil
from those cigarette
packs and roll 'em
in a great big ball?
Horace, i came in here
to talk to you
about the new robot toy.
Now, i've worked in the office
next to you for 15 years.
I know all about how you used
to collect tin foil.
Now, will you listen
to me for a second?
You must have had a
very miserable time
when you were a kid.
Right. I couldn't wait
till i grew up.
All right, what
do you want?
There's something wrong
with this.
There is not!
I designed that toy!
There's nothing
wrong with that toy.
Kids'll be crazy
about that.
Listen, you know
what that does?
I know what it does.
I mean, i mean,
a toy where the
eyes light up
and it talks and
everything...
horace, i'm trying
to help you.
It's a good toy.
I know it's a good toy,
but it can't
be turned out
at the price
mr. Judson wants.
Now, look here...
he's going to blow
his stack
when he sees this.
It's got too many parts,
believe me.
You think
it's wrong?
Well, i know it is.
Look, all you have to
do is work it over.
How's betty?
What?
Betty.
Well, now, what
has betty got
to do with...?
Thanks a lot.
I'll look it over.
Mr. Horace ford,
who has a preoccupation
with another time-
a time of childhood,
a time of growing up,
a time of street games,
stickball and hide and go seek.
He has a reluctance
to check out a mirror
and see the nature
of his image-
proof positive
that the time he dwells in
has already passed him by.
But in a moment or two,
he'll discover
that mechanical toys
and memories
and daydreaming
and wishful thinking
and all manner
of odd and special events
can lead one
into a special province,
uncharted and unmapped-
a country of both shadow
and substance
known as the twilight zone.
Laura... what's the matter?
I don't want horace
to see this.
It's his birthday
present.
Well, how are you?
Exhausted.
It's not easy
shopping for
your husband.
What did you get him?
Oh, a smoking jacket.
That proves
he's going to be 38.
The surprise party's all set
for friday night?
All set.
Wh-what's the plan?
Everybody's going to meet
at your place at 7:30,
and then you're all coming over
to our place together at 8:00.
Horace thinks the two of us
are going to a movie.
I'll make him answer the door
when you ring.
He'll go through the floor.
Oh, len, would
you take this
home with you?
I don't want...
i don't want
horace to see it
around the house.
Sure. I'll bring it
with me friday night.
Thanks. Is he busy?
Well, pretty.
I'm going to
take him home.
It's almost
6:00, anyway.
See you friday.
So long, honey.
Horace, horace!
Oh, mr. Judson.
What are you doing
at the window?
Nothing, just thinking.
Thinking about what?
I don't know... business.
Whose business?
You certainly haven't
been doing
very much thinking
about ours.
Take a look at this.
Well, look at it.
I know what it is.
Well, what happened?
I don't know, mr. Judson.
Do you know how much
we could lose
if we put this toy
into production the way it is?
That's a good toy.
Very good, but that has
nothing to do with it.
Look, horace, you've
been here a long while.
It's time you realized
that we're in business
to make a profit.
Now, this robot toy
is too complicated,
too many parts,
and i want it simplified.
What do you want
to simplify?
Well, the eyes don't have
to light up.
Sure, the eyes have to light up!
What, do you want to ruin
the whole thing?!
The eyes lighting up-
that's the beauty part!
That's the
terrific thing.
What's the matter, horace?
Nothing! Well, you're
just talking
about ruining
the whole thing!
I don't want to argue
about it.
I just want
the whole design redone,
and i need it
right away.
Listen, don't
you remember
when you used
to play soldiers?
Well, this robot thing...
laura...
is this the office of
horace maxwell ford?
Oh, hello, laura.
Well, aren't you
surprised to see me?
Yeah, i'm surprised.
What time is it?
About 6:00.
Horace, i've never
been so exhausted
in my whole life.
I've been shopping
all day long.
I'm going to take you home.
Okay.
I'm going to fall
into bed tonight,
literally
fall into bed.
Boy, i got
some homework to do.
Oh, not again.
What is it?
That robot toy.
I'm telling you,
that nutty mr. Judson
is trying to ruin
the whole thing.
That toy has no meaning
unless the eyes light up.
Hello, children.
How's my boy?
Fine.
You hungry?
A little.
Good, dinner's
almost ready.
Oh, laura, there's
something's wrong
with the chicken.
It's like leather.
These birds they
sell you nowadays-
like people don't
know what chickens
are anymore.
It looks all
right to me.
Well, how was
the office today?
It was okay.
What's the matter?
Nothing. Nothing's the matter.
No, i can tell
just from your voice.
What is it?
Nothing. Everything's fine.
Let's have dinner.
Boy, i'm telling you,
that mr. Judson
is just plain nuts.
The guy reminds me of corey.
Hey, mom,
you remember mr. Corey?
Mr. Corey, mom-
i had him in 5-b.
Hey, hey, laura,
listen, did i ever
tell you
what we used
to call him?
Hey, guess.
Come on, let's get
ready for dinner.
I'm not even going
to tell you.
I'll never forget
the time
he caught me
with a candy ball in my mouth,
see, the kind
that-that change colors
while you suck on them.
Horace...
boy, he made me stand up,
and every minute,
he'd point that pointer at me
and he'd say,
"mr. Ford, what
color is it?
What color is
it, mr. Ford?"
I got to take it
out of my mouth
and tell him.
Oh, i thought hermy brandt'd
bust trying not to laugh.
Horace...
hermy brandt...
boy, the greatest stickball
player in the whole world.
I'll never forget
this time...
horace...
this fire drill, see?
One time...
do you know what he used
to do in fire drill?
Let's have dinner.
He'd... oh!
Gee... what great times.
I was ten.
Boy, what great,
great times.
Horace, why
don't you stop?
Nobody cares about when
you were ten anymore.
I care.
You're almost 38.
So what?
You don't act
38 sometimes.
So what?
That's what i
mean- "so what."
What kind of an
answer is "so what"?
I'm telling you it's dry.
Why do you have
to keep talking
about when you
were a kid?
It's still dry.
Why don't you just be quiet
for once, will you?!
Horace!
Horace?
Let him go.
Horace.
Laura was probably
just tired.
She didn't
mean to yell.
Hey...
hey, you remember hermy brandt?
No.
Listen, how come
you never remember anything
about randolph street?
It was a terrible street.
I just want to forget it.
What was terrible?
I had the greatest times.
Like, like, you remember
when pop used to give me
the indian burn?
Why do you always have to talk
about when you were a kid?
Ah... randolph street.
You know what i think
i'm going to do?
I think i'm going back there
right now.
Horace?
Why shouldn't i?
Horace...
it's just a dirty
old street.
What are you going to see?
Stay home.
Where are
you going?
Horace?
Horace, listen...
frank on a roll?
Three cents each.
Bread and butter.
Davy!
You come home
or you're going to get smacked!
Ice cream!
Get your chocolate,
vanilla,
strawberry ice cream!
Get your ice cream here!
Watch where
you're going.
Give me that back!
Ring-a-levio,
caught, caught, caught.
Ring-a-levio.
Hey, hermy.
Hermy brandt,
come on.
Well, it's nice of you
to come back.
Laura?
Where were you?
Why didn't you tell me
where you were going?
Listen, laura...
i was down on randolph street.
What's the matter?
I don't know.
Laura...
there's something
i got to tell you.
Take off your hat.
I know.
Listen...
hey, uh... i saw some kids
on the block...
little kids- maybe...
maybe ten, 11 years old.
Laura...
they were the kids
i played with when i was ten.
The same kids.
You're perspiring.
L-i'm not.
You're not
listening to me.
I heard you.
I think you're catching cold
or something.
Wipe off your face.
They couldn't have been
the same kids, dear.
That's nonsense.
Well, they were.
I saw them.
L-i saw...
hermy brandt
and george lambert
and cy wright.
Well, maybe
they justlooked
like some kids
you used to know...
no, i'm telling
you, they were.
Horace, you're talking
like a child.
He dropped this.
You can't turn these things out
like donuts!
Well, you tell him
i am rushing it!
What does he think i am?!
Aw, let him do it!
Sure, sure, you tell him that!
What does he want
out of me?!
Judson?
Yeah.
Well, he wants to get
that toy in production
in time for christmas.
Well, what's
he nagging me for?!
He's got six months.
Now, take it
easy, horace.
Look, he's a pretty nice guy,
but he's a businessman.
Now, you got to remember that.
Uh, don't you start
on me, too.
What's wrong, horace?
I don't know. I...
listen, i... i'm very nervous.
I saw a kid last night.
You ever been
on-on randolph street?
Well, it doesn't make
any difference.
Randolph is-is my old street
when-when i was a kid.
He was wearing knickers,
this kid i saw.
You remember when you used
to wear knickers,
where the...
where the buckles and all-
they're all the time
slipping down?
So he was wearing these...
kids never wear knickers
anymore!
I'm telling you, never!
But he is...
wearing these knickers and...
you won't believe this...
but i swear it's true.
I was...
walking on the street...
and all of a sudden, i hear
a kid yelling, "ring-a-levio!"
Ring-a...?
Well, that's a game
we used to play.
Ring-a-levio.
You... you know how that can
make you feel, hearing that?
I was a very good
ring-a-levio player.
See, you got
to be very fast.
You need a lot
of stamina.
Boy, the running
you have to do.
See, first,
you choose up sides.
You go, "one potato,
two potato, three potato, four."
You remember that?
And then one side's
got to hide.
So, this time, i'm hiding
behind the grocery,
back behind where
they keep the cartons and all...
well, now, horace...
and i fell asleep.
Is that ridiculous?
I fell asleep.
When i woke up, i take one look
at my mickey mouse wa...
mickey mouse watch.
Oh...
gee, i haven't thought
of that in 20 years.
Hey, you remember when you had
a mickey mouse watch?
What a deal that was...
horace, uh...
i got some work
stacked up
on my desk.
L-i just stopped
in to say hello.
I wanted to tell you
about how silly...
i'll see you
later, huh?
Horace...
i want to ask
you something.
What was the
point in shouting
at my secretary
on the phone?
She was shouting at me!
I was in the same
room with her.
She spoke in a
normal voice.
Aren't you happy
with your work here?
Sure.
Horace, you're a fine designer.
You have value for this company.
For our sake as well as yours,
i don't like
to see it dissipated.
But you've been
behaving badly.
Is there something wrong,
maybe at home?
L-i'm just trying
to get this thing done here!
I'm not speaking just to hear
the sound of my own voice.
Horace!
I'm sorry i'm late.
The subway was tied up
for about 20 minutes.
Somebody jumped?
Nobody jumped.
Why do you have to think
of something like that
right off?
Well, it happens.
Just read the papers.
Something broke down.
You can't kiss your
poor old mother
hello anymore?
Yeah, sure.
Don't bother to wash up.
It's overcooked already.
You tired?
Yeah.
Listen, horace...
there's a great double bill
at the regent.
I'm going back
there tonight.
Where?
Randolph street.
What for?
I got to see
those kids.
Why?
Because i want
to see them.
It's important.
Important?
Veal cutlet.
Succotash.
It's canned,
but you can hardly tell it
from fresh.
Now, help yourself
to the meat, horace.
If it's stringy,
blame it on the subway.
You sure nobody jumped?
Mother.
What's so great about disasters?
What?
You know, i remember you
from randolph street.
Every time there was an accident
or something,
you was always right there
in the front row, watching.
Horace.
Well, it's the truth.
Now, what-what about that time
that harvey bender got his arm
caught in the fire hydrant?
We all think they're going to
have to bust it to get it loose.
You never budged
out of the front row.
Harvey bender?
Who's harvey bender?
What are
you talking about?
If that wasn't
the nuttiest thing...
what's he talking about?
The hottest day
of the summer,
and he thinks to clog up
the fire hydrant.
What do you mean, you don't
remember harvey bender?
Gee, we were
all playing emmy, see,
you know, you know,
on a manhole cover,
and man, i'm cleaning up.
Oh, gosh, i remember it
just as if it was this morning.
See, i got this big fat purey,
and i'm...
i'm cleaning up, and all
of a sudden, this nut says,
"let's open up
the fire hydrant."
Ah, that was the nuttiest kid,
i swear.
His favorite thing was
shake, spear,
sock in the ear.
Horace, stop it!
What's the matter?
Just stop it.
He was one of the kids
last night.
Who was one of the kids?
Harvey bender.
What are you talking about?
I saw him last night.
Don't you know
that's impossible?
I know what i see.
He was ten years old
whenyouwere ten years old.
He's as old as you are.
I tell you, i saw him.
He's a grown-up man!
Well, you think so...
you think so, do you?
Let me tell you, i saw him
last night on randolph street.
And i saw george lambert,
and i saw cy wright,
and they arestillkids!
Horace, what are you saying?
Feel his head.
He's got a fever.
Now, leave me alone.
I got no fever.
Mother, be quiet.
Horace, sit down.
Feel his head.
Will you let me alone?
Mother...
listen, darling,
i want to talk to
you quietly just
for a minute.
I don't know what's been
happening at the office,
but i see you
when you come home at night,
you're tired.
I mean,
overwork can cause...
i want you to see a doctor.
What for?
Just to have a checkup.
Yeah, you think i'm imagining
this thing about the kids.
No, i don't.
Yes, you do.
Horace, listen.
Where are
you going?
Horace!
Please.
Frank on a roll?
Three cents each.
Bread and butter.
Davy!
You come home,
or you're going to get smacked!
Ice cream!
Get your chocolate,
vanilla,
strawberry
ice cream here!
Ice cream!
Watch where
you're going.
Give me that back!
Ring-a-levio,
caught, caught, caught.
Ring-a-levio.
Hey, hermy.
Hermy brandt,
come on.
Let's swipe some apples.
You each grab one.
Hey, micky, larry.
Hey, wait!
Can you imagine
not being invited
to that birthday party?
Can you imagine?
Yeah, and i'm supposed
to be his best friend.
He stinks!
We ought to mob-ilize him,
right, hermy?
Oh, and how.
Horace?
Horace.
Horace, are
you all right?
Why don't you
say something?
Same thing happened
all over again.
Well, sit down
over here.
I was worried
about you.
I'm glad
you're home.
I mean, the way
you ran out of here...
nothing changed.
Same man wanted me
to buy a hot dog.
Those people says
"bread and butter."
This big guy
bumped into me.
What are
you talking about?
I'm telling
you, laura,
i'm telling you,
laura, no-nothing
changed.
It's some kind
of a pattern,
and i'm in it.
The kids...
they... i mean, they
swipe some apples,
they run into an
alley, and i heard
them talking.
I almost died.
I mean it.
I remember being in
it from 28 years ago,
but i don't
remember how.
Oh, god, horace... stop.
Listen, i'm going
to call a doctor.
You're not.
I don't need
a doctor.
I'm not sick.
I saw this.
Please. Now, you have
to listen to me.
You have to have some help
on this thing.
Just let me
alone, will you?
Why don't you get into bed
for a couple of days?
I mean, you don'thave
to go to work.
Stay home
from the office.
He dropped this.
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
Laura, hey,
aren't you supposed
to be home
baking a birthday
cake or something?
Now, don't tell me
it's going to
be store-bought-
not a woman with
your talents.
I don't want horace
to see me.
I have to tell
you something.
I don't know
how he got
to the office
this morning.
I begged him
to stay home.
Leonard, i've
got to get him
to see a doctor.
What are
you talking about?
Well, something's
happening to him.
It's this thing
with the kids.
He's...
well, it's
like it's...
eating him alive.
Laura...
look, he-he's had that
ever since i can remember.
I mean, i've always been able
to snap him out of it.
Not now.
You know he's
been going back
to his old street?
Yeah, he started
to tell me about it.
He tells me he sees kids
that he grew up with,
and they're the same age.
I don't know what
to say to him.
Len, he's got to have help.
I'm not saying i'm the best wife
in the world, but i try.
L-i try hard.
Now, i make a home
for his mother.
That's not easy.
But i love horace.
Sometimes i don't know
what to say to him,
but i love him.
Do you want me to talk to him?
Len... make him see a doctor.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid for his job
and for him.
I'm just afraid.
I will.
L-l-i'll talk to him.
Look, uh... laura,
it's after 4:00 now,
and the surprise party
is tonight.
Now, suppose i hold off
until tomorrow?
L-i just don't want to get him
upset before the party.
Oh... but he's so upset now.
Len...
help me get him to
a doctor tomorrow.
L-i'll talk to him.
I'll see you
at 8:00 sharp.
I just finished
the designs
for that
kangaroo toy.
Mr. Hop-hop,
they're going to call it.
Thought i'd come in
and kill some time.
Who thought of that name,
"mr. Hop-hop"?
I did.
No kidding. When?
Last week.
Oh, it's a real good name.
Catchy.
Listen, leonard,
did you ever hear
of this thing...
"step on a crack
and break your
mother's back"?
And it's got
another part to it.
I... i've been
trying to remember
it all day,
and i can't
remember it.
I never heard of it.
Look, you were telling me
a story yesterday
about something that happened
on your old block,
and you never did
finish it.
"Step on a crack..."
what happened
the other night?
I don't want
to tell you.
You'd just give
me a blank look
and tell me i'm
crazy or something.
What are
you talking about?
I don't want
to tell you.
Hello, leonard.
I'd like to speak
to horace alone
for a minute,
if you don't mind.
Oh, mr. Judson,
i was just going to ask you
to come in and go over
that hop-hop toy with me.
In a little while.
I'll see you in your office.
Well, the designs
are all finished.
In a little while,
leonard.
How are you,
horace?
Okay.
You look tired.
I'm not tired.
I thought maybe
you'd have
the robot toy design
finished by now,
and i'd like
to see it.
I don't have them.
Why not?
I don't know why not.
I just haven't
gotten to them.
What have you
been doing?
What have
i been doing?
What-what-what do you think
i've been doing?
Well, horace, you...
you haven't been very
helpful around here
for quite a while.
Helpful? I don't know
how you can say that.
That toy has to get
into production.
Maybe you'd
better start on
something else,
and leonard
can finish up.
Listen, that's my design,
and nobody else is touching it.
I still run this firm, horace.
You are not taking my stuff!
Lower your voice.
Look, horace,
i'm trying to be decent to you
because i think
there's something wrong.
I think maybe
you're ill.
I'd like you to take
a leave of absence,
and i want you
to see a psychiatrist.
I think you're approaching
a nervous breakdown.
I am not approaching
any nervous breakdown,
and i don't know
who you think you are,
talking to me like that!
I'm only trying to help.
There's nothing wrong with me.
That may be, but if there is,
it-it's nothing
to be ashamed of.
I want you to take
a leave of absence and find out.
I am not taking
any leave of absence.
Well, the way things are,
i'm afraid
you can't work here anymore.
All right, all right,
all right, all right!
All right, then,
i can't work here anymore!
I'm sorry, horace.
I wish you'd think about it.
Would you please
just get out of here?!
Would you, please?!
Laura.
All right, uh,
one chocolate chip.
543 dayton street,
apartment "d."
"D" as in david.
That's right.
10:00 tonight.
Thank you.
Laura, do you think
i bought enough
potato chips?
Oh, mm-hmm.
What shall i
do with this
so horace
won't see it?
Well, i don't know.
Maybe put it
in your bedroom somewhere.
Where is he?
What time is it?
Ten of 8:00.
I'm getting worried
about him.
He should have been
home an hour ago.
He probably got stuck
at the office.
I'm going to
call him there.
It looks good.
The way they bake cakes
these days,
i hope it tastes
as good as it looks.
Well, hello.
How come you're
so late?
I didn't know
what time it is.
Why, it's
ten of 8:00.
Hello, dear.
I'm fired.
You're what?
What are you
talking about?
Mother.
I went and had a hamburger
at the drugstore.
That's why i'm late.
You're fired from your job?
Will you,
for heaven's sakes?
Horace, i want to know.
You're trying to be funny.
No.
Why were you fired?
I was inadequate in my work.
Well, that's not so.
Iwasinadequate in my work.
Who said that?
It doesn't
matter, horace.
What doesn't
matter?
A man loses a job
he's had for 15 years,
and it doesn't matter?
What do they mean, inadequate?
A man like you?
A top designer
of toys?
Do they know what they've got?
Pure gold.
Mother.
Listen, maybe they don't know,
but i know what you did
for them in 15 years.
They've got to be told.
Your life's blood
is in that place.
Look...
i want you to get whoever it is
down there at that firm there-
that mr. Johnson
or whatever his name is-
get him on the wire
and tell him what's what.
I'm not calling anybody.
But you're fired.
$140 a week.
Do you think you can find
$140 a week on the street?
What's going
to happen to us?
I don't know.
Because all of a sudden,
my whole life
is going before me.
I don't know why.
I can't tell you what it is...
but it's been ups and downs,
ups and downs.
I'm 61 years old, 61.
It's time i shouldn't
be afraid anymore.
Why don't
you look at me
when i'm talking
to you?!
What's going to happen to me?!
Shut up!
I am going to talk
to horace alone.
What did i do wrong?
Ever, in my whole life?
If somebody could tell me...
i couldn't help it.
It's only a
job, darling.
There are plenty
of other jobs.
You were stagnating
there, horace.
I never had another job.
What are you
going to do?
Why did she have to cry?
She's an old woman, horace.
I mean, it's unfair
for her to cry.
Well, that's always her first
reaction to trouble- crying.
She'll be all right.
Did you get any severance pay?
I don't know what i got.
I just walked out.
Well, we'll forget about it
for now.
We'll think about it
this weekend.
Monday, you can start looking.
We'll make a list
of places.
She's scared stiff.
She'll be all right.
I have to support her...
...and you...
horace, i have
to tell you something.
And me- that
makes three people.
Well, you think
that's easy?
You know what
mr. Corey says
to me today?
He says he thinks
that he's...
mr. Corey was
your teacher in 5-b.
Well, mr. Judson.
You know what mr.
Judson says to me?
He says he-he
thinks i'm having
a nervous breakdown.
He's out of his mind.
Listen, laura,
i'm telling you,
i saw those kids.
I know who they are.
Horace...
they were running
up and down the street,
and-and-and swiping apples,
and yelling, and having fun.
That's all they were doing-
having fun.
They yell, "fins."
Listen...
did you ever yell "fins"?
But that's not what
we were talking about.
Itiswhat
we were talking about-
me having to make a living
for three people
while they're
just swiping apples
and running up and down
the street.
Well, you're a
grown-up man!
What do you think
you're supposed to do?
They were sore
'cause some kid
hadn't invited them
to a birthday party.
That was their biggest problem
in their whole life!
Horace, now,
you've got to stop!
You don't have to shout.
Horace?
Horace, where
are you going?
You can't go out now!
You can't! Horace!
What's wrong with him?
Tell me, laura.
What are you
going to do?
Who are you
going to call?
Laura, for
heaven's sakes,
i've got to know
what's going on here.
Who are you
going to call?
I don't know.
That's the whole thing.
I don't know
who i'm going to call.
What's the name
of a doctor?
Tell me the name
of a doctor.
Horace?
Surprise!
Happy birthday!
Frank on a roll?
Three cents each.
Bread and butter.
Davy!
You come home,
or you're going to get smacked!
Ice cream!
Get your chocolate,
vanilla,
strawberry ice cream!
Watch where
you're going.
Ring-a-levio,
caught, caught, caught.
Ring-a-levio.
Hey, hermy.
Hermy brandt,
come on.
Come on.
Let's swipe some apples.
You each grab one.
Hey, micky, larry.
Hey... wait.
Hey, can you imagine
not being invited
to that birthday party?
Can you imagine?
Yeah, and i'm supposed
to be his best friend.
He stinks!
We ought to mob-ilize him,
right, hermy?
Oh, and how.
Why don't we bust in
on the party?
Fellas.
Oh, what for?
Listen, fellas,
there's something
i got to tell you.
Naw, he'd probably bawl
or something.
Now, you got to listen to me.
I have to tell you this.
Step on a line,
you break your father's spine.
Will you
cut it out?
Hey, hey,
fellas...
look at me.
I'm standing
right here.
Hermy, hermy,
are you my buddy?
Why don't you
listen to me?
Aw, you-you guys...
you think i don't know when
i owe you guys some apologies?
Georgie?
Hey, cy?
Aw, come on, what are you giving
me the treatment for?
Will you listen?
Will you please listen to me?
I couldn't help it.
I'm telling
you, fellas,
you got to give
me a chance.
Hermy, i'm your
best friend.
Will you listen
to me just for
a minute?
Well, if it ain't
horace maxwell ford.
Horace maxwell ford.
The birthday boy.
Why didn't you invite us
to your party,
horace maxwell ford?
You dopey nut.
We're going to mob-ilize you.
No, come on. No, don't!
Don't! Please, no!
Ow!
Oh, matches.
Happy birthday!
He dropped this.
Oh!
Horace.
I'm here.
It's all right,
horace, i'm here.
Laura?
Yes. It's all right.
Don't ask me anything.
I won't.
Because i could never...
just don't.
Are you all right now?
Yes.
But you're all cut
and everything.
It doesn't matter.
Let's go home.
I don't know what
happened to me, laura.
I have no idea.
But...
for one minute...
or one second...
or maybe one hour-
i don't know-
i saw something that...
made every memory
i ever had a lie.
Because when i was a kid,
it was an ugly, sad,
unbearable nightmare.
And i saw it.
I know what it was.
I remember it now.
I don't know what happened
to you, either, horace,
but i think
we're all like that.
We remember what was good,
and we black out what was bad,
maybe because we couldn't live
if we didn't.
Let's go home.
There's a
party waiting.
Exit mr. And mrs. Horace ford,
who have lived
through a bizarre moment
not to be calibrated
on normal clocks or watches.
Time has passed, to be sure,
but it's the special time
in the special place
known as... the twilight zone.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org