Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it
is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Probe 7 calling base.
This is probe 7 calling base.
This is probe 7...
probe 7 with a landing report.
Over to you, base, over to you.
Probe 7, this is base.
You're coming through low
but audibly.
Go ahead probe 7.
I've crash-landed
into a planet system
4.3 light years from our sun.
Most of my equipment's gone.
As of the moment, i don't know
this planet's density
or its atmospheric composition,
but i'm alive and breathing.
Your visual image
is very indistinct.
Can you increase your power?
I've got half a generator
and three solar cells left.
Just how i'm getting through
to you, i can't even explain.
Can you effect repairs?
If so, how long do you estimate
it will take?
Oh, give me about 20 years,
new right arm,
maybe replace my head,
i could make a start.
In short... in short,
i need help.
I need help desperately,
and i need it right away.
We tracked you on impulses
to your approximate locations.
We have nothing back here
that can reach you. Nothing.
You'll have to make
those repairs yourself.
I have no power.
I have no propellant at all.
I've got a ship that looks like
fragments from a space puzzle.
You tell me you've got nothing
to send out for me,
you're telling me you're
crossing off one spaceman.
Repeat, please.
Your last message was not clear.
I'll give it to you
in just a few words.
This craft is not going
to fly anymore-
not forward, not up,
and not back there.
Isn't there anything
you can do to help me?
Look, i'm losing power.
I've lost visual contact.
I'll have to sign off for now.
Acknowledge, will you, base?
Remain on this frequency.
We will expect to hear from you.
Colonel cook,
this is general larrabee.
We understand your spot.
We wish we could help you.
There's only a possibility
that if you check out your ship,
we can transmit instructions
to you for its repair.
Now, that's a possibility.
Why don't i just build
a new one, general?
That's a possibility, too.
I'll transmit again
as soon as possible.
Heaven help me.
I wonder...
i wonder if that's
a possibility.
One colonel cook,
a traveler in space.
He's landed on a remote planet
several million miles
from his point of departure.
He can make an inventory
of his plight
by just one 360-degree movement
of head and eyes.
Colonel cook has been set adrift
in an ocean of space
in a metal lifeboat that has
been scorched and destroyed
and will never fly again.
He survived the crash,
but his ordeal is yet to begin.
Now he must give battle
to loneliness.
Now colonel cook
must meet the unknown.
It's a small planet
set deep in space,
but for colonel cook,
it's the twilight zone.
Anybody around here?
Anybody hear me?
This is probe 7 calling base.
Probe 7 calling base.
Over to you, base.
We read you very well, colonel.
Tell us your situation, please.
Relatively unchanged, general.
I worked on the solar cells so
i'll be sending out more power.
It'll be temporary,
but you're coming in
much stronger now, too.
What about your ship?
Probe 7
is no longer probing, general,
unless it's the few subterranean
feet where i landed.
I've been outside.
There's plant life,
but i was pretty sure of that
when i spiraled in.
The gravity pull's
about the same as ours,
and what i can tell
of the atmosphere,
that's roughly similar as well.
We've got
a major problem here, cook.
There's been a major crisis.
War is imminent.
The next 24 hours
will probably tell.
There's always a major crisis
and there's always talk of war.
You'll forgive me, general,
but my own problem has
a little more immediacy for me.
It's a little more personalized.
I've got a week's food left
and two broken bones in one arm.
Can't another ship
be sent out for me?
There isn't another ship, cook,
unless we build one.
If we have war
in the next few hours,
there isn't going to be anybody
left around to do any building.
That's the realistic view,
colonel.
That may go down hard,
but those are the facts of life.
Ten hours from now,
perhaps six, four hours,
we'll be committed back here.
I'm talking
half a billion people, colonel,
not just one lonely man.
Do you understand this?
Very well, general.
Very, very well.
Um...
any point in my trying
to contact you further?
Yes, colonel, two points:
One, to help your loneliness,
and two...
to see if your own world
still exists.
It's a moot question, colonel:
Which of us has
the better chance of survival?
Over to you... and out.
Base calling probe 7.
This is probe 7.
Come in, base.
Anything new to report, colonel?
I've done some exploring,
general.
I'm very much alone here.
No sign of anything?
Anything or anyone?
I've got a wind
that sings sad songs to me.
There's some fruit trees
that might provide food
if it's not poisonous,
and that's it.
That's all of it.
Not that it will provide
vast solace to you,
but at 9:00
this morning, cook...
we went to war.
And?
Our entire seacoast went.
It took 12 minutes.
Exactly 12 minutes.
We-we retaliated?
Oh, indeed.
With alacrity
and great effectiveness.
And we still are.
Our world is doing
a little wholesale dying now.
Are you safe?
For the time being.
Our location's classified.
The trouble is,
we can't stay here much longer.
There have been bombs
as close as 400 miles from us.
It's only a question now
as to our manner of death-
very fast or very slow.
It's that kind of choice.
You know, it's really a pity
we didn't send others
along with you.
What you think of as a prison
might be a haven.
What you think of
as a haven, general,
is a very large, dark dungeon.
Maybe this world has only night
and no day.
So far, only darkness.
And i don't care very much
for solitary confinement.
Unfortunately for both of us,
we have very little choice
in the matter.
What's happening there, general?
What's going on?
We're going to have to move
out of here now.
I don't know
whether we'll be able
to contact you again or not.
Try, sir, if you can.
L-i'd like to hear a voice.
Silence or cries?
That's the story from our world.
Silence or cries.
God bless you... and good luck.
Good luck.
I've got company.
I've got company!
Whoever and wherever,
welcome, welcome!
Come on down
and meet your genial host.
Let me see you.
Please, whoever and wherever,
let's shake hands.
Come on!
Let's shake hands.
I need a friend.
Come on!
Come on, friend.
Come on out.
Probe 7, this is base.
This is our last contact, cook.
Just a few minutes ago,
we got ours.
500% increase
in the radioactivity around us.
From what we can gather,
the enemy had it
just as bad as we did.
We wiped them out;
they wiped us out.
Just one last forlorn wish
for you, son.
Whoever you'll meet there,
however you'll meet them,
i hope it can come without fear.
I hope it can come
without anger.
I hope your new world
will be different.
I hope you'll find
no word such as hate.
I hope there'll be...
all right, come on out.
You've got quite a choice.
You can be friendly,
you can be neutral,
or you can be dead.
You'll get hungry
in a little while.
Or don't you eat?
I'm going to walk out of here
so you can have a chance
to get out when i'm not here.
I'll be outside.
You'll hear my footsteps
so you'll know that i'm leaving.
You may not understand
this language,
but the tone
may be getting through to you.
You can come out now
when-whenever you want
and we can talk.
You know what's
going to happen
in a few minutes?
I'm going to wake up
from this nightmare,
and i'm going to
charge out of bed
like a rocket,
and i'm going
to tell them back home,
"you can talk about dreams
from now on,
"but i get the prize
for the most imaginative dream
of the space age."
You understand?
Do you understand?
Do you understand anything
i'm saying?
My name is cook.
I come from
another planet.
I crash-landed here.
I cracked
up my ship.
I'm the wingless spaceman,
no place to go
and all the time in the universe
to get there.
Look...
this is my galaxy.
See, i went off-course.
I didn't have enough
power to get back.
This was the only
place i could find
that looked
inhabitable.
Here, right here,
where we are.
Oh, what difference
does it make?
You're probably an
illusion anyway,
just as those
markings you left
are an illusion
as well.
So... you can
disappear anytime now.
Understand?
That's your galaxy.
That's your planet.
That's where
you came from.
Your planet got
out of its orbit
and moved away
from your sun
that's where you went,
where your world went.
But you got out.
How many others?
You...
you...
two, three,
four, five...
and... any others?
Em.
No, em.
Your ship.
What about your ship?
Where's your ship?
Ship? Ship?
Cook.
Emman...
norda.
Norda?
Norda.
So, how does it figure?
Anyway, we're
stuck here.
A one-armed man
with a broken rib
and a tired woman.
What have you
been living on?
Uh, what food?
What to eat?
Well, i can
offer you food
and i can offer
you companionship.
We could spend the rest
of our lives together
drawing diagrams...
which would become
rather tedious.
But the brighter of
us will have to learn
the other's
language eventually.
Come, norda.
Eat.
You understand?
Food.
Eat...
food...
food.
Food.
Flah, em...
norda!
Norda, please, please...
i'm not going
to hurt you.
Please.
It's not just the language.
It's our breed.
It's the way we ultimately
always respond to one another.
Good luck to you.
Good luck.
I can't give you any soil test.
I can't send you
any plant species
or animals
or anything like that,
but i can give you
an observation
as to the psychological makeup
of man.
He's a frightened breed.
He's a very frightened breed.
Must be a universal trait.
Must be the case
wherever there's life.
So we're not alone on that.
It is really quite a pity...
as you may
have perceived
if any of you have survived...
do you hear me, base?
Do you hear me?
...i hope it can come
without fear.
I hope it can come
without anger.
I hope your new world
will be different.
I hope you'll find
no word such as hate.
I hope there'll be...
ah, just in time
to say good-bye.
Going to try another place
over in that direction.
More vegetation,
fruit trees-
even flowers, it appears.
Sort of, uh...
sort of like a garden.
I'm going to try
to live there.
De ekkel.
O-toh te ur.
Indeed you may.
Indeed you may come.
And we'll both live.
I don't know how
or for how long, but we can try.
It would help
if we could
communicate.
Might as well start right now.
What do you
call this?
In your language.
Eat?
No.
No, not eat.
Not food.
Earth?
Erd-thah?
Erd-thah.
Earth.
We've just given
this place a name.
All right.
We'll call it earth.
Earth.
Cook.
Adam cook.
Norda?
Norda.
Eve.
All right, eve.
Well, we're dispossessed,
and now we're going to possess.
This is our home now.
This is earth.
Sep-luh.
Ees...
sep-luh.
Is that your food?
Is that what you've
been living on?
What is it?
Eat.
Food.
Do you know these people?
Names familiar, are they?
They lived a long time ago.
Perhaps they're part fable.
Perhaps they're part fantasy.
And perhaps the place
they're walking to now
is not really called eden.
We offer it
only as a presumption.
This has been
the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next ontwilight zone,
three national guardsmen
on a maneuver
traveling across the same ground
formerly occupied
by george custer.
In an outfit called
the 7th cavalry.
Time and its
infinite complexity meshes
in what evolves
as a stunningly different story
about soldiers and indians
suspended in limbo
between then and now.
Ontwilight zonenext, "the 7th
is made up of phantoms".
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org