Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
A honey
from hunnicut!
Drive it in
good health!
Too much power, eh?
We're just looking.
Well, that's what
we want you to do.
Nobody pushes you
around here.
No, sir, young man.
Around here, you can pause,
exhale, check, recheck,
think, peruse, contemplate,
wade through,
thumb over, dip into.
Be my guest, folks.
We were thinking of
maybe a little coupe-
something
around $500-
but as late
a model as we can...
late?
You shock me, you know that?
You know your husband
shocked me just then?
Well, he was only...
do you know why
you shocked me?
I'll tell you why
you shocked me.
It's because you've succumbed
to the propaganda
of every cement-headed clod
up and down this street.
I said propaganda.
They like to push
the late models,
don't they?
They do, don't they?
You know why they
push the late models?
You think it's
because they're honest,
law-abiding, rigidly
moral churchgoers?
Let me tell you
something, young man.
They push...
they push the late models
because that is
where the profit margin is.
They'll cram those
post-'54s down your gullet
because they would rather
make a buck than a friend.
They would rather
make a profit
than a relationship.
They would rather
cram their wallets
full of cash
than fill their hearts
with the fellowship
of men to men.
We're really
just looking
for a good
transportation car,
and we thought
the newer the car...
new? That's where you've
completely gone wrong.
That's where you've
suddenly gone amiss.
That's the juncture that's
headed you into a blind alley.
You don't want a new car.
You don't want one
of those rinky-dink,
slapped-together
on an assembly line,
covered with
chintzy chrome,
fin tails, idiotic names
and no more workmanship
than you can stick
into a thimble.
No.
I'll tell you what you want.
You want the craftsmanship
that comes with age
the dependability
of proven performers
the dignity of
traditional transportation.
This is what you want.
A '38 coupe.
It'll get you where
you want to go.
It'll get you back.
This, as the banner
already has proclaimed
is mr. Harvey hunnicut-
an expert on commerce
and con jobs
a brash, bright and larceny-
loaded wheeler and dealer
who when the good lord
passed out a conscience
must have gone
for a beer and missed out.
And these are a couple
of other characters-
a little old man
in a model-a car
but not just any old man
and not just any model-a.
There's something
very special about them.
In a few moments, they'll give
harvey hunnicut something
that he's never
experienced before.
Through the good offices
of a little magic
they will unload on mr. Hunnicut
the absolute necessity
to tell the truth.
Where they come from
is conjecturable
but as to where they're
heading, this we know:
Because all of them and you
are on the threshold
of the twilight zone.
And did you know
that the original prototype
of this car
was the mark ii tank?
When you go down the freeway,
everybody else, out of the way!
Where the gearshift is
used to be the cannon.
Now, why don't you and i
sit down and talk turkey
because this baby is
the one you're going to buy.
This baby is the one that
you're going to drive off...
well,
first of all...
could we look
it over a bit?
Look!
Here, sit in it.
Get the feel of it.
Relish in the luxury.
See how they built cars
in the days
when cars were really built!
Come on, young fellow!
You, too, madam.
Park yourself in there
and enjoy it to
your heart's content.
Boy, you know what
you really should have
when you sit
in a car like this?
Candlelight,
a bottle of good wine
because this baby here
has dignity.
Relax for a minute,
i'll be right back.
Oh, how do you do.
Well, that depends, grandpa.
If you came here
to park this
i'll just charge you
nominal rates
but if you're here
to sell it
you'll have to give me
three and a half minutes
for my little laugh.
I'll give you 15 bucks for it.
Any junkman will give you 12.
The smithsonian might top
us both by a buck or two.
It's a wonderful old car
and they built them better
in the old days, i think.
Ah, grandfather dear
that is the old
rhubarb, the saw
the turkey everybody
and his brother
is trying to pull
on the open market.
Cars were built better
in the old days, ha!
Ten years ago
they didn't know
how to build cars.
Now it's the new
cars that sell.
Don't mind these.
It's the new cars
that sell.
that run.
It's the new cars
that combine the genius
of mind, muscle
and the assembly line.
Oh, please...
but i'll tell you
what i'll do for you
because i love
your face.
You remind me of
my own grandfather
rest his soul,
a man of dignity
down through his
declining years
until he died rescuing a
capsized boatload of people
on the east river.
I'll give you
25 bucks for it.
Probably have
to tear it down
sell it wheel by
wheel, bolt by bolt
to any itinerant junkman
that comes around
but 25 i'll go.
$25?
Mm-hmm.
I kind of need
the money
but couldn't
you make it 30?
You try me,
old friend.
What does that mean?
That means that
25 is going, going...
that means that
25 is... gone!
There we are.
Ten, 20, and 25.
Now, i'll tell you
what you do.
You go in that
little office there.
You take your car
registration papers
with you,
and hold it...
did i say car?
Vehicle, hmm.
Now, here, hmm.
Comfy?
Signed, sealed and
delivered, mr. Uh...
hunnicut.
Oh, yes, and here
are the keys.
Thank you.
Oh, by the way,
mr. Hunnicut.
There is one other
small item
i ought to mention
to you about the car.
Do, do.
It's haunted.
Haunted?
You don't say.
Oh, yes,
without a doubt.
The car is
quite haunted.
It's been haunted
ever since it came off
the assembly line
and every single
one of its owners
can attest
to this fact.
Well, now,
i don't suppose
you'd mind telling me
how it's haunted, hmm?
You sign right there.
Or how i can
un-haunt it?
Oh, you'll find
out soon enough.
I will.
As for un-haunting it
you'll have
to sell the car.
Oh.
Well, good day,
mr. Hunnicut.
It's been
a real pleasure.
Likewise, likewise.
I think you may find
that you have actually gotten
the best of the bargain at that.
My ancient friend, you do me
the ultimate injustice.
Our little transaction,
haunted or otherwise
was my charity case for the day.
You dwell on that, will you?
Dwell on it.
No, no, no, mr. Hunnicut.
You dwell on it.
And i rather think you will.
Well?
How much is it?
It's not for sale.
Why not?
Uh... well, i don't know.
This car we were
just sitting in.
That's the one
you were pushing.
Yeah, sure.
I... i guess
i'm not pushing it anymore.
This is a wreck, it's a rum-dum.
It...
oh... it hasn't got any points,
it hasn't got any rings
it hasn't got any plugs
and it'll leak gasoline like
it owns every oil well in texas.
But the tires...
are very bad,
and the chassis's been bent
and if i said anything
about it being a runabout
why, i meant it would run
about a block and then stop.
And it'll cost you double
what you pay for it
when you start taking
it in for repairs
and you'll start taking
every third thursday
of the month.
Well, what else
have you got?
Oh, what else,
well...
i... i'll...
i haven't anything else
worthwhile to show you.
Everything in this lot should
have been condemned years ago.
I got more lemons
per square foot
than a fruit grower in salinas.
And what you ought to do
you ought to hit one
of those reputable places
and get what you pay for,
and something you really like
but, uh, you shouldn't
come around here anymore.
Okay.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Oh, hey...
never mind.
Let's go look
at television sets.
Sorry, i'm late, boss.
I was down
at the junkyard
checking on the '34
chevy wheel discs.
I found four of them.
Hey, what's
the action, boss?
Hmm?
Oh, things are a
little quiet around...
irv, you won't
believe what i...
nah, you won't...
hey, how about trying
to move that '35 essex?
Move it is right.
It won't get anywhere
under its own power.
All right,
knock it down to 55
tell everybody it's a museum
piece, last of its kind.
And look!
You keep that hood closed,
you dope!
How many time i gotta tell
you...
when you got an engine you can't
see for rust
you gotta play a little
hide-and-seek.
You don't
go advertising the fact
you're trying to job a car
that carried french soldiers to
the first battle of the marne.
Now listen, irv, i...
...want you to put
a sign on the car
that says it's for sale
as is, no guarantees
and i...
think you
better open up
both sides
of the hood
so they can get a better
look at the engine.
You want to sell it or
keep it for an heirloom?
What's the matter...
do i look all right to you, irv?
What did you have for dinner?
No, no, this is nuts.
This is power of suggestion
or something.
Hey, that old gleep
that sold me
that model-a,
a real nutsy.
Gave me a song
and dance
about a haunted car.
You get that?
Haunted car.
And i was stupid enough
to stand there
and listen to him.
What i should have done
was call up the local hatch
reserved a rubber room
for him.
Honey, this is
your ever-loving.
Now, look, baby
about tonight
i'm going
to be a little late.
Well, it's
inventory time.
Look, i told you it
was inventory time.
What i'm going to be
doing tonight is i...
i'm going to be
playing poker with the boys
and when i told you it was
inventory time last month
i was playing poker
with the boys then.
You were doing what!
Honey, don't
listen to me!
This is nuts,
i'm sick or something.
Look, what i'm really
going to be doing tonight
is i'm... going to be
playing poker with the boys.
What is this?
Am i crazy or something?
I got no control
over what i'm saying.
I got no control...
irv...
i'm in the midst of a calamity.
That old gleep
i was telling you about
the one who said
that car was haunted...
he was right.
Whoever owns that car
has to tell the truth.
Hey, irv, you dig?
Did you ever hear
anything more ghastly?
Me... harvey hunnicut
from now on, as long
as i own that car
i have to tell the truth.
Well, here are the signs
you wanted, boss.
Yeah.
I've heard of low pressure
before, boss
but let's face it-
this is no pressure.
Irv, you know my wife
isn't speaking to me.
Would that that were
your only worry, boss.
You haven't moved a car
off the lot in three days.
I know.
That old lady who came in
yesterday afternoon
to buy that old auburn...
i mean, let's level now.
How do you start a sales pitch
by telling the customer
that if the car
was one year older
moses could have driven it
across the red sea?
There's a limit
to honesty, boss!
Irving, i...
i used to feel
that way myself.
I hate to bother
you now, boss
but it's that thing
about my raise.
Your raise?
Well, it's six months today
i don't want to bug you,
but you promised.
You said that in six months
if i'd sold three cars,
that you
would turn...
oh. Yeah, well, sure.
When i... i...
the day you get more money
out of me,
it'll be below zero
in the fijis.
Every yokel who works here
starts and stops
at the same salary.
I only dangle that raise
in front of them
just as long as it
takes them to get wise.
Irv... irv...
for you to get more money
out of me
would be just about as easy
as...
pouring hot butter
into a wildcat's ear.
Irv, that hurt me
more than it did you.
Correction.
This is going to hurt you
a lot more than it hurts me.
What's your pleasure, sir?
Oh, luther grimbley here.
Honest luther grimbley.
30 years in politics,
currently up for reelection.
Alderman, 13th ward.
You've probably heard of me.
Delighted.
Something nice
in a model-a?
Beautiful, isn't it?
That depends.
If you take 12 aspirin
and shut your eyes tight
you might call
it beautiful.
But in the cold
light of day, son
it's a wreck.
What about
its condition?
Well, let me tell
you one thing...
the block's cracked.
Block cracked?
Block cracked.
What else?
You can see
for yourself.
You take a good look
at these tires.
The rubber's shot.
Yeah, sure is.
Might be good
for a few years
not many, though.
Many?
This car is living
on borrowed time.
What...
what's she worth?
Oh...
i mean assuming some clod
who wanted a real bum car
to use for a gag
or something
maybe... uh...
50 bucks?
50 bucks!
All right, maybe 60.
Why not 30?
You don't understand,
do you?
This is a bad car,
you see.
It's a lemon.
Lemon?
Why you dirty dog, you.
You clever son of a gun.
That's the truth.
That's the absolute truth.
I've seen all kinds
of routines
all kinds of routines
but you clever
little cookie, you.
This is the old reverse
english, isn't it?
The old twister-oo?
Why you sharp-shooting,
sharpie!
You knew i wanted it,
didn't you?
You little devil you!
You knew i wanted it.
I'll tell you what.
I'll give you
25 bucks for it.
On account of it's good politics
to drive an old car.
Makes people think you're
not getting rich off of them.
25 bucks!
How about 22½?
Huh?
I didn't notice
the dent in the fender.
Oh.
I mean $22.50,
the car and no strings.
No, uh, strings?
You better trot out
the strings, buddy boy.
Trot out the strings.
I want to know what i'm getting.
Well, $22.50, the car as is,
and, uh...
and, uh, what?
Uh... well... uh...
the car's haunted.
Haunted?
The car is haunted?
So it's haunted.
I swear, you're the
cleverest cookie in the...
you ought to be
in politics.
Haunted?
How is it haunted?
Well, whoever owns it
has to tell the truth.
Whoever owns it has
to tell the truth?
The whole truth,
and the only way
he can stop telling the truth
is to sell the car.
How about this baby?
That's no baby.
That's a great-grandfather.
Hasn't got any transmission,
no rear end, no axle.
That one's shot.
That's the goods,
is it?
You have to tell
the truth, don't you?
That's it.
That's the reason
for the song and dance.
You have
to tell the truth.
Well, what about
the model-a?
I mean, in spite of
the fact that it's haunted
it's, it's still a swell...
conversation piece.
For some people,
maybe
but not for old,
honest luther grimbley.
Buddy boy,
i'm in politics.
When you tell me
i got to start telling
the truth all the time
holy hanna!
You know something?
I couldn't make
a single political speech.
I couldn't run
for office again.
Now why don't you
sell this car
to boss ryan
over at 12th ward.
I'd love to hear him
tell the truth just once.
Or the mayor, the mayor!
Why don't you...?
Hey, why not even
to this guy, huh?
Who?
This fella?
Say, that's
not a bad idea.
If you could get him
to tell the truth
that might be
the greatest gag
of all time.
Yeah...
why not, huh?
Oh, boy!
That would be...
your reasoning seems
valid, mr. Hunnicut.
It's your motives
that we're concerned...
don't worry
about my motives.
I bought the car
for 25 bucks
i'm selling
it for 25.
Talk it over
with your boss.
I believe we'll accept
your terms, mr. Hunnicut.
You say $25
american money.
25 american dollars.
I got the papers.
Now, this is
the bill of sale
the transfer of title,
the car registration.
Have your boss sign all three of
them on the dotted lines there.
I'm empowered to handle
the signatures myself.
Oh, no, no.
The boss has to sign
them, you dig?
The boss, the boss
has to sign them.
A sort of memento
or souvenir, is that it?
Uh, yeah,
something like that.
Well, i'll see
what i can do.
Here we are.
And here is the money.
25 american dollars.
You lucky dog, you.
You got a million bucks
worth of propaganda here
you know that?
Now all you have to do
is to try to tell
your folks
that this is the kind
of a car
the average american drives.
You try and
tell them that.
These are your copies,
these are mine.
That does it.
Your boss is now
the new owner of this car.
Drive it right off, buddy boy.
You drive it right off.
Is this the living end!
And i got
his signature right here.
Nikita khrushchev.
Uh, long distance?
Operator, say,
if an american citizen
has something real important
in the way of news...
uh, well...
i mean if it affects the foreign
policy of the united states...
well, what i'd really
like to know is...
can you get me through
to jack kennedy?
Couldn't happen you say?
Far-fetched, way out,
tilt-of-center?
Possible, but the next time
you buy an automobile
if it happens to look
as if it's gone through
the battle of the marne
and the seller is ready to throw
into the bargain one of his arms
be particularly careful
in explaining to the boss
about your grandmother's funeral
when you were actually at chavez
ravine watching the dodgers.
It'll be a fact
that you're the proud possessor
of an instrument of truth
manufactured and distributed
by an exclusive dealer
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling, creator
ofthe twilight zone
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, we bring you a show
called "the invaders"
written by mr. Richard matheson.
And in this room you'll watch
miss agnes moorehead
in a tension-riddled attempt
at escape
from a pair of very improbable
housebreakers.
This one we recommend to science
fiction buffs, fantasy lovers
or to anyone who wants to grip
the edge of his seat
and take a 24-minute trip
into the realm of terror.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
? please, please
don't be a litterbug?
? 'cause every litter bit
hurts.?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org