Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Uniquely american institution
known as the neighborhood bar.
Reading left to right are
mr. Anthony o'toole, proprietor
who waters his drinks
like geraniums
but who stands four-square
for peace and quiet
and for booths for ladies.
This is mr. Joseph j. Callahan,
an unregistered bookie
whose entire life is
any sporting event
with two sides
and a set of odds.
His idea of a meeting at
the summit is any dialogue
between a catcher and pitcher
with more than one man on base.
And this animated citizen
is every anonymous bettor
who ever dropped rent money
on a horse race or prize fight
or a floating crap game
and who took out his
frustrations and his insolvency
on any vulnerable fellow
barstool companion
within arm's and fist's reach.
And this is mr. Luther dingle,
a vacuum cleaner salesman
whose volume of business
is roughly that
of a valet
at a hobo convention.
He's a consummate failure
in almost everything
but is a good listener
and has a prominent jaw.
Don't give me
that, callahan.
I don't pay off
on a bum call.
Three umpires call
the man out.
I call
60,000 fans call
the man out.
The final score was
pittsburgh 3, dodgers nothing.
You and i got an even bet, pal.
I happened to have the pirates.
You got the dodgers.
So you owe me
five dollars.
The ball was foul
when it hit him
so instead of an out,
it was a foul ball.
So who's to say there wouldn't
have been a man on base?
And when pignatano got a single
a run would have scored.
And furthermore, callahan,
you're nothing but a cheating
insult to the american bookie.
I'll give you five seconds
to take back that innuendo.
Callahan, i told you
once before already.
You start another brawl
in here
and i'm going to fix
that mouth of yours
so any future
drinking you'll do
is gonna be through
a tube stuck in a vein.
Me? Why me?
Tell it to the troublemaker.
The number-one welcher
of all the western states
sitting over here.
His father owes my father from
the second dempsey-tunney fight.
Yeah? Yeah? Yeah?
Mainly on account of
it was a bum call.
Hey, buddy, did you see
the tunney fight?
You remember the referee
with the long count?
The guy was knocked
clear out of the ring.
You could have gone up in the
stands, got a can of beer
engaged in a
little conversation
come back,
sit down in your seat
and the referee still
wasn't finished counting.
Now, i ask you,
how about that?
I ask you,
how about it?
Me?
Yeah, yeah, you.
Did you watch the game
on television last night?
You talk about
bum calls.
Duke snider was up
and it was in
the ninth inning.
Two men were out.
Howard and moon were
on first and second.
And this umpire
with no pupils in his eyes
calls a foul ball an out.
Did you see it?
) as a matter of fact i did
watch the game on television.
Exceptional defensive play,
exceptional.
Abner d-d-doubleday
would have been proud.
Never mind about
abner doubleday.
I'm willing to leave
it up to you.
Was it a foul ball
or was it an out?
It appears to me that the ball
fell into fair territory
and therefore when
striking the ground
and hitting the batter
the rules very definitely state
the batter was out.
You asked the man,
you got an answer.
Of course you
realize, pal
that you're
calling me a liar.
Now, i'm not an
unreasonable man
so i'm going
to give you
one more chance.
Was it a
foul ball
or was it
an out?
Well, it's
my considered opinion...
how's come you got to
always be hitting dingle?
You hit him last week,
you him the week before.
A man can only
stand so much.
I'm tired of this guy
contradicting me.
And when a guy
calls me a liar
there's my honor
to be considered.
Your honor?
You've got nothing
in line in you
from the bottom
of your arches
to where you
part your hair
which is pretty tough
to find.
And when you die
they'll have to screw you in the ground.
Am i crooked?
You got to
believe me.
Am i crooked?
Dingle, dingle,
for once...
for once, why can't
you be neutral?
Am i crooked?
Why don't you tell the man?
Wait a minute,
back off.
Are you serious
about this?
And these two unseen gentlemen
are visitors from outer space.
They're about to alter
the destiny of luther dingle
by leaving him a legacy
the kind you can't
hardly find no more.
In just a moment, a sad-faced,
perennial punching bag
who missed even the caboose
of life's gravy train
will take a short constitutional
into that most
unpredictable region
that we refer to
as the twilight zone.
This man don't know the
first thing about baseball.
If anybody
can tell me
the phillies
deserved
winning the pennant that year
they're out
of their minds.
You sure
we're invisible?
Beyond any doubt.
I wish they were.
You don't have
to do that.
You don't even
have to answer.
Just because he don't like the phillies...
let me tell him.
You have a brain of
your own, don't you?
You have your
own viewpoint.
What did you think of
the phillies of 1953?
Phillies... 1953?
That's right.
That's right,
phillies of 1953.
You ever see such jerky-looking creatures?
And one head yet.
Typical earthmen.
Not really though.
The one in the middle,
the one who just suffered
the physical damage
he may be the one
we've been looking for.
How do you mean?
Silence,
i'm receiving his waves.
Name is dingle, abject coward
does not even possess what earth
creatures call minimum muscles.
Decidedly a sub-physical type.
I think we have
found our subject.
You intend to give him
the additional strength?
We haven't found
anyone weaker, have we?
I believe he will be
an exceptional subject.
Give him around 11 secograms atomic weight.
That should make him
roughly 300 times stronger
than the average
human being.
Yes, i think
that will do it.
We had better contact central laboratories
tell them we have
found a subject.
In other words,
you're telling me
that you thought robin
roberts had more stuff
than clem levine?
Well, to be frank and candid
those two men,
as good as they both are
and all things
being equal...
come on already,
take your pick.
Roberts?
For the last time.
You start one more
roughhouse in here
and i won't let
you come back.
Now, look what
you've done.
How you feeling,
dingle?
C-c-clem l-l-l-levine
was definitely superior.
You see?
All i made him do
was see things
clearer.
I can observe him now.
Let him have it.
How about it, dingle?
How you doing?
Definitely clem levine.
Dingle, would
you mind
a little advice?
Now, the whole world
is full of guys
that are going to get
punched in the nose
no matter who they
pick in a ball game
who they
vote for.
Now, you want
to know my advice
for what you should do
for the rest
of your life?
Just don't talk,
just nod.
Somebody asks you who
you like in the third
you just smile.
Understand, dingle?
What's the matter?
It's very odd.
What's odd?
I... i feel f-f-funny.
Funny?
Yeah.
Wonder what
caused that?
Caused what?
Well, this vacuum
cleaner, it's...
light as a feather.
Not that the machine
isn't right.
No, sir, it's the lightest on the market.
Yes, sir,
i tell you
it's a handy-dandy
piece of merchandise.
Guaranteed to lighten the load
and lengthen the life
of that partner in the home,
th-th-the housewife.
But i didn't know
it was this light.
Dingle, i always
figured you
for a nice guy.
You never caused me no trouble.
Now why all of a sudden
you got to wreck my front door?
Mr. O'toole,
i'm mystified.
I'm absolutely
mystified.
This door seemed to come
right off in my hand.
You here again?
Didn't my old man say
he was gonna punch you
in the nose
if you came around here
bothering us again?
You're quite right.
It's the wrong number.
I was headed
across the street.
Now that's not the best
of all possible manners, is it?
Aw, go peddle your vacuum
cleaners, you creep
and throw me
my ball back.
All right, run out for the pass.
Hey, mister, where'd you learn
to fling a ball like that?
Why, i don't know.
I really don't...
what is happening?
What on earth is
happening to me?
Taxi, taxi, please.
Thank you.
Oh, believe me, this is as much
a mystery to me as it is to you.
They don't make handles like
they used to, do they?
Oh, i'm sorr...
excuse me, miss.
Yes.
I don't want you to
think i'm a masher.
I'm certainly
not a masher.
But would you mind
answering a question?
That depends.
Well, what i mean
is looking at me
in a perfunctory,
cursory first surveil
do i appear abnormal
in any way?
Not at all.
Not unless you plan
to use that in the park.
Oh, that.
Do you know that up
until a few hours ago
i sold those.
Or i went through
the motions.
I was a very
bad salesman.
Miserable.
You know, last week
i only made 89 cents
in commissions.
That was for
an attachment.
It's the
upholstery nozzle.
And i sold it to a drunk
who thought it was
a divining rod for alcohol.
Oh, i fully expect
to be fired
but that is the least of my trouble.
Would you be interested
in hearing the most
of my worries?
Go ahead.
Watch.
You see?
Now, w-w-watch this.
Hey, buddy, i'm a reporter
with thebulletin.
Would you mind doing that again?
With the rock?
That's right.
Incidentally,
what's the gag?
There's no gag, see?
Get another
one of those.
This i got to get
in the paper.
Goodness.
Mr. Dingle, if what
we hear is true
do you realize how much money can be made
on a tour with
our carnival?
Mr. Dingle, this
is a con artist.
Your future lies
in television.
You're the walking,
talking embodiment
of every american male's
wish fulfillment.
You're john q. Citizen.
You're babbitt,
you're tom, dick and harry.
Now here's our idea
for the series.
A simple 15-minute
address by you
with little examples of
your physical prowess.
It's a natural for
breakfast cereals
tonics, vitamin
pills, anything.
And i keep
telling you
you line up
with me
i'll get you some easy setups.
Inside of
eight months
i'll have
you fighting
for the world
championship.
That's so
ridiculous.
Would the people
surrounding mr. Dingle
just get out of
the way, please.
Out of the way.
The camera in there and
that light there and...
hello, there, friends.
Jason abernathy here with your
show, tv probes the unusual.
And our unusual subject today
is mr. Luther dingle
who, if what actual
onlookers say is true
is the world's strongest man.
Mr. Dingle...
mr. Dingle, would you care
to give us an example
of this fantastic alleged
strength of yours?
I'd be ha-happy to.
Is it all right,
mr. O'toole if i...
are you kidding?
I ain't done so much business
since the night they repealed
the 18th amendment.
Be my guest,
mr. Dingle.
First, i'd like to start
with simple things.
Wonderful.
Wait a minute, dingle.
Ain't you ever heard of
bygones being bygones?
That's amazing.
Bravo!
Had enough?
Most inferior.
We give him the
strength of 300 men
and he uses it
for petty exhibition.
Give him 20 or
30 seconds more
then remove the power.
Excellent idea.
And i think
we should be off.
Three planets on
tomorrow's itinerary.
One should be particularly interesting-
contains only females.
And now, ladies...
and now, ladies and gentlemen
i believe the most
unique trick of all
i shall raise this entire
building with my bare hands.
What? Raise
the building?
He can't
do that.
I don't
believe it.
I don't know.
He seems to
have lost it.
He's a fake, that's what he is.
I feel sorry for him.
Poor little guy
he's lost
his belief.
He's a sad little man,
isn't he?
Uh-oh!
All right, leave off
of poor dingle here.
Now, come on,
everybody out of here.
Come on, beat it.
Ladies and gentlemen
you have this station's
abject apology.
We didn't realize that it
was a trick... obviously...
well, we're
off the air...
for good, i think.
So long, hercules.
Bring that thing
out of here.
How are you, fellas?
Nice seeing you.
Where are
you from?
Venus. How about you?
Mars. Conducting
experiments?
Yeah,
and you?
Sudden introduction
of strength
to subnormal earthman.
How about you?
Sudden introduction of
extreme intelligence.
Find any interesting
subjects?
That one over there.
He's referred to
as a dingle.
He certainly is
sub-physical.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he's sub-mental, too.
Looks likely enough.
Give him the intelligence quota ray.
How strong?
Make it about...
let's see.
Perhaps 500 times
more intelligent
than the
average human.
Roebuck's ready.
Here's the pitch.
High and outside.
He couldn't hit the
length of the bat.
I'll lay you five
to one he gets on.
Logan? Are you
out of your mind?
Hey, hey, dingle.
What about it?
What will he do?
Various factors are
brought into play here
involving the laws
of probability
interspersed with
the process of calculus
fenaglian laws of chance
and the subdivisional grepple
which is based on
the position of bodies
in mathematical relationship
to other bodies.
Now, in this case,
using the two factors
represented by the
divisions involved
i think that the batter will
unquestionably hit a home run.
A home run by johnny logan.
Holy mackerel!
How about that?
Light.
...two to one.
A tremendous blow over
the left-field fence.
Now, it appears to
me it is apparent
in a
mathematical plan
that the entire
quantum theory
of space and
time relativity
must have been equated
with the parellelian role
of definitive numerical
dialectic algebraic
and must be
further annotated...
exit mr. Luther dingle,
formerly vacuum cleaner salesman
strongest man on earth,
and now mental giant.
These latter powers will likely
be eliminated before too long
but mr. Dingle has an appeal
to extra-terrestrial note-takers
as well as to frustrated
and insolvent bet-losers.
Offhand, i'd say
he was in for a great deal
of extremely odd periods
simply because there are
so many inhabited planets
who send down observers
and also because of course
mr. Dingle lives his life
with one foot in his mouth and
the other in the twilight zone.
Rod serling, the creator
ofthe twilight zone
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
A radio.
A carryover from that other era
when quiz shows
went up to only $64
and entertainment was aimed
only at the ears.
Mr. Charles beaumont
has given us
a most unusual story
called "static."
We invite you to watch
mr. Dean jagger
fiddle with a few of these
knobs, change a few stations
and find a couple of programs
that are broadcast
only in the twilight zone.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
see the newandy griffith show
each week
over most of these stations.
Consult local listings.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org