Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Charlie?
Go back to sleep,
ella, it's early.
What time is it?
My watch stopped.
It's pitch black out.
It must be 3:00 or
4:00 in the morning.
Look how black
it is out there.
It's the middle
of the night.
Oh, i think you're
crazy to get up now.
What's so special
about hanging
a little...
go back
to sleep, ella!
Well, why don't you?
You'll have all
that excitement today.
You're the one
that needs the sleep.
Bring us breakfast
over about 8:30.
What time they string him up?
Well, you know what i mean.
What time does he get hung?
He get'sexecutedat 9:30.
And i hope
the whole town
doesn't turn out.
When i see a bunch of
cold-blooded gawkers
getting their jollies
from seeing a man die,
i just...
just bring us breakfast
over at 8:30.
Oh, charlie?
How does he like his eggs?
Edible.
They're the last ones
he's going to eat
so make them edible.
I don't get it.
What don't you get, deputy?
Sheriff, it's 7:30
in the morning,
and it's pitch
black outside.
I've never seen
it any blacker,
but it's 7:30
in the morning.
Now, what's
going on?
I don't know, deputy.
It's 7:30 in the morning
and it's pitch black outside.
To tell you the truth...
i don't know why.
I don't know why at all.
Sheriff charlie koch
on the morning of an execution.
As a matter of fact,
it's 7:30 in the morning.
Logic and natural laws dictate
that at this hour
there should be daylight.
It is a simple rule
of physical science
that the sun should rise
at a certain moment
and supersede the darkness.
But at this given moment
sheriff charlie koch,
a deputy named pierce,
a condemned man named jagger,
and a small,
inconsequential village
will shortly find out that
there are causes and effects
that have no precedent.
Such is usually the case
in the twilight zone.
How about that?
You see it
outside?
You better
run an extra
in that paper
of yours.
I've been answering
the phone
since 6:00 this morning.
One fellow called, said the
electricity had gone off-
it was tomorrow night.
Another godly woman,
who professes to read her good
book with admirable regularity,
tells me it's
the end of the world
and she can quote the chapter
and verse to support her thesis.
Now, you're well-versed
in all things
regarding law and
order, sheriff koch.
What's your thesis?
It's quarter to 8:00.
It's quarter to
8:00 in the morning
and it doesn't make
any sense.
Daylight should have
come two hours ago.
Well, in between
reassuring people
that this was not
an interplanetary
invasion,
nor the end
of the world,
i placed a call to
the state capital.
Is it black there?
It appears that
across the face
of the entire earth
we are the only ones
groping in darkness.
So it seems
the phenomenon
is quite localized
and we'll just have
to seek elsewhere
for company to
share our misery.
Have you seen
jagger this morning?
I seen him.
I brought him in
a cup of coffee.
I also reminded him
about what day it was.
I'll bet you did.
How did you
occupy yourself
as a lad, deputy?
Torturing
small animals
or just pulling
wings off flies?
What do you mean
by that, mr. Colbey?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Can i talk to jagger?
Go right on in.
As a point of
interest, sheriff,
is jagger innocent?
Mr. Colbey, that is a matter for
a jury, public opinion and god,
and that, thank the lord,
has nothing to do with me.
So let us all praise god
for the morning's impartiality.
And for justice being served
deluxe style.
Deputy...
why don't you shut your mouth.
I got a right to an opinion.
Indeed you have,
deputy.
Indeed you have.
But there's just a few
disturbing facets
about this case.
One...
the murdered man
was not a decent man.
He was a cross-burning,
psychopathic bully
who attacked the man in there.
And two, deputy pierce here
saw it happen
and then perjured himself.
Now, wait a minute!
Perjured
is the word, deputy.
Now, you said
jagger shot him
from across the room.
No such thing.
The murdered man had
powder burns all over him.
This might not have
proven self-defense
but it would've pointed
to it and maybe helped it.
And you, sheriff koch,
you saw the body.
But i didn't hear
any comments
on those
powder burns
when you gave
your testimony.
And your courageous editor here
in covering the trial
didn't see fit to include
this insignificant addendum
though he also knew at the time
he was being very selective
about what truths he was writing
about, what truths he wasn't.
You're right, deputy.
Justice is
being served...
on a platter with
its tongue cut out
just like the carcass
of any dead animal.
Let me know when
you're ready.
It's pitch black
outside.
Almost 8:00
in the morning.
Not a speck
of daylight.
This place doesn't
have any windows
so it could
be christmas eve
or the fourth of july
and i would not know
the difference.
You got any religious
affiliation, jagger?
None.
Anyone you want to see?
Nobody.
Anything to say?
Nothing.
No priest, no friends,
no comment.
Just what have
you got, jagger?
I got the blues, mr. Colbey!
I got the blues.
I'm just about
an hour away
from a hanging
and i've been lying there
and i have been thinking
that i would like
to rip these bars apart
and get out of here.
Or i'd like to save everybody
else the trouble
and hang myself right here.
But, you see, i don't have
the strength for one
or the guts for the other
so i'm just lying there,
and i am just waiting.
Well, in that case, would you
care to make a statement
about guilt or innocence?
Guilt or innocence, and you
want me to make a statement?
I'd appreciate
one.
I don't think anybody
should leave this earth
without making a comment-
you, me, anybody.
Well, that's a
reasonable request, mr. Colbey.
Considering the fact that you're
not leaving this morning
that's
reasonable.
I'm guilty, mr. Colbey.
That take you off the hook?
And that's supposed
to mean what?
That's supposed
to mean
you're on the
popular side.
There are good guys
and bad guys-
that's human nature.
Well, i'm worse
than a bad guy.
I'm a town kook, i'm a neurotic.
I'm the one with the causes
and the banners.
I'm the village idiot
who tries to be
his brother's
keeper.
Do you understand,
mr. Colbey?
The man i killed
was the white knight.
He did what
his other pals
in this town
wanted to do and
didn't have the guts.
Hewas the cross burner,
the bomb thrower.
Hehandled the whipping of
some poor, scared colored guy.
Oh...
the man you killed
was no saint
but we don't dispense
life or death
just because somebody
offends us.
That's the distinction
between men and animals.
Well, that's very well said.
That's very well said,
mr. Colbey.
You tell that
to the man
who's going to
fix my rope.
You tell it to the sheriff
and his deputy
to the townspeople
who are going to stand around
and watch my eyes bulge out
and enjoy my agony.
You tell them.
You tell them about
the difference
between men
and animals.
But you better be ready
to draw pictures
because this language
they just don't dig!
9:00 in the morning.
Why is it so dark?
Is it
an eclipse?
Can't be.
I'm listening
to the radio.
Ain't no eclipse.
It's weird.
It's just
plain weird.
But scientists can offer
no explanation
for the strange phenomenon
of darkness
that has suddenly
and inexplicably
covered the remote
little midwestern village.
It is now 9:00 a.m.
Eastern standard time
but last reports indicate
the darkness there is total.
There is no remote hint
of any kind of daylight.
Looks pretty good.
That ought to
tend to him.
But who's going to tend to us?
Who or what is going
to tend to us?
Ten more minutes.
You, uh,
going to go through
with this, sheriff?
Why not?
The law says may 25,
at 9:30 in the morning.
Well, it's may 25,
and it'll be 9:30
in the morning.
Quite apart from
the fact, mr. Pierce,
that you're not the
most sensitive of men,
did it ever occur to you
there's something
odd going on here
and we better dispense
with business as usual
until we find out
exactly what is going on?
You know something?
I take an awful lot
of dirt from you.
And just who
are you, anyway?
A little-shot editor of
a crummy little paper.
That's right,
a crummy little paper
that crawls along on
its hands and knees
from one edition
to the other.
You got more creditors
than you got readers.
That'll do
it, pierce.
No, that won't do it
by a long shot!
Now, maybe you
feel like turning
your cheek
to this crumb
but there ain't
no rule book
that says i got to.
He says
i perjured myself;
says i lied.
He wasn't
throwing no bouquets
at you, neither.
Maybe i don't deserve any.
You were right, you know.
I saw the victim.
He did have powder burns.
But when a committee
of townspeople came to me
and said there'd be no autopsy,
i just bent my head
and i nodded.
We all got little axes
to grind, don't we?
I want to be reelected
sheriff.
You want to keep
selling newspapers.
And deputy pierce here...
he likes to feel
important;
he likes
to be popular,
likes to stay on
the good side of people.
Here we are, gentlemen,
treading water in a sewer.
I don't take it
from him
and i don't take it
from you!
You better unravel it, pierce,
or i'll spread you
all over this yard.
Let's go get
the prisoner.
At last, mr. Pierce.
A labor of love, huh?
Do you suppose, reverend,
there might be some
theological explanation?
Theological explanation?
For the death, or the darkness,
or both.
You know, reverend,
maybe if we thought
it was some divine act,
we could sort of live with it.
This is not the first gallows,
reverend, nor the last.
Or he won't be the first
unhappy man died an early age.
We won't be the last mourners
on earth either.
Did you see him?
Did you get to talk to him?
Briefly.
He wouldn't see me.
Wouldn't even let me inside.
It's a pity.
He's a very lonely man.
But he won't be lonely
very long.
He's got a few
minutes, hasn't he?
He used them up already.
We're four minutes behind.
You can talk to
him, reverend.
Take
your time.
It'smytime.
I got nothing
to say.
Then let's go.
Let's get on
with it!
Yeah!
You don't want
to waste
your last minutes,
jagger.
Now, you and i are
a different faith,
and obviously
a different color,
but you stood up
for me and mine.
You spoke for us,
and god help us,
you killed for us.
And i feel
you deserve
some measure
of peace.
I want to give you some.
That'll give me some peace.
I don't need
any words, reverend.
No quotations in or out
of the bible.
Come on, let's get it
over with!
Yeah!
Patience!
I promise you,
i will please you all,
believe me.
I'll choke and suffer and dance.
Oh, you'll get
your money's worth.
Believe me.
Quiet!
But i tell you
what i won't give you,
you muckers!
I won't give you
the satisfaction of saying
that i'm
sorry.
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah!
Don't return
their hate.
Don't dishonor
yourself.
Why don't you
get out of here.
I got too much
hate in me
to keep plugged up
anymore.
When he came at you, jagger...
did it feel good to you then?
What difference?
When you aimed that gun
at his head,
that wasn't such a bad moment,
was it?
Good, bad, who cares?
When you killed him, jagger,
when you blew his head off,
there were no regrets then,
were there?
You enjoyed that, didn't you?
You know it!
Yes, yes, i...
i know it now.
Now i know it too well.
You're guilty.
This manisguilty.
It's important to get
with the majority, isn't it?
That's...
that's a big thing nowadays,
isn't it, reverend?
That's all there is,
is the majority.
The minority must have died
on the cross 2,000 years ago.
You seen the light,
reverend.
You really
seen the light.
Haveyou?
Have any of you?
In all this darkness,
is there anybody
who can make out the truth?
He hated and he killed
and now he dies.
And you hated, you killed,
and now there's
not one of you...
not one of you
who isn't doomed.
Do you know why it's dark?
Do you know why it is night
all around us?
Do you know what
the blackness is?
It's the hatehefelt,
the hateyoufelt,
the hate all of us feel,
and there's too much of it.
There's just too much.
And so we had
to vomit it out.
And now it's coming
up all around us
and choking us.
So much hate,
so much miserable hate.
Look.
Look what's happening.
It's getting even darker now.
I can't...
i can't hardly see
anything now.
That's crazy, ain't it?
I mean what he said.
Ain't that crazy?
You know what's
going to happen?
Believe me, you know
what's going to happen?
This here stuff's going to lift.
It'll all of a sudden
just plain lift.
Why it's just... just fog
is all it is.
No more than fog.
And it'll lift.
And there'll
be the old sun,
high up and bright.
You wait and see.
There'll be the old sun
shining to beat the band.
Well, it could happen,
couldn't it?
Couldn't that happen, koch?
Colbey?
There'll be sun again.
There'll be daylight.
I don't know.
I don't know if there'll
ever be daylight again.
Only god knows.
I'm sure only god knows.
And still the phenomenon
remains unexplained
except for the reports
coming in of similar occurrences
here in the united states
and elsewhere.
At 2:00 this afternoon
a dark cloud appeared
over a street in dallas, texas.
The mayor of west berlin
verified that a rectangular area
over the berlin wall
has suddenly gone dark.
In budapest,
european newspapermen
passed over censorship
an article
about several square blocks,
including a political prison
which was suddenly thrown into
darkness early this morning.
In birmingham, alabama,
an area in shanghai, the entire
northern section of vietnam,
a section of chicago, illinois,
the darkness continues
to make itself known.
A sickness known as hate;
not a virus, not a microbe,
not a germ-
but a sickness nonetheless,
highly contagious,
deadly in its effects.
Don't look for it
in the twilight zone-
look for it in a mirror.
Look for it before the light
goes out altogether.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next time out we bring you
a few decibels of sound
in a bizarre opus about a man
who breaks eardrums
for a living.
We welcome to the program
two fine talents,
mr. John mcgiver
and miss penny singleton,
who will prove
the following point:
Namely that too much
of a good thing
can have nightmarish results
and that all things
are not necessarily
as they meet the eye or the ear.
Onthe twilight zonenext
"sounds and silences."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org