Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it
is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Still burning.
How long,
you figure?
Three... four hours at the most.
Any idea how many?
My guess is
if general custer's
really looking
for the sioux,
he's going to have
his britches
full of 'em
before the
sun goes down.
Is that the junction
over there?
Bighorn and the
little bighorn-
that's where
they converge.
That'd put them in at the ford,
about four miles up.
That's where he's thinking
about crossing.
Them sioux...
wonder where
they are now?
I wouldn't be too impatient,
mr. Two stripes.
We can go on back
and tell your general custer
this indian trail
is just as fresh as ever.
Little too fresh
for my pay.
Hey, those were shots,
weren't they?
Yeah.
Hey, tiger!
Whoa, easy.
These are just
maneuvers.
Everybody starts
getting trigger-happy,
it's going to turn
into a real war.
Hunting season, huh, maybe?
How about that, mccluskey?
How'd you like to go
hunting some buffalo?
Let's, uh, go
have a look.
Well, if it's the enemy,
i'm giving up.
They can take me
prisoner of war,
and i'll sit out the
rest of the games.
I'm getting
mighty hot
in that portable oven
we're driving.
Mccluskey, i'm
surprised at you.
The old man, the
sergeant here,
we've had our
eyes on you, son.
We was thinking
of recommending
you for o.c.s.,
wasn't we, sarge?
Other than the
fact that you read
a map upside down
and, uh, couldn't navigate
a plow across a ballroom,
we think you've got
a lot of potential.
It's a wigwam.
An honest-to-pete
wigwam.
Oh, there's
a million men
in national guard,
but it's just my luck
to ride around in a tank
with the last of the
red-hot eagle scouts.
You're right,
mccluskey,
that's a wigwam.
Now, why does that
make you so happy?
Well, it's interesting.
Right over there's
the junction of the bighorn
and little bighorn
rivers.
Not far from there
is where custer fought.
Yeah, custer?
Custer who?
General custer.
That's where
the 7th cavalry
fought the sioux indians.
Hey, take a look at that.
Hey, where'd
you get that?
7th cavalry.
How do you figure,
sarge?
Well, i figure it's
in pretty good shape,
considering it's been
laying around here
for about 80 years,
wouldn't you say?
You know, there must
be a lot of ghosts
running around
a place like this.
Oh, yeah, ghosts,
sure, mm-hmm.
Yeah, mccluskey's
got it right.
Somewhere along this river
they fought a pretty big battle.
Custer and 200-odd men
against 2,000 sioux, probably.
Yeah, custer's last stand.
Didn't you ever hear of it,
langsford?
L-i heard of it, mccluskey.
I heard of it.
Why don't you boys
get you a job in a museum?
Maybe they'd send you
out here on an expedition.
Then you can run around
and pick up some antiques.
I thought this was
supposed to be
a motorized patrol,
sarge,
and i thought
that we were
supposed to be
involved in some war games.
Now, personally,
i don't care.
I'd just as soon be out
reconnoitering
in some dark saloon
someplace
or, uh, maybe hanging
around the y.w.c.a.
In a pinch, i'd settle for
something tall and cold and...
d-don't you think
we'd better get back
and find the c.p.?
Shoot, what's the matter,
mccluskey?
Don't you want
to hang around
and wait
for the union cavalry, huh?
So, this is where they fought,
huh, sarge?
Right around here?
Yeah, yeah, it was
around here someplace.
You know, when i was a kid,
i read about everything
that was ever written on it.
Custer and the 7th
were an advance guard
for a general named terry.
Last thing anybody
ever heard from custer
was that he was
dividing his regiment
into three parties.
He was planning on surrounding
what he thought
was a small bunch of indians.
And, uh, see,
captain benteen took
three troops and
he went south;
and major reno, he
crossed the river
and he followed
an indian trail;
and custer went
right up the middle
and rode right into 'em,
and he was slaughtered.
1876.
That was the year.
Ah, now, come on,
now, sarge.
Somebody planted this thing
around here for a gag.
That canteen's
not 80 years old.
Well, shoot,
it's practically new.
Either that, or, uh,
we've had some...
come on, let's get out of here.
Come on, you guys.
Let's get back to the tank.
What was that?
That was the wind.
Yeah... the wind.
Yeah, that's what it was,
the wind.
June 25, 1964.
Or if you prefer,
june 25, 1876.
The cast of characters
in order of their appearance:
A patrol
of general custer's cavalry
and a patrol of national
guardsmen on a maneuver.
Past and present
are about to collide head-on
as they are wont to do
in a very special bivouac area
known as... the twilight zone.
All units reported
in now, finnegan?
Yes, lieutenant.
Good.
Bluebird 7,
come in, over.
Bluebird...
connors, the captain
wants to see you
in his tent
right away,
and it sounded
like to me
it was a little more
than an invitation.
Captain?
How nice of you
to come back.
Did you happen to bring
the tank with you?
Sir?
You were
gone so long,
i thought maybe you
drove it out to a lot
and traded it for
a convertible.
Well, sir, we got
a little, uh, hung up
down by the riverbed
there.
Hung up by what?
The blue team
went north of us,
you went south.
For a guy with as much
regular army as you've got,
you've played this one bonehead
from start to finish.
If there'd been
an umpire around,
you'd have your tank
crossed off and your men.
I'm sorry, sir,
but we, uh, heard
some rifle fire down there
and we went to check it out.
Rifle fire?
According to the lieutenant,
you were down at
the little bighorn-
40 miles away from where
you were supposed to be.
How'd you hear
rifle fire?
That's just it, sir.
We never found out where it
came from or who it came from.
I think you guys must have had
a bottle in that tank.
Tomorrow, you'll
take your tank
and head up here-
rosebud creek.
Follow the creek
for about 15 miles.
We figure the blue team
must've moved across to...
what's the matter with you,
connors?
Are you hung over?
No, sir. No, sir,
nothing like that at all, sir.
But that
rosebud creek-
that's custer's route.
When he left
the yellowstone river,
he went with a major reno,
and reno followed a trail
along that creek.
Sergeant, let's
synchronize, shall we?
My watch says
23:20 hours.
My calendar says 1964.
If you've got a big
thing for these indians,
you got here a little
late in the day.
Captain, i want
to tell you we heard 'em!
Heard what?
Indians!
Their war cries!
Where? When?
This afternoon, sir,
at the junction
of the bighorn
and the little bighorn.
Captain,
now, i know this sounds crazy-
believe me, i know it-
but we found a canteen...
well, i must have left it
in the tank, sir.
That canteen is marked
7th cavalry.
And we found a tepee
close to the river.
A tepee?
Are you bucking
for a section 8, sergeant?
That's the same tepee
that reno's scouts found
the night before the battle!
Reno's scouts, huh?
Reno being...?
Major reno.
When custer split his force
into three columns,
and sent reno's
to the north...
all right, connors,
that'll do.
Line up your patrol
and head out at 0600
tomorrow morning.
And if you meet
any indians...
if you meet indians, will
you take it very slow?
Because they're all
college graduates
and they're probably running
tests on the soil.
Where to now, sarge?
Well, we'll, uh...
we'll follow this trail
about two,
three more miles.
That's reno's route.
Yeah.
Aw, for pete's sakes.
Are you guys
still on that?
It's reno this, benteen that,
custer something else.
I don't know what's
the matter with you.
You talk about it
all night.
Hey!
Hey, wait a minute.
Hold on, now,
wait a minute.
That's an
incinerator,
or it's somebody cooking
a steak or something,
or it's some tourists
that don't dig smokey the bear.
Will you guys
knock it off, huh?
It figures. It has to.
Reno's scouts found the tepee
the night before the battle,
and the following morning,
the column saw smoke signals.
And late that morning,
they got their first indian.
When the war party went by,
one of their troopers shot
the last rider.
Aw, will you stop it?
Come on, now, i
can take a joke
just like
anybody else,
but this is
too much, man.
I'm telling you,
this is too much.
You're going
to tell me
that somewhere
around that bend,
we're going to run into
a war party of sioux!
Well, look, i'm telling you,
man, if that happens,
i'm checking myself in
with the medics, man,
for the rubber room.
But i want to make it
a reservation for three,
you understand me?
Mccluskey,
you moron!
Kid, what are you
shooting at?
Give me that-
mccluskey, look!
Oh, my dear god.
An indian horse without a rider.
I killed him.
Sergeant, i just fired blind
into that dust cloud, but...
all right, langsford, you,
uh, you got something to say,
well, why don't you
say it?
No, sarge.
I got something to ask.
I'd like to know
what's going on around here.
I don't know.
I don't know for sure.
But i got an idea.
Somehow, some way, we're...
following the same trail
that custer did.
Look,
let's figure it out.
Now first, the tepee.
Now, when did we find it,
yesterday afternoon, right?
Just like
the scout did before.
And the smoke signals...
just like reno's column
saw the next morning.
Mccluskey...
he gets himself
an indian, just...
just like on
the day of the battle.
All right, connors.
Okay, let's say... let's
say that you're right.
Let's say that this
thing is happening,
just like you said it is.
Let's say that we're going to
follow this trail just like
well, just like
they did it, huh?
Now, what i want to know is
what's going to happen next?
We're going to wind up
at a massacre.
That's what.
You gonna stop it?
Yeah, stop it, or...
join it.
Finnegan?
Has connors reported in?
Not yet, sir.
Get him.
Yes, sir.
Bluebird 9?
Bluebird 9, this is c.p.
Bluebird 9, bluebird 9, over.
This is bluebird 9,
go ahead, c.p.
They're
acknowledging, sir.
Connors?
This is the captain.
It's mccluskey, sir.
Mccluskey?
Do you think you guys
might extend yourselves a bit
and give me your position?
We're about four miles
down rosebud creek.
We're about to cross over.
You're about to come back here
on the double.
You're about to report
to me personally.
You're about to do it
within the next half-hour
or you'll be spending the
next three national holidays
in the guardhouse,
do you read me?
Yes, sir, just a minute.
Here's sergeant connors.
Captain,
this is connors.
Connors, do i have to send
a couple of m.p. S down there?
Captain, look,
we're just a mile
from where major reno
met the sioux!
Listen to me, connors.
I'm going to give this
to you just once.
When these maneuvers are over,
you can come back here
on a vacation
and dig arrowheads,
or anything you like.
But right now, i want
a government-issue tank
back here at the command post
with three national guardsmen
named connors, mccluskey and
langsford right alongside it.
Now, you've got
exactly 30 minutes
to bring her back here.
Acknowledge!
Connors, acknowledge!
Connors!
He's broken off,
sir.
Lieutenant!
Take a jeep and three
men down rosebud crick.
Just follow the tread marks,
and bring 'em back.
What if they resist?
I'll tell you, lieutenant.
First apologize,
then shoot each one in the leg.
Do you read me?
All right,
let's move out.
Nothing.
Nothing and no one.
And right down there
is where reno had his battle.
Well...
you guys better manufacture
a couple of indians in a hurry.
Because, uh...
i know a national guards captain
that's probably on his way here
with a net!
Where are they, sarge?
How come we missed out?
You want
an explanation?
We missed out
because we're looking
for dead cavalry,
buried indians
and an 80-year-old battle.
That's why
we missed out.
Now, i've been doing
some thinking about this thing,
see, and i got it figured out.
This whole thing
is strictly an illusion.
That's the goods-
it's an illusion!
We've talked ourselves
into a stinking illusion.
No, that's not it.
That's not it at all.
Mccluskey...
do you remember
what it was that reno
found before the battle?
He even sent a message back
to custer about it.
Sure, the village.
What village?
What do i have to tell you guys
to straighten you out, huh?
Tell me.
Reno's scouts
found an indian village,
and it was an hour after that
that the whole troop
went into action.
Aw, man, my aching back.
I swear, i give up.
I give up!
This is where the men
separate from the nutsies.
Where're
you going?
I'm going to cut back to c.p.,
if i can find it.
But don't worry, boys.
I'm going to send you
a padded ambulance.
Arrivederci...
you all!
It's the village.
That's a mirage,
is it, langsford?
It's not really
there, is it?
I don't know, man,
don't ask me anything.
Don't-don't ask
me nothing, i...
i'll go down
and scout it.
You know, an hour ago
if he'd said that,
i'd have laughed
at him or shut him up,
but now
i don't know.
Just be careful,
mccluskey.
All right, what happens
now, sergeant?
I mean, what happens next?
Beyond the village
is where benteen engages.
Well, i mean, uh,
what about custer?
He loses a right arm.
And as of the moment reno
got cut off back there,
custer's column was doomed.
Man, this is wild.
I mean, this is really
wild... it's, uh...
it's like
chasing history.
It's like chasing history
and trying to change it.
Yeah.
Connors?
Langsford?
If it's a mirage
it sure went the route.
Kid,
you all right?
What's
the matter?
I just seen the granddaddy
of all mirages.
This one's sticking
out of my back.
Bluebird 9, bluebird 9.
This is c.p.
Come in, bluebird 9.
Captain.
You'd better tell me
they're just
a few hundred yards behind you.
I can't tell you that, sir.
Then you'd better be
telling me something else...
like the whereabouts
of an m-4 tank.
We found the tank, sir.
And this was on it.
"Crossing rosebud creek.
"Trying to reach
7th cavalry.
Have to."
I don't get it.
I swear
i don't get it.
What's he mean by the
7th cavalry, captain?
Who's the 7th cavalry?
It's a very hot outfit
headed up by a tiger
by the name of george custer.
Don't ask me any more.
I wouldn't be able
to tell you.
Come on, just
hang on now.
We're going
to make it.
Just hang on.
I'll make it
all right.
Just a few hundred more feet,
that's all.
Right over that ridge.
Come on.
All right, fellows...
let's do it!
There's no sign of the men
on either side, captain.
The tank's up there
on the ridge,
but there's no sign
of the men-
no sign at all.
Keep looking.
Yes, sir.
Put them
on report, sir?
Put 'em on report.
Captain!
"William connors...
"michael mccluskey...
richard langsford."
Kind of
a coincidence, sir?
Quite a coincidence.
Too bad they couldn't
have brought the tank up.
It would have helped.
Beg pardon, sir?
Nothing, lieutenant.
I didn't say anything.
Sergeant william connors,
trooper michael mccluskey,
and trooper richard langsford
who on a hot afternoon in june
made a charge over a hill
and never returned.
Look for this one
under "p" for phantom
in a historical ledger
located in a reading room
known as... the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
No one likes to age,
but it's a natural process
like death and taxes
and the weather.
But next time ontwilight zone,
we tell the story
about what happens
when a certain man doesn't age.
As a matter of fact,
he grows younger.
Patrick o'neal stars in
"a short drink
from a certain fountain."
Now if this one doesn't
pull you up by the shoulders,
i don't think anything will.
I hope we see you next time.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org