Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Reveille,
old tiger.
Come on, get up
now, come on.
All right, all right.
Well, i knew you
were swacked, but really.
Oh, boy.
I didn't have
thatmuch to drink.
Oh, hoo-hoo.
Hey, bob, where are we?
I had hoped we were
in the bedroom
of an apartment
on west 12th street
in new york city.
Well, we're not.
Yeah, hmm.
Hmm, i don't get it.
All right.
We went to sleep
at home...
didn't we?
Well, of course
we did.
Well.
Remember, we
left the party
up in
bedford village.
And you drove.
I had to, remember?
You were, uh...
sleepy.
Let's say
unable to drive.
Even had the top down.
I thoughtthat
would revive you.
And then somewhere
above riverdale...
well, somewhere
above riverdale-
what?
Wait a minute.
Something...
came down
on the car from overhead.
A shadow.
And then...
that's all i remember.
You probably
plowed us into another car.
I did not
plow us into another car.
All right, all right.
Let's just say,
another car plowed into us?
We were probably knocked out.
No.
You were already
knocked out.
All right, all right,
just, ugh, oh, honey.
Look, it's prob...
it's no big deal.
Somebody brought us here,
put us to bed,
there's probably
bacon sizzling
and scrambled eggs
waiting downstairs right now.
In fact, i think
i can smell it now.
Good morning.
No scrambled eggs.
Well, they must
have gone out.
Probably expected us
to sleep for a while.
Well, they must be
pretty casual types
to just go off and leave
us sleeping up there.
I'm going to find
out where we are.
Oh, uh, information- 411?
I don't know.
Just dial "o."
Bob!
Bob, what do
you mean, "bob"?
The thing wasn't wired in.
You pulled it
too hard.
It still has
to be wired in.
Well, just put
it back, please.
Got a pencil?
No.
There must be one
around here somewhere.
Mmm, she's not
a very good housekeeper.
All the drawers stick.
Bob, would you
help me please?
This is stage bread,
a... it's a prop.
Just empty cartons.
Well, it's a good thing
i don't believe in ghosts.
Well, neither
do i, but...
let's, uh, let's get
out of here anyway.
Bob and millie frasier.
Average young new yorkers
who attended a party
in the country last night
and, on the way home,
took a detour.
Most of us
on waking in the morning
know exactly where we are.
The rooster or alarm clock
brings us out of sleep
into the familiar sights,
sounds, aromas of home
and the comfort
of a routine day ahead.
Not so with our young friends.
This will be a day like
none they've ever spent.
And they'll spend it
in the twilight zone.
Must have gone.
Well, what
do we do now?
Let's try one
of the neighbors.
Boy, i wish i could
remember how we got here.
Reminds me of the
coney island spook house.
Does it strike you
that, um, it's just
as spooky out here?
There's not even
a bird singing.
Maybe they're just
being considerate
of your hangover, darling.
Stop needling me.
I'm not needling.
But if you'd been
sober enough to drive
maybe we'd be home now
instead of wherever
this is!
Oh, hicksville.
Boy, i don't see
how they stand it
in this small burg.
Hmm, you mean
all these people
are just standing around
staring at us, huh?
Why, where, do
you see any?
No, not a soul.
That's the way
it is in these small towns.
They peek from behind curtains.
Give me the big
city any day!
At least there you know when
you're being stared at.
Oh, look,
there's one citizen
that makes no pretense
about staring.
Isn't he cute?
All right, look,
come on, honey.
No, no, shh, i
think he's tame.
Oh, come look.
Yeah, yeah, ah,
he's a real doll.
Hey, nice baby.
Hey, sweetheart.
I touched him
and he fell over dead.
Yeah?
This thing's been
dead for years.
Stuffed.
What would anybody want
with a stuffed squirrel?
Oh, mill, don't ask
me to figure out
why anybody does anything
in this hick town.
Shh, they'll hear you.
Where're you going?
First, i'd like to
find out where we are.
Second, i'd like
to use their phone.
Third, i'd like to beg, buy,
borrow or steal an aspirin.
I just want to go home.
I want to go home!
Is there anybody here?!
Can anybody hear us?!
Please, won't somebody
help us?!
Please, somebody!
God, it's
that kid again.
Well, at least the
town's not deserted.
Yeah, maybe they're
all in one place-
a, a town meeting,
or something like that.
Sure, on a sunday morning.
Yeah, especially
on sunday.
That's where
they must be!
They're in church!
Ah!
Wait, we just
can't walk in.
Watch me.
What'll you tell them?
I'll tell them i'm tired
of their creepy town
and i'll pay anybody
anything he asks
to get us on
a train or bus
that'll get us back
to civilization.
Maybe they're praying.
Maybe we'd better wait.
Here's the church,
there's the steeple,
open the door...
nobody.
What now?
Ah.
This'll bring them.
Look outside.
See if anybody's coming.
Where'd everybody go?
There isn't anybody.
Just us.
Oh, come on.
There isn't a person
or a thing alive
in this town.
And yet...
what?
We're being watched.
No.
Now you're
getting delusions.
Was that a delusion?
I'm going to find that kid.
Hey, kid.
Come on out.
We want to talk to you.
Where are you?
Nothing in this
town is real.
The house we slept in,
this child we can't find,
that squirrel,
stuffed with sawdust.
Show me one thing
that's real.
That tree is real.
Ah...
tree, i love you.
Get me out of here.
Honey, look, wait!
There's bound to
be an explanation.
What, what?
All right, just
calm down, darling.
Here.
Hey, maybe there's going
to be a wedding here today.
Sure, sure, they
fixed up the lawn
to make it look pretty.
I mean, you
know how these...
yeah, okay.
Bob...
look, the grass, the ground.
Wha... look.
Why...
why, this... this isn't grass.
It's paper-mache.
Where are we, bob?
Where are we?
Hey!
Hey, anybody here?!
Somebody?!
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Boy, am i glad to see you!
We've been wandering
around here all morning.
You're the first person...
bob.
I don't know what it is...
a trick, a joke!
Is there somebody watching us?
Are you watching us there,
behind those curtains?
Is this a test?
Are you trying to find out
how much of this we can take
before we turn
into blathering idiots?
Is this some kind of a joke?
Bob, please don't try
to find out anything more.
Let's just
keep going, hmm?
Honey, look at that.
Get in.
You think it's all right?
Come on, baby,
come on, let's go.
Bob, stop, you're going
to flood the motor
stomping on it that way.
What, yeah, you
want to drive?
You're the one
who drove us
into this nuthouse
in the first place.
There's no motor.
How... the...
there's no engine in this thing.
Hey, you hear what i said?
I mean, uh, isn't that a...
no motor.
Huh...
what's the matter?
Well, what have
i done now?
Honey?
I did not drive us
into this place.
I'm sorry i said that.
It's all my fault
for being too
tight to drive.
Do you remember
any more?
Hmm?
Anything that
happened...
how we got here?
Only what i've already
told you, bob.
I was driving along
somewhere above riverdale.
You were asleep
in the back seat.
And then something...
a shadow, or something,
enveloped the car, and...
and that's all i remember.
I guess i fainted.
Crashed?
I crashed- that would explain
everything, wouldn't it?
No, not to me.
Yeah.
I crashed.
Maybe we're dead, bob.
Maybe this place is hell.
Did you...
did you ever hear
of a railroad in hell?
No.
But the train probably
doesn't stop here.
Well, we'll take
the next one.
Come on.
Let's find out where
the station is.
Wait, my shoes!
Wait, don't... wait for me!
Wait for us!
Whoo, don't go!
Hello, you
beautiful train.
Oh, did you ever see
such a beautiful train?
Ho, ho, i never saw
a more beautiful train
in my life.
What about tickets?
We'll get them
from the conductor.
We've got the whole
car to ourselves.
Oh.
Oh, what a nutty little town.
And how.
Boy, i still wonder
how we got there.
Come on, honey.
Admit it, you did have
a few drinks at the party, now.
Didn't you?
One or two.
Mm-hmm.
Well, somewhere along the line,
your drinks caught up with you.
And you got lost,
and we ended up here
in centerville.
I suppose that's the kind
of screwball thing
that i would do.
How do you put up with me?
I don't know, i just have
a weakness for screwballs.
You certainly have
a good one.
Well, well...
it wasn't all that bad
back there now, was it?
Not a bit, no.
In fact, i only jump a foot
when somebody says "boo."
Boo.
Oh!
What?
Wait'll i get
back to the office.
I can see old mr. Peabody now.
"Frasier, we're a team here."
Yeah.
"When one member
of that team lets us down
the whole
organization suffers."
Oh, no. No!
Now, well, uh... maybe it's not
the same centerville.
It's the same one.
I saw on the street-
nothing moving
nothing real.
How did we get back there?
We've gone in a circle.
Come on.
No, i'm not going back.
Not back.
We're going to get
on that main road
and keep right on walking.
Come on!
Wait!
Let's run, huh?
Could you?
I could gallop
if it would get us out
of here any faster.
No, we better
save our energy.
Might be a long
road ahead.
We still have a few
hours of daylight.
The sun will be up.
Bob!
Be careful with
your pets, dear.
Daddy brought them
all the way from earth.
Oh, can't i play
with them, mommy?
After lunch, dear.
Right now,
put them back.
Oh...
go on.
The moral of what you've
just seen is clear.
If you drink, don't drive.
And if your wife
has had a couple,
she shouldn't drive, either.
You might both just wake up
with a whale of a headache
in a deserted village
in the twilight zone.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org