Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Hey! Anybody home?
Hey!
Man, don't ever sneak
up on a man like that.
I'll tell you
one thing, daddy.
You sure got
a swinging shop here.
You got everything
right here
to cut a record
but jenny lind.
I'm floyd burney.
Floyd burney,
you know.
What have you got
for me?
Come on, dad, come on.
They told me
back at the highway
you're the music man
for this piece of nowhere.
I know this is the place.
Let's get with it.
Look, dad,
don't hold out on me.
You got a good folk song,
i'll pay you top dollar,
but it's got
to be authentic.
I got enough jokers
back home writing phonies.
No. No song.
No song...
they got to you already.
Who was it,
that harlan trio?
No, the pole river
boys, right?
Dad, i'm telling you,
they're going
to steal you blind.
Now, anything you got
is only p.d. -
you know,
public domain.
What i'm trying
to tell you is, dad,
you ain't got
no rights, catch?
Now, me,
that's different, dad.
See, me... i pay cash
on the line.
Now.
No.
Nobody comes here.
I ain't got nothing
they would want.
Tell you what.
Suppose...
just suppose now
i was to buy one
of your, uh...
one of your little
treasures here.
No.
Yeah, sure,
and then we,
you know, we talk
a little bit,
get to know one another,
and first thing you know,
you loosen up,
right, dad?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, this must be the place.
What did you hear?
Mm-hmm. Same thing
as you did, dad.
All right, now,
how much, how much?
Come on, you're
missing the beat.
Now, how much?
All right,
whatever it is,
take it
out of there, huh?
Mr. Floyd burney,
a gentleman songster
in search of song,
is about to answer
the age-old question
of whether a man can be
in two places at the same time.
As far as his folk song
is concerned,
we can assure mr. Burney
he'll find everything
he's looking for,
although the lyrics may not be
all to his liking,
but that's sometimes the case
when the words and music are
recorded in the twilight zone.
What's your name, honey?
Mary...
mary rachel.
Oh, yeah.
That's a lovely name.
Lovely name, lovely song.
How's it go again?
That song is secret.
It belongs to somebody.
It can't belong to anybody.
Nobody can buy it.
It's public domain.
Who got to you?
They made me promise
not to sing it anymore.
Oh, they did, huh?
Uh, who was that made you
promise not to sing it again?
The rayford brothers.
Rayfords.
Rayford...
yeah, yeah, i know them.
Sure, they work
out of chattanooga.
The older guy's the short one,
plays vibes...
no, no... no, no.
That was the raytones.
Rayford...
the rayfords?
I must go.
Wait a minute.
Come right
over there.
That's good.
Listen, can you let
me hear a little bit
of it, maybe
just one chorus?
Just sit down here.
That's good.
Know how to play
one of these?
Well, let's
just try, huh?
Let me get that
out of your way.
That's good,
fingers, good.
Now, mary rachel,
i want you to
play this to me
and sing it for me
just as if you
and i were
the only two people
in the world, okay?
? he said, "come wander
with me, love?
? "come wander with me?
? "away from this sad world?
? come wander with me."?
? he came
from the sunset?
? he came from the sea?
? he came
from my sorrow?
? and can love only me.?
I've got to go now.
They'll be looking
for me.
Wait a minute.
Please, i must go.
When will i see you again?
I mean, tonight?
You can't ever see me again.
I'm bespoke.
Bespoke?
What is that supposed
to mean, bespoke?
You're bespoke,
i'm floyd burney- so what?
Let me make it plain
to you, honey,
so you'll understand.
Now, i need that song.
I don't know what act
those rayford brothers got,
but that song was meant for me,
and i need it.
Do you understand?
What do you
want for it?
It belongs to somebody else.
Then i'll buy it.
What do you want... 50 bucks?
A hundred?
Well, what do you want,
a percentage?
It can't be bought,
not that way.
Honey, anything can be bought.
It's a buyer's market
with a price tag on everything.
All you got to know
is just how to find the tag.
Mary rachel,
i won't hurt your song.
All i'll do is
transpose it.
Here, sit
down, listen.
I'll just change
the key a little,
that's all.
? come wander
with me, love?
? come wander with me?
? away from this sad world?
? come wander
with me.?
Would you really take me away?
Oh... far from this sad world,
mary rachel.
And you'd love only me?
Only you, mary
rachel, only you.
? oh, where is the wanderer?
? who wandered this way?
? he's past all his wandering?
? and will never go away.?
? come wander with me, love?
? come wander with me?
? away from this sad world?
? he sang of a sweet love?
? of dreams that would be?
? but i was sworn to another?
? and could never be free.?
Yeah. Yeah, i'm
going to really run
with this one.
Do you still love me?
Sure, sure
i do, honey,
but, uh, we're
wasting time.
When will
you take me away?
Just as soon
as we finish
listening to
the playback.
Now, you tell
me the story
any way you want.
It's the story
of my love.
I love you.
I've always loved you.
Yeah, well, i tell
you what, honey.
Don't worry about it.
I'll think of something.
I bet i could
run this thing
right to the top
as a straight vocal.
? the rayfords were brothers?
? four men tall and bold?
? and for one i was chosen?
? with my love still untold?
? they heard of the wanderer?
? they heard he loved me?
? they heard...?
You know, that's
a great bit.
That really is.
The thing the rayfords
got going for them there.
Sure, put your own
name in a song.
Every play, you
get a free plug.
Uh, who's that?
Billy rayford.
Yeah? How's he
know to come here?
He always comes here.
Honey, don't you
have to go home
and pick up
a few things?
We got a long
way to go.
But you said
you'd buy me things-
bells and bonnets
and bright beads.
Yeah, sure, honey.
I tell you what.
You wait here,
and i'll go talk
to this cat.
No, not this time.
What do you mean,
not this time?
Honey, relax.
You're with me,
floyd burney.
So, you're one
of the rayford brothers, huh?
I know you.
You're the singing man,
ain't you?
Yeah! Yeah, that's me,
floyd burney.
Yeah, i sing a little.
Hear you're the one
who's after mary rachel.
Mary rachel?
Don't lie.
I seen you,
and folks heard
your sugar talking
about taking her to norfolk.
Norfolk?
What do i want to take anybody
to norfolk for?
I'm taking you to my brothers.
They know how to deal
with your kind.
Now, listen, dad,
i want to tell you something.
Now, i got agents,
and i got business managers,
and i got publicity people,
and they know where i am
every minute.
Billy?
? you killed billy rayford?
? bespoke unto me?
? struck him down in his anger?
? 'neath an old willow tree?
? by the lake
where our love dwelled?
? 'neath an old willow tree?
? you killed billy rayford?
? 'neath an old willow tree.?
All right, how
did you know,
and how did that verse
get on the tape?
It's always happened
that way.
"Always"? What is
this, some con game?
What are you
talking about?
How many other guys
you hook into this?
No one else. Only you.
It's always been you.
Man, we got to split!
If you run, they'll catch you.
You know that.
What doyouwant me to do,
lay down and play dead?
Maybe if you didn't run
this time...
if i hid you,
maybe it could be different.
Hide me? Where?
I'd find someplace.
We could always be together.
Yeah, stay out here, huh?
Uh-uh, ain't no way,
baby, forget it.
Not for old floyd burney.
I come too far too fast
to get buried out here
in sticksville.
We're gonna
split- come on.
Come on, which way?
If you run,
they'll catch you.
Don't you understand?
We got to get out of
here before that kid's
brothers find him.
It's too late.
They've already found him.
? they sought out
their brother?
? and found him alone?
? they wept by the lakeside?
? for a boy
hardly grown.?
No... no!
? they wept by the lakeside?
? and vowed he must die?
? the wandering
stranger...?
Stop it! Stop it!
You hear me?!
I don't want to hear any more!
But it's our song.
It belongs to us,
and we belong to it.
Then take it back.
I don't want it.
Take it back!
I can't. It's been used.
They're coming.
Come on.
Come on, get up.
Don't run.
Stay with me
this time.
This time, stay with me.
Don't run, don't run.
I'll always love you.
Help me.
You got to help
me, old man.
You got to hide me!
I'll pay you.
I'll pay you
anything.
It's too late.
I'm floyd burney,
the rock-a-billy boy!
Don't you understand?
They don't want me.
They want
somebody else.
I don't even sing
that kind of song.
I'm with the big beat.
Wait, listen,
i'll show you.
This is my stuff-
here, listen.
? my baby's like
a honey tree?
? sweet as can be?
? now, she don't
go with other cats?
? she only digs me.?
Where you going?
Where you going, old man?
Where are you going,
old man?
In retrospect, it may be said
of mr. Floyd burney
that he achieved
that final dream
eternal top-name billing-
not on the fleeting billboards
of the entertainment world,
but forever recorded
among the folk songs
of the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
We go wild next time
with some science fiction
ingredients
that should do a sizable job
of shocking.
Ms. Hazel court
and mr. Mark richman
lend their talents
to a piece called "the fear."
If you've ever wondered
what nature of beast
might come out of the sky
in an interplanetary invasion,
watchthe twilight zone
next time.
You'll get your answer
in most visual terms.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org