Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
? my grandfather's clock
was too large for the shelf?
? so it stood 90 years
on the floor?
? it was taller by half
than the old man himself?
? though it weighed
not a pennyweight more?
Such a long face.
? my grandfather said?
Honey.
? that of those he could hire?
? not a servant
so faithful he'd found?
? for it wasted no time...?
What's wrong?
I have to go up to talk to him.
I don't know what to say to him.
He's so happy, singing.
Honey, i know
how much you love him,
and i love you,
but we have
to face facts.
I know.
You're good for me.
Someone's got to take care of
the homely women of the world.
Hmm, thanks loads.
? 90 years without slumbering?
? ticktock, ticktock?
? with life's seconds
numbering?
? ticktock, ticktock...?
Good, that, uh,
that...
grandpa?
Come on down.
Oh, marnie.
Don't waste your
eyesight, grandpa.
Well, you know,
once a clockmaker...
and it's been
a few minutes off lately.
Grandpa, are you all right?
Me?
Why, never better.
Why, marn?
Well, it's just that you
didn't come down for dinner.
In fact, you haven't
been out of your room
all day.
Well, my friend's
been acting up today.
I can't seem to get it regulated
just right, you know.
Grandpa,
we know how you love the clock.
I...
but-but you see,
it's ticking along
nicely now.
We shouldn't have any trouble
for a long while.
Of course, with a clock
as old as that,
well, you-you're bound
to run into problems, you know.
Just like old people.
Oh, oh, oh.
Now you ignore that.
Just ignore the clock
and ignore me.
The main thing is really
you and the baby, you see.
That's more important
than...
will you get some rest?
Take care of yourself.
Oh, you know me.
L-i never sleep.
At least eat.
Well, maybe later.
Promise?
Promise.
Okay.
Oh, it's... it's running slow.
I didn't wind it properly.
They're making me so nervous.
I'm becoming careless.
I mustn't... i mustn't let them
make me nervous.
Please, please, don't stop.
I'll never forget
to wind you again.
I promise.
Each man measures his time-
some with hope, some with joy,
some with fear.
But sam forstmann
measures his allotted time
by a grandfather's clock,
a unique mechanism
whose pendulum swings
between life and death,
a very special clock
that keeps
a special kind of time...
in the twilight zone.
Where is he this morning?
Still sleeping,
i guess.
I'm not surprised.
He must have been
fiddling around with that clock
till 4:00
in the morning.
Did you hear him?
Sit down.
Will you please
sit down, honey?
Is that all
you're having?
I'm not hungry.
What about the baby?
I'm sure you don't have
to worry, doug.
Honey, now, let's not
start fighting again.
But you have
to face the fact
your grandfather's
just not a well man.
He's always been so alert,
so easy to be with.
Maybe it's just
a temporary thing.
Maybe it's a little something
we don't know anything about.
Why don't we let
mel avery talk to him,
just to make sure.
You think i'm crazy,
don't you?
Mel avery
is a psychiatrist.
He's a head shrinker.
You don't have
to tell me, i know.
Grandpa, mel's been
a friend of ours for years.
He and doug
went to college together.
You've met him.
I've met lots of people.
But i don't let them
tinker with my head.
Sam, no one's going
to tinker with your head.
All we're suggesting
is that you see mel
and talk to him.
Well, why do i need
to see a psychiatrist?
Well, your preoccupation
with the clock, for instance.
I'm fond of my clock
and that makes me crazy.
My, what a strange world
we live in.
You have to admit you spend
a lot of time with it.
Sometimes
half the night.
Aha! Just because
i have insomnia
and working on the clock
relaxes me,
that makes me a candidate
for the loony bin.
I've had insomnia
all my life.
So did my father.
He died at 90.
90 years without slumbering-
just like the song says.
Grandpa, doug only has
your best interest at heart.
Yeah, my best interests.
All right, son.
I'll see your friend
the psychiatrist tomorrow.
You may be surprised
when you find out
who the crazy one really is.
That clock was completed
exactly 76 years ago.
And it was presented to
me the day of my birth.
You see, doctor,
my father was very much
in love with my mother.
And in those days,
it was very
fashionable
for husbands
and wives
to be in love
with each other.
And it's no longer
fashionable, huh?
If it were, the woods wouldn't
be full of psychiatrists.
So you and the clock
were "born" on the same day
so to speak.
Oh, now, you're trying
to get me to say
that i think that the clock
is a real, living person.
Well, i don't.
It's a mechanism.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Then why be so extraordinarily
concerned with it?
Well, that clock's worth
hundreds of dollars.
It also is a
family heirloom.
Wouldn't you want to keep
a thing like that
in perfect condition?
Well, yes, but, uh...
you're not sure, huh?
Yes, i'm sure.
But we're not talking
about my clock,
we're talking
about your clock.
Oh, so you have a grandfather's
clock, too, doctor, huh?
As a matter of fact,
my wife bought one recently.
She collects antiques.
Tell me about it.
Well, it's
eight feet tall,
hand-carved,
built in germany
in 1874 by, uh... uh...
mr. Forstmann,
we were talking about you.
Oh, i thought we were
talking about your clock.
Yes, we were,
but we somehow
got off the track.
Track? Are we going
to talk about trains now?
Mr. Forstmann,
if you don't care to talk
about anything else...
oh, i could talk
about clocks
for hours, doctor.
But your time's
expensive.
Mine's free.
Oh, there, uh,
there is one thing, doctor.
Yes?
When my clock stops ticking,
i'll die.
You really believe that?
Oh, there's no doubt about it.
Does that make me crazy?
Well, crazy is a big word.
But it is
a rather strange idea.
If i had a clock like that
i'd get rid of it.
Oh, either the clock goes
or i go.
That's what you're telling me.
I didn't say that.
I think you did.
Good day, doctor.
Be careful, boy.
Be careful.
Don't worry, pops,
we got it.
Right there.
Well, what do you think?
I don't know, pops.
I'm not
an interior decorator.
Hey, wait.
What happened?
My clock!
Now, look, pops.
Take it easy.
Oh, i'm all right.
Boy...
you had
us worried
for a minute.
Not yet, i guess.
Not yet.
Doug, look.
Oh, no, honey...
he's trying to make
some compromise
with us, doug.
Well, children.
Hello, grandpa.
I thought
we'd give it a try there.
To see how it looks.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Sam, take a look
for yourself.
It sticks out
like a sore thumb.
Yeah, i guess it does.
Sam, we might
as well be honest.
The doctor says
the clock should go.
The doctor said that?
He says you're being
obsessed by the clock.
He says
it's bad for you.
Senile- that's what
he really said, isn't it?
No, grandpa.
And he wants you
to put me away.
No, grandpa,
he didn't say that.
Well, i'm not going
to any loony bin.
I'll tell you what
i am going to do.
I'm going to sell the clock.
I love this clock
and your nursery
is beautiful.
Marnie,
it's just perfect.
Thank you.
Do you want
some more coffee?
We can talk a little bit.
Love it.
You know, i refuse
to get pregnant
until i have my
nursery all planned.
George didn't think
that was logical.
I have to agree
with him, carol.
Mr. Forstmann,
where will you be living
after the baby comes?
Carol, he'll be
staying right here
in his own room.
Oh, well, of course,
i didn't mean anything.
I'll be
needing his help.
You going to keep
the clock here?
Just temporarily.
Carol, do you
know anyone
who might like to buy it?
Sure, me.
I wish i could afford it.
Do you mean that?
Do i?
You know what i think
about antiques
and that clock will
just make our hallway.
Oh, well, i think
that we can work out something.
I mean, you could pay me later.
It doesn't
matter.
Are you serious, mr. Forstmann?
Yes. It would be perfect.
You living next door to us
i could visit
the clock every day.
I mean, i could take care of it.
Keep it
in good condition.
And we'd appreciate it.
It's not one
of your eight-day clocks.
It's special.
You have to wind it
every other day.
Grandpa...
i don't think carol would
like you tinkering with it.
It'll be her clock.
But it would only take
a few minutes every other day.
Oh, i wouldn't mind, marnie,
and he could take
good care of it.
I'd appreciate
it, really.
It's up to you two, anyway.
I can't wait to see
what it looks like.
George doesn't think
i'm a bargain hunter.
Wait till he hears about this.
Good morning,
marnie.
grandpa.
You're up early
this morning.
Well, early to bed,
early to rise-
you know,
ben franklin?
Or was it
george washington?
I'm off
to wind the clock.
George and carol
are out of town.
Didn't you
know that?
Out of town?
Just for the weekend.
You'll hardly miss a visit
to your clock.
Don't you realize that the clock
winds down after 48 hours?
Grandpa, are you going
to start that again?
We've all been so happy
for the past two weeks.
All of us.
Yes, yes, we've been happy.
Two weeks of borrowed time.
I should be grateful.
It's running out.
It's dying.
Hold it right there.
Look, officer, i have
to wind the clock, you know,
it's running down.
It must be wound,
it must be.
Oh, sure, sure, mister.
Where do you live?
I live next door there.
But you don't understand-
i have to wind the clock.
Come on, come on.
You'll wake the
whole neighborhood.
Look, please, just let me
wind the clock,
and then i'll go home.
That's private property.
I can't let you
go in there.
You have to!
Now, look, mister,
i can't let you
go in there.
Don't you see?
Don't you see,
i'm running down.
And if that stops,
i'll die.
I'll really die.
Oh, i don't think so.
You mustn't do this,
you mustn't.
Just let me wind
the clock, please.
Can i get something
for you, grandpa?
I won't need anything.
Don't worry, marnie,
it's, it's better this way.
Better?
Good night, grandpa.
Good night, sweetheart.
It is...
it is better this way.
It has to come sometime.
And i want it
to come for me here.
Sam, old friend...
it's been a good life.
But now it's
time to go.
Well, don't let me detain you.
How the heck
did you get in my bedroom?
I don't believe
we've been introduced.
Your face is familiar.
I'm your spirit.
Your time has come, sam.
After all, you are 76.
Don't give me that
spirit of 76 stuff.
And who says it's my time to go?
Have you forgotten
what your father told you?
And your grandfather?
About what?
Didn't they always tell you
that when the clock winds down
you'll die?
Yes, and you know something?
I used to believe that stuff.
You should have.
They told you often enough.
But that's silly.
Don't you
know that?
I do.
I've been to a psychiatrist.
So what?
So he told me he didn't think
i needed the clock.
And he didn't think i was crazy.
And you know what?
He was right and we're wrong.
You know, personally,
i never trust the psychiatrists.
Well, you're
from another generation.
See, i live in the present.
Live, i said.
Look at me.
You're just a figment
of my imagination.
Why, i can see
right through you.
I've got
a great-grandchild coming.
And i plan to stay around
a while to play with him
to, uh,
watch him grow,
take him
to school.
Maybe even to college.
I repeat,
i don't believe in you,
therefore you don't exist,
right?
Right.
Marnie.
What are you doing up
this time of the night?
I was worried
about you, grandpa.
The thing
to worry about
is that great-grandchild
of mine.
Now, you let me up,
let me out of this bed.
My goodness,
you shouldn't worry
about me.
Come on downstairs
and i'll get you
a good cup
of hot chocolate.
Be careful of the steps.
Must be careful.
It's my great-grandchild.
Look out.
Marnie?
I think i cheated
your friend.
That old clock
hasn't been running right
for the last 40 years.
Why, it's taken everything
i ever learned in clockmaking
just to keep it going.
Really, grandpa?
Uh, as a matter of fact,
it stopped ticking
for the last time
just a few moments ago.
How do you
know that?
Don't ask me how i know
but i know.
And a strange thing
happened, marnie.
When that clock died,
i was born again.
Clocks are made by men,
god creates time.
No man can prolong
his allotted hours,
he can only live them
to the fullest-
in this world
or in the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next time we enlist the aid
of a very talented scribe,
earl hamner, jr.
He's written a story called
"ring-a-ding girl"
and in the milieu of fantasy,
this one is strictly
a blue ribbon entry.
It stars maggie mcnamara
and it involves a movie actress,
a publicity tour,
a strange flight, an airplane,
and some occult occurrences
designed to send shivers through
you like a fast subway train.
Next time out on
the twilight zone,
"ring-a-ding girl."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org