Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Here they come.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury,
have you reached
a verdict?
We have, your honor.
And what is the verdict?
Your honor, we find
the defendant, adam grant,
guilty of murder
in the first degree.
The defendant will rise.
The defendant will rise!
Adam.
Adam grant, you have been tried
by a jury of your peers,
and found guilty.
Do you have anything
you wish to say
before sentence
is passed?
Very well.
It is the sentence of this court
that for the brutal
and despicable crime
of murder
in the first degree
you shall be put to death
by means of electrocution.
No!
Not again!
I won't die again!
You can't make me die again!
Oh, god, please,
please, please...
tell them,
mr. District attorney,
that this isn't real.
Make 'em understand they're
only a dream i'm having!
You fools!
You kill me, you'll die!
You believe me,
make him believe me!
Tell the district attorney
he's prosecuted himself
and everybody in this building
and everybody in the world!
Tell him, mr. Carson,
before it's too late!
Tell him! Tell him!
Adam grant, a nondescript kind
of man found guilty of murder
and sentenced
to the electric chair.
Like every other criminal caught
in the wheels of justice,
he's scared right down
to the marrow of his bones.
But it isn't prison
that scares him-
the long silent
nights of waiting,
the slow walk to the little room
or even death itself.
It's something else
that holds adam grant
in the hot, sweaty
grip of fear.
Something worse
than any punishment
this world has to offer.
Something found only
in the twilight zone.
Coley!
Lay off of that thing, will ya?
I'm sorry, grant.
I didn't know
i was bothering anybody.
It's all right, coley.
It's my fault.
I...
i got you out of
a bad movie i saw once,
just like everything else
in this corny dream.
Grant!
Let me give you some advice.
Don't think about it.
You think about it, you'll
crack up like phillips there.
Listen to him.
Mother, i'm sorry.
Don't let them hurt me, mother.
Don't let them hurt me.
Phillips!
Shut your face!
A month ago,
he was a human being.
Now what is he?
An animal, a thing.
Why?
Because he couldn't
stop thinking about it.
I know it.
It's...
it's just different with me.
You mean
you want to die?
No.
Well, it ain't different
with you.
So don't
kid yourself.
Sometimes
i wonder, too,
what it's going
to be like.
I'll tell you what it's like.
You walk out of your cell,
pass two gray doors,
78 steps to the final door.
It's painted green.
There's a guard
that opens the door for you,
and you go into a room.
It's tan.
It's all tan.
There's nothing in it
except one chair.
It's like a chair
you used to sit in
when you were a kid.
It's hard and solid.
Ah, cut it out, cut it out.
They strap your arms and legs.
Then they attach the electrodes.
It's funny.
They always feel cold
to the touch at first.
Aw, grant,
you talk
like you been
through it already.
Then they
drop the mask.
It's musty.
It smells like
an old sofa.
And then you wait...
every muscle tense,
straining.
Any second,
any second...
then you can almost hear it.
They pull the switch.
Madame.
I am a poor
lost traveler
seeking food
and lodging for the night.
You're loaded.
Hank, i've just been
insulted by your wife.
She's says i'm loaded.
Well, aren't you?
That has nothing
to do with it.
Hey, hey,
take it easy.
That's
my best gin.
Dear friends,
when i die
i don't want to see
any full bottles around.
That's
not funny.
It wasn't meant to be.
It was meant
to be a comment
on the short, unhappy
life of paul carson.
Come...
drink and be merry,
for tomorrow...
oh, shut up, paul.
Sorry.
Well, only a few more hours.
I knew it.
I knew it the minute
you walked in.
We're not nervous enough.
Oh, no, we have to listen
to the great city editor
with his news behind the news.
If i'm not
welcome here,
then i shall
go elsewhere
and breathe
my last...
oh, never mind.
I've had enough
of this wake anyway.
Good night, dear.
What about dinner?
Lost my appetite.
Oh, the steak
can come out
in five
minutes.
Hank.
Now, don't start it.
I've got to start it.
I'm not upset
or disturbed
or nervous anymore.
I'm scared.
That's ridiculous.
I know it is,
i know it is,
but that
doesn't help.
Do you mean to say
you believe
that crazy story?
God, help me,
hank, but i do.
At least, i believe
it's possible.
Well, why not?
Can we prove
he's wrong?
Maybe not,
but that's a poor reason
for believing
in anything.
I can't prove
that the world
isn't going to end.
But it isn't.
This guy killed
a man in cold blood,
and he's going
to pay for it.
Those are the facts.
Anything else is
speculation, fantasy.
Are you sure?
Yes, i'm sure.
Then what are you
so steamed up about?
I...
i'll tell you why.
Because a little
part of you believes, too.
Just a little, tiny part
of henry ritchie says
"maybe this grant
is right.
Maybe this is
all a dream."
The thought has
occurred to you, hasn't it?
Hank, haven't you
ever stopped
and said,
"this couldn't be real.
"I couldn't be
the district attorney.
"I couldn't have
a lovely wife like carol
"and a lovely home,
money in the bank,
not in any real world."
Haven't you, hank?
Well, of course.
Everyone has.
If you're a success,
you're bound to
think it's a dream.
If not, you think
it's a nightmare.
This only proves
that grant is human.
He can't believe
what's happening to him
so he tries to
convince himself
that it isn't,
not really.
Yeah, that's what
i thought too at first.
But hank, i been talking
to this kid a lot lately,
and he makes sense.
Go down and see
for yourself.
Don't take my
word for it.
It wouldn't do
any good.
You only listened
to him once.
That was enough.
Hank, for my
sake, please,
go and see him.
Let him tell you.
Please, hank.
It's pointless but...
thanks.
Jiggs.
Jiggs!
Yeah?
What time
is it?
9:05.
Why, you got a date somewhere?
No, i'm just expecting someone.
The governor,
right?
With a nice fat pardon
in his fist.
No, it's the district attorney.
He usually comes around
about 9:00.
Oh, you don't say?
The d.a. Himself, huh?
Yeah, yeah, the d.a. Himself.
You got a great
sense of humor, pal.
Wait a minute.
There's something else
that doesn't work-
the watch.
Yeah, how is that?
Prisoners about
to be executed
aren't allowed
to wear watches
because of the glass.
You see, he's right
on time, huh, jiggs?
Ten minutes, mr. Ritchie.
All right.
You can leave us alone.
Hello, grant.
Hello, mr. Ritchie.
You don't seem
surprised to see me.
I'm not-
you always come.
I mean, the district
attorney always comes.
It isn't always you.
Grant.
Yes?
I take it you're
sticking to
this dream
story of yours.
That's right.
It can't possibly
do you any good now.
You realize...
i should,
after all this time
every night,
i explain.
Every night,
it's the same.
All right,
explain again.
Well, it's very simple.
When i die, you die,
and everybody in this world dies
because this world
does not exist.
It's a dream of mine.
It's a nightmare.
Can't you
understand that?
No, grant,
i can't understand that.
Not because it's a new idea.
I can't understand it
or accept it
because it doesn't make
any kind of logical sense.
But it does.
It's the only thing
that does make logical sense.
Take you, for instance.
You think
you'd be visiting a man
that was just about
to be executed in real life?
Of course not.
They wouldn't
allow you in here.
Or you take me.
You don't know
any more about me
than you did when this
thing started- i'm a stranger.
There are a hundred
vagrants in every town
without names,
without histories.
Stop that!
We know
you're
mentally sound.
And i don't think
you're deliberately lying to me.
I'm going
to destroy
that story of
yours, grant, now
once and for all.
You say that all
this is a dream,
and that when you're
electrocuted you wake up,
and when you wake up,
we all disappear, right?
That's right.
What about our parents
and our parents' parents
and everybody who never
even heard of you?
What about them,
mr. Ritchie?
A dream builds
its own world, mr. Ritchie.
It's complete.
With a past, and, as long as
you stay asleep, a future.
What about us then
when we sleep and dream?
Or is that when
you're up and around?
You only sleep and dream
because i dream you that way.
All right, now answer me this.
You're scared now- why?
Why are you scared?
You've got to wake up sometime
even if you're electrocuted.
So why don't you just
sit back and enjoy it?
Enjoy it.
Let me tell
you something.
Mr. Ritchie,
how soundly do you sleep?
What's that got...?
You dream,
don't you?
Certainly, sometimes.
Haven't you ever been hurt
in one of those dreams?
Fallen out of a window
or been drowned or tortured?
You have!
Don't you remember
how real it had seemed?
Remember how you
woke up screaming?
Well, let me ask you something,
mr. Ritchie.
How do you like to wake up
screaming every night?
That's what i do.
Because i dream the same dream
night after night after night!
It's this one!
It changes a little bit.
The people get twisted around,
but it's the same dream.
You've got to believe me!
I can't
go on dying!
I can't go
on dying!
I can't,
i can't...
i'm telling the
truth, mr. Ritchie!
Please, let me live and
i'll keep you alive.
I'll dream you every
night just like this.
Wait a minute!
I'll prove it to you.
You wife,
she has a steak cooking for you.
Go home, look
in the oven.
It'll be
something else.
Please!
Well?
What's wrong, hank?
That's a roast.
What about it?
Hank, what about it?
Grant.
Huh?
Did i wake you up?
No.
What's funny?
Nothing's funny.
Well, you was laughing.
I heard ya.
Hey, grant, listen,
i been thinking about
what you said,
about this all being a dream
and all.
Well, now, maybe it won't work,
but if you told that story
to the governor,
he might let you out
on a psycho.
He wouldn't believe me.
You don't believe me,
do you, jiggs?
Oh, that's got nothing
to do with it.
If you think it's true, see,
why, then you got a loose cog
somewhere,
and they don't burn guys
with loose cogs.
What if i proved it to you?
How?
Well, jiggs, don't you think
that all of this is just...
just a little bit too much
the way it should be?
I don't get you.
Well, i mean
it's so pat.
I got tried and sentenced
the same day.
It doesn't work like that.
But you see that's the way
that i saw it in my mind
and so that's the way it is.
Or you take this place here-
you and coley
and his harmonica,
or phillips
and his mother.
It's like a movie.
Real death houses
aren't like that.
But you see, i've never
been in a real death house
so that's...
that's my impression of it.
Man, you've really flipped.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, the brothers
grimm, as i live...
what are
you doing up?
I'm not up.
I'm down, just like you
and your funny friend here.
Have they...?
15 more minutes.
That's another thing.
Why does this always
happen around midnight?
Because that's
when it happens.
Yeah, but why?
You tell me why.
According to grant,
he doesn't know anything
about these matters
except what he
sees in the movies.
In the movies, it always
happens at midnight.
Because movies
are technically accurate.
That's strange, too,
come to think of it.
Then don't come
to think of it.
Hey, screws,
you're wasting your time.
You can't kill him.
You want to know why?
I'll tell you why.
Because you're nothing
but dreams. Dreams!
You hear that, screws?
Is there anything
you wish to say
in these few moments
remaining to you, my son?
No.
Then let us pray.
There's no need.
There's always a need
for prayer, my son.
Only in the real world,
father,
not in a nightmare.
You feel detached
from reality?
I not only feel it-
i am detached.
I wonder where i've seen you,
where your face came from.
It's familiar.
Almost every time
it just about
comes to me.
We've never met.
Oh, yes...
yes, we have.
Father beamon.
Of course,
father beamon
from over
at spring hill.
No wonder
i didn't recognize you.
You died
when i was ten years old.
Oh, everybody
came to your funeral.
My name is
beamon but...
yes, and then
a young priest came
and took your place...
that was carson.
You know,
i'm using him
for the editor.
Be still, my son.
But what about ritchie,
the district attorney?
He must have been
a schoolteacher of mine.
Maybe he was a friend of dad's.
Hey, grant,
they can't do this to you.
You're home in bed, asleep.
Remember?
Grant! Grant!
It's time to wake up, boy.
Wake up! Wake up!
You could at least get
a stay of execution.
I know you can do that.
What good
would it do?
We'd simply
have to go through
the whole thing
all over again.
Maybe not,
look, hank.
Forget all about
that dream stuff.
Whether that's true or
not, it doesn't matter.
What matters is
the kid believes it.
That means
he's got a case.
The psychiatrist...
the psychiatrist
made a mistake.
It wouldn't be the first
time. Get a week's stay.
We'll throw in another team. No.
Why not? Because
we might be wrong?
Well, maybe we are,
but maybe we're not,
and in my book, that's
reasonable doubt.
Hank, that kid is
sick in the head.
Are you going to send
a mental incompetent
to the chair?
I regret this, paul.
I'll regret this
as long as i live.
Hello. This is henry ritchie.
I want to speak
to the governor.
Right away.
Well, i don't care.
This is an emergency.
Wake him up.
Hurry.
Having trouble
putting this through. He's...
yes, this is henry ritchie.
Governor, i don't have time
to explain,
but i want you to grant
a stay of execution
in the case of adam grant.
He's calling now.
Here they come.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury,
have you reached a verdict?
We have, your honor.
And what
is the verdict?
Your honor, we find
the defendant, adam grant,
guilty of murder
in the first degree.
The defendant will rise.
Adam.
We know that a dream
can be real.
But who ever thought
that reality could be a dream?
We exist, of course,
but how, in what way?
As we believe,
as flesh and blood human beings,
or are we simply parts
of someone's feverish,
complicated nightmare?
Think about it,
and then ask yourself
do you live here,
in this country, in this world,
or do you live instead
in the twilight zone?
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, the very considerable
talents of mr. Shelley berman
are utilized to bring you
another in our weekly excursions
into the never-never land
of the wild, the woolly
and the wondrous.
He plays the part
of a little man
who yearns for the serenity
of a world without people,
and as it happens,
he gets his wish-
to walk an uninhabited earth
and face the consequences.
Our story is called
"the mind and the matter."
I hope we see you then.
Now this isn't just
a word from the sponsor,
it's simply
a very good suggestion.
It stands for real refreshment.
Before we meet again,
try oasis
for the softest taste of all.
Be sure and watchgunsmoke,
starring james arness,
saturday nights over most
of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org