Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Mr. Smith-
what's your present
course and speed?
Setting on course
2-6-0 degrees through.
Speed, 10 knots,
sir.
Come right
to new course 2-7-0
and navigate turns
for 15 knots.
Aye, aye, sir.
Come right to
new course 2-7-0.
Aye, sir.
Coming right to
new course, 2-7-0.
All engines
ahead standard
indicate 1-2-6,
turns for 15 knots.
Aye, sir.
All engines ahead
standard.
1-2-6 turns
for 15 knots.
Engine room answers.
All engines ahead
standard,
1-2-6 turns
for 15 knots, sir.
Very well.
Steady on new course 2-7-0, sir.
Damage report, sir,
on the motor
whale boat.
Let's hear it.
It's completely
filled with water.
It took a licking
in that storm.
It was a corker
of a swell, sir.
I'm aware of the
storm, mr. Marmer.
I'm also aware
of the swell,
and i'm aware that
that boat was not
properly secured
for heavy weather.
A 13-year-old sea scout
would've rigged in
and secured that
boat properly.
Yes, sir.
Tell the chief
boatswain's mate
i want to see him
in my cabin.
Aye, aye, sir.
On the double!
Chief boatswain's mate bell
reporting as ordered, sir.
At ease, chief.
That shouldn't be
too difficult for you,
should it?
Sir?
The state of
being at ease.
You're the champion
of the fleet,
when it comes
to being at ease, bell.
I don't understand, sir.
You're the chief
boatswain's mate.
You run the deck division,
handle the boat's rigging
in and out,
supervise the heavy equipment
and eight or ten other cardinal
duties you're responsible for,
not the least of which,
chief boatswain's mate bell,
is the proper securing
of the whale boat!
Now, last night,
we had a bad swell.
That boat should've
been rigged in.
Instead it was
left swung out,
and as a result,
she's 80% damaged
and filled up
like a pool.
Where were you?
Begging the captain's
pardon, i...
don't beg
my pardon!
Just tell me,
in a brief explanatory way,
why you couldn't handle
the initiatives
of a chief
boatswain's mate,
and why the efficiency
of this ship suffered.
We had nine
hours' warning
of that storm,
bell.
This ship should've
been 100% prepared.
Instead it wasn't,
and i want to know why!
I did the best i could, sir.
I...
i haven't been feeling
up to par.
Well, did you report
to sick bay?
No, sir, i didn't
report to, um...
to, uh, to sick bay, sir.
Now, look, chief,
i'm not in business
to pistol-whip my crew.
I want a tight ship,
that's true-
but i happen to care very much
if one of my sailors
has a problem
and can't function
because of it.
You've rated
4-0
all the way
down the line
for as long as you've
served on this ship.
Suddenly,
in the last three days,
you've stowed away
your seamanship in the trunk
and come up with some dumbhead
boners i wouldn't expect
from a
17-year-old boot.
Bell, what is the problem?
There is
a problem, then.
No, sir, no problem, sir.
I...
i'll watch it
in the future, sir.
All right.
We'll leave it that way, then.
If you want to bend my ear,
you know where my cabin is.
Aye, sir.
Chief?
Hey, chief,
you all right?
You okay, chief?
You look a little
woozy there.
Yeah.
Yeah, i'm okay.
Sir, contact
bearing 2-8-0.
1,100 yards.
Echo quality
is sharp.
Evaluate as
possible submarine
but not moving.
Plotting dead
in the water.
D.i.w.?
Ship to listen.
Sounds like...
sounds like
hammering or
something, sir.
Bridge, sonar.
Bridge on.
I have sonar contact
bearing 2-8-0 degrees
true range 1,100 yards.
Sounds like
a metal object.
Bearing clear.
What kind of
object, sonar?
We can't tell, sir.
From its appearance
on the scope,
it's some kind
of large object.
It could be a submarine.
Bridge, aye.
Sonar puts
a contact, captain.
2-8-0, 1,100 yards.
Evaluation,
a possible submarine.
Possible submarine?
Stay on course.
I want to check
the scope.
Incident 100 miles off
the coast of guadalcanal.
Time, the present.
The united states naval
destroyer on what has been
a most uneventful cruise.
In a moment, they're going
to send a man down 30 fathoms
and check on a noisemaker-
someone or something
tapping on metal.
You may or may not read
the results in a naval report
because captain beecham and
his crew have just set a course
that will lead this ship
and everyone on it
into the twilight zone.
How long have you been
in contact?
About three
minutes, sir.
It's a funny one.
Sure sounds like
tapping on metal.
That's what
i think, sir.
Bridge, change course to 0-3-0
and reduce speed to five knots.
Bridge, aye.
Try making contact
by underwater telephone.
I've already
tried.
No response,
sir.
It stopped now.
But sonar still
has a contact.
Stay on it.
I'll be
on the bridge.
Steady on course,
0-3-0.
All engines ahead,
one-third,
5-0 rpms for
five knots, sir.
Very well.
We're directly over the object.
All engines stop.
Aye, sir.
All engines stop, sir.
Very well.
Do you hear it, sir?
Hold it.
I want dead quiet.
Ain't that a kick
in the head.
What do you
suppose it is?
Ghosts, man, ghosts.
What do you think
it is, chief?
I never heard anything
like that before.
Stow it!
Let's keep it quiet
down there.
You okay, now, chief?
Yes.
I'm okay.
You blacked out
up on the deck, chief.
I'm all right.
Yeah, now, i think
you better lie flat
for a little while.
I'll be all right.
Yeah, i wouldn't
doubt it, chief, but...
right now you look like
a class-a shipwreck.
We still stopped?
Yeah, we're
still stopped.
We're all curious
about what's making
that noise.
What's the trouble,
chief, hmm?
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy, that's
a funny feeling.
What kind of feeling?
I, uh...
i can't describe it.
What do you suppose
that is down there?
Don't you worry about it,
whatever it is.
Just get some rest.
Mr. Smith?
Captain?
I want you to stay grafted
to me, lieutenant.
I may have to be
turning in a report
that'll stick me
on a garbage barge.
Or in the navy hospital.
I want 15 witnesses
at my hearing
and all on my side.
Could be a sub, sir,
and we could
be hearing it.
It's only about
30 fathoms.
Sure, it could be
a sub, mister.
That's probably what it is.
But what about this sub-
has it got two arms
and a fist?
Somebody's making
that noise down that.
Lieutenant, do we have
a diver onboard?
Yes, sir- mcclure,
first division.
Have him report up
here on the double.
We'll send him
down there
and have him knock
on the door.
And then what, sir?
We'll see who
invites him in!
Boatswain's
mate mcclure
reporting, sir.
You're the diver,
right?
Right, sir.
Here's the picture.
We've got something
below us, mcclure.
We don't know
what it is.
It's metal, the
size of a sub hull.
Get your equipment
and go down there.
Stay in touch with us
from the moment
you hit the water
till the moment
you reach it.
Is that understood?
Yes, sir.
Whatever the object is,
there's somebody inside,
or at least something
that's making a noise.
When you get down there,
listen to the sound
very closely.
We may be getting it
distorted up here.
Aye, aye, sir-
i understand.
Hop to it.
Aye, sir.
It's wild.
That it is,
lieutenant.
But if it isn't a sub, sir,
what is it?
Maybe it's a
spanish galleon
with a treasure chest
and a loose lid
that's off its hinges.
Or maybe it's...
maybe it's just
our imagination.
Diver going over
the starboard side.
Bridge.
This is the captain.
I hear you loud and clear.
Keep talking, mcclure.
It's a sub, sir.
No question about that.
Have you reached her, mcclure?
I'm standing alongside.
I don't hear anything, though.
Mcclure.
Her bow is buried about
15 feet into the bottom.
I can't read any identification.
It's covered up.
On the side of
the conning tower.
Can you read a number there?
No, sir, there's
been damage there.
The number's been obliterated.
Do you hear that, mcclure?
Yes, sir, i do.
She's coming from amidships.
I'm moving toward there now.
Yes, sir, that's where
it's coming from.
Tap on the hull and see
if you get a response.
Was that you, mcclure?
Yes, sir.
No response, sir.
I don't hear anything anymore.
There should be three hatches.
One on the bow,
one on the conning tower,
and one on the stern.
Is the ship upright?
She's upright, sir,
at about a 30-degree angle.
Climb up on her deck
and check the hatches.
See if you can open them.
The mar hatch is buried, sir.
I can't get through to that.
I'll check on the one
over the conning tower.
Mcclure, what's the condition?
The conning tower hatch
is all bent, sir.
I can't move the wheel.
This whole deck appears
to have been scraped.
Wait a minute.
Hatch on the stern
the same way, sir.
I can't turn her.
Whoever she is, sir,
she must've really caught it.
Say it again, mcclure.
She must've what?
Caught it, sir.
The whole deck is pockmarked
with shell damage-
machine gun damage, too.
Was that you, mcclure?
No, sir.
It's coming
from inside the hull.
Answer right away.
Answer right now.
This is wild.
There is
somebody inside.
Can you pinpoint
the sound, mcclure?
Can you tell precisely
where it's coming from?
I think...
i think it's...
wait a minute.
Yes, sir.
Directly amidships.
Just below the tower.
Call sonar.
Try to telephone again.
Sonar, bridge.
Try your underwater
telephone again.
Roger.
Unknown station,
this is lady. Over.
Bridge, sonar.
No response, sir,
on the phone.
No more contact, sir.
Stay as long as you can
and then come up
when you're ready.
Aye, aye, sir.
Get the com officer-
i want a message.
"Action to com seventh fleet.
"Info to cinc pac fleet.
Appraise him of situation."
Get on it.
Radio, bridge.
Radio, aye.
Captain wants a message.
Action to com seventh fleet.
Info cinc pac fleet.
Have located sunken sub.
Position, latitude
0-9-3-0-0-0 south.
Longitude 1-6-0-4-8-0-0 east.
Request confirm location of
all known sinkings this area.
Will remain this area
until further advised.
Precedence,
operational immediate.
Radio, aye.
Any ideas, captain?
Oh, an even dozen.
Only every one
of them nullifies
the one ahead of it.
If it's one of our subs,
we would have a report.
Even if it's
somebody else's,
why haven't they gone out
the torpedo tubes?
There's another
common denominator.
That sub was hit by shellfire.
Whatever action took place
must've happened
within a period of hours
or no one would
still be alive.
But there's been no action
or we'd have seen it
or heard it.
Now, put all that together
and it spells nothing.
Mcclure is on his
way back up, sir.
Have him report
to the sonar shack.
That's where i'll be.
Yes, sir.
How do you
feel now, chief?
You had
a pretty good sleep.
Um...
what's new from down below?
Nothing much.
Scuttlebutt is were going
to try and take her in tow.
Hey, doc.
Yeah, chief.
Um...
i was just wondering
about something.
Go ahead, chief.
This feeling
of mine, i...
what kind of
feeling, chief?
I can't...
i... i get
this feeling...
i can't stay
in one place.
I got to get up
and go out.
This crazy feeling
that i'm...
that you're what,
chief?
That somebody is
ordering me someplace,
is pulling me
someplace.
And if i didn't
stay put,
if i didn't fight it,
i'd go up on deck,
and i'd never
come back.
Huh?
Pretty... sound
pretty nuts?
Don't you worry about
what it sounds like.
Chief, i think
maybe you better
stay down here with
me a little while.
Come on, now.
Everything's going
to be all right.
Just take it easy
and get a little sleep.
There is somebody
inside her, sir.
I'll lay odds on that.
What about the sub itself?
Could you judge her length?
Oh, i'd guess her
to be 300 feet, sir,
with a 25-foot beam.
She sounds like one of ours.
She looks like one of ours.
There were ballast tanks
and flooding ports
on the underside.
She's moving, sir.
That was the other
thing, captain.
She wasn't stuck in tight.
Deep, yes, but not tight.
She seemed to be swaying
when i was down there.
Are you cold, mcclure?
I've been warmer, sir.
And you will
be again,
but now you'll
get colder.
Get some coffee,
and go back down.
Check her bow.
She may have
pulled herself loose,
and you can read the number.
Sonar, bridge.
Sonar, aye.
Radio report
from com seventh fleet
reports no sinkings of any kind.
Authorizes us to remain on scene
and operate at own discretion
for salvage and rescue.
Roger.
No sinkings?
All right.
Mcclure, if you can get me
a number off her hull,
we may be able
to sleep tonight.
Aye, sir.
If they're
in there and alive
and can't use
the torpedo tubes,
how do we get them out?
Bridge, this is mcclure.
Go ahead, mcclure.
This is
the captain.
She's pulled herself out, sir.
Here's your number, captain.
7-1-4.
7-1-4?
She's one of ours.
Come on up here, mcclure,
and get yourself
a broiled steak on me.
Get that book
with the hull numbers.
7-1-4.
7-1...
here it is,
7-1-4.
"Commissioned
december, 1941.
"Sunk in action
"first battle
of the solomons,
august 7, 1942."
August 7, 1942.
Well, that was 20 years ago.
Captain beecham,
who's down there?
Who's inside that sub?
Somebody who dies damn hard.
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
Who is it?
Uh, chief matthews, sir.
Come on in, doc.
Stand easy, chief.
Oh, thank you, captain.
What is it?
Captain, i'd like
to talk to you
about one of the men.
Sure, sit down.
Thank you, sir.
Go ahead.
What do you know
about chief bell?
I know his rating
and his service
record.
What else am i
supposed to know?
He's down in sick bay.
I know that-
what's the trouble?
It's an illusion
or a psychosis or whatever.
I don't know.
That's a little out
of my line, captain.
I do know, though, that he
needs help- psychiatric help.
I'm sorry to hear that, doc.
Funny.
Captain?
Funny about some men.
Bell, for instance...
21 years navy.
Served in everything
from a scow to a carrier
and all of a sudden he cracks up
like a dinghy in a storm.
I never figured
a man like bell
would crack up.
Would you, doc?
I can't say, captain.
But as for cracking up,
that's what he's doing.
He has a look about
him i can't describe
but it's not a look
you see very often.
Usually it's an hour
after a battle
when the eyes
face outward
but you know they're
really looking inside.
Well, that's what
he looks like-
like a man who's
just been picked up
off a raft
full of dead men.
That's what he
looks like, captain.
All right.
Keep him down there.
When we put back
to port,
i'll recommend
hospitalization
for him
and some examinations.
Thanks for
coming in, doc.
Aye, aye, captain.
Quiet, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, it's too quiet.
How long has it been now?
About three hours.
Is he going to send mcclure
down there again?
Beats me.
All i know is, there's
a boiler tender second
who's making book in
the crew's quarters
that that thing below us
is a sea monster
with three heads,
and we're all living
on borrowed time.
Captain.
I don't know what
scares me more:
When they pound
or when they shut up.
I don't know what
scaresmemore:
A 20-year-old sub
with somebody alive inside
or what the commander
of the pacific fleet
will say when i tell him
there's a 20-year-old sub
with somebody alive inside.
Coffee, captain?
Please.
Furthermore,
i've got a chief
boatswain's mate
who has something
eating at him.
Bell?
Mm-hmm, bell.
What made him
black out?
Well, that's part
of the problem.
Could be he's
dredging up
a couple of
memories.
What do you mean,
memories?
Well, this is world war ii
revisited for him.
He was picked up here
after a sinking.
A sinking?
Sit down, marmer.
That's the way i hear it.
He was on a ship that was hit-
the only survivor.
They pulled him out
of the water.
He had a pretty rough time.
Maybe he is
dredging up memories.
Here we go again.
I'll be in the sonar shack.
Still coming from
down below, captain?
Yeah.
How's the patient?
Well, he's asleep.
I'm just going to
get some coffee.
Well, you keep me
posted, will you?
Aye, aye, sir.
What's the matter,
chief, what happened?
I was looking
in the mirror,
and i saw
faces that...
they were
staring at me.
They were
pointing at me.
Now, i know
this sounds crazy,
but they were there.
It was as if they
were ordering me
into the mirror,
pulling me in...
doc?
You, uh, see me
in the mirror?
Huh?
Yeah, i see you.
Now, i see you
just fine, chief.
Now, you remember
that, huh?
I see you fine.
Now, nobody is ordering
you anywhere,
and you're not
going anyplace.
We're going to whip this,
i promise you.
We're going
to whip this!
It's some equipment down there.
Something loose that's
swinging back and forth,
hitting the bulkhead.
It's possible.
It's the only
explanation.
A 20-year-old sub in
the deep six since the war?
Well, whoever it is,
whatever it is,
it's losing steam.
I wouldn't
make book on this,
but i've got a hunch
that if we don't get inside,
and i mean quick,
we're going to miss the boat.
So we go down again.
Like you told the o.d.,
we knock on the door.
We don't knock on
the door this time.
Now we kick
the door open!
If you break
in that way,
it's a sure bet
the pressure
will kill whatever's
alive down there.
Then we do it
the one other way we've got.
Send a message to com sub pac.
Tell them we're
going to need
a sub rescue
ship here.
Tell them to report to scene
for rescue attempt.
Airlock chamber, huh?
That's all
we've got left.
Get on it right
away, will you?
I'll be
on the bridge.
Radio, sonar.
To com sub pac,
emergency precedence.
Where are you
going, chief?
Doc, who's outside?
What?
Who's outside
in the passageway?
There's nobody
out there
who shouldn't be.
Let me tell you
something, chief.
You can talk yourself into
any kind of nightmare you want.
You just have to let
the gates down a bit,
and that stuff seeps in.
Only there's nobody blowing
it from the other side.
It's you, yourself.
Now, there's nobody out there.
Nobody at all.
Now, who did you think
was out there?
I don't know.
You're wound up
tight, chief,
and i think you're doing
most of this to yourself,
because there's nothing out
there on that passageway
except a long stretch
of deck and steel.
Nothing else.
You want to
take a look?
Doc, what's
happening to me?
Doc, no, please tell me
what's happening to me.
You've got to grab
hold of yourself.
You're going
to talk yourself
into a straightjacket.
You're going to build
so many nightmares
into that brain
of yours...
the same feeling?
It's the same thing.
It's just as if
somebody out there
was waiting for me.
Just as if something out
there's pulling me.
Hey, doc?
What, chief?
Doc, i'm scared
to open the door.
Well, then don't.
I told you
there's nobody out there.
Doc, i'm scared to open
this door, but i got to.
Oh, my dear god
in heaven.
Did you see them, doc?
Did you see them?
Men...
men looking at me.
They were... they were wet,
they were dripping wet,
and they were not alive!
No, i didn't see
anything, chief.
Neither did you.
Now, did you hear me?
You didn't see a thing.
Not a bloody
worshipping thing.
All you saw was what your
scare-brain told you to see.
That's all that it was.
What you talked yourself
into wanting to see!
Seaweed.
That about does it,
mcclure.
Go down, and see
if you can get another response.
It'll be a great help
to the sub rescue outfit
if you can confirm
a specific location.
How will they
get in, sir?
Through the forward torpedo
compartment of the stern.
They'll have to blow
each of the six other
compartments between them
before they can enter
any part.
Well, what if i
don't get an answer?
We haven't heard from them
in almost a half hour.
If you can't get an answer,
come on back up.
The a.s.r. Team
will pick it up from here.
No survivors then, sir-
is that what it'll mean?
That's what it'll mean-
no survivors.
Okay, mcclure,
hop to it.
Aye, sir.
I've reached the sub, sir.
The next noise you hear,
that'll be me.
Go ahead, pound away.
What about it, mcclure,
any response?
No response, sir.
No response anywhere.
Keep trying a few minutes.
Yes, sir.
Mcclure?
I've found something.
Wait a minute.
It's a pair of dog tags.
What about response, mcclure?
Can you hear anything?
No, sir, i don't hear a thing.
Well, give them
a few more minutes,
and then come on back up.
Yes, sir.
No soap, i guess.
No soap.
That frosts,
that really frosts.
To get so close to those
poor devils and then...
that sub rescue ship
is due here about 0300.
Keep your eye peeled.
I'm going aft.
Aye, sir.
This is what
i found, sir.
Thanks, mcclure,
good job.
Go get yourself
some coffee.
But i will need you
one more time.
When the a.s.r.
Team gets here,
you'll have to go
down with them as pathfinder,
give them
all the help they need.
Excuse me, sir, but...
well, you better look
at those tags.
They're yours,
aren't they?
Mcclure found them
on the deck of
the sub down there.
When did you
lose them, boats?
That was a...
long time ago, sir.
When?
Um...
oh, uh...
20... 20 years
ago, sir.
20 years ago.
Sit down, boats.
Go ahead, sit down.
Go on.
I was, uh...
...aboard ship, sir.
What ship?
Submarine.
Sir, that... that one
down below us, that...
that was my boat.
What's making the noise
down there, boats?
Do you know?
What's it
all about?
We were on the surface.
It... it was night.
I was, uh...
i was a signalman then.
I was supposed to put
an infrared filter on the, uh...
...on the, uh, signal light,
otherwise, the japs
would have seen us.
They would have seen the light.
They would have found us.
I understand.
I don't know...
i don't know
what happened.
I, uh...
l-i dropped
the, uh, signal light.
The infrared filter fell off.
They were waiting for us out
there, the jap destroyers.
They saw
our light.
They let us have it.
They straddled us
with their first salvo.
The, uh, captain took the sub
down, but it was too late.
They unloaded depth charges.
That sub wasn't ever going to be
able to come up again.
What about you, boats?
I got flung over the side
when that first salvo hit.
Mm-hmm.
And, uh...
all the time i...
...i was in
the water there,
i could,
i could...
you could what?
I could, uh...
i could
hear the, uh...
hear the, um...
i could hear the
voices of our guys.
They were, uh...
they were screaming!
All right, boats!
Boats, sit down!
All right,
all right now.
I know what it was.
This thing has
been bugging me.
I know,
i know what it is.
All right,
what is it?
I got out, see?
One guy in our whole
crew- i got out.
Oh, i got picked up later
by one of our destroyers.
I got out.
You understand
that, captain?
I... i sunk
that sub, right?
I was responsible.
Yes.
I got out.
I want you to
listen to me now.
Yeah, that's what this
thing... this thing...
see, them guys...
them guys down
there in that sub,
they know i'm up here.
Bell, i want you
to hear me out now.
Yeah, that's what this
thing has been, see?
I should be down
there with them.
Now, bell...
i should be
down in that sub.
I should be dead.
Bell!
See? And all this
noise, see-
this pounding,
this clanging-
that's them guys
down there.
They're calling
muster on me.
Bell, i want you
to hear me out now.
Bell, bell, i want you
to hear me out!
Bell!
Captain, shh! Shh!
Bell, i want you to quiet
down and hear me out
and listen to a little logic
now and a little reason.
Bell, listen to me!
Now you listen to me.
They're calling
muster on me.
Bell, listen to me!
Just listen to a little
logic, a little reason!
One man
does not sink a sub,
and one lousy circumstance
does not decide a battle,
and one case
of sudden fear
does not add up
to a coward.
You've been taking
a dirty rap for 20 years.
You've slept with it,
you've hung it around your neck,
you've let it dig deep down
inside and tear you to pieces.
Let me tell you something, bell.
It's not deserved,
it's not right.
It's a dead weight guilt
that you've blown way out
of proportion to the facts.
And do you know
what the facts are, bell?
The facts are that that sub
was dead in the water
and surrounded by enemy craft.
That was a crew that was doomed,
do you understand that?
A frightened
sailor
didn't destroy
that ship
or kill off
that crew.
Bell!
You've got
to understand.
A war did!
A set
of circumstances did!
Now, bell,
you've got to believe me.
All you should put in your
seabag is a regret, not a guilt.
Do you understand,
bell?
Not a guilt!
By your leave, sir.
They're calling
muster on me.
Bell!
They're calling muster on me!
Man overboard,
starboard side!
starboard side.
Pass the word,
man overboard, starboard side.
We've been searching
for ten hours, sir.
It's no use.
We can't find
the body.
The rescue team ought to
be in that sub by now.
Yeah.
You got in.
Yes, sir.
It was a wreck
inside, sir.
Nobody had a chance.
Nobody?
Nobody, sir.
The periscope shears
had been cut in half,
and one whole section
was just hanging there
swinging back and forth.
That was making the noise then.
Thatwasmaking the noise,
wasn't it?
I guess so, sir.
But...
but what?
There were eight men
in the control room.
Eight men, or what
was left of them, and...
one of them...
one of them
had a hammer in his hand.
Mcclure...
let's just say that
that's part of the story
you tell your grandchildren,
that you make up yourself.
Tell them anything you like.
Aye, sir.
Funny thing, how long it
takes some men to die
or to find any
peace at all.
Sometimes i think that's the
worst thing there is about war-
not just what it does
to the bodies...
but what it does to the minds.
So rest in peace, chief bell.
I think it's your due now.
Small naval engagement,
the month of april, 1963.
Not to be found
in any historical annals.
Look for this one filed
under "h" for "haunting"
in the twilight zone.
Next ontwilight zone,
a marvelously exciting excursion
into a very strange place
called "valley of the shadow."
It comes from the probing mind
of mr. Charles beaumont,
and whether
you're a science fiction buff,
a fantasy lover
or just needful of some escape,
this one should fill
most of your requirements.
I thought you told me
my car was going
to be repaired.
Please sit down.
I don't want
to sit down.
I want to know why
nothing's been done
to my car.
Why it's just
sitting out there.
Primarily because
you won't be needing it anymore.
Oh, no? Well, why?
Because you are never going
to leave peaceful valley.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, i think i got
this thing figured out.
Oh?
Well, sure.
Peaceful valley
is a town full of lunatics,
and you guys
head the list.
Now what do you mean
i'm not ever
going to be able
to leave here?
'Cause, mr. Redfield,
you stumbled upon
the best kept secret
in the world.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org