Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Children, your father
and i are going to divorce.
Now if you don't
know what that means,
well, it means that he's
going to live in one place,
and, well, i'm going
to live in another
just as far apart as we can get.
What we want to
know from you kids
is do you want to live
with me or with her?
Now, it's going to
be up to you two.
You've got to
make up your minds.
We want it the way it was.
You better forget that.
Amen.
This time we'll be good.
We won't fight, or cry
or make noise.
We'll be good, won't we, jeb?
What do you
mean, sport?
Y'all hate each other
'cause you got us.
Well, i'll tell you one thing...
if it hadn't been for you two,
we wouldn't have stuck together
as long as we have.
So show us
a little consideration.
We don't have to stay
with neither one of you.
Come on, jeb.
Come back here!
We're not through
with you.
What do you kids
think you're doing?
We can't get back.
We've got to.
What are
they doing?
Come out!
Jeb, get out of there.
You hear your daddy?
Aunt t, help us, please!
Aunt t?
Come out of there!
Please, aunt t.
Kids!
Jeb?
What do they mean,
"aunt t"?
What do you kids
think you're doing?
Jeb?
Do you hear your daddy?
You're really going
to get it this time.
Sport, do you hear me?
Jeb?
Are you coming out of there,
or i'm coming after you?!
They're down there
an awful long time.
Yeah, i know.
Do something-
they're drowning!
Hurry!
Oh! Please don't let them drown.
Don't let them drown.
They're not down there.
They've got to be.
A swimming pool
not unlike any other pool-
a structure built
of tile and cement and money,
a backyard toy for the affluent,
wet entertainment
for the well-to-do.
But to jeb and sport sharewood,
this pool holds mysteries
not dreamed of
by the building contractor
not guaranteed
in any sales brochure.
For this pool has a secret exit
that leads
to a never-never land,
a place designed
for junior citizens
who need a long voyage
away from reality
into the bottomless regions
of the twilight zone.
Introduction to
a perfect setting:
Colonial mansion, spacious
grounds, heated swimming pool-
all the luxuries money can buy.
Brother and sister,
names jeb and sport, healthy,
happy, normal youngsters.
Gloria sharewood by name,
glamorous by nature.
Gil sharewood,
handsome, prosperous,
the picture of success.
A man who has achieved
every man's ambition-
beautiful children,
beautiful home, beautiful wife.
Idyllic? Obviously.
But don't look too carefully,
don't peek behind the facade.
The idyll may have feet of clay.
You're home early,
darling.
Just what were you
doing in town today?
So now i'm being followed.
Darn you
loud-mouthed kids!
Pipe down
out there.
Jeb?
You're still
holding your breath?
You're gonna suffocate yourself.
It's the only way
i can keep quiet.
Mama didn't mean
we couldn't breathe.
It was the yelling
and the hollering
that was making her head ache.
I'm just a natural born
screamer.
Can't play unless i holler.
I saw your car in the parking
lot next to the tv station.
I had an interview-
anything wrong with that?
I'm sick and tired
of my talent going to waste.
Your what?
My talent.
Now what high-fashion model
can hold a candle to me?
Is that what you
are this week?
High-fashion model?
Seems to me that last week
you were an artist.
If they call me,
i'll take the job.
You've got a job here-
taking care of those kids.
What's the maid for,
sugar?
What are you for, sugar?
Look down there-
what do you see?
A swimming pool.
A pretend game, stupid.
What do you see?
Well...
a river, and you and me floating
down on a raft like tom sawyer.
See, jeb?
Mm-hmm.
We're coming
to an island
full of caves
and rattle snakes
and pirates.
And witches.
Well, you can have one witch,
just one.
A fat one.
Whoever heard of a fat witch?
Well, i don't like skinny ones.
They don't make fat ones.
Look, it's my witch.
I can make them fat
if i want to.
It's my game!
Darn you loud-mouth kids.
Now pipe down out there.
I love you, sport.
You're silly.
I'll have
my supper now.
Cook for you after
the way you talked?
Baby, you drink your supper.
Oh, you witch.
In the yard is a big, old swing
made out of a car tire.
There's a little boy swinging.
He gets tired of swinging
and goes into the kitchen.
Smells like chocolate cake.
There's a lady there.
She picks the little boy up
and hugs him.
The little boy is happy.
The lady gives the little boy
chocolate cake and...
have we been bad?
Heck, no.
Maybe i was bad
and i didn't know it.
Aw, fishhooks,
they'll stop after a while.
Hey! Want to have some fun?
Where'd you
come from?
What mischief
you brats in now?
Talking to this boy.
What boy?
He's gone!
Darn fool
kids.
Your supper's
going to be ready soon.
You better be there on time.
Now do you
hear me?
Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am.
Come on, you guys.
Where?
A secret place. Come on!
Who are you,
where are you from?
Follow me!
Let's go
with that boy.
She said
not to leave.
They don't care
what we do.
Come on.
They're going to
hurt each other.
Listen, boy,
i'm older than you
and i'm ordering you
what to do.
Now, follow me.
Howdy.
We weren't sure
you was coming.
Aunt t sent these
just in case.
Aunt t?
Where are we?
At aunt t's.
Where's that?
Secret place.
Sure got here funny.
Just dived in our pool
and came out here.
Sport, how did
we get here?
I figure there's a hole in our
pool that nobody knows about.
Maybe we got
caught in the tide.
Don't you laugh
at my brother.
at me, either.
I'll chew you up
and spit you out.
Let's see you!
I'll get you.
Come and get me!
Aunt t, she's going to
beat me up, aunt t!
Are you really,
child?
Yes, ma'am, i aim to.
I'll have to ask you
to fight outside.
You're liable to break up
something in here.
And i guess-
fight fair, fight fair.
No hitting a man when he's down,
no hitting below the belt.
You know the rules.
Now, while they're
settling their difficulties
you can finish icing the cake.
Thank you, ma'am.
And when
the two come back
if they have
any teeth left
they can help
us eat it.
My, you are
very accomplished.
Have you had much
experience with cakes?
No, ma'am,
this is my first one.
One would
never guess it.
Oh, what,
back already?
We didn't go yet.
May i do that?
Me, too?
I thought you were going
to beat each other up.
We'd rather do that.
All right, you come round
here and be the boss.
Sit down
right there.
You're such
solemn children.
Don't you know
how to laugh?
What's there to laugh at?
Well, i'm rather
a ridiculous old party.
You could laugh at me.
You're not funny, you're nice.
Oh, thank you.
Riddles, then-
who knows a riddle?
What do you call somebody
who crosses the ocean twice
and doesn't take a bath
either way?
What would you call him, whitt?
A dirty double-crosser.
Aunt t,
all the frosting's gone.
Well, you've made
a handsome job of the cake.
Now, while it's cooling,
i'll assign you new children
to your chores
and i'll show you
where your rooms will be.
Why,
what's the matter?
We didn't come
here to stay.
My dear, children
always come here to stay.
No.
But i want to.
Jeb sharewood, come back here.
I want to stay
with aunt t.
She's a kidnapper.
No!
I've seen children
i would have stolen
to get away
from unworthy parents,
but i always resisted
the temptation.
Sport? Jeb?
They're calling us.
But i want to stay, sport.
You darn kids, where are you?
We better go home.
Those voices you hear calling
at first seem quite strong,
but after a while, they'll fade
and one day, you simply
can't hear them anymore.
Sport?
We've got to go home.
Can you tell me why?
Because we're their children,
we love them and they love us.
Then you must
go back.
And you, too.
Your sister's reasons
are quite valid.
How do we
get home?
Same way
you got here.
We'll come see
you again soon.
Oh, no, my darlings.
I expect this
is our good-bye.
Finding your way here again
would be quite difficult,
if not impossible.
Good-bye, aunt t.
I'll race you back
to the swimming hole!
Have you found them?
Not a sign.
I told them
not to leave this yard.
They
have no respect for you.
You're not firm enough.
You just don't spend
enough time with them.
You try putting up with
their screaming and whining
24 hours a day.
Mama!
Sport! Jeb!
Where have you two been?
We've been calling you
for an hour.
Get out
of that pool.
Sport, where
have you been?
Jeb, get out
of there now.
In the pool.
You're lying,
i looked there.
We really were, daddy.
We came up
on the other side
and made a chocolate
cake with aunt t.
Cake with... what's
he talking about?
We caught a fish.
He's just making
things up, daddy.
He's lying
to cover up
whatever
you been in.
I want the truth,
boy, no more lies.
I wasn't
lying, i wasn't.
Jeb,
listen to me.
Get to your room
and stand in the corner
until you're ready
to tell the truth.
It was just a game, daddy.
We were just pretending.
There isn't any aunt t.
You go along
too, sport.
Those darn kids.
Sport? Jeb?
Sport?
Here, mama.
What are you
doing here, sport?
I got up early.
I couldn't sleep.
Well, where's
your brother jeb?
In his room.
He's not in
the house anyplace.
I haven't seen him.
Is breakfast ready?
No. Now, your father's waiting.
Want to have a talk
with you kids.
What about?
There's going to be
some changes around here.
Things going to be better, mama?
You bet your sweet life
they are.
Now you go find jeb.
Another one
of your chores, jeb,
will be to help whitt
bring in the wood.
Why do there have to be chores?
Every child
must have chores to do.
It teaches him dignity of work
and the joy of labor.
Makes big muscles,
too, like mine.
Let's see.
Big,
ain't it?
Wow.
Oh, come along, boys,
keep working.
Aunt t,
what are all the shoes for?
For the children.
You mean all the children got
holes in their swimming pools?
Oh, my dear, no.
Some of them come down chimneys
or you open a door
and there they are.
Sometimes you find them
on street corners or doorsteps
like whitt there.
Oh, sport,
dear, come in!
I can't, i'm dripping wet.
Oh, one minute.
There you are, my dear.
Thank you, ma'am.
I told you she'd come.
Well, i'm surprised
that either one of you made it.
It's very rare that anybody
comes back here the second time.
Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
You're not
bothering me.
I'm glad to have somebody
to help me do my needlepoint.
You do sew?
No, ma'am.
Well, you'll be surprised
how quickly you'll learn how.
I can't stay.
Oh.
I only came
to get jeb.
I ain't going.
Things are going to be
different at home now, jeb.
Mama told me.
Told you what?
They aren't going
to yell at each other.
Is that all?
No.
We're going to
take trips.
Where?
Oh, everywhere-
disneyland, ohio...
australia,
the north pole.
Anywhere
we want to go.
I don't want to go
to them places.
Are you coming
or do i throw you
over my shoulder
like a sack of potatoes?
Sport, has something
changed at home?
Yes, ma'am.
Everything will be
different now.
In what way?
They're going to love us.
Really?
Yes, ma'am, my mama told me.
She wants to tell jeb, too.
Jeb, you'd look undignified
if sport threw you
across her shoulder
like a bag of potatoes.
If i was you,
i'd go willingly.
I'm staying right here.
If we leave this time,
we won't never get to come back.
If what sport tells us is true,
you weren't meant
to be here at all
but at home
with your mother and father.
Do i have to go?
I strongly advise it.
There's only one
truly precious thing
in the world
that one human being
can give to another
and that's love.
If i was
a young person
on my way to receive
that wondrous gift,
i'd go with
a smile on my face.
Oh, much better.
And i do think
if love was waiting
somewhere for me,
well, i'd run to it
just swiftly as the wind.
You ain't kidding me?
I ain't kidding.
Bye, whitt.
Bye.
Don't worry, aunt t,
everything will be all right.
Good-bye,
love.
Maybe, um, we ought
to wait till tonight.
No, let's get it over
with now.
I've got people
waiting at the office.
For once put your family
ahead of your office.
You miserable...
breakfast ready?
I told you to find jeb,
not play in the pool.
He was
in the pool.
Don't you know what happens
to children who lie?
They go to hell
and get burned up.
Sit down, your father's
got some good news.
Sport told me.
We're going to be
a happy family
and take trips.
Jeb, uh...
uh...
you tell them.
Children, your father
and i are going to divorce.
Now if you don't
know what that means,
well, it means that he's
going to live in one place,
and, well, i'm going
to live in another
just as far apart as we can get.
What we want to
know from you kids
is do you want to live
with me or with her?
Now, it's going to be
up to you two.
You've got to
make up your minds.
We want it the way it was.
You better forget that.
Amen.
This time we'll be good.
We won't fight or cry
or make noise.
We'll be good, won't we, jeb?
What do you
mean, sport?
Y'all hate each other
'cause you got us.
Well, i'll tell you one thing...
if it hadn't been for you two,
we wouldn't have stuck together
as long as we have.
So show us
a little consideration.
We don't have to stay
with neither one of you.
Come on, jeb.
Come back here!
We're not through
with you.
What do you kids
think you're doing?
We can't get back.
We've got to.
What are
they doing?
Come out!
Jeb, get out of there.
You hear your daddy?
Aunt t, help us, please!
Aunt t?
Come out of there!
Please, aunt t.
Kids!
Jeb?
What's the matter
with them?
Are you coming out of there?
Aunt t, please!
Aunt t, aunt t, help us!
Aunt t, please take us.
What do they mean,
"aunt t"?
What do you kids
think you're doing?
Do you hear your daddy?
You're really going
to get it this time.
Sport, do you hear me?
Jeb?
Are you coming out of there,
or i'm coming after you?!
They're down there
an awful long time.
Yeah, i know.
Do something-
they're drowning!
Hurry!
Oh! Please don't let them drown.
Don't let them drown.
They're not down there.
They've got to be.
Howdy!
Jeb? Sport?
Isn't this good,
jeb?
What's the matter,
sport?
Thought i heard something.
Children, where are you?
Please come back.
Aunt t...
may i have another
piece of cake, please?
Me, too.
Indeed.
Isn't it good?
Oh, this is fine.
Good cake.
Mm-hmm.
A brief epilogue
for concerned parents:
Of course there isn't
any such place
as the gingerbread house
of aunt t
and we grown-ups know
there's no door at the bottom
of a swimming pool
that leads to a secret place.
But who can say how real
the fantasy world
of lonely children can become?
For jeb and sport sharewood,
the need for love
turned fantasy into reality.
They found a secret place
in the twilight zone.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org