Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
The economy of our world,
now, then, and forever,
have always found
the insidious breed
of international bankers.
These are the worshippers
of the purse.
Their religion
is monetary gain.
Their shrine is gold.
Their loyalties, first,
foremost, and primarily,
deal with money.
What's wrong with that?
Examine the phenomenon
of foreign control.
You examine it,
and you will note
with absolute clarity
that the lines lead
directly to palestine!
They lead directly to africa!
They lead directly...
to the vatican!
Uh, um...
so, so, there we are!
There it is!
There is a conspiracy!
There's a insidious,
enveloping conspiracy!
A conspiracy personified
by the yellow man...
by the black man...
and by foreigners
who come in
and infiltrate
into our economic structure.
Oh, there'll come a morning,
yes, there will,
there will come a morning
when these men
have taken over your home,
taken over your daughters...
and they'll be sitting
right there on your doorstep.
If anybody's
sitting on your doorstep, buddy,
he's a man in a white coat.
You better
just go with him, quietly.
You think that's funny,
don't you?
You think it's funny
your country can be sold out.
That they can sell out your flag
and birth rights.
That's funny, huh?
Well, do something
about it, punk.
You're such
a big tiger,
why don't you come down here
and do something about it?
Let me tell you something
right now.
Someday this country's
going to wake up.
And when they find out
how izzy sold them out,
and how rastus sold them out
and how pancho sold them out,
they're going to make up a list
of all the people
that get paid back.
And you know where you'll be?
Right on the top of that list!
Come here, i'll fix...
come here!
What's the matter, punk?
No more big speeches?
No more big talk, huh?
Know what you'll see
when you get home
and look in the mirror?
A scrawny little kook
with a big mouth.
A big hater when you got
a couple of punks
in front of you.
Problems, fellas, huh?
The communists,
the communists did this.
Which ones?
All of 'em,
all of 'em were communists.
What about
some names, jack?
If you press charges,
we'll need names.
Forget about it.
We can handle
this ourselves.
Need medical attention?
We don't need any.
Okay, jack.
Hey, jack.
You forgot your, um,
your flag.
There'll come a day
when guys like you
will crawl on your belly
just to salute this.
There'll come a day.
Let me know the date, jack.
That morning,
i'll cut my wrists.
Hey, pete.
Pete, i'm glad
you're okay.
Boy, there must've been
eight, ten guys
on top of me.
I had all i could
do to get away.
You get a mean crowd, pete.
Get a hot night,
you get a mean crowd.
I told you guys that.
Every time you
get a hot night,
you get a couple of
stiffs in the crowd
and they swing it
all the wrong way.
Remember when i was
telling you that, pete?
Remember how i was telling you
every time you
get a hot night...
it's all right.
It's done. It's done.
Sure, pete, sure.
Why?
I tried so hard.
I tried so hard
out there tonight, i...
i couldn't...
get through.
I couldn't get through
to any of them.
I knew
what i had to say to them,
i knew what i had to tell them,
and i just cou... i couldn't.
I couldn't get it out.
I couldn't
find the words.
Someday, they're going
to have to listen.
Someday they're going to cheer!
Someday they will, pete.
They will.
Portrait of a bush-league
fuhrer named peter vollmer.
A sparse little man
who feeds off his self-delusions
and finds himself
perpetually hungry
for want of greatness
in his diet.
And like some goose-stepping
predecessors,
he searches for something
to explain his hunger
and rationalize why a world
passes him by without saluting.
The something he looks for,
and finds, is in a sewer.
In his own twisted,
distorted lexicon,
he calls it
faith, strength, truth.
But in just a moment
peter vollmer
will ply his trade
on another kind of corner...
a strange intersection
in a shadowland
called the twilight zone.
Wash your face.
It's not a mortal wound.
I think you'll survive.
When you get home,
put some iodine on it.
Want a cup of coffee?
A drink?
May i have a drink, ernst?
I have wine, you want some?
Onesipswine, peter.
This is not medicine.
Well, i'll keep that
in mind for next time.
For the next time?
Just how many next times
do suppose a person has
in the scheme of things?
Don't lecture me, ernst.
I'm sick and tired,
and i don't need
to be lectured.
Can i stay here tonight?
It remains here
for you, as usual.
You're a good
friend, ernst.
You're a good friend.
A man does what he believes in.
A man usually does.
Well, i believe
certain things.
Is that a fact?
Yes, well,
what difference does it make
if we don't think alike
about the same things?
I mean, we're friends.
You've known me
since i was a kid.
When you were
a little kid, peter,
and i used to find you crying
at my door late at night...
i could pity you then.
And now?
What do
you think?
Now you peddle hate
on street corners
as if it were popcorn.
It's not hate,
it's, uh, a point of view,
it's a philosophy.
Ah, i know
the philosophy.
I know it quite well.
Nine years in a place
called dachau.
You know who
put me there?
Peter vollmer.
A lot of peter vollmers.
Frustrated men...
sick men...
angry men.
But the result,
the effect-
never mind the cause-
12 million bodies
in shallow graves.
And it all started
with young men in uniform
talking on street corners.
You let me come here.
You let me come here;
you never sent me away.
No, i never did.
I never do.
That's the weakness you scream
about on your street corners.
Sentimentality, softness,
the weakness that makes a man
his brother's keeper.
Oh, i must be one
of the worst
of your criminals,
peter.
Sentimental...
soft!
And very preoccupied
with my brother.
I should close the door on you.
Perhaps... this is my sickness.
I... i only
see the boy...
not the man.
Sleep on the couch.
Look... why don't
you understand?
You're like a father.
You're the only thing
in the world
that i've ever loved.
What have i ever had to love?
What?
A drunken father who used to
slam me against the wall?
An old lady...
who had no marbles in her head?
She didn't even recognize me
half the time.
That's why i used
to come here, because...
because you were
gentle with me,
and you'd talk to me,
you feed me.
You took care of me.
Ernst...
ernst, you're my father.
That's the boy again speaking.
A little boy
with so much fear in him.
Rest.
Rest well.
Who's out there?
Who is it?
A friend, mr. Vollmer.
A friend?
You have need
of friends, allies.
Come down,
mr. Vollmer.
Come down, and we will talk,
you and i.
Hello, mr. Vollmer.
Who are you?
How did you know where i was?
I simply followed your tears,
mr. Vollmer.
You said that you had something
to talk about.
I do, i do indeed.
I have you to talk about,
and the things you believe in,
which are the things
i believe in, as well.
Your success, mr. Vollmer,
will be my success.
Go on.
Good.
Let us start by your learning
what are the dynamics
of a crowd.
How do you move a mob,
mr. Vollmer?
How do you excite them?
How do you make them feel
as one with you?
L-i don't know. How?
Join them first,
mr. Vollmer.
Join them?
Yes, when you speak to them,
speak to them as if you
were a member of the mob.
Speak to them in their language,
on their level.
Make their hateyourhate.
If they are poor,
talk to them of poverty.
If they are afraid,
talk to them of their fears.
And if they are angry,
mr. Vollmer,
if they are angry,
give them objects
for their anger.
But most of all,
the thing that is most
of the essence, mr. Vollmer,
is that you make this mob
an extension of yourself.
Say to them things like...
things like...
"they call us hatemongers.
"They say we're prejudiced.
"They say we're biased.
"They say we hate
minorities- minorities.
"Understand
the term, neighbors:
"Minorities.
"Should i tell you
who are the minorities?
"Should i tell you?
"We...!
Wearethe minorities!"
That way, mr. Vollmer.
Start it that way.
I... understand.
I think i understand.
Neighbors...
neighbors.
They call us...
hatemongers.
They say...
weare prejudiced.
weare biased!
They say
that we hate the minorities!
The minorities.
Understand the term, neighbors.
Shall i tell you
who the minorities are?!
We, we, we...!
Wearethe minorities!
Because patriotism...
is a minority.
Because love of country...
is the minority.
Because to live
in a free, white america
seems to be
of a minority opinion!
Let me tell you something,
neighbors.
I want you to dwell on this,
just dwell on it.
We had the atom bomb,
and suddenly...
the russians had it.
We wanted
to send men into space!
But it was the russians
who got there first!
We had the hydrogen bomb!
It was the russians
who exploded theirs.
Who gave them the bombs?
Who sold us out?
Who stabbed us in the back?
Well...
if it's a minority opinion
that we have to survive,
then we are the minority.
And this minority
will not stop
until it is the majority!
This minority
will not give up the fight!
This... is the promise
and this...
this is the legacy!
Pal, we're in
there now, huh?
No more street corners?
Oh, boy, are we
going now, huh?
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Nice speech.
Thank you.
Look, i'm not going
to wait much longer.
If i don't get paid,
you don't have the hall
tomorrow night.
Gibbons, will
you cool it?
Can't you see
we're busy?
I'm not waiting
not another
five minutes!
I want it settled now.
I told you, no dough,
no rental.
No dough, no hall
tomorrow night.
I'm not running this
place for pleasure.
What seems to be the problem?
This is a very
hungry man here.
He got to have
his shekels,
his little old money.
I told you guys
you're three weeks
back in the rent.
You said you'd
give me it a week ago.
All i got was cigarette
butts on the floor.
Am i to understand
you're going to lock us out
for a couple weeks' rent?
You understand right.
$200 due,
$200 that i ain't received.
We happen to be
a young movement.
We're still struggling.
We need time to grow.
But i don't rent time-
i just rent the hall.
It's the money
or you build a platform
in the street.
Whew.
What are we
going to do, pete?
We got to do something.
I don't see why we walk
tiptoe with this guy.
Why don't
i educate him?
I can,
i guarantee it.
Somebody left
this for you.
Who?
Nobody saw him.
It was left
at the back door
with your name.
Two c's!
Hey, how about
that, huh?
We needed
200 bucks' rent,
and there it is!
Did you see
who left this?
No, i didn't.
The message was just
for you to get it.
Gibbons,
come and get it.
Where'd the dough
come from, pete?
You have any idea?
You were great tonight,
pete.
You were
really something.
I can't describe
how it sounded.
You had them...
just like that,
you had them.
We're going
to make it now, frank.
Now we'rereally
going to make it.
You bet your life.
An excellent performance,
mr. Vollmer.
Very effective.
You learn quickly.
Thank you.
I'd like to know
who i'm thanking.
It does not make
very much difference.
I am just pleased i could help.
You learned the style very well.
You delivered the speech
exactly as i told you.
I'm very obliged.
The money?
Oh, it was the least i could do.
We could not very well have you
thrown out into the streets.
I happen to feel your work
is very important.
Are you one of us?
One ofyou,
mr. Vollmer?
You might say
iamyou.
Now, i have some suggestions.
I will continue
to give you advice.
But there is a matter
of great importance
that must be taken care of.
What is it?
An expedient,
mr. Vollmer.
Oh, you might
call it a, uh...
acause celebre.
Something to cement
the organization together.
I don't understand.
A martyr.
The organization needs a martyr.
How do you find a martyr?
You do not find one,
mr. Vollmer.
You choose one.
You take one of no value,
and you make him into a symbol.
You wrap him
in a flag,
and you make
his death work
for you.
Find a man
who is of no value
while he's alive
but who can serve you
when he's dead.
Is there such a one?
We're waiting,
pete.
I'll be right
there, nick.
Sure, pete.
You talking to
somebody, pete?
You tell frank to come in here.
Alone.
Sure thing, pete.
Right away.
Excellent, mr. Vollmer.
An excellent choice.
I was just thinking...
there must be some other way.
Another way?
There is no other
way, mr. Vollmer.
And if you soften up,
if you weaken now,
there is no point in going on.
Now...
when frank
comes back,
tell him you have
discovered an informer.
Tell him the informer
has done you
irreparable damage.
Tell him
the informer
must be put
out of the way.
But... put out of the way
cleverly, mr. Vollmer.
Put out of the way subtly.
Put out of the way
so that there is some question
as to who is responsible.
Nick's, uh, been with us
from the beginning.
From the beginning?
Oh, no, mr. Vollmer.
None of you were there
at the beginning.
None of you.
Nick's a friend of mine.
This is an act of friendship.
We are allowing him
to serve the cause.
Nick said you
wanted to see me.
We've got a stoolie
in the group, frank.
A stoolie?
Nick.
Nick's been talking.
I think he's been hired
by the police.
Nick?! Nick
has done that?
I know it for a fact.
Everything we've done
and everything we've said...
nick's told.
What do we do, pete?
Get rid of him.
Make it look
like somebody else did it.
Make it look like somebody
who hates us did it.
I understand.
I understand, pete.
You call it...
you've got it.
Cross off the fat one.
Anything else?
Right.
We now, all of us,
have a martyr.
We have a martyr!
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
It's a good crowd.
Right up to
the ceiling.
What's the matter,
stanley?
Nothing, pete.
Then why the look?
It's nothing,
it's nothing at all.
You can tell me,
stanley.
What's the matter?
Nick was my friend, pete.
He was a nice guy.
I miss him.
Do you want me
to really tell you
what nick was, stanley?
Would you really like
a rundown?
He was a fat pig!
With no guts.
He was a greasy bigmouth
who copped out
at every turn.
He was a nickel-and-dime
judas,
and he got exactly
what he deserved.
So don't mourn
for nick, stanley.
Because he doesn't
rate mourning-
not that pig.
A man of honor died last week.
A decent, courageous fighter
for the cause of freedom
gave his life.
He gave his life for us!
Some skulking... assassin
murdered him!
But friends,
and neighbors,
and co-fighters...
...nick bloss
did not die in vain.
They stilled his great heart...
...but they could not
stifle his memory.
They could not...
obliterate his courage.
wipe away his honor.
He lives in you,
and he lives in me.
He lives deep in the gut
of every human being
who wants to see
the united states of america
be free.
Nick bloss
died for this.
And you and i...
we must live for this!
...and letsomebody else
concern themselves
with the lifeblood
of a nation...
he's got a
voice on him.
I knew it
when it was just a whimper.
That's a bad
kid, that one.
Used to be... used to be
people would laugh at him.
But lately, he
gets the crowds,
and not many people
laugh either.
You've know him a long
time, haven't you?
Since he was a child.
A silent, little boy
with very little to say.
(vollmer continues orating
in background
we're overdue to cut away
the cancerous...
i've seen it before.
I've seen it all before.
That was another time, mr. Ganz.
Another place,
another kind of people.
That doesn't
go here.
That's what we said, too,
they were brown scum.
Temporary insanity,
part of the passing scene...
too monstrous to be real.
So, we ignored them
or laughed at them.
Because we
couldn'tbelieve
that there were enough
insane people
to walk alongside
of them.
And then one morning,
the country woke up
from an uneasy sleep...
(vollmer continues orating
in background
...and there
was no more laughter.
The peter vollmers
had taken over.
The wild animals
had changed places
with us in the cage.
This nation of ours
is being beaten to death!
Just as sure
as the almighty
made communists,
catholics, and jews.
There's no time to stand around,
scratch our heads,
and pull our beards,
and twiddle
with our earlobes...
but not again.
It mustn't happen again.
We can't let it.
We simply can't
let it happen again.
All, all that nightmare.
...violence happens to be
the only way to be violent...
oh, no...
no, not this time.
...we do not want
to be pushed.
Now, i want to ask you
a few questions.
You just answer yes or no
to the following.
Do you want...
the united states of america
to remain free?
Yes!
Do you want your homes infected
with the vermin
from foreign shores?
No!
Now, listen to this one.
Do you want
a bunch of mongrels
to come over here...
go on, mr. Vollmer.
You were saying?
I can tell them
what you were saying.
I've heard it before.
I've heard it
a thousand times before...
in munich, in berlin...
on a hundred different
street corners.
It was
drivel then,
and it is
drivel now.
You've got to stop, ernst.
Well, what is this one here?
The new model?
A 1963 fuhrer
right off the assembly line?
Well, this one is not so new.
He's not so fresh.
This one is nothing
but a cheap copy!
Peter, we've got
to do something.
We're losing the audience.
Let me get rid of him.
Just leave me alone.
Well, let me tell you
about this one.
About the breed, the species.
They're all alike,
they are all alike.
Problem children...
sick, sad, neurotics,
who take applause like a needle.
That's enough, ernst.
Please...
please?
Listen to me, peter,
and let them listen.
Or else
i'll tell them
about a quaking,
whimpering boy
who cried on my couch;
who still
cries on my couch.
Please don't,
please, ernst.
Pete, don't let him do this.
Put him down.
Yeah, put me down,
put me down.
Shut me up.
Stifle me- why don't you?
Why can't you?
Because this
is your courage
right here.
This is your strength.
This...
and the torchlights,
and the crowd,
and thesieg heil!
The rebuttal.
The only sort of answer
your kind knows how to give.
This is your fuhrer.
He's yours.
I give him to you.
A gift from the sewers.
Mr. Vollmer.
You see... the way it is?
I knew him.
I knew the old man.
Is that a fact,
mr. Vollmer?
For such a long time.
I've known him for so long.
He cheapened you, mr. Vollmer.
He tore you to pieces!
Your voice is that of a lion,
your instincts
are those of a rabbit.
And you-
what are you?!
You direct traffic
from the darkness!
You plan the battles,
and you're never there
when they're fought!
Why don't you come out
in the light?
Why don't you come up here
alongside of me?
Why don't you give me a name...
and a face...
and a reason why?
Mr. Vollmer.
I was making speeches
before you could read them.
I was fighting battles
when your only struggle
was to climb out of a womb.
I was taking over the world
when your universe was a crib!
And as for being in darkness,
mr. Vollmer,
i invented darkness!
You... you picked me.
You picked me.
I did not pick you, mr. Vollmer.
You chose my ideas,
you invoked my name,
you stole my slogans.
So now, you must take
whatever else
comes with it.
In the past,
i have given you
suggestions.
Now i give orders!
And from now on,
you must be built of steel.
Steel, mr. Vollmer.
No soft gaps of sentiment.
Like we handled nick.
Like we handled the mobs.
Like we made the speeches.
And bit by bit, gradually,
we shall forge a force-
first an idea, then a force.
Just as i did it before,
mr. Vollmer,
with my own hands!
The old man, the jew,
he'll be back again,
tomorrow night, the next night.
I know him, i know the type.
We sent them into the ovens,
but always,
there was a handful left
to point a finger.
His kind, mr. Vollmer,
his kind are dangerous.
They talk, they think,
they plant a seed.
They hold us back!
Kill him!
Kill the old man!
Kill him?
Kill ernst?
Yes, tonight. Now.
He'll be
in his room.
All right, i'll do it.
I'll do it right now.
And mr. Vollmer...
when you come back,
we will have much
to talk about.
Plans,
campaigns, ideas-
the first steps.
This is only the beginning,
mr. Vollmer.
This is just the dawn.
It will be a long, long day!
You wouldn't listen to me,
ernst.
You wouldn't pay attention.
On the contrary.
I listened to you
all i could stand.
I couldn't even begin to tell
you what's happened, ernst.
It's too incredible,
too unbelievable.
There's no stopping us now.
No stopping you, peter.
An old man stopped you tonight,
with a few words.
He stopped you with the truth.
No, you're wrong, ernst.
It's not just me anymore.
There's someone else behind us.
Someone that you'd tremble at.
He'd have to be
a very imposing figure, peter.
More imposing than you.
More imposing
than that, too, peter.
Only because you don't think
i'll use it.
Which shows you don't know me
very well, ernst.
I know you, peter.
I know you.
From a ravaged little boy
wanting love...
to a torn man
craving respect,
identity, pride.
Peter... i don't fear you,
so you may do
what you have in mind
at any time you wish.
But this last one reminder
to you.
You can never kill an idea
with a bullet, peter.
Never.
I'm all steel now.
Ernst, i'm made of steel.
No sentiment, no softness.
Just purpose and will.
Then shoot.
Kill.
Destroy me.
All steel...
all strength.
But at the expense of the thing
most other men have.
Some... fragments
of decency
to tell them
right from wrong...
make them feel guilt
at dishonor...
that make them...
...that make them love.
Yes, peter...
you have steel...
...but you have no heart.
Mr. Vollmer!
Sentimentality?
None.
Steel tonight?
Steel.
And no regrets?
None.
What did you destroy tonight?
Only a disease.
A growth that was on our flesh
that had to be removed.
Not a man?
No, hardly a man.
How did it feel?
It felt...
it felt like i was immortal.
Mr. Vollmer!
Weareimmortal!
You peter vollmer?
We have a warrant
for your arrest.
Charge is complicity
in murder.
Victim's name
was nicholas bloss.
That should be
familiar to you.
Throw that gun away.
Walk toward us
with your hands up.
There's something
very wrong here.
You've made a terrible mistake.
I'm made out of steel.
Don't you understand
that i'm made out of steel?
Where will he go next,
this phantom from another time,
this resurrected ghost
of a previous nightmare-
chicago, los angeles,
miami, florida,
vincennes, indiana,
syracuse, new york?
Anyplace, everyplace,
where there's hate,
where there's prejudice,
where there's bigotry.
He's alive.
He's alive
so long as these evils exist.
Remember that
when he comes to your town.
Remember it
when you hear his voice
speaking out through others.
Remember it
when you hear a name called,
a minority attacked,
any blind, unreasoning assault
on a people or any human being.
He's alive
because through these things,
we keep him alive.
The talented author
richard matheson
pays a return visit
totwilight zone
with a story called "mute."
It provides an exception
challenge to the acting talents
of barbara baxley,
frank overton
and an unusual 12-year-old
by the name of ann jillian.
Is she burned?
She's alive.
Are you all right?
She's in shock, harry.
Bad off.
Can't talk, can't cry,
can't do nothing.
She's not burned, though.
How could she get out of that
house without being burned?
Don't push, children.
Be careful.
I want you to know
you're not fooling
me for one moment.
I know exactly
what you are.
I know... because my father
tried to force me
into the same thing
when i was your age.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org