Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Good work, gentlemen.
Apples in the barrel.
Yeah, so far,
but we ain't
spent anything yet.
Yeah, you know
brooks is right.
$1 million worth
of gold bullion,
and i'm still
wearing coveralls,
and i got $1.20
in my pocket.
That's this year,
senor decruz.
Today, this,
but tomorrow...
tomorrow, gentlemen...
like croesus, midas
and all rolled
into one.
Man, you see that
train engineer
when he hit
them brakes?
He looked like
he thought
the world was
coming to an end.
Why not?
When i blow up tracks,
i blow up tracks.
Point out a foundry
for me, decruz,
i'll forge
you a medal.
Oh, come on, come on,
look out, look out.
Get out of the way.
What's your
trouble, brooks?
May we get to
business now?
Let's get the carts
and start
unloading.
Come on, come on.
Down.
Oh, man, you're
a heavy little thing.
Are there any more
at home like you?
All right, gentlemen,
procedure as follows:
The gold in the cave
then mr. Decruz will
destroy the vehicles.
Okay, buddy boy,
let's go.
Thepiece de
resistancenow.
The real culmination.
Ultimate ingenuity.
It is one thing,
gentlemen,
to stop a train on its way
from fort knox to los angeles
and steal its cargo.
It's another thing
to remain free to spend it.
And spend it
we shall.
Yeah, but when?
Don't you know, mr. Decruz?
I would have thought
that this aspect
of the plan
would be particularly
clear in your mind.
Maldito vidrio.
Rip van winkle.
That's what we are.
Four rip van winkles.
I'm not sure.
Whatare you not sure of,
mr. Decruz?
Just... lying down
in one of these...
these glass caskets
and getting put to sleep.
I like to know
what i'm doing.
You know what you're doing-
i've explained it
very precisely to you.
All four of us
will be placed
in a state of
suspended animation,
and when we wake up,
that's when we'll take our gold
and enjoy it.
I say everybody
takes his cut now
and takes his own chances.
What you say,
decruz-
but that ain't
what we agreed on.
We agreed we'd
stash the gold here
and then do whatever
farwell tells us to do.
So far he ain't
been wrong-
not about anything.
The train, the gold...
gas he used to put
a whole trainload
of people to sleep-
everything.
All we had to do was
step over a lot of
horizontal folks snoring.
Transfer a fortune
like it was
cotton candy.
Amen to that.
Amen to that,
sure.
But how about
to this?
None of you mind
being helpless
and... closed up in these?
No, mr. Decruz.
None of us mind.
How long, farwell?
How long?
I don't know exactly.
I can only surmise.
I would say that...
...i would say
approximately
100 years
from today's date.
100 years,
gentlemen,
and we shall walk
the earth again...
as rich men, however.
As extremely rich men.
100 years.
Just like rip van winkle.
Introducing four experts
in the questionable
art of crime:
Mr. Farwell, expert on
noxious gases, former professor
with a doctorate in both
chemistry and physics;
mr. Erbie, expert in
mechanical engineering;
mr. Brooks, expert in
the use of firearms
and other weaponry;
and mr. Decruz,
expert in demolition
and various forms
of destruction.
The time is now
and the place is a mountain cave
in death valley, u.s.a.
In just a moment these four men
will utilize the services
of a truck placed in cosmoline
loaded with a hot heist, cooled
off by a century of sleep
and then take a drive
into the twilight zone.
All right, gentlemen.
First of all, i want to know
if you can hear me...
knock once on the side
as i call your name.
Decruz?
Brooks.
Erbie.
Now i'm going to give you,
in chronology,
precisely what will happen.
First,
you are to check your airlocks
located on your right.
See it there?
The red arrow
should be pointed
toward "closed and locked."
Now you are each to count ten,
very slowly.
When you come
to the end of the count,
reach down with your left hand,
there's a small
green button there.
See it?
You are to press
this button.
You will hear
a slight hissing sound.
This will be the gas
being measured
into the enclosures.
All right, gentlemen,
check your airlocks first.
Now begin to count
and on ten,
release the gas.
Good night, gentlemen.
Pleasant dreams.
Good sleep.
I'll see you
in the next century.
Next... century.
It didn't work.
It didn't...
we don't have any beards,
and our nails didn't grow.
Well, mr. Farwell,
with the big brain
and all the answers,
why didn't it work?
It must have worked.
It was foolproof.
All the body functions stopped.
There wouldn't be any growth
of beard or nails
or anything
else!
I tell you,
it worked.
Well, look.
The road's
still there.
It hasn't changed.
It hasn't changed
one bit!
Carajo.
Mastermind, big brain.
Instead of
a hundred years,
maybe it's an hour,
and so we're
still hot.
And all that gold in there
is just like
a lot garbage to us now
because everybody
and his brother
is going to be looking for it.
Erbie.
We forgot erbie.
This is what did it.
Must have fallen
from the top of the cave,
cracked the glass,
the gas escaped.
Mr. Erbie has proven my point,
however, gentlemen.
He's definitely
proven my point...
the hard way.
How... how long
would it take
for such a thing
to happen?
A year,
or a hundred years.
Chances are,
mr. Decruz,
that we're now
in the year 2061.
2060...
wow.
Okay.
Now the next step, huh?
We load the gold
into the truck
and take it to the first city
we get to, huh?
And then we take
it to a fence
or melt it down
ourselves in some way.
That's the deal,
isn't it?
Why is it, mr. Decruz,
that greedy men
are the most dreamless,
least imaginative,
the stupidest?
Now, listen to me, farwell...
for the first
time in history
we have taken a century
and put it in our hip pocket.
We've taken a lease on life
and outlived our stay.
We've had our cake
but we're still going to eat.
That's quite an adventure
out there, mr. Decruz,
though you're a little
insensitive to it.
It's a world
we've never seen before-
a brand-new, exciting world
that we are going
to walk through.
But with gold,
farwell.
With a million bucks
worth of gold.
That's how we're going to walk through it.
Of course.
I wonder...
what kind of a world.
We all loaded up?
All loaded.
Okay, let's pull out.
Brooks, you drive.
I'll hop in the back
and make sure the gold
doesn't fall off.
Well, aren't you
the most thoughtful little thing
that ever
come down the pike?
What's the matter?
You stay in back
and watch the gold, huh?
Decruz, i wouldn't
trust you with gold
if it was filling in
your own mother's tooth.
No, buddy boy,
you drive.
I'll check the back.
Well, okay.
Okay, amigo.
Where's the
water can?
We might as well
get that loaded.
Over there where
we buried erbie.
Decruz!
Mr. Brooks had
a very bad accident.
I keep underestimating
you, mr. Decruz.
Yeah, well,
we'll do it my way now.
We'll pack
as much as we can,
put them in
two knapsacks,
and hit the road.
I can't think of any
other alternative
at the moment.
Hold it, decruz, hold it.
I've... got to rest.
How we doing,
farwell?
The map said...
the map said 28 miles
to the next town.
At this rate,
we won't reach it
till tomorrow afternoon.
At this rate,
you'll never reach it.
There hasn't been a car,
not a single car.
What if...?
"What if" what?
What if there were a war?
What if they dropped a bomb?
What if this highway
stretched to...
stretched to what?
Stretched to nothing,
mr. Decruz?
Stretched to nothing at all?
Wouldn't it be the irony
of all ironies-
walk... till our hearts burst
carrying all this gold?
There's a world left, farwell,
and that proves it.
That means there's
a town up ahead.
We're going to make it, buddy.
We're going to make it.
Come on. Let's get going.
My canteen is gone.
I must have left it
back on the road
the last place
we stopped.
I haven't any water.
Water?
Oh, i believe there's some water
around here you could drink.
Let's see, uh...
oh, here's some water.
One drink, one bar of gold.
That's the price.
You're out of your mind.
One drink, one bar of gold.
I keep underrating you,
mr. Decruz.
You're quite
an entrepreneur.
Ain't it the truth.
One drink,
one bar of gold.
That's the going rate
today, mr. Farwell.
It may change tomorrow-
i haven't checked the market-
but for today it's one for one.
Let's go,
mr. Farwell.
What's the matter?
You pooped already?
You had a good
night's sleep,
and we've only
been on the road
a couple hours.
Stop... must stop.
Must have water,
decruz.
Must have water.
Well, all right,
farwell.
I got about a quarter
of a canteen left.
Please, decruz.
Mr. Farwell,
the rate of exchange
has gone up a little bit today.
It's two bars
of gold
for one swallow.
Water, please.
Mister... mister...
this is gold here.
You can have it.
Drive me to town.
If you give me water...
gold...
it's real gold.
You can have it.
I'll give it to you.
I'll... give it to you.
Poor old fella.
I wonder where you came from.
Who is it, george?
What's the matter
with him?
Some old tramp.
That's what he was.
He's dead.
What's that?
Gold- that's what
he said it was.
He wanted
to give it to me
in exchange
for a lift into town.
Gold? Now, what
in the world
would he be doing
with this gold?
I don't know, he was probably
off his rocker.
Anybody walking in the desert
this time of day
would be off his rocker.
Can you imagine that?
He offered this to me
as if it was really
worth something.
You know, wasn't it worth
something once, george?
I mean, didn't people
use gold for money?
Sure, about
a hundred years or so ago,
before they found a way
of manufacturing it.
When we get back into town,
we'll have the police
come out and pick him up.
The last
of four rip van winkles
who all died precisely
the way they lived:
Chasing an idol across the sand
to wind up bleached dry
in the hot sun
as so much desert flotsam
worthless as the gold bullion
they built a shrine to-
tonight's lesson
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
There are all kinds of wagers
and all kinds of odds,
from the spin
of a roulette wheel
to a two dollar across the board
at a racetrack.
But next week
onthe twilight zone,
with the aid
of mr. Franchot tone,
we tell the story of possibly
the strangest bet ever to occur
in the annals of chance.
Our program is called
"the silence."
I hope we'll see you then.
Here's something that doesn't
require any imagination-
it's oasis.
If you just took this puff,
you'd agree
it's the softest taste of all.
Before we meet again,
try oasis
for the softest taste of all.
Be sure and watchgunsmoke,
starring james arness,
saturday nights over most
of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org