Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
This road is the afterwards
of the civil war.
It began at fort sumter,
south carolina,
and ended at a place
called appomattox.
It's littered with the residue
of broken battles
and shattered dreams.
Ma'am?
Do... do you mind
if i have myself
some of your
water, ma'am?
Please.
Thank you.
Beautiful once, wasn't it?
The tree i mean, ma'am.
Once it was...
very beautiful.
War claims
a lot of victims...
men, animals and...
and god's own beauty.
Ma'am, would you mind if
i sat here for a spell,
and rested a bit?
Not at all.
Thank you.
Oh, uh... you mind if
i strum a few chords
on my guit' box here?
Not at all.
My husband used
to play the guitar.
Ah, did he now?
And he's, uh, now...
where is he, ma'am?
He was killed.
Yellow tavern
with general stuart.
I'm sorry.
Brand-new gray...
and gold braid...
and a thousand flags.
Trumpets
and drums.
Nothing but trumpets and drums.
Beat the yanks in a month,
that's what they said.
Beat the yanks in a month.
How wrong
they were.
And we stood by
in our summer dresses
and cheered them on
and threw flowers-
felt so grand.
Not many tears, just a few
because we were so sure
they'd all be coming back
just as they left.
How wrong we were.
Not feeling well, ma'am?
I'm all right,
it's the fever...
but i'm on the mend now.
It's left me a little weak,
that's all.
A little weak.
Still they come...
morning and night,
night and morning,
they walk
down that road.
The young ones
and the old ones.
How worn they look.
How tired.
Are there hundreds of them
or thousands of them?
Wouldn't you think...
wouldn't you think
that with so many, my jud...
my jud might be amongst them?
Sergeant?
Ma'am?
Would you do
me a favor?
If i can, ma'am.
Would you play
your guitar real loud?
I mean, real loud,
drown me out?
Loud, ma'am?
I'm so sick to death
of hearing
my own crying
and the sound of
footsteps on the road.
Please play it loud
so i can hear music.
Oh, ma'am...
please, sergeant!
As you wish, my lady.
? black is the color
of my true love's hair?
? her lips...?
? are something wondrous fair?
? the purest eyes...?
In just a moment you will
enter a strange province
that knows neither
north nor south-
a place we call
the twilight zone.
Charlie?
Hmm?
Charlie constable.
Charlie!
Charlie, it's lavinia.
We thought you'd been killed-
that's what everyone said.
They said you'd been shot
in the head at gettysburg.
Oh, i'm so glad
you've come back, charlie.
I'm so glad
you're all right.
Couldn't you stop
a minute, charlie?
I'm almost
there, lavinia.
Your wife will be
so glad to see you.
So very, very glad.
I won't need
all this weight.
I'll leave it here.
Oh, charlie.
Leave it here.
I got to keep moving.
I got to keep going.
Good-bye.
Oh, charlie.
Will you give
susan my best?
And tell her when
you get settled,
to please come over.
Though i expect
she'll want to keep
you to herself.
I know if it
were jud...
if it were jud
come home to me,
i'd hold him
close, so close,
i'd not let him
leave again.
I'm sure, lavinia.
That was
charlie constable.
They said he had been
killed in gettysburg-
shot through the head.
Thank god,
they made a mistake.
Thank god...
what's wrong, ma'am?
Why...
there's... there's blood
on his cap.
There's blood
on charlie's cap.
You finished already?
Yes, ma'am.
I got a feeling for wood.
You know,
whether it's chopping it,
or carving it or...
or wearing it.
Yeah.
Like my... my guit' box here.
See this?
Oh.
Made that myself.
Of course, it's not as good
as the one i got at home.
I had more time then,
you understand?
I can remember my daddy
used to say to me,
"you're going to wind up
nothing but a good-for-
nothing troubadour."
That daddy of mine...
i can see him now, the way
he used to look at me,
his face all squinted
up like a persimmon.
He'd stick his finger
right in my...
he'd say, "ebbie... ebbie,
you got nothing inside you
"but soft mush
and sad ballads.
Ain't you ever goin' grow
up and become a man?"
Oh, he was a proud one,
the day i
marched off to war.
He was just as proud
an old rooster.
You know, there was his son
marching off to war
to become a man.
I come back...
back half of me.
But i did come back.
You know that song of yours,
what is it?
What is it?
? black is the color
of my true love's hair?
That the one?
? her lips?
? are something
wondrous fair?
? the truest eyes?
? and the daintiest hands?
? i love...?
Jud, my husband,
he... he used
to sing that song.
Did he now?
Hmm.
I wish you could
have met him.
He was a very
gentle man.
A very nice man.
I can remember nights
why, he'd sit here
on this very porch,
and he'd play and sing.
Even the crickets
would keep quiet.
I bet you
they did, too.
And the bullfrogs
down at the pond-
it was just as if they
had stopped their noise
so they could
hear the music.
Then the yankees came...
like blue locusts they had
to eat away at the trees...
the land...
...and everything on it.
I owe them for much.
For our house...
our land...
our trees...
for everything that was...
including my husband's life.
I owe them for much.
Ma'am...
hmm?
Why don't you go
away from here?
This place is
no good for you.
Why, this place is all i have.
Sergeant?
Yes, ma'am.
What do you suppose
happened to that yankee
who... who killed my husband?
Do you suppose he's marching
home to his own kin now?
Do you suppose
he's laughing and singing
and telling all his neighborhood
about the rebels he's killed?
All the bullets and all
the heads he shot them through?
No, ma'am,
i don't reckon anything
like that at all.
And you let that kind
of poison set on your mind,
you'll die from it, ma'am.
I got a gun inside.
A gun?
Uh-huh.
It's an old shotgun.
And i keep thinking
about how someday-
some moment- a yankee
is going to come by here,
and i'm going to
take out that gun,
and i'm going
to aim it at him.
I'm going to
aim it at him,
but first i'm
going to tell him
that he can
consider this
the last shot
of the civil war;
a bullet in exchange
for the one my husband took.
No, ma'am, i don't want
to hear no more talk
about butchery and bloodshed.
There's hundreds and thousands
of our men and boys
that were killed and maimed.
And then mr. Lincoln...
murdered.
No, i don't want to hear
no more about...
who's that?
Hello?
Yes.
I wonder if you
could tell me
if there's any
water around here?
There's some water
out here in the well.
I'm sure the lady
of the house
wouldn't mind if you
had some, lieutenant.
You...
you traveling far?
Just up the road.
But i've been
on it a long time.
You, too?
Yes...
yes, a long time.
Oh... still, it seems
to me that i know you.
We met somewhere, huh?
That's possible.
I don't know what it is
but i'm trying to remember.
Go on,
what is it that you remember?
I got it.
I got it, i was laying
on the side of the road,
a shell had just exploded,
tore off half my foot.
You came by
with a patrol of yankees,
and you stopped there
on the side of the road,
and you bent over
and you took care of me.
You stopped the bleeding.
Don't you remember that,
lieutenant?
Yes, i remember that.
Sure, of course you do!
I'd like you to meet
the lady of the house.
Ma'am, this is... ma'am!
You best pay heed to
the sergeant's gratitude
because it's the last
gift you'll ever get
this i promise you.
Let me have
that gun, ma'am.
This your pleasure, ma'am?
And duty.
A little of both perhaps.
Then you'd best get on with it.
Ma'am, lieutenant here
tried to save my life.
You've thanked him.
Now if you'll
step aside
so i can thank him
for a few other services...
i... i couldn't have missed you.
I couldn't have
missed you.
It doesn't make
any difference
whether you did or
whether you didn't.
Wait a minute...
wait a minute,
now it's coming...
now, i got- i remember they
got you that day, lieutenant.
You were tending me
and this shell exploded
in the trees over our head
and this hot steel went
spraying all over the place.
I remember you standing up
and clawing at your eyes
and screaming, "i'm blind!"
I remember thinking
they killed you.
I remember... thinking
that you were dead.
That doesn't make
any difference now either.
That water
from the well...
certainly, lieutenant.
I wish you the best, ma'am.
I do wish you
the best.
And you, sir.
Thank you.
And this, too,
shall pass.
This, too,
Wait and see.
Miss godwin?
Good morning, sergeant.
Morning, ma'am.
You come down for a mintue?
Mm-hmm.
You're leaving?
Yes, ma'am, i'm leaving.
I come to say good-bye
and to thank you.
I got to get back on the road,
to wherever the road leads.
Well, i can tell you
where that road leads.
It leads past 50 miles
of places like this,
burned-out houses and...
yes, ma'am, but...
you see, mrs. Godwin,
i was up most of the night
and i was thinking
about a lot of things.
I was thinking about
that blind lieutenant
and your young friend,
charlie constable,
with the blood
on his hat,
and... and then sometime during
the night they stopped coming,
and it got quiet on the road
there, it got real quiet.
And in that quiet just before
dawn, it come to me...
what did?
I don't know just how
to explain it to you, ma'am,
but it's got to do
with that road
and those men
moving down.
There was union soldiers,
too, ma'am.
Some of them helping my boys,
some of my boys helping them
but all of them, all of them
moving down that road together
just as if...
just as if what?
I don't know, ma'am.
But there's something down
the end of that road,
and i got to find out
what it is.
So, i'll just take
my leave, ma'am,
and i wish you well.
Sergeant, sergeant,
i'd be alone.
Please don't go,
stay here.
No, ma'am.
There's nothing here that
could ever belong to me.
What do you think you'll find
at the end of that road?
A future? A new south, perhaps?
A new confederacy
born out of the ashes?
Please...
? black is the color
of my true love's hair...?
Jud!
How fares
my wife?
Oh, jud, please...
please, oh...
i've been ill, jud.
I've been very ill.
But i'll be all right,
now you've come home.
This was home,
lavinia.
It isn't any longer.
We can rebuild it all.
We can paint
and we can plow the fields,
and we can buy seed...
what's the matter, jud?
Sergeant?
Captain.
You know.
I think i do.
I'm not sure,
but i think i do.
Mrs. Godwin,
i have no doubt...
no doubt at all
i'll be seeing
you again in time
at the end
of that road.
Jud, what's happened?
Your life, lavinia-
well, it's kind
of like a song.
You play it
right to the end,
and when the notes
are finished,
and they die out,
there's only silence.
And that's
when you move on.
Jud?
Are we...
are we dead?
Yes, like all those
men on the road.
Mine came at yellow
tavern with a bullet,
and yours came
here with a fever.
No, jud, no.
I am alive!
And i don't want
to leave here
because if i do,
it means that i've
given up everything.
But there's nothing
to give up.
Jud, don't leave me.
I'm not leaving
you, my darling.
I'll wait for you.
I'll meet you at
the end of the road.
Oh, jud.
I'll wait for you.
Jud, come back to me!
Jud, come back!
Jud...
you're staying
behind, my dear?
Maybe... maybe
it's not so wise.
I'm afraid.
Of course you are.
And i am, too.
"Of all the wonders
that i yet have heard
"it seems to me
most strange
"that men should
fear;
"seeing that death,
a necessary end,
will come
when it'll come."
That's from shakespeare,
julius caesar.
You see, my dear,
i'm dead, too.
I guess you might say
i'm the last casualty
of the civil war.
No.
And i'm the last
man on this road.
No.
Jud!
Incident on a dirt road
during the month of april,
the year 1865.
As we've already pointed out,
it's a road
that won't be found on a map,
but it's one of many that lead
in and out of the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week
we engage in a game of pool
that's both an activity
and a title.
A play written
by george clayton johnson
and starring mr. Jack klugman
and mr. Jonathan winters.
It's the story about
the best pool player living
and the best pool player dead.
And this one, we submit, will
stay with you for quite a while.
Next week onthe twilight zone,
"a game of pool."
You have no answer for her
except "yes."
To help many people
in many ways,
give the united way.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org