Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Mother, i'm having a baby,
and i'd rather do it myself.
We'll have to operate at once.
Scalpel... suture...
watch it, nurse!
Great dinner.
Glad you like it.
Tastes like
corrugated plastic.
Keep being late.
What do you expect?
I don't expect nothing.
I'm just getting sick
of it.
You're getting
sick of it?
How do you
think i feel?
I don't get a
man coming home.
I get a used article
from the cab.
Hey, cut it down
to a roar, will you?
Remember, we got company.
Anyway, i told you-
guy hails me when
i'm heading for the garage.
Have to haul him
all the way up to...
to... to yonkers.
I've heard that
one before.
One day yonkers,
one day la
guardia airport.
You don't fool me, joe.
Who's the chick?
Ah, you're crazy.
Mother...
hey, how long
is that guy going to be?
I got wrestling
coming on.
Big tag team match-
fat louie
and the russian duke
versus the panther man
and sweeney.
You can't look me
in the eye anymore,
you're so guilty.
But don't jump
out a window, joe.
One of these days,
i'll even up
the score.
It'll be a real
tight ball game.
That good-looking
freddy broome, the butcher,
is always looking me over.
You'd think i
was cleopatra.
Ah, shut up.
What are you trying to do,
start a fight?
Once that joker in there
gets done fiddling,
i'm going to watch
wrestling
and then flake out.
I'm pooped.
I'll bet you are.
You drove to yonkers,
maybe even went twice.
You shouldn't
drive so much, joe.
You'll ruin
your health!
How's it coming, mike?
Who knows?
It may live.
You've been at it
an hour now.
I could build a new set
in half the time.
Oh? Is that so?
Sure, and you better get wise.
I didn't just step
off the ferry from jersey.
I know how you guys operate.
Do you?
Naturally.
First you kill
a five-buck hour,
then you say
you got to take the set
down to the shop-
another 20 bucks.
Then you start switching tubes
around at $2.50 a crack.
I get some poor sucker's
old ones, and he gets mine.
It's a racket-
that's what it is.
A penny-ante cosa nostra.
So save yourself
a headache, see.
I ain't swinging
for no big bills.
In that case...
the set's ready.
What?
It's... it's ready.
And this time,
it's on me.
Free.
Hey, wait
a minute!
Well... you can't win them all.
Your wife, your wife!
That's all
i ever hear!
Hey, phyllis, come on in.
What do you know?
We can get channel 10.
If you were any
kind of a man,
you'd get
rid of her.
Phyllis, hurry up, will you?
Channel 10!
I trusted you.
I didn't hold
anything back!
I waited!
Aw, come on, don't cry.
Do anything, but
don't cry, will you?
Portrait of a tv fan.
Joe britt.
Cab driver.
Tonight mr. Britt is going
to watch "a really big show"-
something special for the cabby
who's seen everything.
Joe britt doesn't know it,
but his flag is down
and his meter's running,
and he's in high gear-
on his way to the twilight zone.
Marry me.
Marry you?
Oh, now, look, baby,
we're talking about
two different things.
Love is flowers and
wine with the dinner.
Marriage is a floor mop
and two pounds
of hamburger.
Oh, well,
i don't mind hamburger.
Uh, with onions.
What's the matter, joe?
You struck dumb
or something?
You big slob!
You spilled the beer.
It's a good thing
your mother gave us this rug.
I hate it, and anything,
even beer stains,
is an improvement.
Now quit clowning.
You say we can get
channel 10?
Leave it alone.
What's the matter?
Oh, come on, joe,
i got dishes to do.
I said leave it alone!
What's the matter with you?
You nuts or something?
You yell at me
to come watch channel 10,
and when
i drop everything, you...
what's the matter, joe?
Is the set still on the blink?
Yes! That is, no!
There must be
something screwy.
You know there's no channel 10
around here.
I'm sorry i yelled at you.
I must be traffic happy
or something.
I'll turn on the wrestling.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
for the main event of the
evening, we bring you a rematch
between those two titans
of wrestling-
those fearless performers
of the physical arts-
the wild panther
and the russian duke!
What happened to the tag team-
fat louie and sweeney?
Great dinner.
Glad you like it.
Tastes like
corrugated plastic.
Keep being late.
What do you expect?
I don't expect nothing.
I'm just getting sick
of it.
You're getting
sick of it?
How do you
think i feel?
I don't get a
man coming home.
I get a used article
from the cab.
Hey, cut it down
to a roar, will you?
Remember,
we got company.
Anyway, i told you-
guy hails me when
i'm heading for the garage.
Have to haul him
all the way up
to... to... to yonkers.
I've heard that
one before.
One day yonkers, one
day la guardia airport.
Joe?
Joe!
Joe, wake up.
What's the matter?
Are you okay now?
What?
What happened?
Well, i don't know.
You probably fainted.
Feel better?
Yeah.
Sure.
Must have been
something i ate.
Yeah, it could be.
Didn't it taste like
corrugated plastic?
Well, what did
you expect?
I had to heat
it three times.
Listen, joe,
maybe it's your heart.
Why don't you go to bed,
and i'll call a doctor?
No, there's just
something mighty screwy
with that television.
Are we off on that again?
Listen, phyllis...
are you sure you never saw
that repair guy before?
Now iamgoing to call a doctor.
Now, now, wait a
minute, wait a minute.
Phyllis...
what would you say
if i told you that...
that i saw myself on tv?
Huh! Were you smiling?
And what would you say
if i told you i saw you on tv?
You're cracked.
You're losing your marbles.
That's what i
figured you'd say.
Okay, forget it.
You're a
stupid cow.
A bird brain!
Or else you're up to something.
Joe, baby...
"joe, baby."
Never mind that
"joe, baby" stuff.
I'm on to you.
You're trying
to trap me!
Well, you'll have to
get up mighty early
in the morning, see?
Youaresick.
Now, listen...
you go back
into the kitchen,
look up that repair guy
in the phone book.
Tell him to come back here,
you understand?!
All right, joe.
Because if he don't,
so help me,
i'll go down to his shop,
wherever it is,
and drag him here!
Who do you two think
you're fooling with?
Okay, okay, i'll
call him right away!
Meanwhile, you
get in bed.
Hello, dr. Saltman,
this is mrs. Britt.
Could you come
right over, please?
Ha! Ha!
I'll kill you!
Now turn on
the tv, joe!
You, you...!
Come on! Come on!
Give it up!
You, you... you call
yourself a wife?!
You dirty...!
Well, you will, huh?
Going to kill me,
are you?
I'll kill you!
Let me go!
Phyllis...
phyllis!
What have i done?
Phyllis...
phyllis!
Now what's the
matter, joe?
Joe, what's the matter?
What's the matter?
Can't you hear?
Can't you see?
Look!
Oh, god...
it's a trick!
Well, i've given him a sedative
and i'll write
a prescription
for some tranquilizers.
And we'll just have
to wait and see.
Perhaps it would be wise
for you to seek
more expert advice.
I'm only a family doctor,
you know,
and psychiatry
is not my specialty.
However, i feel that
your husband's condition
could be
relatively simple.
I read an interesting paper
on research
that might apply
to your husband's condition.
What condition,
doctor?
Well, according
to this article,
it's possible for anyone
to have delusions
directly attributable
to our overmechanized culture.
Really?
Mm. Now, you say
he's a tv addict.
Well, perhaps
he's been staring
at this electronic blessing,
the television set,
for so long that its life
has become his.
Yeah?
And he's reached
such a stage of confusion
that he no longer knows
whether he's watching
the action
or participating in it.
Now, mind you,
this is not an illness
affecting only the juvenile
or moronic.
I, on occasion,
have found myself asking
for sutures and sponges
during operations performed
by television surgeons.
Oh?
Uh, but never mind.
In mr. Britt's case,
i rather feel
he thinks
he has murdered you.
What?
Or rather,
that he will.
He seems to be
quite bewildered
regarding the past,
present and future.
Well, in any case,
it could be serious,
so would you have him
in my office
first thing
in the morning, hmm?
All right, doctor.
And see that he gets
a good night's rest tonight.
Good night.
Good night, doctor.
Now, you folks out there
in tv land,
you know old country boy's
not joshing you
when he tells you
that this sale
ain't gonna be going on
much longer.
'Cause fast as we move 'em in
now, we're gonna herd 'em out.
We buy by the herd,
and we sells 'em by the herd.
Oh, for you folks uptown,
that's called volume buying.
Well, now, shucks,
about all a country boy can do
with a buck or two
he makes on a sale
is to keep the lights on,
pay the ranch hands.
Now, you know that old country
boy shoots straight with you.
I mean, he tells you right now
if any of his beauties
come up late.
Will you take this little philly
right here?
Hot dog, this one...
phyllis.
The doctor wants you
to go to sleep.
That's why he gave you
a sedative.
I can't sleep.
You wouldn't be
able to, either,
if you'd seen
what i did.
Well, stay awake.
Only, what you saw-
i don't want
to hear about it.
He told you?
Yes. He said
not to worry.
He said... he said
for you to just go to sleep
and everything
would be fine.
Is there anything
i can get you?
No, no, that's okay.
Phyllis...
yes?
I got to talk
to you. Sit down.
Oh, no, you don't.
Every time you start that,
we wind up having a fight,
and if you don't mind,
tonight i'm passing.
I'll make sure there's no fight.
Don't you worry about that.
Anyway, i got nothing
to fight with you about.
If anyone is to blame for us
not getting along, it's me.
Now, come on, sit down.
Oh, youaresick.
You're not well, joe.
If you were in
your right noodle,
you wouldn't talk
like that.
No, i mean it.
Come on, i mean it.
Come on, sit
down, honey.
Look, phyllis...
you know, driving a cab
is pretty lonely work.
You're all by yourself
for hours and hours,
and in between times,
people are
yelling at you
to slow down, go ahead,
to take madison avenue,
to not take
madison avenue,
to turn right,
left, stop.
And on top of it,
everybody says
you're crooked.
So... when somebody comes along
and smiles at you
and calls you "mister,"
well, maybe you go all to pieces
and start to think
the moon and the stars
are your private property
and that it's spring.
Well, you act like
a first-class donkey,
kicking up
your heels
like you were
17 or 18.
Get what i mean?
No.
Well...
there ain't no point
in drawing you pictures.
What i was trying to tell you
is that, well, you know-
seeing you dead like that,
it was an awful shock
and it made me realize that...
well, you know what
i'm trying to say.
No. Say it.
Okay, i will.
It took a shock like that
to make me realize that...
that you are not...
well...
it's you i'm in love with.
I'm touched.
All right.
I'm really touched!
All right, don't get nasty.
What am i supposed to do,
get all dewy and gooey?
Am i supposed to fall
all over myself
because my husband of 27 years
finally decides he loves me?
I didn't mean
it that way.
After chasing
half the bronx
and the entire borough
of manhattan,
you pin the blue ribbon on me,
which means i win
a used nitwit
to feed, to pamper,
to keep and obey
till death do part!
Take it easy, phyllis.
I'll take it easy.
I'd take
a butcher knife to you
if you weren't in bed
and out of your right mind.
Who's out of his right mind?
You are!
If you think i'm going to take
your dirty doings lying down...
so some guy hailed you
on the way to the garage
and asked you
to take him to yonkers.
No wonder we've been short
of money for the last month!
You've been blowing it all
on that flea-bitten floozy!
Get out of here!
You bet i will!
If you think i'm going
to live with a man
that's done what you've done...
giving you
the best years of my life...
i trusted you!
Well, mr. Britt,
i'm going to take you to court-
you and that fancy woman
of yours,
whoever she is!
Go ahead, if that's
what you want!
That's the
thanks i get
for wanting
to be honest.
That's the thanks i get
for wanting to turn over
a new leaf.
Kill me- i'd like
to see him try it.
I'll tear him limb from limb,
the dirty, rotten cheat.
I don't know
what i ever saw in her.
She ain't got no understanding.
She wouldn't know sympathy
if it hopped up
and bit her on the backside.
Your honor,
the prosecution objects
to these interruptions
by the defense.
They've had their chance
to refute
the testimony
of our expert witness,
and all they did was to put
dr. Saltman on the stand.
Now, even he testified
that in his opinion,
the accused was sane
when he committed the murder.
So in this summation, when i
demand the penalty of death...
phyllis!
I'll "phyllis" you!
Phyllis!
What are you trying
to do, drive me bugs?
How can you stand there
listening to this?
Joseph britt, you
have been found guilty
by a jury of your peers.
It is the judgment
of this court
that you be taken to the
sing sing state prison
and there be
kept in custody
and put to death
in a manner
provided by the law.
How can you just stand there?
You must be bugs!
What you see is
in your mind, joe,
and what you hear
is your conscience.
There, take a good look!
Turn it off.
Why? It's just another
program like wrestling.
Let's watch it together.
I haven't had a
good laugh all day.
Get out of my way,
phyllis!
Ooh, i'm so frightened.
You scare me to death.
Oh, my, my, how rough you are.
Tell me what
you see, joe.
What did you see, joe-
lady wrestlers?
What do you see, joe-
a burlesque show?
Fan dancers from yonkers?
Yonkers?
Fan dancers?
Did you see
them, joe?
Yonkers, yonkers, yonkers!
Fan dancers!
Fan dance!
I'll kill you!
Ha! Ha!
Now turn on
the tv, joe!
Give me...
oh...
you...
come on, come on,
give me that!
You... you...
you call yourself a wife?
Oh, you dirty...!
Get off of me!
Well, you will, huh?
Going to kill me,
are you?
I'll kill you.
Phyllis...
phyllis!
What have i done?
Oh...
i didn't really mean it.
I killed her.
Oh...
fix your set okay, mister?
Youwillrecommend
my service, won't you?
The next time your tv set
is on the blink,
when you're in the need
of a first-rate repairman,
may we suggest
our own specialist?
Factory-trained, prompt,
honest, 24-hour service.
You won't find him
in the phone book,
but his office
is conveniently located-
in the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next ontwilight zone,
we move into new orleans
for the mardi gras,
and we do it with a vengeance.
Robert keith and milton selzer
appear in a bizarre story
of men, masquerades and masks.
This is a small shocker
to wind up your week,
and if it doesn't send you
to a psychiatrist,
it'll send you
at least to a mirror.
Ontwlight zonenext,
"the masks."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org