Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Tonight's story onthe twilight
zoneis somewhat unique
and calls for a different kind
of introduction.
This, as you may recognize,
is a map of the united states
and there's a little town there
called peaksville.
On a given morning
not too long ago
the rest of the world
disappeared
and peaksville
was left all alone.
Its inhabitants were never sure
whether the world was destroyed
and only peaksville
left untouched,
or whether the village
had somehow been taken away.
They were, on the other hand,
sure of one thing- the cause.
A monster had arrived
in the village.
Just by using his mind,
he took away the automobiles,
the electricity, the machines,
because they displeased him.
And he moved
an entire community
back into the dark ages
just by using his mind.
Now i'd like to introduce you
to some of the people
in peaksville, ohio.
This is mr. Fremont.
It's in his farmhouse
that the monster resides.
This is mrs. Fremont.
And this is aunt amy,
who probably had more control
over the monster in the
beginning than almost anyone.
But one day she forgot.
She began to sing aloud.
Now, the monster
doesn't like singing
so his mind snapped at her,
and turned her
into this smiling, vacant thing
you're looking at now.
She sings no more.
And you'll note
that the people
in peaksville, ohio
have to smile.
They have to think happy
thoughts and say happy things
because once displeased,
the monster can wish them
into a cornfield or change them
into a grotesque,
walking horror.
This particular monster
can read minds, you see.
He knows every thought,
he can feel every emotion.
Oh, yes, i did forget something,
didn't i?
I forgot to introduce you
to the monster.
This is the monster.
His name is anthony fremont.
He's six-years-old
with a cute, little-boy face
and blue, guileless eyes.
But when those eyes look
at you,
you'd better start thinking
happy thoughts
because the mind behind them
is absolutely in charge.
This is the twilight zone.
Howdy, anthony.
Mighty good
to see you today.
Mighty good.
And it's such a
good day, isn't it?
A real good day.
It's a terrible
hot day, though.
hot day.
Oh, i wouldn't
say that, aunt amy.
No, sir, i wouldn't
say that at all.
It's fine. It's just fine.
It's a real good day!
What are you
doing, anthony?
My, that's real good,
whatever it is.
I was just wondering
what you were doing.
I made a gopher
with three heads.
See him?
Yeah.
Yeah, my, he's
a real fine one.
I ain't never seen a gopher
with three heads before.
I'll make him dead now.
I'm tired of playing with him.
Be dead.
Gopher, you be dead!
My, my, that's real fine
that you done that.
That's-that's
real fine, anthony.
You're a good
boy, anthony.
We all love you.
Don't we, aunt amy?
Don't we love anthony?
We sure do love him.
We love that boy.
Howdy, mrs. Fremont.
Howdy, bill.
Got everything?
Pretty much.
Didn't have any
more laundry
soap, though.
All out of laundry soap.
Well, that's
to be expected.
Not even the bar
soap, though, huh?
All out of that, too.
Oh, we've been out
of that for a year.
You know that,
mrs. Fremont.
We ain't had no bar soap
for over a year.
But i... i got
a couple of cans
of tomato soup in here.
Didn't even know
we had them left.
Bill...
and anthony just loves
tomato soup, don't he?
So i brought that.
Oh, bill.
You'll tell him,
won't you, mrs. Fremont?
Tell him i brought
the tomato soup
because i heard he liked it.
Tell himibrought it,
won't you?
Yes, i will, bill.
Course, i will.
Matter of fact, i'll
tell him right now.
Oh, no, you don't have
to do that, mrs. Fremont.
You don't have to go
to that trouble now.
I got to get going.
I got to get back
to the store.
You don't have to be
frightened of him, bill.
He likes you.
He's told me that
several times-
how much he likes you.
Well, that's real nice
to hear, mrs. Fremont.
He's a real clever boy.
You know what he
was doing out there?
Making some kind
of furry animal.
Yesterday he made one...
i never did see
the likes of it.
He invented it
all by himself.
It had real sharp teeth.
It tried to bite him.
I was kind of hoping
that...
i got to get going,
mrs. Fremont.
But i'm real glad
that anthony keeps
making these things.
Oh, see you
tonight, bill.
Tonight?
Tonight is television night.
Anthony's going to
put a nice picture
on television.
And we're going to have the
surprise party for dan hollis.
A real nice surprise party.
Oh, i... i'll be here,
mrs. Fremont.
I'll certainly be here.
Where's anthony?
I think he went
into the barn.
I keep telling him
he shouldn't go there,
but he keeps on...
amy?
It's a real good thing
that anthony goes in the
barn, a real good thing.
But agnes,
he isn't even around...
even so, amy...
you don't have to
keep saying it...
even so, it's nice
that he goes in the
barn, it's real nice.
We mustn't think anything
bad about him, amy.
But he isn't even around.
Amy, dear, you know as well
as i do that sometimes...
sometimes he can hear
what we're thinking,
no matter where he is.
So, you just
keep thinking
real nice things.
And tonight, we'll
have dan hollis'
birthday party,
and, and we'll just
have a-a delightful time,
just a real nice,
delightful time.
But it's a terrible,
hot day.
I... hope it cools off
by tonight.
I wouldn't... say
it was hot, amy.
Why, it's just right.
Why, it's just a...
real good day.
Just a... a real good day.
Well, howdy, anthony.
I was looking for you
a bit ago.
Your mama said you
was out in the barn.
I was looking
at the cow.
Oh, oh, that's good.
That's... real good
that you were looking
at the cow.
Now, uh...
you weren't playing any
tricks on your old dad,
were you?
I mean, remember last year when
you... when we had the pigs?
I turned them into monsters.
Oh, doggone
if you didn't.
Funny looking
things, too.
But good things, anthony,
real good things
and it's good
that you done that.
Oh, it's real good.
Television night
tonight.
I'm going to make
television for everybody.
Oh, you sure are, and
everybody is looking
forward to it, too.
Just like they do
every week when you
make television.
And we're going to have
that surprise birthday party
for dan hollis, too.
Was you looking
for something, anthony?
Could i get you
something, son?
No kids came over to play
with me today.
Not a single one.
And i wanted someone
to play with.
Oh, well, anthony,
you remember the last time
some kids came over to play-
the little fredericks boy
and his sister?
I had a real
good time.
Oh, sure, you did.
You had a real good time,
and it's good
that you have a good time.
It's real good.
It's, uh, just that...
just that what?
Well, anthony, you, uh...
you wished them away
into the cornfield
and their mommy and daddy
were real upset.
About what?
Well, it's just that if you
wish people away like that
there won't be no one left.
Maybe next week we'll talk
to some of the folks
about bringing
their children over.
We'll do that,
won't we?
And i can make
some of those
funny animals, dad.
Yeah, yeah... it's fun,
it's lots of fun to do.
That's bill soames' collie.
That's that dog
that comes around.
Yeah, yeah, that
does sound like
bill soames' dog.
Not many dogs left
now, anthony.
You... why, you wished
them all away.
I don't like them.
They didn't like me.
I hate anybody like that.
I hate anybody
that doesn't like me.
Why, everybody
loves you, anthony.
Theyloveyou, son.
You're everybody's favorite.
I heard somebody think
one time-
i don't remember when,
but sometime-
that i shouldn't wish away
all the automobiles and things
and electricity.
They said that it wasn't good
that i did that.
Somebody thought that one time.
Who? Who thought that?
Oh, why,
that was, uh...
teddy reynolds who thought that.
He owned the farm
up the road.
He shouldn't have thought
those bad thoughts!
That's why i made him
go on fire.
That dog.
That collie dog.
He doesn't like me.
He's abaddog.
Anthony?
Did you do something
to bill soames' dog?
Did you, son?
I put him in the cornfield.
He isn't outside anymore.
Bill soames' collie was
out in the yard.
Why, anthony put him
in the cornfield.
Isn't it a real good thing
that he done that, honey?
Isn't it a real good thing?
Yes, it was a
real good thing...
that he done that.
It was a real good thing.
That's all the television
there is.
Oh, it was
wonderful, anthony.
Wasn't it,
everyone?
Oh, that was
real good.
That was real good.
Wasn't anthony's television
wonderful tonight?
Oh, it was
just the best.
It was much better than
the old television.
Much better.
And now, the
big surprise
for dan's
birthday.
Go ahead, ethel.
Give your
hubby the
big surprise.
What's this?
Oh, perry como!
Why, i haven't
heard perry como
in years and years.
Happy birthday,
darling.
Happy birthday.
Hey... you better
be careful.
I'm holding a
priceless object.
Look, do you think
we could play it?
Gosh, what i'd give to hear
some new music.
Well, just
the first part-
the orchestra part
before como
sings.
I don't think we'd better, dan.
After all, we don't know
just where the singing comes in.
It'd be taking
too much of a chance.
Better wait till
you get home.
It's good i can't
play it here.
Oh, yes,
it's good.
It's very good.
Uh, and now it's
time for pat riley
to play the piano.
Uh... pat?
My pleasure.
It would be good
if you told me
what to play,
anthony.
It would be real good
if you'd tell me
what music you'd
like to hear.
Just play-
play anything.
All right.
All right,
i'll play, uh...
i'll play
"moonglow."
That's a nice
old tune.
Oh, that's
a nice tune.
Oh, yes, that's
a very good tune.
Don't make any noise
when the music's playing.
I don't like any noise
Dan...
dan, please.
Please what?
I'm not doing anything.
I'm just drinking
this peach brandy.
one of my birthday presents,
that's all i'm doing.
Dan, please, for
the love of heaven
please don't
say anything.
Who's saying
anything?
I'm not saying
anything.
anything at all!
Go ahead,
pat, play.
Go on, keep
playing.
You know, this is
real good brandy.
Real good.
You folks know something?
There's only five bottles
of real whiskey left
in the whole village.
Only five bottles.
There's one rye...
two scotch,
one after-dinner
liqueur and...
and this here.
When that's all gone...
there won't be any...
any whiskey left at all.
None at all.
No whiskey at all.
Nuts! I can't even
play my own record.
I can't even play perry como!
Don't play that, pat.
That's not what
i want you to play.
Play this-
? happy birthday to me?
? happy birthday?
? to me...?
Dan!
? happy
birthday?
? dear danny?
Please stop!
Be quiet.
? happy birthday to me.?
Play it, pat.
Play it so i
can sing right.
You know i can't
carry a tune
unless somebody
plays it.
You...
you and her, you had him.
You had to
go have him.
? you are my sunshine?
? my only
sunshine?
? you make
me happy?
? when i
am blue...?
You monster,
you.
You dirty little
monster.
You murderer.
You think about me.
Go ahead, anthony.
You think
bad thoughts
about me...
and maybe some man
in this room...
some man with guts...
somebody who's
so sick to death
of living in this
kind of place
and willing to
take a chance
will sneak up
behind you
and lay
something heavy
across your skull
and end this once and for all!
You're a bad man!
You're a very bad man!
You think that.
Go ahead, anthony,
i'm a very bad man.
Keep thinking
that.
Somebody sneak
up behind him.
Somebody end
this now!
While he's thinking
about me!
Won't somebody
take a lamp or a bottle
or something and end this?
You're a bad man.
You're a very bad man,
and you keep thinking
bad thoughts
about me.
Wish it into
the cornfield.
Please, son, wish it into
the cornfield, please.
He was a bad man
so i turned him into
a jack-in-the-box,
a jack-in-the-box that
still had his bad face.
And you mustn't think bad
thoughts about me, either,
or i'll do the same
thing to you.
Play some
more music.
It's good what
you done to dan.
It's real good.
That was swell.
It was just swell.
That was...
really good.
I kind of liked it
a little bit better
when we had cities
outside and...
and we could get
real television...
things like that.
Amy, it's...
it's real good
for you to say
such a thing.
It's real good.
But how can
you mean it?
Why, anthony's
television is
much better
than anything we
ever used to get.
Oh, yes,
it's fine.
Why, anthony's
television
is the best television
we've ever seen.
It's snowing
outside.
Anthony, are...
are you making it snow?
Yes, i'm making
it snow.
Why, that will
ruin half the crops!
You know that,
don't you?
Half the crops,
that's what that'll...
dad...
but it's good that you're
making it snow, anthony.
It's real good.
And tomorrow...
tomorrow is
going to be
a real good day.
No comment here,
no comment at all.
We only wanted to introduce you
to one of our very
special citizens-
little anthony fremont,
age six,
who lives in a village
called peaksville,
in a place
that used to be ohio.
And if by some strange chance
you should run across him
you had best think
only good thoughts.
Anything less than that
is handled at your own risk.
Because if you do meet anthony
you can be sure of one thing-
you have entered
the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you about next week's
story after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
This is the lobby of an inn
in a small bavarian town,
and next week, we'll enter it
with a former s.s. Officer.
It's the first stop
on his road back
to relive a horror
that was nazi germany.
Mr. Joseph schildkraut
and mr. Oscar beregi demonstrate
what happens to the monster
when it is judged by the victim.
Our feeling here
is that this is
as stark and moving a piece of
drama as we've ever presented.
I very much hope
that you're around
to make your own judgment.
Faith is for those
who look for it,
who try each day
to know it better.
Worship together every week
at your church or synagogue.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org