Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
So...
"the undersigned,
"having accepted
the following propositions:
"A, that prior
to the inception of language,
"man communicated
by telepathic means;
"and b, that this ability
not only still exists
"but can be redeveloped
to its former effectiveness;
"do hereby agree
to the following precepts.
"One, that we shall
henceforth dedicate
"our professional
and private lives
"to the study of
mental telepathy
"and whatever
extrasensory functions
"may be supplemental
to it.
"Two, that the findings
of the study shall be applied
"not only to ourselves,
but to all our children.
"Three, that
each family unit
"shall reside
in a location
"calculated
to prevent
"the interference
of society.
"Four, that monthly
correspondence
"shall be exchanged
"until such time as
they will establish
"a joint colony
"in which communication
of every sort
shall be exclusively mental."
There are sure to be
other details, of course,
but for now, this should suffice
to get us started.
Comments?
More than sufficient,
i think.
Most specific.
Karl?
It is what
we agreed upon.
That sounds very much
like disapproval.
No, no, no.
Not at all.
I will be pleased
to sign.
You are certain now?
This should not
be entered into
unless with
absolute assurance.
He is assured, holger.
His apparent
uncertainty
is only...
a sympathetic
reflection
of my own.
You are still uncertain?
Not in the general concept,
holger.
I agree with it, believe in it.
It is yet that i wonder,
do we have the right to impose
this study on our children,
even those unborn?
You speak as if we plan
to harm our children.
Isn't it rather that we hope
to bestow upon them
a gift beyond price?
Of course that is
our hope, but...
we offer them no choice
in the matter.
Is that just?
I too am a mother, maria,
devoted to the welfare
of my child,
yet i am convinced it is just.
It is more than just.
It's inevitable.
Destiny demands it.
Did you and
holger decide
definitely not to
stay in europe?
Yes.
There's a house
in pennsylvania
which was left to
holger by an uncle.
We plan to
live in it.
Oh, excellent.
What town is this?
German corners.
What you're witnessing
is the curtain-raiser
to a most extraordinary play:
To wit the signing of a pact,
the commencement of a project.
The play itself
will be performed
almost entirely offstage.
The final scenes
are to be enacted a decade hence
and with a different cast.
The main character
of these final scenes is ilse,
the daughter of professor
and mrs. Nielsen, age two.
At the moment,
she lies sleeping in her crib,
unaware of the singular drama
in which she is to be involved.
Ten years from this moment,
ilse nielsen is to know
the desolating terror
of living simultaneously
in the world
and in the twilight zone.
Yeah?
Sheriff wheeler?
Yeah.
This is tom poulter.
The nielsen house is burning.
What?
There's a fire
at the nielsen house.
Big fire- hurry.
Right.
What is it?
Fire at the nielsen house.
Did it just start?
I hope so. If it didn't...
max, it's harry.
There's a fire
at the nielsen house.
Call the volunteers.
Get the truck out.
I'll be there
in 10 or 15 minutes.
Got it?
I told them
when they first came here
they shouldn't live
so far out of town,
but they wanted
their privacy.
That girl...
that lovely girl...
we'll never put that out.
Never mind the house.
Keep the woods from catching.
Come on, let's check out back.
They're done for.
Poor kid.
Harry, over here, quick!
Do you think she's...
is she burned?
She's alive.
Are you all right?
She's in shock, harry.
Get a blanket on her.
Bad off.
Can't talk, can't cry,
can't do nothing.
She's not burned, though.
How could she get out
without being burned?
I don't know.
Is she hurt?
Not physically.
I think she's in shock.
We'd better get her to bed.
We'll have to use sally's...
the other bedroom, cora.
All right.
Cora.
Oh, i'm sorry.
She's beautiful.
She looks just
like sally.
Doesn't she?
You want
something to eat?
No, i haven't got time.
Thought i'd take some coffee
to the boys.
Are her parents...?
No way of knowing.
Can't get close
to the house yet.
It's burning too hard.
Well, how...?
Tom poulter found her outside.
Outside?
We don't know how she got there.
I expect her parents
are dead, though.
It's an awful fire.
Poor child.
There's something wrong
with her.
I know she's not deaf or dumb
or retarded or anything.
Before she fell asleep,
i tried to get her to talk.
She didn't say a word.
Not a word.
Even in shock,
the powers of speech
aren't completely gone.
It's as though she doesn't know
how to talk.
Be careful.
Mother?
Mother!
Where are you, mother?
Are you near me, father?
Mother!
Father!
Where are you?
No... no!
They're dead!
Ilse!
Ilse, what is it?
I'm not going to hurt you, ilse.
What's the matter, darling?
They're dead.
They're dead!
They're dead! They're dead!
And there's no way of getting
in touch with her relatives?
Everything burned.
Tom poulter said
the nielsens get
three letters from europe
the end of each month.
Maybe they're
from relatives.
We can wait till
the next batch arrives
and write
to the three addresses.
What'll we do with
the girl until then?
Well, we'll have
to keep her here.
Only be for a week
or so, cora.
Unless the girl
can tell us something.
Nope.
You don't think
she can talk, either?
I tried everything i
could to get her to.
That explains it.
What?
The times
miss frank and i tried
to talk the nielsens
into putting the girl in school,
the answer
was always no.
Maybe there's something
physically wrong with her.
Well, we'll have doc steiger
check her over.
I don't think
he'll find anything.
I just can't understand it.
They were educated people.
They didn't even teach
their own daughter how to talk.
They were strange people,
too, cora.
They hardly ever spoke
themselves.
We should put the girl in school
while we're waiting
for those letters-
teach her
how to talk, anyway.
Well, not right away.
She has to start sooner
or later, doesn't she?
Harry, she just lost
her parents.
I didn't mean tomorrow
or the next day.
You know,
it's a crime,
a girl that age
not being educated,
not even knowing
how to talk.
Her father
a professor, too-
keeping his own child
in ignorance.
Well, something's
got to be done.
Somebody's got to undo
what her parents
did to her.
I'm not surprised-
their decision
to live out of town.
Why wouldn't they teach her
how to talk?
And there's no reason
why she can't talk.
I don't understand it.
He says he just can't
understand it.
There's nothing wrong
with her.
He... he checked
everything.
What is it, ilse?
You can tell us,
darling.
Nobody's going
to be angry with you.
Don't be afraid
of us, ilse.
of us.
Cora, leave her alone!
Well, i can't
just ignore her.
She's been here
over a week now.
What's the use?
There's just no way
of getting
through to her.
Well, i have
to keep on trying.
Ilse.
Didn't they ever talk to you?
I wish i could
make you understand.
She was swimming
in the lake...
it's... it's almost
as if you understand.
Bye, hon.
Bye-bye.
See you at lunch.
Hello?
Yes, he is.
Harry.
Yeah?
Yeah, tom.
All right,
i'll be right over.
The letters from
europe are in.
I'll see you in
a little while.
Now they'll come and get me...
take me to the other children
who are the way i am.
Did you get them?
What?
The letters.
Tom poulter couldn't
let me have them.
It's against the law.
He's got to send them back.
All he could do was let me copy
off the return addresses.
I'm going to write to them now.
It's all right, ilse.
You run along now.
Suppose you have
to write them.
What do you mean?
Thanks.
Nothing.
Wha... what are you saying
to them?
About the fire,
the nielsens dying,
asking them
if they're related to the girl
or know where
any of her relatives are.
Well...
what if her relatives
aren't any better for her
than her parents were?
What are you talking about?
It's my duty
to find her relatives.
Who they are or what they are
is none of my business.
The welfare of a child
is everybody's business!
We are not in a
position to decide.
We're in a position
just to send her away,
just get rid of her.
Then maybe she
won't ever talk.
Maybe she'll go
through life
just being afraid
of shadows!
Cora... i understand.
Sally gone and another child
in the house...
but she's not our child, cora.
We have no rights
where she's concerned.
There's something wrong
with her.
Our job is
to make every effort...
is that why you want
to get rid of her?
I don't have to answer that,
do i, cora?
Now they'll come and get me.
Ilse!
They'll never find me now.
Never! Never!
Oh, please, help me!
I'm here, ilse nielsen!
Help me, please!
Leave her alone.
Leave her alone!
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
Now, who could
that be?
Probably miss frank.
Well, aren't you going
to let her in?
Yes, cora,
i asked her to come.
Hello, miss frank.
Mrs. Wheeler.
Won't you come in?
Thank you.
Afternoon,
miss frank.
Glad you could come.
I thought it was my duty.
Don't put me in school, please.
Won't you sit down?
Cora!
As i told you
a few days ago,
i've written
to these people in europe
four or five weeks ago.
We just haven't had
any answer.
We don't know
what we're going to do with her.
While we're deciding,
she ought to start getting
an education.
She most certainly
should.
It was positively
criminal of her parents
not to have started her
education years ago.
The smugness of them.
The insufferable
disdain.
"We do not wish
our daughter to
go to your school."
Just like that.
In many ways,
the fire was a
blessing of her life.
What?
I'm not referring
to her lack
of education,
mrs. Wheeler.
But to call such a hideous thing
a blessing.
I'm sure i didn't mean it
that way, mrs. Wheeler.
The first thing
she must learn
to do, of course,
is talk.
If i may see her now?
I'll get her.
She's a very shy
little girl, miss frank.
She'll... need
understanding.
She shall receive
it, mrs. Wheeler.
Come here, ilse.
Well,
i think we're going
to get along just fine,
you and i.
Don't let her touch me.
Please.
No, not her.
No.
It'll be fun, darling.
Don't be afraid.
Come on.
Good morning,
mrs. Wheeler.
We were just
about to start.
Good morning,
miss frank.
I do hope everything
will be all right.
Ilse's...
don't be afraid.
Now, you just leave her here,
mrs. Wheeler.
She'll feel at home in no time.
Well, i was wondering
if i just couldn't stay
for a little while.
As long as you're here,
she'll be upset.
She can't begin to adjust
until she's alone with us.
Believe me, it's the only way.
All right.
Good-bye, dear.
I'll pick you
up after school.
Don't be afraid.
She's going to be fine,
mrs. Wheeler.
We'll take good care of her.
Right up front,
now, ilse.
Class...
this is ilse nielsen.
We're going
to have to be
very patient with her,
because her parents
never taught her
how to speak.
She doesn't understand
one word of english.
But we're going
to help her learn, aren't we?
Yes.
We are going
to work with her
until she's exactly
like everybody else.
Aren't we, class?
Yes, miss frank.
Now, ilse,
can you say
your name, ilse?
Try to say it.
Your name, child.
Ilse.
Try to say it, child.
Your name.
You'll learn.
"This is a boat.
A boat sails
on the ocean."
Ocean.
"The men who live...
"who live...
and work on the boat
are called sailors."
He's trying to tell about the
boat, but the boat isn't words.
It isn't words.
Why don't they learn
the way father taught me?
You must pay attention, ilse.
If you do not pay attention,
you will never learn.
I said, "get up, ilse."
Up.
Now, we'll try again.
Say your name- ilse.
Your name- ilse.
Ilse nielsen.
Do you understand?
I will help you to understand.
I will say your name for you.
Ilse, ilse.
Class, tell ilse her name.
On the count of three.
One, two, three.
Ilse.
Ilse, ilse, ilse...
don't push, children.
Be careful, be careful.
I want you to know
you're not fooling
me for one moment.
I know exactly
what you are.
I know, because my father tried
to force me
into the same thing
when i was your age,
and after many years
of concentrated effort,
i overcame that sickness
which my father had forced on me
as i am going to help you
overcome it, ilse.
It's true, isn't it?
They've been training you
to be a medium,
trying to distort
your innocent mind
to communicate with the dead.
You've been trained
to be a medium, haven't you?
Haven't you?
No, it isn't true.
That's not what
they were training me for.
You understand me.
You know what i think.
Don't you see, ilse?
You've proven my point.
You've proven it to me.
You are a medium.
No, i'm not. You're wrong.
I'm not a medium.
I was wondering...
mrs. Wheeler.
Oh, ilse,
was it so bad?
No, she's coming along nicely.
Oh, she was
a little timid at first,
but she's learning.
She's most definitely learning.
I'm so glad.
We'll see her
tomorrow morning, then.
Yes.
Good-bye, miss frank.
Come along, dear.
The next day and the next day
and the next day.
Please, sir.
Where could we
find authority?
Authority?
Yes, uh... how
do you say it?
The constable, the...
sheriff.
Oh, yes, yes.
The sheriff.
Turn around.
Bitte?
That building.
Oh.
Danke.
Uh... thank you.
Constable.
I feel so guilty, karl.
What else
could we do?
We simply could not
get away any sooner.
We have our own
responsibility
to the project.
I know,
but almost three months
since we last heard
from holger and fanny.
If they only
hadn't chosen
such a far-removed
location for their work.
They are americans, karl.
We could not have
expected them
to reside in europe.
Do you still think
that something bad
has happened to them?
Why else would
they have failed to write?
I hope you are wrong.
That lovely child.
And such a talent.
Their progress with her
has been phenomenal.
It is almost as if...
as if she wasborntelepathic.
I think that of
all the children,
she had the
most potential.
Yuck.
Hello?
It's me, cora
yes, dear?
Well, what is it, harry?
Harry.
The ones from europe
are here, cora.
Did you hear me?
Yeah.
I'm going to have to
bring them over to the house.
We'll be over in a little while.
If we'd only
heard from you...
but not a word.
You can understand
why we felt free
to start adoption
proceedings.
We understand
completely, sheriff.
However, as i've said,
we received no letters.
Just don't
understand it.
Well...
holger and fanny dead.
I still can't believe it.
How horrible.
Even more horrible,
the thought of ilse exposed
to people who do not understand.
Cora, this is professor werner,
mrs. Werner.
My wife.
Mrs. Wheeler.
How do you do?
Won't you come in?
Thank you.
They say they never received
those letters i wrote to them.
Oh?
That's odd.
Won't you sit down?
Thank you.
She burned those
letters, maria.
Yes, i know.
How terribly she suffers.
Frau werner,
you came a long way.
Yes, we did.
Are we going to tell them
anything about ilse?
Not unless we have to.
May we see ilse?
Well, i'm going to pick her up
at school in a little while.
School?
They should never have sent her
to school.
Ilse?
Ilse nielsen.
Stand up.
Stand up, ilse.
Come forward.
Face the class.
Straighten up.
Shoulders back.
Now, what is your name?
Your name.
What is your name?
Class...
we will do again
what we've been doing
for the past week.
On the count of three,
think ilse's name.
Don't say it aloud.
Ready?
One, two, three.
Ilse, ilse, ilse, ilse,
ilse, ilse, ilse, ilse...
here they come.
Ilse...
this is professor
and frau werner.
Hello, young lady.
Ilse, you must concentrate.
Your father was
in contact with us.
Our children once were
being trained just like you.
They're in germany.
Ilse, you remember
the pakt, elkenbergs-
us, the kalders,
your father and your mother.
Dusseldorf, ten years ago.
The pact, the project
about mental telepathy.
Germany, ten years ago.
The pact... telepathy.
The werners are
from europe, ilse.
They were friends
of your parents.
Ilse- think!
Ilse, where
is your mind?
Your mind, ilse.
Concentrate!
My... name...
is ilse.
My name...
My name is ilse!
Don't cry, baby.
Don't cry.
I'm here,
i'm here.
Don't cry, darling,
i'm with you.
I'm with you.
You can't take
her away from me!
Cora!
No!
I won't let them.
I love her.
And she loves me,
and sheneedsme.
You have no right.
You have no right!
I want to
apologize again
for my wife
and myself.
We thought...
we understand.
Naturally,
you would think
that we have come
to take ilse
back with us.
However, as i've said,
we have no legal power
to demand her...
being no relation.
Good-bye, sheriff.
Good-bye.
Good luck.
Uh...
and thanks again.
Your bus ought
to be along
in five or
ten minutes.
I hope we have made
no mistake
letting them keep her,
even though the nielsens
did give us
the legal right to...
i don't think
so, karl.
To take her
to the other children now
would be terrible for her.
Her facility is gone.
Even with work,
it might not return.
I suppose.
But all those years holger
and fanny spent on her...
wasted.
Wasted?
If they had not made
her mind so receptive,
how could they have led her
out from the burning house,
even though
they were trapped?
But the loss, the loss-
it isn't right.
There is no right or wrong
to it, karl.
They all meant well.
No one wanted anything
but to help her.
But to lose everything?
She has not lost everything.
She has gained something, karl.
Gained?
We always knew
that holger and fanny
did not really care for her.
Maria.
They were not unkind.
They gave her what affection
they had in them to give.
But the project
always came first.
You know that, karl.
For them, ilse was
less a daughter
than she was an
experiment in flesh.
She's going to be all right.
For now, she's loved,
and that is so much more
important than telepathy.
Isn't it?
Yes, liebchen.
Much more important.
It has been noted
in a book of proven wisdom
that perfect love
casteth out fear.
Well, it's unlikely
that this observation
was meant to include
that specific fear
which follows the loss
of extrasensory perception.
The principle remains,
as always, beautifully intact.
That of ilse nielsen,
former resident
of the twilight zone.
Mr. Richard matheson
lets his typewriter
pay us a return visit
next time out ontwilight zone
with a story
called "death ship."
Now this one is
for science fiction aficionados,
ghost story buffs
and any and all
who file away clues
with an eye toward
outguessing the writer.
Next ontwilight zone,
misters jack klugman,
ross martin and fred beir
take an extended trip
through space on a death ship.
Captain.
Something glittered
down there.
What is it?
Something down there?
Mason thinks so.
There was something.
We stay together.
No one takes any risks.
That's an order, mason.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org