Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension,
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
I know it's...
it's an incredible story.
I, of all people, know this,
that you won't believe me
no, not at first.
But i'm going to tell you
the whole thing.
Then you will believe,
because you must.
You must believe!
It happened many years ago,
after the first world war.
I was on a walking trip
through central europe.
But one night i...
one night i got lost in a storm.
Yes? What is it?
Please...
please, let me in.
I'm lost.
I'm sorry, we don't
allow visitors
in the hermitage.
Oh, i'm not
a visitor.
I'm... i'm
a stranger here.
I'm... i'm lost.
No, you don't
understand.
I'm lost.
I'll be all right
once i dry out.
Wait here.
I have to speak
to brother jerome.
Brother jerome
will see you now.
What was that?
The wind.
Come.
Why have you come here?
My... my name is ellington.
I'm on a walking trip,
but got lost in the storm.
Excuse me.
I saw light here.
What do you want from us?
Shelter
and maybe
some food.
We cannot help you.
You will have to leave.
Now, mr. Ellington... now.
The prostrate form
of mr. David ellington-
scholar, seeker of truth, and
regrettably, finder of truth-
a man who will shortly arise
from his exhaustion
to confront a problem
that has tormented mankind
since the beginning of time-
a man who knocked on a door
seeking sanctuary
and found instead the outer
edges of the twilight zone.
Help me!
No, please, in the name
of mercy, help me.
You're not one of them.
No, my name
is ellington.
I'm an american.
Shh!
We have only moments.
Come closer... come.
They're mad,
mr. Ellington...
all of them, raving mad.
Listen, i was in the village
in schwartzwald.
I was walking in the street
with my woman.
We paused to rest by a tree
and we kissed.
Is it wrong to kiss?
Tell me.
I... i don't think so.
Of course you don't.
You don't think so,
i don't think so.
But jerome...
the lecherous old fool.
We looked up... and i saw him
standing close by.
I tried to open
my mouth to speak,
but before i could
utter a sound,
he raised that heavy staff
he carries.
You've seen it?
And he hit me again and again.
Why?
For revenge.
Because she refused
his advances.
He took his fury out on me.
I... i'm sorry, i... i find this
difficult to believe.
Of course you do,
mr. Ellington.
That's the strength
of the man.
He makes his madness
seem a harmless thing.
The... the madness
of a religious zealot.
This is not a religious order,
mr. Ellington.
These so-called
brothers of truth,
they're outcasts, misfits,
cut off from the world
because the world
won't have them.
Mr. Ellington,
please.
You must
believe me.
I don't say they're evil.
I say they're mad.
Where are you going?
I'll speak to jerome.
No! He's the greatest
maniac of them all.
But then how can
i help you?
Mr. Ellington!
I did not know
that you were
well enough to walk.
Come with me,
please.
I must talk
with you.
This way.
I must ask you to leave
the hermitage, mr. Ellington.
We have no facilities
for the care of the ill.
Arrangements can made
at schwartzwald.
Just a minute.
No, not a minute, not another second, mr. Ellington
- now!
Why?
I have already
explained that.
No, you've
explained nothing.
No one asked me to come
here, i realize that,
but that's no excuse
for your behavior.
My son...
i'm not your son.
You don't understand.
That's right, i don't.
So why don't you tell me?
Why are you in such
a hurry for me to leave?
What are you afraid
i'll find out?
It's the man you have
locked up in the cell,
isn't it, brother?
Well, that isn't
a secret anymore.
I know about him.
What man is this,
mr. Ellington?
The one we just left.
The one who's been
screaming his head off.
I'm not sure you know
what you're saying.
Look, brother,
i don't know much
about this cult of yours-
what's permitted,
what isn't permitted-
but i seriously doubt
if you have the authority
to imprison a man
against his will.
That is quite true.
We have
no such authority.
Then why have you done it?
No man has ever
been imprisoned
in the hermitage,
mr. Ellington.
I was just talking
with him.
You talked to no man.
You have been very ill,
mr. Ellington.
You've suffered
delirium.
Oh, now don't tell me
you didn't hear that.
Honest men make
unconvincing liars.
I'll find out
eventually, you know?
What do you mean?
Just what i say.
The police will be
very interested to learn
that you people are keeping
a man in prison here.
I tell you,
there is no man!
All right, just forget it.
Mr. Ellington...
yes?
Would you really
go to the police?
Would you?
Very well.
I have told you
the truth
but only
a part of it.
Now i see i shall
have to tell you
the whole truth.
Shut the door,
mr. Ellington.
Then you do hear it?
As i have heard it
every hour of every day
for five long years.
Why did
you lie?
I didn't.
When i told you that no man
howled at the hermitage,
i was being perfectly honest.
What you saw is not a man.
It is the devil himself.
Yes, the devil himself.
What you saw in the cell
is satan.
Otherwise known
as the dark angel,
ahriman, asmodeus,
belial, diabolus, the devil.
You asked for the truth.
Now you have it.
You do believe me,
don't you?
Uh... sure, of course.
No, now it is you who are
lying, mr. Ellington.
You don't
believe me at all.
Quite to the contrary.
You're now quite certain
of what you suspected-
that i am mad.
Sit down,
mr. Ellington
and we'll see.
Let me tell you a story
and we'll see how certain
you are that i am mad-
how certain you are
of anything.
I suppose you fancy yourself
a sophisticated man.
You consider us to be primitive
because we live
here in solitude,
away from the so-called
"real world."
We are misfits.
No, no...
oh, please.
I know all the theories.
I assure you, brother, that...
no, mr. Ellington.
It is i who am assuring you.
I am not the ignorant fanatic
i would appear.
Oh, i coped with your world
for 40 years...
and rather successfully at that.
The best schools,
a degree in philosophy,
a job that took me
to the ends of the earth.
This beard...
this staff...
and this faith...
are merely the results
of a different point of view.
If you could
understand that,
you could listen
to what i have to say
with an open mind.
Five years ago, there were
no howls in the hermitage.
There was simply
the bombed-out ruin
of an old castle belonging
to the family wolfen.
Baron wolfen gave it
to the brotherhood of truth
as a gesture of charity.
Our job was
to tend the vineyards
and save what souls we could
by constant prayer.
But this isn't a religious
order, is it, brother?
We feel that we are
recognized by god.
Truth is
our dogma.
We believe it to be
man's greatest weapon
against the devil,
who is the father of all lies.
All right, go on
with your story.
You were tending
the vineyards.
At that time, shortly
after the great war,
the world was in chaos.
Everywhere
was unhappiness
except in this
little village below.
For some reason,
the people of schwartzwald
refused to yield
to despair.
They lost none
of their faith.
They continued as they
had been for centuries-
honest, god-fearing
and happy.
This village was
a plum to satan
one he could not resist,
so he came here
and embarked upon
a program of corruption.
But you stopped him.
Yes!
You see, mr. Ellington,
he made the same mistake
thatyouhave made.
He underestimatedme.
He thought he would
have no difficulty
in tempting the old fool.
But i had him in a cell before
he knew what happened.
But if he's the devil,
how do you keep him locked up?
With the staff of truth-
the one barrier he cannot pass.
Tell me, how did
yourecognize him?
He doesn't look evil.
The devil hath power
to assume a pleasing shape.
I had seen him before
in all parts of the world
in all forms and guises,
wherever there was sin
wherever there
was strife
wherever there was corruption, persecution
there he was also.
Sometimes he was only a
spectator, a face in the crowd,
but always he was there.
Now...
you see, i hope,
why you must say nothing
of what you've seen
and heard here.
Brother, it's not
that i doubt you
you understand,
only isn't it possible
you might have
made a mistake?
No! Think,
mr. Ellington.
Think of the peace
of the world
these last five years.
Think of
this country now.
Is there
another like it?
You haven't put
an end to suffering.
There's still
murders, robberies.
Even now while
we're talking,
people are starving.
The suffering man
wasmeantto endure.
We cause most of
our own griefs.
We need no help
from him.
It is the unnatural
catastrophes,
the great wars, the
overwhelming pestilences
the wholesale sinning
that we have stopped.
I believe you, brother.
Do youtruly?
Yes.
I admit, i was
doubtful at first,
but you've convinced me,
absolutely.
I promise to keep
your secret.
Good, my son.
Tomorrow, if you
feel well enough,
you may leave.
In the meantime,
brother christophorus
will look after you.
Please, go directly
to his room.
Good night, brother.
He lied to you, didn't he?
I can see that.
What did he say?
He said you
were the devil.
The devil...
that's good.
That's wonderful.
What a dream
for an old devil-
to catch the devil
and lock him up.
You don't believe him,
do you?
No, of course not.
Then help me.
Look, here, why don't i just
go get the authorities?
It would be
my death warrant.
The authorities would return
and find nothing.
Jerome is mad...
but he's shrewd, too.
Brother jerome was fearful
you might lose your way.
Come.
Why are you locking
the door?
To protect you.
Rest now, mr. Ellington.
Remember you're still
a very sick man.
You've come.
Good!
What do you
want me to do?
Lift off
the wooden bolt.
Is this all
that holds you in?
Yes, lift it off.
Well, why haven't
you done it yourself?
Please, there's
no time for talk.
Mr. Ellington,
in the name of mercy.
If you fail now,
they'll kill both of us.
Don't you understand that?
Hurry, hurry!
Stop! Stop!
Put this on- the storm.
I'm sorry
for you, my son.
All your life
you will remember
this night
and you'll know,
mr. Ellington
whom you have
turned loose
upon the world.
I... i didn't believe you.
I... i saw him and
didn't recognize him.
That is
man's weakness
and satan's
strength.
In that moment
i decided to spend the rest
of my life tracking him down
to recapture
the evil i'd released
the evil that soon took the
shape of the second world war
the korean war,
the hideous new weapons of war.
I swore i'd find him again
as brother jerome had done.
It took many years,
but i did it.
See, i have him in there now.
So you understand now?
You understand why you must not
under any circumstances,
go near that door.
You see
how important it is
that he stay locked up.
Good.
I am sending him back
to brother jerome.
He'll do a bit of howling,
but pay no attention to that.
It's a trick, i know.
Yes, i must go now.
I must go, i...
i have
preparations to make.
I'll be back
in just a few minutes.
Remember... remember...
keep that door locked.
You can catch the devil,
but you can't hold him long.
Ask brother jerome,
ask david ellington.
They know,
and they'll go on knowing
till the end of their days, and
beyond, in the twilight zone.
Rod serling, creator
of the twilight zone,
will tell you about
next week's story
after this word from
our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, you'll see
these bandages unwrapped,
and you'll get a good, close
look at the face beneath them.
It's an excursion into the odd
and into the very,
very different.
Our play is called
"the eye of the beholder,"
and it comes recommended.
I hope we'll see you next week
onthe twilight zone.
Thank you and good night.
Be sure and see
the colgate-palmolive company's
new comedy show,
my sister eileen
wednesday night on many
of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org