Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Good morning, mr. Templeton.
Our new guest
this week, marty-
his name is what?
Page, sir.
Mr. Edward page.
Page.
Page, page.
Has he been
here before?
No, sir. He's new.
Oh.
These new, too?
Yes, sir.
Every hour
on the hour.
Hmm.
Mrs. Templeton is not
very discreet these days,
is she?
Well, her discretion
was an early fatality.
It didn't last very long.
Perhaps she's
waiting for the day
when these won't do
what they're
designed to do.
Perhaps i'm waiting
for that day, too.
Mr. Templeton, you
shouldn't say that.
Oh, don't distress
yourself, old friend.
When a man my age
marries a woman her age,
he gets exactly
what he deserves.
I'm old, marty.
Oh, mr. Templeton,
you could never be old.
Old and getting older
every minute that we
stand here speaking.
They say- or at least
they've said it
in most of my plays-
that when a man
achieves years
he achieves reason
and contentment.
I haven't.
Mr. Templeton,
may i suggest
that possibly
this isn't the day
for you to go
down there?
Perhaps i should
telephone the theater
and explain that you
can't start rehearsals.
Well, thank you, marty,
but i'll go down there.
I shall rehearse
this play,
and it will open.
I shall cover up
the years with makeup,
and i shall stand
in the right places
and hope to say
the right lines
and, when it's over,
they'll all say to me,
"you were wonderful,
mr. Templeton."
Then the stage manager
will see to it
that i'm properly
delivered to you
so that you can properly
deliver me back here
so that i can
go back there
and do it all over
again next night.
I won't see,
nor particularly care,
about what's going on
outside there,
or anywhere
in this house.
All i want will be
to go to bed, marty.
That's the best place
for me-
bed, sleep, oblivion.
Now, sir, you shouldn't
talk like that.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
I don't
love her anymore.
I don't remember when i did.
You know, i can't recall
one single, separated,
contented moment.
I haven't had many
contented moments in my life.
But i do recall some.
Long ago.
Laura.
The freshest, most radiant
creature god ever created.
18 when i married her, marty.
25 when she died.
Why did he have to take her?
Please,
mr. Templeton, sir,
don't do this
to yourself.
You know, there are some
moments in life
that have an indescribable
loveliness to them.
Those moments with laura...
are all i have left now.
Do you understand
that, marty?
Yes, mr. Templeton.
I believe i do, sir.
But it...
don't distress yourself,
old friend.
I'm all right.
I'm quite all right.
Pleased to present
for your consideration
mr. Booth templeton,
serious and successful star
of over 30 broadway plays,
who is not quite
all right today.
Yesterday and its memories
is what he wants,
and yesterday is what he'll get.
Soon his years and his troubles
will descend on him
in an avalanche.
In order not to be crushed,
mr. Booth templeton will escape
from his theater and his world,
and make his debut
on another stage
in another world that
we call the twilight zone.
You're late, booth.
After 12:00.
The boy wonder
won't like it, kiddo.
Who is the boy wonder?
Arthur willis, directing.
No, no, no.
You must be mistaken.
Dothmeager's
our director.
Was. Canned him
last night.
What?
We need someone
with more pep, zip.
Not my racket,
but i know what's good
and what's bad
as well as the next guy.
And i wanted
to drop by this morning
and let everybody know
that i'm personally
interested in this thing.
Art willis is okay
with you, isn't he?
Well, i've heard
of him, of course
but i... i don't
actually know him
uh... mr. Uh...
i'm sid sperry.
Remember?
My money is backing
this play.
Oh, yes, of course,
mr. Sperry.
I'm rather forgetful
about names.
Always have been.
It's okay.
Just so long as you don't
forget your lines.
I say this once,
just once.
And only once.
But i say it now
and expect each
and every one of you
to understand it.
Michael franz
is producing this play.
Mr. Coombs
has written it.
You have been hired
to act in it,
and i have
been contracted
to direct it.
So make
no mistake
about what we
are here to do,
and make no mistake
about me.
I will direct this play
myway at all times.
Is that clear?
Like that.
Like that very much.
In control, that boy,
right from the start.
Give us a good play.
Us, mister...?
Sperry, templeton.
Sperry.
Yes, mr. Sperry.
I... i apologize.
That was impolite
of me.
I won't forget again.
Call his home!
Valencia.
Never mind.
Some of us are young.
Some of us are old.
But neither state
precludes any of us,
young or old,
from ignoring
the basic cooperation
that will be
necessary here.
When i direct,
there are no significant personalities
in the cast
of any play,
but there are three
significant dates
in the life
of a play...
the first day of rehearsal,
opening night, closing night.
The last two are related
and dependent upon the first.
Therefore, the first day
of rehearsal
is an extremely important day.
When i call
rehearsal
for 12:00,
templeton,
i meant 12:00
for everyone,
young and old-
everyone to be
in his place
and ready to work
at 12:00 sharp.
Are you ready
to work with us, templeton?
I asked you a question.
I expect an answer.
Answer me!
Answer me,
templeton!
Speak up, templeton!
Speak up!
No...
come back here,
templeton.
Booth!
Come back!
Templeton!
Come back here!
Booth templeton
inthe great seed?
1927's big hit?
1927.
That's more than 30 years ago.
Barney flueger.
Barney!
Hey, mr. Templeton.
What year is this?
1927.
Say, you're not
trying to kid me,
are you,
mr. Templeton?
Most assuredly
i'm not.
Your wife
just phoned
and said for you
to meet her
at freddie
iaccino's.
My wife?
But laura's dead.
Well, she's the
best-looking ghost
i ever saw,
mr. Templeton.
No offense, of course.
Where's laura?
Where did you say
she's waiting for me?
At freddie iaccino's,
just around the corner.
Hello, booth.
Freddie.
Yeah, what?
It is you.
You're alive.
Sure.
What did you expect?
Can't be too
careful these days.
All the time somebody's
wanting a raid or something.
What'll it be tonight,
steaks or chops?
What?
Well, your wife's having
the kansas city.
She isn't at
our usual table.
She's over there.
Well?
What?
Steaks or chops?
No, nothing. Nothing
to eat tonight, freddie.
We're not staying very long.
Oh, barney,
you're a scream.
Oh, hi.
Hi, booth.
We didn't wait.
Barney.
Barney flueger.
The same.
To know him
is to love him.
Sit down,
old man.
I'll be
right back.
Laura...
laura, darling.
Booth, my goodness.
Come on, sit down.
The kansas city's
great tonight.
It's juicy.
See? I told you.
Laura, i...
what's the matter?
You look worried.
Hmm?
Booth, how
many times
have i told you
to take your
makeup off
before you come
in here.
Makeup?
Laura...
laura, darling,
let's go
someplace else.
Somewhere
where it's quieter.
Where there aren't
so many people.
Why?
Well, i want to talk
to you, laura.
Well, i want to have
a good time.
Oh, yoo-hoo!
Could you get me
another of these, please?
Thank you.
But i have to talk
to you, laura.
Well?
I...
oh, laura,
darling...
i'm here.
I don't know
for how long,
or even
how i got here,
or-or who put me
here, but i'm here
and i want to make good use of the time.
I want to have you alone
to myself.
Booth, don't be dull.
Aren't you going
to eat, old chap?
New band's
swell.
Laura, laura... barney...
you better
order.
Yeah. He's
right, honey.
Listen to me, you two...
oh, it's so
hot tonight.
Hey, george, bring
him one of these.
I'll be glad
to get into a cold tub.
Booth, will
you tell me why,
on this glad,
green earth,
you're wearing
an overcoat for
on a night like this?
Will you tell
me now, booth?
I mean, really.
I'm not so certain
that it is a glad,
green earth.
Oh, laura, laura,
darling...
barney...
i'm not so certain
of this earth,
or of anything
in it, right now.
I... oh, please,
listen to me.
Listen to me,
won't you?
Laura, laura,
something's happened.
Something
very strange.
Please try to understand.
This... this isn't makeup.
I've grown older, darling.
In another
world, many...
for many, many
lonely years...
i've had only
a memory of you
to live on.
You, too, barney.
Why, you were
my one and only
best friend.
But both of you have been
only memories for a long time.
And now, tonight...
or today, or... whatever it is,
and wherever i am in...
in space or time,
i have you back again.
You're alive.
You didn't die.
Life is going on here.
It's just as if you never died-
either of you.
You do understand, don't you?
Oh, sure.
Laura, do you understand?
Sure.
Come on, let's have
a good time, huh?
Laura...
why are you so different?
Well, that's the way
i am, booth.
That's the way it is.
I mean, what did you expect?
Yes, old chap,
whatdidyou expect?
I...
i don't know.
But you were my love.
Everywhere, at all times.
Why, we couldn't walk a street
or sit in a restaurant
without everybody
knowing
that we
were in love.
Are you finished?
I don't like what you've become.
Shut up.
Shut up, both of you! Shut up!
Laura, laura, come with me.
No.
You're a silly old fool
of a man.
That's for me.
Stop it! Stop it!
Why don't you go back
where you came from?
We don't
want you here.
Oh, yeah,
come on...
no, no, please, please.
Oh, come on...
did it happen?
"What to do
when booth comes back."
"Table in speakeasy.
"Enter booth as laura
throws back her head
"and laughs too shrilly.
'You're a scream,
barney. A real... '"
'the same.
"'To know him is to love him.
Sit down, old chap.'"
'Why don't you go back
where you came from?
We don't want you here.'"
Acting.
They were acting for me.
They wanted me to go back
to my own life...
and live it.
Templeton.
One question:
Are you in or are you out?
I am definitely... in.
And it is definitely
mr. Templeton,
especially to one
so young as you.
Now, wait
a minute...
excuse me, mr. Sperry,
but i never allow anyone
not directly connected
with the production
to attend my rehearsals.
I insist upon that.
Just who do you
think you are?
Sidney... run along.
Now, then, shall
we start rehearsal?
I'd like that,
mr. Templeton.
I've just had a most remarkable
experience, young man.
I couldn't possibly
expect you to comprehend it,
but i'm going to tell you
about it anyway...
someday.
You know,
you were right.
The first day
of rehearsal
isthe most important date
in the life of a play.
Mr. Booth templeton,
who shared with most
human beings the hunger
to recapture the past moments-
the ones that soften
with the years.
But, in his case,
the characters of his past
blocked him out
and sent him back
to his own time,
which is where we find him now-
mr. Booth templeton,
who had a round-trip ticket
into the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
the creator oftwilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
In this $28 a day hotel suite
live three human beings
who have larceny in them
from their toes
to where they part their hair.
Amongst the loot of one
evening's caper is this camera,
which they soon discover
has most unique properties-
it takes pictures of the future.
Stick around
for the development,
next week, onthe twilight zone.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
see the newandy griffith show
each week
over most of these stations.
Consult local listings.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org