Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Oh, i'm sorry, dear.
You keep forgetting i'm
no longer a varsity end.
Oh, it was fun though, huh?
My doctor should have witnessed
that little activity.
If you persist in telling me
about your ailments,
i may just have to run out
and get sick.
It gets dull, you know.
Terribly dull.
I just, uh...
mentioned it in
passing, my dear.
What did you do today?
You, uh... did
you go shopping?
Oh, i had a ball.
An absolute wild ball,
an earthshaking ball.
Want to know what i did?
What?
Well...
first of all,
i had breakfast.
Then i had lunch,
and then i fired
the stupid maid.
And then
i waited for you,
harmon, dear.
So, all in all, i'd say
it was one of those days
that made you simply want
to go jump off a bridge.
Am i getting
through to you at all?
Why, it's smoky the bear.
Flora, dear, you could
start a serious fire.
Big daddy, one of these
long, late nights,
that's exactly
what i'm going to do.
While you're
at it,
why don't you pick up the
remnants of that aged eyesore
that i so happily
knocked over a
few minutes ago?
This came
from my mother.
It's a very old piece, flora.
Oh?
Worth what?
89 cents?
I'll tell you
what, big daddy.
On our anniversary, i'll go out
and buy you six of them.
I'll take them to the dime store
and have them gift-wrapped.
Then i'll find you
some of your
favorite music
and play it on
your old victrola.
Something like, uh,
"come to the wildwood church"?
And other such red-hot
toe-tapping numbers?
It's worth very little
except...
except for sentimental value.
That's a word you may
not understand, "sentiment."
It means "the capacity to love."
Big daddy,
if i don't fill the bill,
why don't you just say so
right out?
Should you fail to know it
there are 14
flights a day to reno,
and i would just adore
to be on any one of them.
Flora, i'm, uh,
i'm not angry, i just wish
that you would, you would...
you would try
to be more careful.
Somebody should have
wished that five years ago
when we took out
our papers.
Oh, i knew
you were old, harmon.
I just didn't
know how old.
You better be
careful, big daddy,
because if you ever take me
to a swinging weekend in egypt,
i just may run away
with a mummy.
I'll, uh, i'll just wash up
and we'll go to dinner.
Yeah.
You do just that.
We'll make it your night.
We'll do something really wild
like go to a band
concert in the park.
A picture of an aging man who
leads his life as thoreau said:
In quiet desperation.
Because harmon gordon
is enslaved by a love affair
with a wife 40 years his junior.
Because of this,
he runs when he should walk,
he surrenders when
simple pride dictates a stand.
He pines away for the lost
morning of his life
when he should be
enjoying the evening.
In short, mr. Harmon gordon
seeks a fountain of youth.
And who's to say
he won't find it?
This happens to be
the twilight zone.
Oh, great.
I didn't ask you
to run the mile,
just to go dancing
or the movies or something.
Don't start telling me
about how you took me
out of a chorus line
and introduced me
to the finer things.
Your idea of
the finer things
is to hold hands in
a mausoleum and listen
to the organ music.
Well, get yourself a nice, tall
glass of warm milk, big daddy,
and curl up with an almanac,
'cause we want you happy,
don't we?
Uh, could i talk
to dr. Gordon, please?
Yes, thank you.
Uh, raymond?
It's harmon.
Raymond, i've got
to talk to you tonight.
Would you please come over?
Uh, drink all right?
Uh, yeah,
it's fine.
You look a little tired, harmon.
Well, i've been, uh...
a little rushed
this past week, so...
flora in bed?
Uh, yes, yes, she went to bed.
She asked to be remembered.
Oh, she'll be remembered.
You ought to get to know her
better, raymond.
She's really...
she's really a very fine girl.
Did i say otherwise?
Well, i know you two
haven't been exactly close,
certainly not as close
as a brother- and
sister-in-law could be.
Harmon...
will you do me a favor?
Certainly.
As a matter of fact, two favors.
First, don't try
to sell me flora.
You know what
i think of her,
i've told her myself to her face
so i have no compunctions
about saying it aloud.
She's a brassy,
conniving, little broad.
Let me finish.
I could forgive her
her hungers, harmon,
or the fact that she's
made out of asbestos
and hasn't got
a heart in her body.
But i can't forgive her
for what she's
done to you.
You know that
she's turned you
into a frightened,
quaking fool.
You dote on her,
you give in to her,
you run after her like a poodle.
That's item
number one.
Now the second favor
is that from now on,
after you've had your battles,
don't call me at odd hours
of the night.
I don't do that very often.
Once is often
and twice is endless.
We're very close
as brothers go.
You know there
isn't anything
i wouldn't do for you.
But i can't run over here
like a saint bernard
every time you get frozen
halfway up the mountainside.
Now, she's a predatory
little alley cat.
And she's always
been that way.
I can just give you so much
solace, so much sympathy,
and after that,
it begins to craw.
Now, what is it tonight?
Just someone to while
away the hours with
or is there something
quite specific?
Um...
um...
this thing you, uh...
been working on.
Go on.
The cellular serum...
you've been successful with it.
You must be out of your mind.
I'm desperate, yes,
but i'm not out of my mind.
You've made
animals younger,
i've seen it myself.
You inject them with your fluid
and they're young again.
Animals, yes.
Guinea pigs,
white mice, hamsters.
I've rejuvenated glands,
organs, sometimes
a complete cellular structure.
But we haven't
scratched the surface, harmon.
We're stumbling
in the dark.
I want you to inject me.
You don't know what's involved.
We're 20 years away from
trying this on a human being.
Why?
We're dealing
in basic life form.
We have no idea of how much
damage might result.
We don't know how
it will affect the metabolism
of the body or the mind,
or the effect on the brain.
We're winging this, we've killed
as many as we've saved.
You said you'd do
anything for me.
Anything within reason.
Oh, but this is
within reason, raymond.
I've come close
to the end of my rope.
I'm at the point where
it matters very little to me
whether i live or die.
I want you to test this serum
on me, make me young again.
I don't want to get any older.
Aside from this pronounced
death wish of yours,
how would you like
to spend the rest of your life
as a mutated freak?
Or a gibbering idiot?
Or a mindless shell?
That's not only possible,
it's highly probable.
We can't control an experiment
on a human being.
It would be catch as catch can.
I'd not only take the risk,
i'd welcome it.
The answer is no!
I wouldn't experiment
on a strange bum i found
on the street...
raymond.
...to say nothing
of my own brother.
Raymond, please, wait, wait.
Raymond, please.
The answer is no.
Good night, raymond.
Thank you for coming.
Harmon.
As a doctor,
i can tell you
what the effects
on the human body are
landing on concrete at the
end of a 500-foot fall.
As a man, can you tell me
what the effects are
on the human brain
when a man is deeply,
totally
and dedicatedly love
with a woman
who can't stand
the sight of him?
Have you even
the remotest idea
what kind of life
this is for me?
I can tell you
what it could be...
should be.
You're a bright, charming,
wealthy, discerning guy,
and you've been
hammered out of shape
by a flashy piece of baggage
not fit to wait on your table.
Well, whatever she is or isn't,
she is the only thing
on god's earth
that i
care about.
I beg you, give me a chance.
Give me a chance to save myself.
And if i don't?
Then we'll see who
reaches the sidewalk first:
The man in the elevator
or the free-falling body.
Oh, my dear god.
I feel sorry for you.
Let me think it over
for an hour or two.
I'll come back.
Is that it?
That's it.
What can i expect?
You can expect a miracle,
but you're not very
likely to get it.
Go to bed now,
don't go to work tomorrow.
I'll be here
early in the morning.
I want to be very close to you
for the next few days.
Well, when can i
expect some change?
Within six hours.
That's when the first
physical change is noted.
As for the mental change,
none of the rats or guinea pigs
have told me
what the feeling was.
I'll be the first.
You'll be the first...
assuming that
you survive.
You want to know
something, raymond?
I'm not only
going to survive,
i'm going to be young
again, i can feel it.
I wonder if she has any
idea what she's done.
Even one slight
little suspicion.
But i promise you
that if you don't survive or
if you're damaged in any way,
i'm going to take it
out of her skin,
piece by piece.
She's going to donate
a pint of blood
for every pint that
she's bled out of you.
That's not a
medical hypothesis,
that's a promise.
Go to bed now.
I'll see you
in the morning.
Well, well, if it isn't
the poor man's kildare.
What brings
you out into the
early dawn, doctor?
Where's harmon?
When last seen,
he was pounding a pillow.
Is he all right?
What is this,
e.s.p. Or something?
I asked you a question-
is he all right?
I presume he is,
but if you don't think so
just go in there
and blow a bugle.
No, i'll wait
for him to get up.
Yeah, you do that.
Take off your stethoscope
and make yourself at home.
Haven't you talked
to him this morning?
I haven't talked
to anybody.
Until you pounded
at the door
at this ungodly hour.
Did you talk
to him last night?
He said something
when he went to bed.
I hardly heard him.
He sounded
lucid to you?
Look, pally, i'm
not the night nurse.
I think you're
in the wrong ward.
Besides that,
you bore me.
How do you feel,
harmon?
How do you feel, harmon?
I ask for vince edwards
and look what they send me.
Ah, it's incredible
what a good night's sleep
will do for a man, isn't it?
Harmon?
What have you...
are you wearing
makeup or something?
Makeup... no, no.
No makeup, just
a good night's sleep.
Well...
you look so different.
Oh, do i?
Yes, you...
well, you look
wonderful
you, you look
so young.
What's happened
to you?
Ask my brother
over there.
No, his brother
doesn't know.
Howdoyou feel,
harmon?
I feel like
a million dollars
tax-free,
that's how i feel.
Know what i'll do
for you, ray?
I'll let you
take me on tour.
They'll write you up
in all the medical journals.
But first you've got
to give me four weeks.
Flora and i are going to go
on a little ocean trip.
An ocean trip?
Mm-hmm.
Well...
well, that's wonderful.
When do we go?
I've been thinking.
We ought to see if there's
anything sailing tonight.
Unless of course
you'd rather fly.
Oh, fly, sail,
who cares?
Ooh, big daddy, i don't know
what you've done to yourself
but let me clue you in
about something:
I don't care,
'cause i like this fine.
Oh, yes, i like it fine.
I don't want you to plan
any trips for quite a while.
Oh, blow it.
I'll just go and change
for you, all right?
Where would you
like to go?
Paris? Rome?
Tokyo? Hmm?
Anywhere you say.
I'm your passenger.
Oh...
mmm, ahh...
why, this is
incredible.
You haven't looked that way
since you were 30 years old.
That's fantastic,
it's absolutely fantastic.
I keep getting younger.
If i keep going at this rate,
i'll be drafted.
If you don't stop,
we may be in trouble.
Oh!
What do you mean, trouble?
What kind of trouble?
I wish i knew...
how much longer it would go on
or how long
before it stops.
Oh, it's still
going on.
I can feel it.
Harmon?
It's still going on,
what... what is...
oh...
harmon?
Harmon, what's
going on with you?
What's happening?
Harmon?
Leave him go.
I want him
to go to bed.
Go to bed, harmon.
Raymond, you tell me
what's happening to him.
Quiet, leave him alone!
What's going on?
Leave him alone.
What is it?
Sit down, flora.
But i want to see him.
You will.
But i don't want you
to wake him.
He's in shock now, and sleep
is precisely what he needs.
I want
to see him right now.
No, not now.
Right now, flora,
as of this moment, you've
got to readjust your life.
What are you
talking about?
Look, is this
some kind of a trick?
I want to see harmon,
i want to see my husband.
Your husband
is sleeping.
When he wakes up,
he's going to need help.
Help?
What kind of help?
I want to see him.
You will.
But i think you'd
best get oriented.
Flora, the ground
rules change now.
Now you stay
in your own yard.
The world doesn't begin
and end with flora anymore.
It isn't just flora's wishes
and flora's temperament,
and flora's
capacity for anger.
Now it's something else.
It's very different.
You have a
responsibility now.
And you're going
to honor it.
You're going to
take care of harmon.
He's going to need you.
Flora!
If you're leaving,
make note of the fact
that what you're wearing
is all that you take with you.
If you think that
i'm going to stay
and take care of a grubby,
thumb-sucking little kid...
that's precisely
what you're going to do.
And short of that
you leave here
exactly as you arrived:
Unadorned.
All the furs
and the jewelry
and anything else
that my brother gave you
remain here.
He can't make me stay here.
You can't make me
stay here, either.
There are other fish
in this ocean, mister.
Indeed there are,
but you're not married to them.
You happen to be married
to my brother.
That's crazy.
Crazy?
No. It's bizarre.
And it's a fact.
And if i ever hear
that he's left alone
with nurses, maids
and governesses,
you're going to find yourself
right back on the chorus line
do you understand?
He's going to get
some attention now.
And i don't mean just
intimate and sporadic visits
between nightclubs
and beauty parlors.
I mean from morning
till night.
Won't he ever grow?
Oh, yes.
As of right now, he'll grow
a little bit older each day,
like any little boy.
And you'll perform
the process together.
As he grows older,
you'll be growing old.
There's a little
poetic justice, flora:
That you should be forced
to drink from the same cup.
And then when
tomorrow comes,
there'll be someone
younger outside
waiting to come in.
Always waiting
to come in.
But it isn't fair, raymond.
It just isn't fair.
Everything...
everything is on his side.
Well, you see, flora,
as you get older,
see how wise you get.
It happens to be a fact.
As one gets older,
one does get wiser.
If you don't believe it,
ask flora.
Ask her any day of
the ensuing weeks of her life
as she takes notes
during the coming years
and realizes that
the worm has turned.
Youth has taken over.
It's simply the way
the calendar crumbles...
in the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next time a new author joins the
ranks of the elves and gremlins
who supply the imaginative
material onthe twilight zone.
His name is richard deroy
and his story is in the best
tradition of the program.
It stars one of the gentlest,
and certainly the most able
of america's actors,
a beloved little fixture on the
american scene named ed wynn.
Next time out
onthe twilight zone,
ed wynn stars in
"90 years without slumbering."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org