Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Yeah.
Mr. Fenton?
Yeah, that's right.
Mrs. Boles down the
street sent me over.
She said you wanted someone
to take care of your lawn?
I rang the doorbell,
but nobody answered.
Then i heard your radio.
The front door was wide open.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Come on up.
If it's just the front
you want taken care of,
i can handle it for,
oh, seven bucks a month.
That sounds fair enough.
I'll come every wednesday
if it's convenient.
Sold.
Great, well, thanks
a lot, mr. Fenton.
So long.
No, wait a minute.
Come on up.
We'll sit down
and have a beer on it.
No, thanks just the same.
No, i mean it.
I've got plenty on ice.
Anyway, you can make
a small fortune up here
helping me clean out
some of this junk.
How about it?
Well, ten minutes.
What did you say
your name is, boy?
Arthur. Arthur takamuri.
Arthur?
That's right.
Well, that's funny.
What is?
Why arthur?
Why not?
I was born in
this country.
Sure. I didn't
mean anything.
I'm just as much american
as anybody, you know.
Well, now, who
said you're not?
You're too
darn sensitive.
Yeah, i guess i am.
Truth is, my name is taro.
I changed it.
A rose is a rose,
you get what i mean?
No.
Oh, what a mess.
This attic's been
like this for 20 years.
Knee-deep in junk.
I found some stuff i haven't
even seen since the war.
Hey, get a load of
this, will you?
Can you imagine
i once got into it?
Sure, why not?
Yeah, you're just
being polite.
I'm a tub of
rancid lard now,
but i was pretty
tough once.
I went all through
saipan and okinawa.
Yeah.
Check my fruit salad.
Crazy, huh?
You ever see one of these?
Yeah.
It's a genuine
samurai sword.
Not a fake
like most you see around.
I took it off a jap officer
who tried to cut off my noggin.
There's something
engraved on it.
Maybe you can
translate it for me.
Sorry, i can't speak any
language but english.
Oh, come on, boy.
My mother spoke japanese,
but me, i never learned.
You said you wanted me to help
you clean up this junk.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
But first i've got to get
a couple of beers.
My throat's full of dust.
Throw anything you want
on the floor and sit down.
Be back in a jiffy.
I'm going to kill him.
Why?
Two men alone in an attic;
a young japanese-american
and a seasoned veteran
of yesterday's war.
It's 20 odd years
since pearl harbor,
but two ancient opponents
are moving into position
for a battle in an attic
crammed with skeletons-
souvenirs, mementos,
old uniforms and rusted metals-
ghosts from the dim reaches
of the past
that will lead us
into the twilight zone.
Well, here we are,
nice and cold.
You partial to beer, carl?
The name's arthur.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
i forgot.
It's just that, uh...
well, you don't look
like an arthur to me.
You don't look like
a soldier, either.
Well, you got me there, boy.
And while we're
at it, mr. Fenton,
i get bugged by "boy."
Europeans are always
calling the natives "boy,"
and moaning about the
white man's burden.
Well, the facts are,
i'm a full-grown man.
I work for a living,
and i answer to arthur,
takamuri,
and believe it or not,
sometimes to mr. Takamuri.
Oh, brother,
are you wound up.
You do this every time a
guy offers you a beer?
Now here, take it. Go on.
I'm sorry.
I guess i got
a headache from the sun.
Ah, forget it, forget it.
The war's over.
But in case you
don't know it,
there ain't a service man
who saw combat in the pacific
who doesn't
respect the japanese.
They fought like tigers,
and it was rare you could
take them without killing 'em.
Bonzai.
Okay.
Say, uh...
where'd i leave
that pigsticker?
What?
You know, the sword.
Oh, didn't you leave it
on this table here?
Well, that's where
i thought i left it.
But it's not there now.
Boy, that thing
gives me the willies.
It's funny if i lost it.
I've been trying to
lose it for years.
Never could make it though.
I should have left it,
instead of picking it up
as a souvenir.
You know what i mean?
You know, i've...
i've tried to give it away,
sell it, hock it,
throw it out with the garbage.
But it always comes back.
Oh, nothing supernatural.
I don't believe in that jazz.
But when people refuse it,
even wrapped as a gift,
when the men on the garbage
truck bring it in,
well, you give up
after a while.
Say...
you wouldn't like to have it,
would you?
No.
What would i do with it?
Why, give it back to me,
of course, point first.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I was just kidding.
Don't let it bother you.
I don't blame you
for not wanting it.
It's a pretty ugly thing.
Especially with
what's engraved on the blade.
Oh, sure,
i know what it says.
I had one of our interpreters
translate it for me
right after i got it.
It says
"the sword will avenge me."
Isn't that it,
arthur?
I wouldn't know.
Oh, come off it, arthur.
Look, mr. Fenton,
i work for a living,
and i'm kind of in a hurry.
Listen, taro.
What's all this stuff
about working for a living?
Now you mentioned that twice.
Don't you think
i work for a living?
I didn't say...
i've been working for a living
ever since i was a kid
and at a job a lot
tougher than mowing lawns,
i'll tell you that.
Right up until last week when
i got laid off, i drove a cat.
You know what a cat is, arthur?
Well, i can tell you this,
it ain't no sports car.
It's a big earthmover.
You ever move the earth, arthur?
Nah, of course not.
You manicure it.
I've got to get going.
Oh, what's the rush?
Sit down, drink your beer.
Just tell me
where you hid the sword.
Where i did what?
You buried it somewhere
to get it out of the way.
You're crazy.
Look, i left that sword
right there on the table.
I remember it distinctly.
Listen, taro-
excuse me, arthur-
are you by any chance
afraid of me?
Why should i be?
Well, i can think
of a couple reasons,
one being my background.
I was in a fighting outfit.
You know what that means?
Well, it's not like
the recruiting posters,
i can tell you that.
A nice, clean-cut lad,
who helps old ladies
across the street.
He has to be a highly-trained
combat machine,
with split-second reactions
in place of emotions.
He's on wires, on his toes.
His nerve ends are dead,
and he's as cold and as hard
and rigid as his helmet.
In fact, there's nothing...
nothing more terrible
to meet on a dark night
than a fighting man
with an m1, a thompson,
a grenade,
or even his bare hands.
Over here!
Come out and die...
some dirty son of heaven,
out in the jungle
just asking for it.
So i... i thought i'd oblige.
Started circling out behind him,
a simple exercise for somebody
with more luck than brains.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
I was only telling you
how it was.
I'm sorry.
Boy, for a minute there,
i thought you were gonna...
i don't know what got into me.
I really don't.
You used that sword
like you were mowing a lawn.
You didn't get that sword
the way you said you did.
No?
No.
You shot that officer
after he surrendered.
You're crazy.
The japanese officer dropped
the sword and surrendered.
You killed him in cold blood.
All right, so what if i did?
So what if i did?
I don't know.
That's your problem.
I...
i don't feel well.
What am i doing here?
I've got to get out of here.
Mr. Fenton, the door's stuck!
Well, you must be weak.
Pull on it.
It won't move.
Did you lock it?
Now, how could i do
a thing like that?
It hasn't got a lock.
Here, let me try.
Well... it looks like
you're not supposed
to leave just yet.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I don't know what i mean.
Well...
i don't know
what's making it stick.
It never did that before.
But never mind, boy.
There must be some tools
up here.
We'll take it
off the hinges.
Nah, forget
the window.
It's too high.
Well, we could break
a pane of glass
and yell for help, but
let's save that for last.
See if you can
find a screwdriver.
Well...
look at the boy.
Becoming a samurai?
Well, forget it, boy.
You couldn't make it.
Now, if you ever
try to come at me
with that thing again,
i'll chop you up
like hamburger.
I don't like that kind
of talk, mr. Fenton.
No?
No.
I got a short fuse,
so don't strike matches.
I grew up in honolulu.
I was at pearl harbor
when it was bombed.
Were you one of the pilots?
I was four years old.
My father and mother lived
in hawaii all their lives.
My father worked for the navy
as a civilian.
Oh, yeah? Doing what?
He helped build
the docks at pearl.
He was foreman
of a construction gang.
He was a war hero.
He was on the docks when
they came that sunday morning.
He was there when the first wave
of bombers came over...
standing there, watching men
of his own race destroy
what he'd built
with his own hands.
The bombers flew overhead.
I stood on the hillside
where we lived,
looked up at the sky
and saw them.
And my mother held my hand
and tried to make me run
inside the house...
but i stood.
And i watched the planes...
while down below at the harbor,
my father was trying
to warn the sailors,
trying to tell the men
on the ships what was happening.
But the bombers came anyway,
and i could hear
the boom, boom, boom, boom
as the bombs exploded.
And i could see the smoke.
And my mother was crying,
and my father was yelling
to warn the sailors,
yelling for them to fire back.
Boom! Boom! Boom!
Planes circled overhead.
They dropped their bombs.
That's not the way
it happened.
He was a traitor.
He signaled the planes.
He showed them
where to drop the bombs.
He was a traitor.
My old man was a traitor.
I got to get out of here.
Arthur! Arthur!
Now, you'd better sit down
and have a fresh beer.
You need it.
Aw, that's stupid.
Y-y-you come up here
to make a few
bucks mowing lawns.
I ask you to
have a beer...
because, well,
if you must know,
i was kind of lonesome.
My old lady got...
got teed off last night
and went to sleep
over at her sister's.
But she'll be back.
I... i guess i drink too much.
You know, arthur,
you're a...
you're a pretty
nice joe.
You know, i knew
that right away
when i first saw you.
That's why...
well, that's why
i asked you up
to have a beer.
So i can... i
can tell you,
man to man, it's been
pretty rough lately.
I... well, they
canned me from my job,
put somebody
else on the cat.
Can you imagine?
Just-just-just
because i had
a few lousy
drinks one day.
Ah, no...
no, it wasn't the booze.
That was just an excuse.
It's all that
cheap labor
they're bringing
over here.
Yeah, they're letting
them in from everywhere-
mexico, puerto rico,
china, japan- foreigners.
We make hawaii a state;
look what we get.
Ah, i'm...
i'm getting off the subject.
My wife.
Well, like i
said, she...
went over to sleep at
her sister's last night.
Said she was all
washed up with me.
Can you tie that?
Now, that's
gratitude for you.
But she's going
to come back.
Mm-hmm.
She knows what side her
bread's buttered on.
And if she doesn't,
well, who needs her?
Who needs her?
A man can make it
alone, huh, arthur?
I mean, well, women
are a dime a dozen.
Anybody that's been to
the orient knows that.
What's the
matter, arthur?
Or do you want me
to call you taro now?
Listen, kid,
don't take it so hard.
I mean, you know,
just because your old man
was a sneaky little
double-dealing traitor,
that doesn't mean you are.
I mean, what
the devil?
You don't have to
go and change your
name and all
and-and forget
you know how to
speak japanese.
There was sneaks and
double-crossers on both sides.
Like you.
Now wait a minute.
Wait a minute, buddy.
You're no better.
You're a murderer.
You killed a defenseless man.
Now take it easy.
What happened on okinawa-
you can't blame that on me.
Now, we were told
not to take prisoners.
That's right.
"No prisoners,"
they said.
Well, you...
you can't hold a
man responsible
for obeying orders,
now, can you?
In the pacific, we were told
that you guys
weren't even human-
you were... you were
some species of an ape-
and not to worry
about burning you
out of the caves.
Now all of a sudden, you're
fine people, highly cultured.
And it's propaganda about
your lousy transistor radios.
Put that sword down, arthur,
and let's have a beer together.
I don't like to drink alone.
Arthur?
Well, arthur, didn't i tell you?
I'm all alone now.
My wife up
and left me.
I called the foreman
on the job yesterday,
and he hung
up the phone.
I'm not such a bad guy, arthur.
Why is all this happening?
Why?
All right.
Don't answer.
If that's what you're here for,
kill me.
Go on, i dare you.
Come on, taro,
i'm waiting for you.
Oh... so that's it.
You're just trying to scare me.
Well, all right.
I'm scared...
but not of dying.
Of living.
I can't make it, arthur,
or taro, or whatever
your name is.
There's nothing left. Nothing!
I've got a box
full of decorations over there.
Decorations!
First, you're an ape,
and now all of a sudden,
you're-you're some kind
of highly-cultured people.
I've been pushed and pulled
this way and that way
until i hate everybody,
you dirty little jap!
Bonzai!
Two men in an attic,
locked in mortal embrace.
Their common bond
guilt-
a disease all too prevalent
amongst men
both in and out
of the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next time out,
we move into the area
of graveyards
and the dear departed
and we tell you a story
about a most distinctive
type of fella
who happily enough has an
equally distinctive profession-
he raises the dead.
Onthe twilight zonenext time,
john dehner, stanley adams
and j. Pat o'malley
lend selective talents
to a little item called
"mr. Garrity and the graves."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org