Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension,
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
All right, mother,
remember, the rule
of the house today is
the moment this is over,
you go back upstairs.
That's fine, chris.
You know i
always follow
the rules
of the house...
except when i don't
agree with them.
Hey, you haven't
got your hat on.
Grandma!
My angel!
Mother, you know
the doctor told you
not to exert yourself.
Oh! I don't exert.
Billy is a feather.
Chris... chris,
get the lights.
Everybody sit down.
All right.
Billy,
shut your eyes.
Here, mother.
Don't open them
till i tell you to.
Happy birthday,
billy.
Open them!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday,
billy!
Isn't that
beautiful?
No, no, no, no,
wait, billy.
Wait, my boy.
First you have to
blow out the candles
or it's no good.
Now, you take
a deep breath, like...
and then blow them out,
all of them.
Good, good!
Good boy.
You make a wish?
What was it?
You tell grandma, ja?
Don't you think we could
all hear the wish, billy?
No, that's a secret
between him and me.
Isn't that so?
Now... mm!
Oh, mother,
why don't you let syl
cut the cake, huh?
You think i'm too old
to cut a cake, eh?
When i am that old
you get the shovel
and dig the hole.
Shovel!
Yes, my angel!
Oh... oh, billy!
Oh, darling.
Oh, my angel.
I am so happy.
My heart is full, i...
i like to say something.
Could i say something?
Sure.
My little billy-
my wonderful little boy.
He gave me life again.
An old woman
good for nothing no
more but to complain.
He held out his hands to me
and...
made me alive.
Why are you
crying, grandma?
I don't know, my angel.
Maybe because i won't
be here with you
for very long.
Why?
I will be away.
Where?
Nowhere, billy.
Grandma's going to be right here
next year
and the year after that.
No... don't lie to him.
I will be gone.
It's time for presents.
Come on, billy!
Gram,
i wish you...
is anything wrong?
No, it...
just a little
short of breath.
Bang!
Bang, bang!
How do you
like that, huh?
This is the one
i want you
to open next.
Wait till
you see it.
This is the one
you asked for, remember?
Billy, don't you want to see
what grandma got you?
Oh, boy!
A telephone!
For us, billy-
for you and me.
So you can always talk
to grandma
even when she's not here-
anytime.
Can i talk
to grandma now?
Good... go ahead.
Hello.
Is there somebody who
wants to talk to grandma?
It's me!
Who are you?
It's me, billy!
Oh, billy...
take me upstairs now, chris.
Don't you
want to play?
I want to, billy.
You just talk
on the telephone-
i will hear you.
Don't be sick, grandma.
Don't be sick.
This is me, billy.
Please don't be sick.
As must be obvious,
this is a house hovered over
by mr. Death,
that omnipresent player
to the third and final act
of every life.
And it's been said,
and probably rightfully so
that what follows this life
is one of the unfathomable
mysteries-
an area of darkness which we
the living reserve for the dead.
Or so it is said.
For in a moment, a child
will try to cross that bridge
which separates
light and shadow.
And of course he must take
the only known route:
That indistinct highway
through the region we call
the twilight zone.
I want to see grandma.
Oh, honey, we can't
see her right now
because she... she's
not feeling very well.
She isn't in any pain.
Can we see her?
Well, i wouldn't advise it,
not that it would hurt her,
but i... i don't think
she'd even recognize you.
Oh, we'd recognize her.
All right, chris.
Honey, you might as well
put him to bed. Yeah.
I want to see grandma.
Billy,
try to understand this.
Your grandmother's sick.
She's very sick.
So why don't you wait
till she gets well again.
I want to see her now.
Come on, honey,
don't do that.
Come on now.
Well, all right, billy,
just for a minute.
Billy...
if your grandmother
acts kind of strange
remember, it's just
because of all the medicine.
Here... blow
your nose.
Good boy.
The family would
like to see her now.
Grandma!
My angel...
are you sick, grandma?
Not no more.
Then why don't you get up?
Hello, ma.
Who are you?
I'm your son, chris.
Your son.
No... no.
My son was taken away...
from me by a woman.
This is my son now-
billy, my son.
What's the matter,
grandma?
It will be so lonely.
I wish you could go
with grandma, billy.
Where?
Away...
far away, billy.
Together, the two of us.
Just you and me, billy.
No one else.
Just you and...
me.
Grandma.
Grandma!
Billy!
Billy?
Billy, didn't you
hear me calling you?
No.
You know you're
not supposed to play
so close to the pond.
What are you doing?
Looking at the fishes.
Well, it's getting cold.
Let's go inside now.
What's that?
Your grandmother's
bracelet.
Honey, why
don't you go up
and play in your room
for a while, huh?
Chris...
what's the matter?
Oh, it's...
it's billy.
He's been walking around
in a trance all day.
Well, he misses
her already.
You know how
close they were.
Yes, i know.
What is that
supposed to mean?
I mean they
were too close.
It wasn't right.
You know that.
You heard what she said,
she called himherson.
She didn't mean that.
Didn't she?
No.
Sylvia, for
heaven's sakes
she was full of sedatives
and she was dying.
Oh, i'm sorry,
chris, it's just...
i guess we're
all upset today.
Hey. Why don't you
come over and play?
Is it cold there?
I had weenies for lunch.
What did you have?
Maybe they'll fix my tricycle.
Billy.
Who are you talking to?
Grandma.
She's lonesome.
She wanted to know
if i can come stay with her.
Can i, mama?
Can i?
Mrs. Bayles?
Oh, just a minute,
shirley.
Feel like being alone?
No, that's the
last thing i want.
Well, i'll make us
some coffee.
Yes, shirley,
what is it?
Mrs. Bayles...
mrs. Bayles.
My name is peterson.
I hate to bother you
at a time like this.
The girl told me about
your mother-in-law's funeral.
What is it?
Well, it's about
your boy.
Billy?
He's all right,
mrs. Bayles.
I just put him
down for his nap,
and he's all right.
But i'm not.
I've been sitting here
shaking for 20 minutes
thinking about
what might have happened.
What might have happened,
mr. Peterson?
Your son
almost got himself killed.
Ran right out
in front of my car from nowhere.
Lucky thing i'm a cautious
driver, mr. Bayles.
Oh, excuse me.
Billy doesn't play
in the streets.
I know, mr. Bayles,
that's why i didn't say anything
when he went out.
All right, shirley,
what happened?
Well, he played
in the streets today.
He ran right out
in front of my car-
didn't even have time
to put the brakes on.
I couldn't have missed him
by more than a few inches.
It wasn't my fault,
mr. Bayles, honest.
All right, shirley,
apparently it wasn't
anybody's fault.
Mr. Bayles...
i think you'd better have
a talk with your boy.
A talk? What about?
Well... when i saw
that he was all right,
i asked him why he did
a crazy thing like that,
running out in the middle
of a busy street.
He said somebody told him to.
Somebody told him to?
Who?
He didn't say.
Mr. Bayles, you know
i'd never tell billy
to do a thing like that.
Who else did he
talk to, shirley?
No one, he didn't
talk to no one.
He just sat up in
his room all day long
just talking on
that toy telephone.
Honest.
Chris...
i'll be
right there.
I'm sorry,
mr. Peterson.
Don't be sorry, just
be glad the boy's safe.
Listen.
Oh, for
heaven's sake.
Hi, pumpkin.
We're back.
Billy, what's
this business
about your running
into the street?
You know,
you had us worried.
I'm sorry.
Well, why did
you do it?
I don't know.
Billy, who were
you talking to
on the phone
just now?
Nobody.
Don't fib to me, billy.
Who were you talking to?
No one!
You're going to tell me!
You hear, now? I mean it!
Easy.
Hey...
mom doesn't like me
anymore, does she?
Why, sure she
does, billy.
She's just upset.
Billy, i'm going to
tell you something.
Now, i want you to
try to understand.
You're not going to see
your grandma anymore.
She didn't go away,
like we said.
She died, billy. Do you
know what that means?
Yes...
i know.
Billy, i know you're
just pretending
to talk to her
on that phone.
I know it's just
a game you made up.
But, billy, for me,
don't do it in front
of your mother.
Why?
Well, because she...
just don't,
hmm?
Okay.
...to me about mommy.
Darling, aren't
you coming to bed?
Chris, don't
shut me out.
Oh, i'm sorry.
I was just...
i know.
Funerals stink.
I wanted to remember
her the way she was.
Now i'll always
think of her that way.
I know how hard
everything's been on you, syl.
Everything you've
had to go through.
But mother never
meant any harm.
I suppose not.
No, it's true.
She had two children before me.
She lost them both.
She just couldn't let go.
I was all she had.
Except for billy.
But billy was me again.
A chance to go back.
To pretend all those
other years never happened.
I know it wasn't right
or fair to you, syl,
but, believe me,
no matter what she did,
she did it
out of love.
Love for whom?
Oh, syl...
oh, i'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
I really didn't.
Why, you're trembling.
Let's go to bed.
Hooray for peter pan!
That's a good story, grandma.
That's our secret,
isn't it?
Nobody knows but us.
Can i have a chocolate
ice cream bar?
My telephone!
My telephone! You broke my telephone!
Syl, what is it?
What's the matter?
Oh, i heard her.
Who? She was there. There on the phone.
Syl, snap out of it.
She didn't
say anything,
but i could hear
her breathing.
Syl...
billy...
billy?
Billy!
Billy?
Billy? Billy?
Billy!
Oh, no... no...
no...
no, no, no...
no, no...
she took him...
she took him away.
She took him.
Don't say that.
Yes, she did.
She took him.
Oh, syl, syl, don't...
don't say that.
How are his chances?
Well, they're
not so good.
If we'd have got him
a few minutes earlier...
well, the doctor will
be here in a few minutes.
He'll give your
wife something.
Thanks.
Mother...
if you can hear me, listen.
You said you loved billy.
At his birthday, you...
you picked him up and...
and you hugged him.
And you said
he gave you life again.
If you really love billy...
give him back.
He's only five.
He hasn't even started.
He doesn't know anything
about going to school...
or girlfriends...
or wearing long pants...
even pitching a baseball.
He's hardly been
out of this room...
out of this house.
There's a whole world
he hasn't even touched.
Mother...
you said billy
gave you life again.
Now you can givehimlife.
If you really love him,
let him live.
Give him back!
Give him back, ma.
Ma?
Yeah...
yeah, we got him.
yeah!
Mrs. Bayles?
I don't know how we did it,
but he's going
to be all right.
Chris!
Oh, chris!
A toy telephone,
an act of faith,
a set of improbable
circumstances all combine
to probe a mystery,
to fathom a depth,
to send a facet of light
into a dark after-region
to be believed or disbelieved
depending on your
frame of reference-
a fact or a fantasy,
a substance or a shadow-
but all of it very much a part
of the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
the creator oftwilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, you'll ride up-front
in this wagon on a trek west.
Your itinerary
is across the great plains,
over the rockies
to a point in new mexico.
And you'll ride alongside
mr. Cliff robertson
in a strange tale of a handful
of american pioneers
who made a detour in time
and found themselves
one afternoon
on the fringe of the future.
Our story is called
"a hundred yards over the rim."
And, believe me,
it's quite a view.
I hope we'll see you then.
See the newandy griffith show
each week
over most of these stations.
Consult local listings.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org