Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Thank you, william.
Yes, sir.
Cut.
What's your point?
That, if it were possible
for a person
to go back in time,
there'd be nothing in
the world to prevent them
from altering the course
of history? Is that it?
That's right.
Let's say, corrigan,
that you go
back in time.
It's october, 1929,
the day before the
stock market crashed.
Now, you know that,
on the following morning,
securities are going
to tumble into an abyss.
Now, using this
prior knowledge,
there's a hundred
things you could do
to protect yourself.
But i'd be
an anachronism.
I really don't
belong back there.
You could sell out the
day before the crash.
But what if i did,
and started the crash earlier?
Now, history tells us that
on october 24, 1929,
the bottom fell out
of the stock market.
That's a fixed date.
It exists as an event
in the history of our times.
It can't be altered.
And i say it can.
Now, what's
to prevent me, say,
from going to a broker
on the morning of
october 23 or 22?
Witness a theoretical argument,
washington, d.c., the present.
Four intelligent men talking
about an improbable thing
like going back in time.
A friendly debate
revolving around a simple issue:
Could a human being change
what has happened before?
Interesting and theoretical
because who ever heard
of a man going back in time?
Before tonight, that is.
Because this
is the twilight zone.
Gentlemen, i'm afraid
i'm going to have
to leave time travel
to h.g. Wells.
I'm much too tired
to go into any more
metaphysics this evening.
And, since no one
has ever gone back into time,
i find the whole blame subject
much too theoretical anyway.
Phil, i'll probably
see you over the weekend.
Don't get lost back
in time, now, corrigan.
I certainly shall not.
Good night, gentlemen.
Good night, pete.
So long,
corrigan.
Well, where do
we get a fourth?
Good evening.
I'm desperately sorry,
mr. Corrigan.
That was
very clumsy of me.
I think i shall survive,
william. I really do.
Did you... did you
have a coat, sir?
No. I'm rushing the season
a little tonight, william.
I felt spring in the air,
so i came out like this.
Well, april
isspring, sir.
What is the date,
william?
Uh... april 14, sir.
April 14, 1961, right?
I beg your pardon, sir?
Oh, yes, 1961.
Well, good night, william.
Take care of yourself.
Yes, sir.
Home.
Home. That's it.
I'll go home...
all right, all right.
Have a bit of patience.
I'm coming.
Yes?
Oh, i'm sorry.
Isn't this number 19
12th street?
That's right.
Whom do you wish to see?
I used to live here.
This... this used to
be the oldest building
in this part of town.
What's that?
Well, that is, as i remember it,
it used to be.
Now, look here, young man.
I can't stand around
all evening
talking about
silly things
like which is the oldest
building in the section.
Now, if there's
nothing else...
do you have a room?
Yes, i have rooms
for acceptable boarders.
Do you come from around here?
Yes, i do.
Army veteran?
Yes...
yes, as a matter of fact, i am.
May i inquire
as to what business you're in?
I'm an engineer.
Oh, really?
A professional man.
Well, right upstairs
and to the right.
Good evening, mrs. Landers.
Good evening.
Off to the play?
Yes. Dinner, and then
off to the play.
Well, enjoy yourselves.
Applaud the president
for me.
We'll certainly
do that.
Good night.
Have a good time.
What did you say?
Well... what did i say?
To the officer. You
said something to him.
She just said
something to you
about the president.
She told me
to applaud him.
Where might your
sympathies lie?
Yes, young man,
which army were you in?
Well, i was in...
the army of the republic, of course.
Well, then why
make such a thing
of applauding
president lincoln?
It's his due,
we figure.
That and everything else,
god bless him.
You're going to a play tonight?
We may or may not,
depending on when my husband
makes up his mind
to call a carriage
to get us to the theater
and to dinner.
What theater?
What play?
Well, ford's theater,
of course.
Ford's theater...
are you all right?
Are you feeling
all right?
What's the name of the play?
I beg
your pardon?
The play- the one you're going
to tonight at ford's theater-
what's
it called?
It's calledour american cousin.
Our american cousin...
and lincoln's
going to be there.
And it's april 14, 1865,
isn't it?
Really, sir,
i'd call these actions
most strange.
Itisapril 14, 1865.
Let me in! Let me in!
The president's going
to be shot tonight!
Let me in!
Now, what has
this one done?
While you idiots
are sitting here,
you're going to
lose a president.
That's what
he's been yelling
all the way over
to the station.
And that's why the doorman at ford's
theater popped him on the head.
He tried to pound his way
right through the stage door,
yelling some sort
of nonsense
about "president lincoln's
going to be shot."
President lincoln will be
shot, tonight, at the theater.
A man named booth.
And how would you
be knowing this?
Are you some kind of a
clairvoyant or something?
I only know what i know.
If i told you how i knew,
you wouldn't believe me.
Look...
keep me here
if you like-
lock me up-
but hear me out.
Let him sleep it off.
Somebody better get
to the president's box
at the theater.
Keep him out of there!
Put a cordon of men
around him!
A man named
john wilkes booth
is going to assassinate
him tonight!
Wellington, sergeant.
Jonathan wellington.
Well... and what can we do
for you, mr. Wellington?
That man you just
had incarcerated-
mr. Corrigan, i believe
you said his name was?
Drunk, sir.
That's probably
what he is.
Drunk or... or perhaps ill.
I wonder if he might be
remanded in my custody?
He might well be a war veteran.
I would hate to see him
placed in jail.
You say you want us
to remand him in your custody?
Precisely.
I'll be fully responsible
for him.
I think perhaps
i might be able to help him.
All right, sir,
if that's the way
you'd like it.
Have corrigan
brought back in here.
This gentleman is going
to look out for him.
That's real decent of you,
sir. Real decent of you.
I'll be outside.
Have him brought out to me,
if you would?
I will indeed,
sir. Yes.
Uh... about that
corrigan, sir.
What about him?
Well, wouldn't it
be wise, sir, if...?
If what?
He seemed so positive, sir.
So sure.
About the president, i mean.
And what
should we do-
send all
available police
to ford's
theater?
And on what
authority?
On the word
of some demented fool
who probably left his mind
in gettysburg?
If i were
you, mister,
i'd be considerably
more thoughtful
in sizing up
a situation
or you'll
not advance
in the next
20 years.
Now, be good enough
to step aside
so i can get on
with my work.
Sergeant,
it wouldn't hurt if...
it wouldn't
hurt if what?
Well, i only meant
to suggest, sir,
that if perhaps
we placed an extra guard
in the box
with the president...
the president
has enough guards!
The whole federal army
is at his disposal.
And, if they're satisfied
with the arrangements
for his protection, so am i!
So should you.
Here.
Try this.
It'll make you
feel better.
Better?
Who are you anyway?
At the moment,
i'm your benefactor.
Apparently,
your only friend.
I'm in the
government service.
But, as a young man
in college,
i dabbled in
medicine of a sort.
Medicine?
Medicine of the mind.
Psychiatrist.
Don't know the term.
What about the symptoms?
They do
interest me.
This story you were telling
about the president
being assassinated...
what time is it?
This time?
Half past 7:00.
Play doesn't begin for another
three-quarters of an hour.
What gave you the idea...
that the president
would be assassinated?
I just happen to know,
that's all.
You have a premonition?
I've got a devil
of a lot more
than a premonition.
Lincolnwill
be assassinated
unless somebody
tries to prevent it.
I shall try
to prevent it
if you
can convince me
that you're neither
drunk nor insane.
If i told you what i was,
you'd be convinced
i was insane,
so all i'm going
to tell you is this:
I happen to know
for a fact
that a man named
john wilkes booth
will assassinate
president lincoln
in his box
at ford's theater.
I don't know what time
it'll happen.
That's something i forgot.
Something
you forgot?
Yes, listen, i...
here. That hasn't
been treated properly.
You'd best cover it.
That's odd.
What is?
Suddenly, i feel faint.
I feel weak,
as if i were...
as if you were what?
As if i were...
suddenly drunk or...
i've never felt this way before.
I've never... i've ne...
you! You...
you devil.
You drugged me, didn't you?
You drugged me!
Had to, my young friend.
You're a very sick man,
and a sick man
doesn't belong in jail.
He belongs in a comfortable accommodation
where he can
sleep and rest
and regain
his composure-
hisreason.
Rest...
mr. Corrigan.
I'll be
back soon.
Please...
please, you've
got to believe me.
Lincoln will be shot tonight.
And that's odd...
...because i'm beginning
to believe you.
Good night, mr. Corrigan.
Rest well.
Somebody...
please...
let me out!
I know!
I know...
our president's
going to be assassinated.
No need to break
the door down, officer.
I've got an extra key.
Now, step aside,
if you don't mind.
Are you all right?
What's happened?
What time is it?
You've got to tell me
what time it is.
It's 10:00.
Come on, corrigan.
You've got to tell me
what you know about this.
You may be a madman or a drunk
or i don't know what,
but you've got me convinced.
I've been everywhere
from the mayor's office
to the police
commissioner's house
trying to get a special guard
for the president.
Then go yourself.
Find out where
he's sitting,
and get right up
alongside of him.
He'll be shot
from behind.
Let me help you up.
He was shot from behind.
That's how it happened.
Then the assassin jumped
from the box to the stage
and ran out of the wings.
You're telling
me this
as if it has
already happened.
Ithashappened- it happened
a hundred years ago-
and i'm here to see
that itdoesn'thappen.
Where's the man who brought
me here? Where's wellington?
Wellington? There's no
one here by that name.
Don't tell me there's
no one here by that name.
He brought me here.
He lives in this room.
There's no one here
by that name.
I tell you, the man
who brought me here's na...
"j.w.b."
Of course.
Mr. John wilkes booth,
who lives in this room.
And that's who
brought you here.
He told me his name
was wellington.
And that's why
he drugged me.
He gave me wine,
and he drugged me.
He didn't want me
to stop it.
He's the one
who's going to do it.
You've got to get
to that theater.
You've got to stop him.
John wilkes booth-
he's going to kill lincoln.
Please, you've got
to stop him!
The president's
been shot!
An actor
shot lincoln.
Oh...
you were
right.
You did
know.
Oh, my dear god.
I tried to tell you.
I tried to warn you!
Why didn't you listen?
Why didn't you listen?!
Why didn't you listen to me?!
Good evening,
mr. Corrigan.
Did you forget
something?
What? Forget something?
You left here
just a moment ago
and i thought you
forgot something.
A moment ago?
Where's william?
William, sir?
There's no
william on duty.
There's no one here
named william, sir.
Oh, pete. Back
so soon, eh?
Want to join us?
We're talking
about the best ways
of amassing a fortune.
What are your
tried and true methods?
You were talking
about time travel-
about going
back in time.
Oh, well, we're on a new tack now:
Money, and the best ways to acquire it.
Listen...
i've got something
to tell you.
Why, of course,
old man.
You all right?
Why, yes.
Yes,
i'm all right.
Well, then, draw up a
chair and come over here
and listen to
a lot of palaver
of self-made
swindlers.
William, here,
has the best method.
William?!
Oh, yes, my method for achieving
security is by far the best.
You simply inherit it.
Comes to you
in a beribboned box.
I was just telling
the boys here, corrigan,
my great-grandfather was on the
police force here in washington
the night of lincoln's
assassination.
He went all over town
trying to warn people
that something might happen.
How he figured it out,
nobody seems to know.
It's certainly
not recorded anyplace.
But there was
so much publicity about it
that people never forgot him.
He became chief of police,
then a councilman,
did some wheeling and dealing in
land, and became a millionaire.
Well,
gentlemen,
shall we get back
to our bridge?
What was it you wanted
to say, corrigan?
William...
william, didn't you
use to work here
as an attendant?
Didn't you spill
coffee on me?
Now, listen here, old chum.
I was a member of this club
while you were still going
to prep school.
I'm certainly
not a snob,
but, well, sir, an attendant?
I really must protest.
In the matter of time
travel, gentlemen,
some things can be changed.
Others can't.
Just as you
say, pete.
Let's see,
i dock.
I bid
one spade.
Well, i'll
pass that one.
Here's
two spades.
Looks peaked,
doesn't he?
Acting so strangely.
What's the
matter with him?
Mr. Peter corrigan,
lately returned
from a place "back there"-
a journey into time with
highly questionable results.
Proving, on one hand,
that the threads of history
are woven tightly,
and the skein of events
cannot be undone.
But, on the other hand,
there are small fragments of
tapestry that can be altered.
Tonight's thesis,
to be taken as you will,
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
This, in the parlance
of the 20th century,
is a used car lot-
a graveyard of active ghosts
who, by virtue of some
exceptional salesmanship
and an indian rubber
stretching of the truth,
remain as commodities
in a world that, by rights,
they should have left
generations ago.
Mr. Jack carson plays the role
of a larceny-loaded con man
suddenly prevented
from telling a falsehood.
Next week onthe twilight zone,
a most bizarre tale
that we call "the whole truth."
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
be sure and see
the colgate-palmolive company's
new comedy show
my sister eileen
wednesday night
on many of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org