Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
This object, should any of you
have lived underground
for the better parts
of your lives
and never had occasion
to look toward the sky
is an airplane, its official
designation, a dc-3.
We offer this
rather obvious comment
because this particular
airplane,
the one you're looking at,
is a freak.
Now, most airplanes take off
and land as per schedule.
On rare occasions, they crash.
But all airplanes can be counted
on doing one or the other.
Now, yesterday morning,
this particular airplane ceased
to be just a commercial carrier.
As of its arrival,
it became an enigma,
a seven-ton puzzle made out
of aluminum, steel, wire
and a few thousand
other component parts
none of which add up
to the right thing.
In just a moment,
we're going to show you
the tail end of its history.
We're going to give you
90 percent of the jigsaw pieces
and you and mr. Sheckly here
of the federal aviation agency
will assume the problem
of putting them together,
along with finding
the missing pieces.
This we offer
as an evening's hobby,
a little
extracurricular diversion,
which is really the national
pastime inthe twilight zone.
Flight 453 to kansas city
now ready for boarding
through gate number 14.
Flight 453, gate 14.
Passengers, please board.
Let's go in there!
What about it?
You need a can opener?
What, do they got
a hot poker game in there?
You tell me.
What about it?
You dead, asleep or what?
George, what's going on here?
There isn't any luggage.
Hey, george!
Ask them who's
responsible
for forgetting
all the luggage.
You better come in here
and check me out.
I don't know what
yourproblems are,
but you're going to have
to tell the passengers
their luggage has
been delayed.
Some idiot let
this plane take off
without so much as
an envelope in there.
I'd be happy to,
except for one thing.
What?
There aren't any passengers!
Come here.
Robbins, you better
call the airport police
and get them over here.
I'll get bengston
in operations.
I hope...
what?
I hope he lets me
finish the story
before he has me committed.
There was nobody
on the plane,
absolutely nobody.
I don't know...
how could it stop
without somebody
on that plane?
All right, ladies
and gentlemen,
would you knock
it off, please?
This is mr. Sheckly
from the federal
aviation agency.
He'd like to continue
the questioning.
She's all
yours, sir.
Gentlemen, this is
not a formal hearing.
It's more in the nature
of a preliminary meeting.
As your operations
chief noted,
we're here to unearth
as many facts as we can.
I'd appreciate hearing from you
only facts.
You can save us all
a lot of time
if you'd avoid
personal hypotheses,
so we can keep the air clear
and not clutter it up
with six dozen theories.
Theories happen
to be my business.
In the 20-odd years,
i've been with the f.a.a.
I've got a pretty
good record
in putting together
jigsaw puzzles.
Maybe some of them
haven't been
as abnormal as this one,
but i'll lay
my betting average
on the line
any hour of the day.
All right?
Let's get down to business.
Now, which one of you
is cousins?
Right here, sir.
You're the ramp
attendant?
Yes, sir.
You were on duty
when flight
107 arrived?
That's right, sir.
Ship came in normally...
did you notice
anything abnormal?
No, she came in
right on the button.
She followed
my signal up the ramp.
She stopped right on the mark
where i told her to.
She cut her engines
when i gave her the signal.
Did you see
the pilots?
When i signal a plane in,
my attention's on the marks
and on the aircraft
on either side of her...
well, actually,
i don't remember...
bengston, is your dispatcher
here from buffalo?
Well, that's me, sir.
I just arrived.
Will you take
a look at this?
Yes, sir, that's
the flight plan.
Did you see
the pilot sign it?
I was at his elbow
this morning
at 11:12 a.m.
Pilot william j. Slocum?
Yes, sir.
Copilot john o'brien,
that's the name of
the first officer?
Yes, sir.
Did you see them
board the aircraft?
Not...
not exactly, sir.
I saw them leave
the dispatch office
and head
for the field.
But to the best
of your knowledge,
that was the crew
of flight 107
when they took off from buffalo
at 11:30 this morning?
To the best
of my knowledge.
William j. Slocum,
john o'brien.
Good pilots, both of them.
Sober, reliable, the best men.
I'm not casting any
stones, mr. Bengston.
It's just that
the names are so...
so familiar.
Well, that'll
be all now,
but stay around where
you can be reached.
Mr. Sheckly...
this is paul malloy,
our public relations man.
Public relations, huh?
How much public, and
what kind of relations
are you poor guys going
to have after this one?
I got 22 years in this saddle
and i've never been licked yet.
Oh, some of them
take a long time.
Couple of tons of metal
spread over 50 square miles
of countryside.
Sometimes, all it is
is a misplaced air scoop
or maybe a loose bolt
in the elevator hinge or...
once in a blue moon,
a pilot with a psychosis.
But it's always something.
And that something
always shows up.
You're talking about a crashed
aircraft, mr. Sheckly.
We're talking about
a disappearing act.
Now, look, this just
couldn't have happened.
An aircraft can't take off
with a full crew, 13 passengers
and land an hour and 20 minutes
later with nobody on it.
It simply is not within
the realm of possibility!
Mr. Malloy, you
are dead right.
But the fact
is it happened.
It can't
have happened.
An airliner couldn't land
that perfectly
with nobody controlling it.
There must be...
therehasto be an explanation-
a legitimate, valid, believable,
understandable explanation.
There's only one
possible explanation.
These 13 people had parachutes.
Now, they kept them
in the baggage compartment.
That's why there
wasn't any luggage.
Then, someplace between here
and buffalo, they jumped out
for a gag
or something, i guess.
That's brilliant.
That's just brilliant.
And what about
the pilots, mr. Holmes?
Or is that part
just elementary?
Maybe they hid
in the restroom.
Sneaked out of the plane
after i went to make
the phone call.
Oh, cut it out.
That's quite an imagination
you have, mr. Cousins.
I'll give you that.
Hey, what if...?
What if...?
What if what?
No, i don't know.
It gets me.
I'll tell you
this, though.
I get spooked just
standing around here.
I get more spooked
inside, though.
All those empty blue seats
just staring at you.
Look, boys...
we have been theorizing
for six solid hours.
I'm just a simple-minded
vice president
in charge of operations,
but i've got a passel of newsmen
out there bugging me to death
as to what kind of
haunted operations
we are running here.
Tell them to keep
their shirts on.
That's whatyou
should be telling them
or a reasonable facsimile
of an explanation.
Then you better get
me another head
and a couple
of sets of arms,
because i've been on
that phone for six hours.
I've had every news service,
every television network
and a couple
of professional mind readers
trying to figure out
what the great big mystery is
we're supposed
to be hiding in here.
And you know how long i can
keep it up, mr. Bengston?
Maybe another 15 minutes
and then the whole thing
is going to pop wide open
and we're going to be stuck
with rotten egg on our face.
And sheckly
and the government
are going to take
our franchise away from us.
Incompetence,
mental instability,
and you name it,
you can have it!
Have you checked out
every one of the names
on this passenger manifest?
No, i have not.
That's all i need now
is to have a small army
of relatives
from upstate new york
clutching at my lapels,
asking me for a
definitive statement
as to where
their loved ones are
who took flight 107 out
of buffalo this morning.
You mean to say,
you haven't even
had one inquiry yet?
Now, that's weird,
isn't it?
Not a single inquiry.
But the ship arrived
only six hours ago.
Maybe they haven't had
time to miss anyone.
No, i'm kidding myself.
Of course, someone would have
made an inquiry by now.
There goes
that old feeling again.
What feeling?
This passenger manifest...
the names look so familiar.
Robbins, you said
something before.
What do
you mean?
About the
parachutes?
No, no, no,
you said something else.
You said you looked
inside the plane
and you saw the blue seats.
Yeah, i said
something like that.
They are blue,
but when i first looked in
the plane, the seats were brown.
Wait a minute,
they were red.
I remember thinking
how faded they were,
but theywerered.
What is all this nonsense?
Haven't we got enough trouble
without you guys worrying
about the interior decoration?
Bengston, come here.
Do you see a number
on that tail?
Of course,
i see a number.
Read it off to me.
N-6-7-5-8-8.
Hey, robbins.
Do you see that same
number on the tail?
N-8-0-4-7-5-8.
Hey, what's the matter?
Are we going crazy
or something?
We're all seeing
different numbers.
Gentlemen, i have a theory.
Unfortunately, the only way
i can prove it or disprove it
is going to put me
in considerable jeopardy.
Any one of you ever hear
of mass suggestion?
So?
I think that's what
we're dealing with now-
a kind of hypnosis.
To put it more bluntly
or perhaps a little
less believably,
i don't think this airplane
is really here.
I think every
one of us
had a little hypnosis
performed on him,
a little suggestion.
Someone somewhere told us that
a dc-3 is inside this hangar
and that it landed this morning.
That's what they said.
So every one of us
had pictured in his mind
a dc-3 as he knows one.
Therefore, one of us
sees the seats as blue,
another sees them as brown,
still another sees them as red.
I read one number
off the tail.
Two other guys
read two others.
Don't you understand
what i'm trying to say?
This particular aircraft
doesn't exist.
It really isn't
here at all.
Are you mad?
Are you trying
to tell us
this is
an illusion?
It's no illusion,
it's here.
I can feel it,
I'm going to prove to you
that you're wrong,
or i'm going to prove
to you that i'm wrong.
And if i happen to be wrong,
i also happen to be dead.
Robbins, will you roll the plane
outside and start the engines?
Sheckly, are you sure
you know what you're doing?
I know what i'm doing.
Start the engines.
If this plane
is imaginary,
then so are those engines
and so are those props.
So if i stick
my hand in them,
nothing is going
to happen.
But if my theory
is for the birds
and those props
are real,
make sure you
notify my wife.
Go ahead, do it.
Well, gentlemen...
i believe i've
proven my point.
Bengston?
Malloy?!
Cousins!
Robbins!
Bengston!
Malloy!
Bengston! Malloy!
Hey, where are you people?
Hey, bengston!
Where are you peop...?
What happened?
Bengston, what happened?
What are you talking about?
Aren't you...?
You're sheckly, aren't you?
Aren't you sheckly
of the f.a.a.?
What kind of a gag is this?
Who do you think i am?
What's going on?
What is
the problem?
What's the problem?
Bengston, are you
off your rocker?
One minute, there's a hangar
full of men and an aircraft.
The next minute i prove
that not only doesn't
the aircraft exist, but...
what else didn't exist?
Mr. Sheckly,
are you drunk?
Or are you
sick or what?
Bengston...
bengston,
where's malloy?
Malloy?
Malloy, you better get up
and zero in
your boss here
as to the cause and
effects of insanity.
You...
"miss penny jackson,
beautiful, young movie starlet
"is shown here arriving
"on trans-east airline,
flight 107
which arrived from buffalo
this morning."
What's going on?
Who is this guy?
How could they have
taken that picture?
How could they
say it landed
and everything
went...?
Went what?
You know this guy?
Mr. Sheckly...
this is paul malloy,
our public relations man.
What are you talking about?
I know who it is.
What's going on here?
Maybe you'd
better tell us.
What is so odd
about a picture of
a flight arrival?
What's so od...?
Bengston,
you check me out.
Didn't that
flight arrive
with nobody on it?
No crew,
no stewardess,
no passengers,
no baggage?
No, mr. Sheckly.
Flight 107
from our airline
arrived at 12:50
today on schedule.
You mean to tell me,
you're not missing
an aircraft?
That's exactly what he's
telling you, mister.
We're not missing
any flight 107,
or any other flight.
Well... how
could that be?
You never missed
a flight 107?
That's right.
You were the examiner
on that one.
On what one?
We lost
just one flight
in some 20-odd
years, just one.
Flight 107.
But, mr. Sheckly,
that was some 17
or 18 years ago.
Flight 107
out of buffalo.
But like i said, that
was 17, 18 years ago.
Well, what
happened to her?
Lost in the fog,
never found.
We figured she must
have gone off course,
went out over the ocean,
went down there.
You never found her?
Never found her.
Mr. Sheckly here
investigated.
But that was one case
you were never
able to button up.
Nobody was ever able
to button it up.
Just sits on
the books as lost,
presumed crashed
for reasons unknown.
Mr. Sheckly...
why don't you let me
drive you home?
For reasons unknown?
But i never been licked
on a case yet... never.
We've always
found the causes.
Always.
We've always
found the causes.
Always.
I never been licked
on a case yet.
We've always found the causes.
Always found the causes.
We've always
found the causes.
I never been licked
on a case yet.
I guess so.
Flight 107- 13 people.
Pilot- william j. Slocum.
Copilot- john o'brien.
What happened to you?
What went wrong?
Where did you go down?
Flight 107!
Hey, flight 107!
Why didn't you leave a clue?!
Why didn't you make a contact?!
Why didn't you?!
Why didn't you leave a clue?!
Why didn't you ever tell anyone
what happened to you?
Picture of a man
with an achilles' heel,
a mystery that landed
in his life
and then turned
into a heavy weight,
dragged across the years
to ultimately take
the form of an illusion.
Now, that's the clinical answer
that they put on the tag
as they take him away.
But if you choose to think
that the explanation
has to do with
an airborneflying dutchman,
a ghost ship
in a fog-enshrouded night
on a flight that never ends,
then you're doing your business
in an old stand...
inthe twilight zone.
Rod serling, creator
ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week
onthe twilight zone,
we use a camera like an x ray
and look under the skin of a
neighborhood of men and women.
It's a little experiment
in human nature and behavior
on the night
that a conelrad broadcast
shatters their composure
with an announcement
of terse terror-
a bomb is coming.
Most of our stories
are a little far out.
This one is very close in.
You'll see what i mean next week
when we present "the shelter."
Be sure and watchgunsmoke
starring james arness,
saturday nights over most
of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org