Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
A brief if frenetic introduction
to mr. Archibald beechcroft
a child of the 20th century
a product of
the population explosion
and one of the inheritors
of the legacy of progress.
Mr. Beechcroft again.
This time act ii of his
daily battle for survival.
And in just a moment
our hero will begin his
personal one-man rebellion
against the mechanics of his age
and to do so
he will enlist certain aids
available only
in the twilight zone.
Why, you clumsy clod!
Oh, i'm sorry,
mr. Beechcroft.
I didn't notice
where i was going.
That's precisely
your problem.
Feeling ill,
beechcroft?
If you'll forgive a
personal observation
you're not
looking too well.
I'm all right,
mr. Rogers.
Keeping yourself fit
is not only a
personal obligation.
Oh, no, in a larger sense
it's part of
your responsibility
to your job
and to the firm
that employs you.
I'm not unaware
of that, mr. Rogers.
Well, then why don't you
pull yourself
together, man?
Get some sleep at night.
Eat regular meals, lots of milk
and fresh vegetables.
Greens! Oh, you can't beat
those greens for vitamins.
I'm a spinach and
lettuce man myself.
I even have them
for breakfast.
Well, if people wouldn't
look at me a little tilt.
But the power's in
the greens, beechcroft.
The power's definitely
in the greens.
You're not drinking,
are you, beechcroft?
I don't drink,
mr. Rogers.
Well, then,
you don't drink
and you don't stay
out late at night...
are you watching
your diet?
If you'd really like
to know, mr. Rogers
if you'd really like
to know precisely
why i am so dead tired
you ought to try coming
to work on the subway
at 7:30 every morning
then jamming
into an elevator
like part of
a herd of cattle
then working in that...
in that cacophonous din
that you call an office.
Always get jostled,
always get shoved
always get
pushed around.
Take hold of yourself, beechcroft.
For goodness sakes,
man, take hold.
I'll take hold,
mr. Rogers.
I'll take hold
when i can achieve
that millennium
that absolute perfection
that comes with solitude.
You read me, mr. Rogers?
People.
People, people!
If i had my way
here's how i'd
fix the universe.
I'd eliminate the people.
I mean, cross them off
get rid of them, destroy
them, decimate them
and there'd only be
one man left-
me, archibald
beechcroft, esquire.
Why, you are quite mad,
beechcroft.
Do you know that?
People!
Mr. Beechcroft.
Mr. Beechcroft!
Here's a place
for you, sir.
I've been saving it.
I am obliged, henry.
Oh, think
nothing of it.
I was...
well, i was just
trying to make up
for this morning.
This morning?
When i spilled
coffee on your coat.
I'm really very sorry
about that,
mr. Beechcroft.
Oh, it's all right.
A friend of mine
works in a bookstore
around the corner.
I went there
first part
of the lunch break.
I got you this.
The mind and the matter:
How you can achieve
the ultimate power
of concentration.
A little on
the occult side
isn't that, henry?
Maybe so,
mr. Beechcroft
but this friend
of mine is...
well, you might say
he's a student of the mind.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, he swears by that book.
He says, to the best
of his knowledge
it's the only one in existence.
Would you believe it,
mr. Beechcroft
i've seen my friend
cause a woman
to purchase a chartreuse
and orange scarf.
How's that?
That's right.
We were in
a department store
and he saw some
woman picking over
a table full of scarves
that were on sale.
And he concentrated
real hard
on the chartreuse
and orange one...
and as sure
as i'm sitting here
in the cafeteria of the park
central insurance company
that woman picked up
the chartreuse
and orange scarf.
Why it's the absolute,
unvarnished truth.
Oh, mr. Beechcroft,
i'm so sorry.
Oh, i...
i thank you so much
for the book, henry.
I... i am indebted.
Well... there.
Uh, mr. Beechcroft,
chapter three-
that's the one on
initial phenomena
of intense
concentration.
Chapter three.
Chapter three,
right, chapter three.
They're right.
They're absolutely,
unequivocally right.
Concentration is the most
underrated, unknown power
in the universe.
Why, a person could...
a person could move mountains.
There's really no limit
to what a man could do
using the power properly.
No limit at all.
People.
If i could just concentrate
hard enough to get rid of them.
Concentration,
that's what it takes.
Concentrate on getting
rid of the people.
Mr. Beechcroft!
Your rent is due,
mr. Beechcroft.
Mr. Beechcroft!
Rent's due.
Go away, disappear
be extinct!
Mr. Beechcroft!
Go away, be extinct,
disappear.
Concentration.
Mind over matter.
Today the landlady,
tomorrow the world.
All right, let's get going.
That'll be just
about enough of that.
? for love...?
All well and good.
All well and good,
to be sure.
But what's to do.
How does one occupy his time?
Too much of a good thing?
Well, i wouldn't, uh,
i wouldn't say that.
But you're thinking it.
Bored to death,
aren't you?
Well, uh, let's
just say that, um...
let's just say
that i am temporarily
somewhat accessible
to suggestions as to, uh...
how to occupy
my time.
So?
Let's face it.
You are bored to tears.
Solitude is one thing
but loneliness...
loneliness
is quite another.
Loneliness nothing.
I despise people.
I loathe them.
And i, archibald beechcroft,
have done away with them
for good and all, mind you?
For good and all.
Thought about
any alternatives?
Alternatives
to what?
to this.
You're bored.
You don't
have idea one
how to occupy
your time.
People are
bad enough
but inactivity
is even worse.
How about it?
Oh, don't talk nonsense, please.
I'm content.
I am honestly and truly content
for the first time in my life.
I've rid myself of
the worst scourge there is:
The populace.
Well...
what about
the thing
that's going
to happen to you
in the after...
shut up.
Although,
if the truth be known...
i would like a little
diversion of some kind
any sort of diversion...
like, um...
like, um, an earthquake.
Uh, for goodness sakes,
no, no, no, not that!
How about a nice little
electrical storm?
Forget it!
I believe i've had it
for the day.
It's preying on
you now, isn't it?
I mean, the quiet,
the emptiness.
Well, the thing
of it is...
it's just that
while i don't care
much for people
it's difficult
not having anyone.
Why not get someone?
That's the point,
someone is everyone.
And i can't
stand everyone
or anyone
for that matter.
There frankly
isn't a breed
or a specie
of human being
that i can stomach.
Ever thought of
a cocker spaniel?
Well...
i never cared much
for animals either.
Of course, of course!
Why didn't i think
of it before?
Think of what?
People!
People who i can stand.
People like...
people like myself.
That's what i'll do.
I'll create people,
but they'll be like me.
A world full of archibald beechcrofts.
Now, that's
a thought.
You bet your life
it's a thought.
You bet your sweet life.
That's what i'll do.
I'll will it.
I'll concentrate
and i'll will
that from now on
everyone i see
will be like me.
It's really quite simple.
People.
It's not enough
they're just a mob.
They're a
dishonest mob.
Kindly deposit ten cents please
or shall i call the police.
Will you please
get off my foot
you ugly little man.
12th floor,
everybody out, please.
Sardines!
The noise, the miserable noise.
I'll go out of my mind.
I'll go out
of my ever-loving mind.
A sty, that's what it is.
Nothing
but people
and people
are pigs.
People, people, people, people.
Is there no respite?
Is there no relief?
Herds, droves,
hosts and bevies of people.
Will you people stop
muttering back there?
I'm trying to work.
Had it?
Undeniably.
Coming through
to you, huh?
Without a doubt.
A lot of me
is just as bad
as a lot of them.
So... what's to do now?
I'll just
put it back
the way it was.
Just the way
it was.
Oh!
Oh, mr. Beechcroft,
sir, forgive me...
uh, nothing
serious, henry.
Just, uh, forget it.
Yes?
I was wondering...
that book
i gave you.
Did you get anything out of it?
Well, uh...
not really,
henry, i, uh...
frankly, i thought
it was a lot of pap.
It was interesting,
but totally unbelievable.
Mr. Archibald beechcroft,
a child of the 20th century
who has found out
through trial and error-
and mostly error-
that with all its faults
it may well be
that this is the best
of all possible worlds.
People notwithstanding,
it has much to offer.
Tonight's case in point
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling, creator
ofthe twilight zone
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
It's been said that singularly,
the most difficult feat
of all mankind is to find
a needle in a haystack.
Onthe twilight zonenext time,
we do it one better.
We pose a problem of finding
a martian in a snow bank.
It all adds up to a kind of
extraterrestrial who's who
with a couple of laughs, and
more than a couple of tensions.
We recommend this
to the space buffs
and the jigsaw puzzle addicts.
Next time onthe twilight zone,
our story is called
"will the real martian
please stand up."
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
hi, this is ed sullivan
reminding you that the colgate-
palmolive company
also brings you star-studded
entertainment on our show
on most of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org