Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Oh, i didn't hear you.
Are you sick,
young man?
No.
You look sick.
My husband
looked like that
just before
he died-
all white
and pasty.
No, no, i'm all right.
Just what he said,
just those words-
"i'm all right."
Went to bed.
Next morning, went to wake him-
there he was sprawled out dead.
You don't drink, do you?
No.
Well, that's
what killed
my jack.
I told him
it was the devil's work,
but he wouldn't listen to me.
And you can see where he is now.
Oh, the devil's
all around us, mister,
all around us,
everywhere we go.
If we don't fight him,
if we don't
stand up to him,
we suffer
eternal torment.
Yeah, i'm sure
you're right.
I know i'm right,
and i'll tell you
how i know.
It was on a sunday.
I was ironing, if you please,
and that's when it came
out of a clear blue sky.
Oh, the dear good lord's
own sweet breath
and his voice
like an electric shock-
i was revelated!
Oh, praise him, mister,
and praise his good works!
Do you read the book?
What book is that?
Why, the good book!
Oh, yes, all the time.
You sure you're telling
the truth, now?
We may be a mile underground,
but he hears every word.
Yes, it's the truth!
All right, leviticus,
chapter five, verse two.
Perfect, you're perfect.
Well?
Lady, please!
"Or if a soul touch
any unclean thing,
"whether it be a carcass
of an unclean beast,
"or a carcass
of unclean cattle,
"or a carcass of unclean
creeping things, and if it be
"hidden from him,
he shall also be
unclean and guilty."
Lady, go away!
Don't you want to be saved?
No, i just want
to be left alone!
We're never alone,
young man-
don't you know that?
He's always with us,
and he'll help us
if we only let him,
but we've got
to be saved first.
Here, read this.
Take it, read it!
It'll change your life.
Oh, the devil means
to have you, mister,
but i won't let him.
I'll fight with you,
and we'll win.
Listen to me,
mister,
it's salvation
i'm talking about!
No, no, no!
What you have just witnessed
could be the end
of a particularly
terrifying nightmare.
It isn't.
It's the beginning.
Although alan talbot
doesn't know it,
he's about to enter
a strange new world
too incredible to be real,
too real to be a dream.
It's called the twilight zone.
I'm sorry to
bother you, ma'am,
but, like, i belong to
the junior woodchucks,
and if you buy a
ten-year subscription
to theladies'
home companion,
i get a genuine toy
typewriter free.
Now, what do you say?
No, thank you
very much.
Hi.
You ready?
And willing.
You disappointed?
I'm a little surprised.
I told you
that there were lines
that i did not cross.
I know. I was
going to wait
till after we
got married,
but something
came over me.
I lost my
self-control.
Well, you look
around for it.
And i'll get you
some coffee.
How come so late?
Who's late?
Who's late? You're late.
What, five minutes?
No, 45 minutes.
Honey, i keep telling you,
get rid of that sundial.
Okay, so you overslept.
Just remember,
it wasn't my idea
to leave at 5:00
in the morning.
Look, i did
notoversleep.
I left the hotel
at 4:30 a.m.
I got on the subway,
i got off the subway,
i came here-
therefore...
therefore you must
have stopped someplace
and had a few short beers,
because now it's almost 6:00.
See?
Yeah, i see, but
i don't understand.
Alan, you're going
to be very proud of me.
Why?
You wanted to take
a lunch, huh?
So i roasted us a chicken.
Oh, great!
Jess...
yeah?
Are you sure?
What do you mean?
I mean, do you know
what you're doing?
Yes, i do.
I am a spinster
well over 20 years old...
and i am sound of mind
and sound of body.
I'm going to visit
a town
i have never seen
before
for the purpose
of meeting and impressing
a woman i've never
heard of before
for the purpose
of marrying a guy
i've known
for exactly four days.
What's so odd
about that?
No, i'm serious.
Well, so am i.
Shouldn't you...
shouldn't you know
more about me
or something?
Like what?
I know your name is alan talbot.
I know that you come
from coeurville, new york,
that you live
in a big white house
surrounded by rosebushes
and trees
and that you do
scientific research on a bomb.
Not a bomb, a computer,
electronics.
Now, you see, you're
romanticizing me already.
Don't interrupt.
You're visiting new york city
for the pure
morbid pleasure of it.
You make $600 a month.
You're very kind
to small animals
and very nice
to old chestnut vendors.
And now you're
very lonely.
And you're
desperately in need
of a woman who's five foot three
who answers to the name
of jessica connelly, right?
Right.
And youaresingle.
At the present.
Alan...
do you think i'm going
to like coeurville?
Only if you
happen to like
great little towns
full of warm,
friendly people.
You've only been gone
a week,
and already
you're homesick.
Well, i better like it.
You will, and you'll
love aunt mildred.
Now, come on,
quit stalling!
Walter!
Walter, no!
No, it isn't right.
Send me back.
Walter...
alan...
alan. Alan.
You were having
a nightmare.
What, in the middle
of the morning?
Who's walter?
Who's who?
You kept saying
"walter."
Oh, well, this is
a poor time to tell you,
but he happens
to be my brother.
Oh?
Yes, it's
a tragic situation.
We keep him locked
in the cellar.
I don't like
to think about it.
Oh, alan, you idiot!
I don't know
any walter.
Well, maybe awake, you
don't know any walter,
but asleep, you're
scared to death of him!
I said i don't know
any walter.
Okay...
okay, you big grouch.
You want me to drive?
Sure, but just
be careful.
It's not paid
for yet.
Ooh, changing
of the guard.
Hey, you see that?
Yeah.
I used to play here
when i was a kid.
Every time i ran
away from home,
i got just
about this far.
Hey, you see
that road?
Uh-huh.
Love alley,
we used to call it.
Great place for
sparking the girlies.
And how would you know?
Well, my love, in
sparking circles,
i was known as the
human electrode.
The human electrode.
What am i getting into?
Oh, alan,
it's lovely.
There's the new
brunswick hotel
over there.
They got an ice cream parlor
and a magazine store.
You can also buy
cigarettes in there
if you can prove
you're over 21.
Mr. Van brooks
isverystrict
about that.
Do you think
i could get by?
Well, maybe...
maybe not.
That's where we
buy our groceries.
That's a fine
old store.
Around the corner
is the depot.
You can't see
that from here.
And the library's
down on oak street.
And over there is...
well, don't stop now.
Alan, what is it?
Well, either
i've got the worst
memory in the world,
or they put up
a new building.
In one week?
Well, it's pre-fab.
I tell you,
young lady,
they don't
build buildings
the way they used to.
Alan, do me
a little favor, huh?
Sure.
Could we stop and have
a little quick one
before we meet the gang?
Just a wee little one.
In the first place,
there's no gang to meet.
There's just
aunt mildred.
And in the
second place,
there's not one
bar in coeurville.
Really? I thought
i saw one.
Nope, nearest
one's temple,
15 miles away.
I'll take you
in the hotel
and buy you a
cup of coffee.
That's fine.
Something i can do
for you folks?
Where's the
restaurant?
Four doors down,
kelsey's cafe.
No, i mean
the one here.
What happened?
Did you close?
Never had one here.
Just a hotel.
This is the
new brunswick?
Yes, sir.
I see.
I know how absent-minded
you scientific men are,
so i know you won't mind
my asking-
are you sure
this is the right town?
Course i'm sure.
Well, alan,
don't snap at me.
I'm sorry, i guess
i'm just nervous.
Look, jess,
let's go home
and get something
there, all right?
Sure, fine.
Is that
your mr. Van brooks?
No. I don't
know who he is.
It's as though 20
years have gone by.
Everything's
different.
I think you're just looking
at things for the first time.
I've lived near times square
all my life,
but i don't remember
seeing it, really, for years.
They could've put up
half a dozen new buildings-
i'd never notice
because i just don't look.
Yeah, that's
probably it.
Now, thati would
recognize anywhere.
You like it?
What if i didn't?
Of course i do.
It's charming.
Come on!
The first thing
we're going to do
is paint it- pink.
Why not purple?
Oh, she must have it
locked from the inside.
Aunt mildred?
Aunt mildred!
Alan, you're going
to shake up the
whole neighborhood.
Well, i have to.
She's hard-of-hearing.
Aunt mildred?
What do you want?
I'm alan talbot.
So?
So i happen to live here.
Now, would you mind
telling me who you are
and what you're doing
in my house?
Are you crazy
or something?
Wait a minute.
Where's aunt mildred?
Who?
Mildred talbot.
Now, listen, mister, let
me tell you something.
You've made some
kind of a mistake.
I live here.
I've lived here
for nine years.
I bought this place
from gerald butler,
and i've got the deed
to prove it.
I don't know anybody
named mildred,
and i don't know
you, either.
Now, you get
off my property,
or i'll call
the sheriff!
Wait!
Alan, what are
you going to do?
What would you
do if you found
some stranger living
in your house?
Call the police!
Hi.
Who'd you want to see?
Would you tell mrs.
Cook i'd like to use
the phone, please?
Mrs. Cook?
Yes. Please hurry.
I'm sorry.
Mrs. Cook doesn't live here.
She died.
What?!
About three... three years ago,
i think.
You aren't her cousin
from sweden, are you?
No, i'm not her
cousin from sweden!
I'm alan talbot, and
i live next door,
and i had lunch with
mrs. Cook a week ago!
Thank you very much.
Come on, alan.
I had lunch with
agatha cook a week ago,
just before i
left for new york.
I know you did.
You mentioned it.
Jess, i don't know
what's going on...
but i'm going
to find out.
Well, that's it.
That's where i work.
The university of coeurville,
established 1912.
Over there- that four-story
building- you see it?
My office
is on the second floor.
Well, what do you think of it?
I don't know what to think.
Well, maybe
they moved it.
Sure. In the week
i've been gone,
they took it apart
brick by brick
and moved it somewhere else.
For pete's sake,
i've made this drive
twice a day for over ten years.
You'd think i'd forget?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Did you get everything
all straightened out?
Sure. I'm out
of my mind.
Oh, alan...
i don't know what
else to think.
What else
can i think?
Somebody i never
saw before living
in my house?
Woman i had lunch
with a week ago
dead three years?
New buildings
in the town?
This is going
to sound crazy, i know,
but do you remember
what you said
when we tried to get coffee
at that hotel?
The one that didn't have
the coffee shop?
You said it was as though
coeurville had aged 20 years.
Do you remember?
20 years in a week?
Well, maybe not in one week.
What do you mean?
I'm not sure.
But what if it's true?
What if 20 years have gone by?
I'm rip van winkle?
Well, why not?
Alan, it's a possibility,
isn't it?
No, i thought
about that.
That doesn't hold up
for a lot of reasons.
For one thing, it would
make me at least 45 years old,
unless i left town
when i was ten,
and that couldn't be,
because i went
to high school and college here!
Except there aren't
any records showing
i ever went to coeurville high.
And the university i work for,
dear old coeurville u.,
doesn't even exist!
It never existed!
Well...
what about your aunt?
I just checked.
There's not a trace of evidence
that a mildred talbot
ever lived here.
It was an idea.
Come on.
Where to now?
The cemetery.
Alan, why are
you doing this?
To find out if the
world's gone crazy...
or if i have.
My parents are
buried here.
If i can just find
their graves...
over there-
talbots have been
buried in that plot
for over 50 years.
Oh!
Those the ones?
That's them, all right.
I'm sorry.
This man says
you caused
a disturbance
at his house.
Do you admit it?
Yes, i made a mistake.
Said you claimed
it was your house.
Well, i thought it was.
I'm sorry.
Are you satisfied?
Well, as long as
he owns up to it.
But you better
not come
pestering me again,
young fellow!
I won't!
Go on back to the car.
I'll be along in a minute.
What's your
name, son?
Alan talbot.
Is this
your wife?
No... we're
just friends.
Well, mr. Talbot,
do you want
to tell me what you're
doing in coeurville?
You the sheriff?
That's right.
What happened
to carl jasperson?
He's the man
i replaced.
Do you know him?
He's my godfather.
Where can i find him?
Over there.
Oh, miss...
i can't force you
to do anything,
because you haven't
broken any laws,
but i'd like to suggest
that you take your friend
to see a doctor.
He looks sick.
And the way he was staring
at that grave...
is he kin
to walter ryder?
I don't know.
Let's go, alan.
How do you feel?
Alan?
Darling, i know
how upset you are,
but there's a rational
explanation for all this.
There has to be.
A friend of mine,
dr. Matthews...
he had a patient once
who couldn't even remember
her own name.
She was on
a plane...
suddenly, she
couldn't remember
where she was going,
or why, or anything.
When he first
talked to her,
she couldn't
remember
a thing about
her life.
But after two weeks,
she was just fine.
It was a form
of amnesia.
I think you should
see him, alan.
You'll like
dr. Matthews.
Put it down, alan! Get away!
Run, walter, run!
Stop the car!
Are you going to be sick?
Yes! Hurry, stop the car!
Look out, you'll kill me with
that... kill me with that...
kill me... kill me...
kill... kill...
jess, can you give me a hand?
I'm coming, alan!
Hurry!
No!
Jess, get away from me!
Get away from me!
Get in the car and drive away
as quick as you can!
Alan, let me help you!
No! I'll see you later
at your apartment.
How are you going
to get back there?
Never mind, just go!
Go now, jess!
Run!
Kill me! Kill me!
Kill me! Kill me! Kill me!
Mister, are
you all right?
Are you all
right, mister?
I didn't see
you, honest!
I came around
the turn.
I didn't see you.
Is it bad?
I don't know.
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
Thank you.
You sure you're
all right, mister?
Yes, i'm fine now.
I still think you
ought to see a doctor.
No, i'm all right, see?
I'm not even bleeding.
Not on the outside, maybe,
but what about on the inside?
I mean, i've heard
of accidents
where guys are
hurt really bad
and they don't
even know it.
Look, i'm fine.
Well, sure.
All i'm trying
to say is...
i'd hate to be responsible
if you started a hemorrhage
or something.
It wasn't my fault.
I mean, you admitted
that yourself,
but even so...
look, i signed a paper
absolving you of any blame.
Isn't that enough?
Yeah. Don't get sore, mister.
I'm just worried
about you is all.
Uh, mister?
It's none of my business, but...
how come you were wandering
around out there
in the middle of nowhere?
I don't know.
Thank you. I'm sorry
i've caused you any trouble.
Mister, i'm just glad
you're alive.
Yes?
Alan?
Darling, i've been calling
every 15 minutes.
I've been so worried.
What happened?
I'm not sure.
Are you all right?
I don't know.
Alan...
look, jess, why don't
you just forget about me?
I don't know what's going on.
Listen to me.
I called dr. Matthews
and i made an appointment
for you for tomorrow morning.
I'll be at the hotel
to pick you up at 9:30.
You'd do that after
everything that's happened?
Yes, i would.
Mr. Talbot, i...
i didn't plan
on falling in love with you,
but i did...
and i'm stuck with it,
for better or for worse.
Well, thank you.
Would you like me
to come over now?
No, uh...
uh...
i'll see you
tomorrow morning.
Good night, jess.
Try not to worry, please.
Good night.
Hello, alan.
I've been waiting for you.
You real?
Well, that's a matter
of opinion.
I used to think so,
years ago.
Now i'm not so sure.
Sit down, alan,
over there.
I'll pour us
a drink.
Go on, sit down.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
By the way, you almost killed me
with those scissors.
Did you know that?
It's a shame you didn't.
But then nothing
ever works out right for me.
See how close it was?
Who are you?
You already know that.
You must.
How else could
you have found me?
I looked you up
in the phone book.
Yeah, but how...
oh, i see.
You've been to coeurville,
haven't you?
Yes!
And you know... what?
Your name.
That's all?
That's all.
In that case, you better have
some of that drink.
Exactly eight days ago, you
were born here in this house.
What?!
I made the delivery myself.
You're drunk!
A little bit...
but not drunk enough.
Will you join me?
I guarantee
no hangover.
Wasn't that thoughtful
of me?
Look, i'm in no mood
for jokes, mister.
Well, that's a pity,
because this whole thing
is a joke.
Yeah, well, i'm
not laughing.
You will,
because the joke's on me.
Would you get
to the point?
Well, you've been to coeurville.
You know that alan talbot
never lived there.
You know you've been behaving
oddly of late.
Judging from that handkerchief
on your arm,
i'd say you know
about that, too.
So, with all
this information,
what do i need to tell you?
Who am i?!
You're nobody, alan,
nobody at all.
Stop it, walter!
Well, whois this watch
i'm wearing? Ask me that!
Whois the refrigerator
in the kitchen?
Don't you understand?
No.
You're a machine, alan,
a mechanical device.
I don't believe it!
I don't blame you.
I wouldn't believe it, either.
But it's true.
The fact is, you were born
a long time ago, inside my head.
All kids have dreams,
don't they?
Well, you were mine.
The others thought
about joining the army
or flying to mars.
They finally grew up
and they forgot their dreams.
I didn't.
I thought about one thing
and longed for one thing always.
Just one.
A perfect artificial man.
Not a robot-
a duplicate
of a human being.
Well, it was harmless.
Not even very imaginative
for a child.
But then i became an adult.
Only somewhere along the line,
i forgot to grow up-
like most geniuses.
I kept my dream.
I created you, alan.
Is that straight enough for you?
You're not only drunk,
you're crazy!
How would you explain that?
Why, it's an artificial arm.
I don't know!
You expect me to believe
i'm a machine
when i know i'm not?
That's ridiculous!
I eat, i drink, i sleep!
Didn't i tell you
i wanted a perfect creation?
Alan...
alan, i want you
to come with me.
Where?
Well, let's call it
the, uh, delivery room.
Don't you want to see
where you were born?
Your birthplace.
Come on.
Turn it off!
Over here, alan.
Your brothers.
Alan talbot i...
alan talbot ii.
Factory rejects.
Any questions?
Where did you get the money
for all this?
I told you,
i'm a genius!
When i found out
how much i'd need
for my work,
i developed
an improved calculator.
Try electronics turns out
3,000 or 4,000 a year.
I get the royalties.
The money was
the least of it.
The failures, though,
they were bad.
I can't tell you how many times
i've failed
and had to start over again.
You did this all by yourself?
No, that wouldn't
have been possible.
I'm afraid the day
of the lone inventor has passed.
I had some of the best
scientific minds
in the world
assisting me.
But, of course,
they didn't take
the project seriously.
To them,
it was just a game-
a lot of theoretical
wool-gathering.
How would
it be possible
to create an entire
nervous system
that worked like
a real one?
How could the brain
be duplicated
with all its subtleties?
You see, i was after
real intelligence.
Mere reactions weren't enough.
Those mannequins can react.
My creation had
to have a memory.
He had to have
abstract reasoning power,
a past, a personality.
Millions
of intricate facets
multiplied by millions
to make true intelligence.
Now...
to accomplish this
from the beginning
would have been
impossible.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
What do you mean,
you decided to use yourself?
Just that.
In certain of your cells,
i made certain impressions.
My own memories went
into the cells.
Some of my talents,
some of my knowledge-
bits and pieces of myself.
So now you're telling me
that i'm you?
That's right.
Well, that's impossible.
I'm me! This is my flesh!
Nonconductive plastic.
I admit, it feels like flesh...
but then, that was the idea.
You see, i cushioned
the mechanical parts
with a foam layer,
and then i worked out a...
but that's not what you want
to hear, is it?
You lived in coeurville?
Yes.
For your past, i gave you
my memories of the town.
Some of them must have been
inaccurate and incomplete.
I left coeurville 20 years ago.
Going there must have been
quite an experience.
Yeah, it was.
What about the university?
Fictitious.
I had to give you a job.
Well, aunt mildred!
All the old ladies
i've ever known rolled into one.
After my parents died,
i lived alone.
The reputation as a don juan is,
i regret to say, imaginary.
Well, that's about it, alan.
The rest you can fill in,
up to last week, anyway.
What about last week?
I wish i knew.
Something went wrong.
I couldn't understand.
You suddenly attacked me
with a pair of scissors
and then ran away.
As you know, i've been unable
to find you since.
What's wrong with me?
I'm not sure.
Whatever it is,
it's wrong with me, too.
We're all potential murderers,
alan, all of us.
But if we're normal, we're
protected by our inhibitions.
You've wanted to kill?
Of course. Everybody has.
But my own inhibitions
have held my impulses in check.
I couldn't kill, no matter
how much i might want to.
So what are you saying?
With you, something
went wrong.
To put it even clearer, alan,
you're insane.
Can i be treated?
Repaired, you mean?
I don't know.
Why not?
Well, as much
as i hate to admit it,
luck had a great deal
to do with your creation.
Skill alone wasn't enough.
You saying i'm an accident?
I'm afraid so.
You see, alan, i was like
a blind man with a machine gun.
I kept firing
and reloading and firing,
and finally i hit the target,
but it was off-center.
I don't even know
if i could come close again.
That's the story
of my life,
right down the line.
Success
in the little things.
Failure
in the big ones.
I told myself
i wanted to make
an artificial man,
but i think
what i really wanted
was to build
another walter ryder-
only without
the drawbacks.
Sort of a reverse
jekyll and hyde.
Everything i wished i was,
my creation would be.
Where i was shy,
he would be aggressive.
Where i was cold and withdrawn,
he would be warm and outgoing.
Loneliness would
be unknown to him.
Disease and pain
and death- all unknown.
He would be unselfish.
He would be ambitious
but not fanatical.
And, oh, alan,
he would be perfect!
That was my dream:
A perfect version
of myself.
I ought to kill you.
That's right. You should.
There's somebody else,
walter- a girl.
We were going to be
married next week.
Is she pretty?
Pretty, intelligent...
and lonely-
something you ought
to be able to understand.
I'm sorry, alan.
Well, that's
a great consolation.
You sure you can't fix me?
Even if i could,
it wouldn't solve your problems.
The girl would find out
eventually.
How?
Well, for one thing, she would
grow old and you wouldn't.
For another, being a machine,
you would suffer
a breakdown someday.
All of these things
never occurred to you?
I guess i didn't really think
i'd succeed as well as i did.
What does
it matter anyway?
There's nothing
that can be done.
Yes, there is.
You're going to create
another alan talbot.
No, i just told you!
You heard me-
another alan talbot!
Only this one's going
to be right.
And he's going to walk
out of here tonight,
and he's going to marry
a girl named jess,
and for the first time
in his miserable life,
he's going to be happy.
Well, i don't understand.
You give me
a pencil.
Now, this is
her name...
and address.
She said she
would meet me
at 9:30 in
the morning,
but she'll
be home now.
What's the matter, alan?
What is it?
Now, you take it.
Take it and get out... now.
And hurry!
Alan...
alan?
Just a minute.
Who is it?
I'm sorry to
bother you, ma'am,
but, uh, see,
like, i belong
to the junior
woodchucks,
and, uh...
come in, alan.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
I don't know.
I've been so worried.
After yesterday, i didn't-
forget yesterday.
Whatever happened,
forget that.
Oh, but, alan...
please?
We just had a rotten nightmare,
that's all.
Now we're awake, and
everything's going to be fine.
Will you try to believe that?
Do you?
Yes.
Okay.
Then so do i.
If you promise
to tell me about it someday.
I promise, someday.
Now, will you fix
me a cup of coffee?
Sure.
Would you like something to eat?
How about a couple of mother
connelly's hand-fried eggs?
They're guaranteed
to make a new man
out of you.
Thank you.
In a way it can be said
that walter ryder succeeded
in his life's ambition,
even though the man he created
was, after all, himself.
There may be easier ways
to self-improvement,
but sometimes it happens
that the shortest distance
between two points
is a crooked line
through the twilight zone.
The ingredients:
An american destroyer,
the pacific ocean,
and a ghostly sound of hammering
from 30 fathoms below.
They add up to a strange tale
of the bizarre and nightmarish.
Mike kellin
and simon oakland star
in a very different kind
oftwilight zone
which we call
"the thirty fathom grave.
Ain't that a kick
in the head.
What do you
suppose it is?
Ghosts, man, ghosts.
Here it is,
7-1-4.
"Commissioned
december, 1941.
"Sunk in action
"first battle
of the solomons,
august 7, 1942."
Well, that was 20 years ago.
Captain beecham,
who's down there?
Who's inside that sub?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org