Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
You're looking at the house of
the late mrs. Henrietta walker.
This is mrs. Walker herself,
as she appeared 25 years ago.
And this,
except for isolated objects,
is the living room
of mrs. Walker's house
as it appeared
in that same year.
The other rooms upstairs
and down are much the same.
The time, however,
is not 25 years ago, but now.
The house of the late
mrs. Henrietta walker is,
you see, a house which belongs
almost entirely to the past;
a house which,
like mrs. Walker's clock here,
has ceased to recognize
the passage of time.
Only one element
is missing now-
one remaining item in the estate
of the late mrs. Walker:
Her son alex, 34 years of age,
and up till 20 minutes ago,
the so-called
perennial bachelor.
With him is his bride,
the former miss virginia lane.
They're returning
from the city hall
in order to get
mr. Walker's clothes packed,
make final arrangements
for the sale of the house,
lock it up and depart
on their honeymoon.
Not a complicated set of tasks,
it would appear,
and yet the newlywed mrs. Walker
is about to discover
that the old adage
"you can't go home again"
has little meaning
in the twilight zone.
Thank you, darling.
Well...
well, shall we
get started?
Darling?
Yes, of course.
Did you call
mr. Wilkinson
and tell him
when we'd be back?
Oh, no, i forgot.
Well, you'd better call him
now, then.
You have to sign
the papers before we leave.
Yes, of course.
I thought i'd clean
the place up a little
before we left.
I'll get it
out of here.
Uh-uh. You go call
mr. Wilkinson.
I thought i left
his card right here.
I can't seem
to find it.
Well, get the number
from information.
Oh, of course.
Look... i'll tell you what.
You go on up and pack,
and i'll call mr. Wilkinson,
all right?
Oh, darling,
everything's going
to be all right.
I'm so happy
to be mrs. Walker
at last,
after all
these years.
Come on, go on up
and pack.
All right.
Oh, would you give me the number
of wilkinson realty, please?
On main street.
Thank you.
Mr. Wilkinson?
Virginia lane.
I mean, virginia walker.
Yes, yes, just now.
Oh, thank you, mr. Wilkinson.
Oh, yes, i am very happy.
Yes, we're back now.
If you'd bring the papers over
so mr. Walker can sign them,
you can show the house
while we're gone.
Oh, right away.
Fine. We'll see you
in a few minutes.
Thank you.
Alex, i thought
you were going to...
oh, there's
plenty of time.
What do you think
we should take out
of here when we move?
The television set,
i guess, huh?
And, uh, the electric clock.
It's only a
few years old.
Darling, i thought
we decided
to discuss all that
after the house was sold.
Sold?
I know, but i
just thought
that maybe we
should decide now.
I mean, like, in the
kitchen, for instance.
We'll take the
refrigerator
and the stove.
They're pretty new.
I just bought
them for mother
a few months...
a few months
before she died.
All right, alex, fine.
We'll discuss it later,
but we've really got to leave.
Of course.
Well?
What about the radio?
It's pretty old,
but we could have it fixed.
Maybe it works now.
Look at it.
It weighs a ton, i bet.
Look at all this carving-
all the work
they put into it,
the craft...
the programs
we used to hear on this.
Major bowes,
fred allen...
and all the music.
We used to sit in here
all the time listening to music.
Mother's favorite
was eddy duchin.
I just remembered...
she used to be crazy
about a record of his
called "the lady in red."
You remember that?
Uh-huh.
? the lady in red?
? all the fellows are crazy
for the lady in red...?
Broken.
I knew it was.
She used to sit in this chair
and look
at the movie magazine.
Funny i should remember
that, too.
She gave it up
a long time ago.
Sometimes, she'd make
a pan of fudge for us,
and we'd sit here...
alex, darling,
come on.
We have to leave when
mr. Wilkinson comes.
Maybe we could
get this fixed.
Used to be
a real good clock.
We'll discuss that
later, huh?
He's mine now!
You'll never get
your claws on him again.
Alex?
Alex!
Oh, i, uh... i was just looking
at some of my old things
that mother kept.
Look. Looks as good as ever.
No...
alex...
i thought you
were going...
look!
The hardy boys
in secret of the caves.
Bill bolton
in hidden dangers.
Tarzan and the antmen.
Tarzan and the jewels of opar.
Alex, please.
Remember these?
Funny old things.
Alex...
oh, and the stockings
that went with them.
Stockings for a boy.
"It takes a real boy
to know a real stocking."
Funny i should
remember that.
It's a quote from an ad
in a mail-order catalogue of...
gosh, it must be 25 years ago.
I wonder why mother kept them.
Because she would have liked
for you to stay
exactly as you were
when you first wore them.
I'm sorry, alex.
I didn't mean that.
You're not angry
with me, are you?
No.
It's just that i
want us to be happy.
Alex, that's all
i've ever wanted.
Do you, uh...
want me to help?
I can manage.
You aren't angry
with me, are you?
No.
I'll make you happy,
alex.
You'll see.
You won't be sorry.
Uh...
i'll wait for mr.
Wilkinson downstairs.
He should be here
any moment now.
I don't want to sell the house.
I don't want to sell it, mother.
Afternoon, mrs. Walker.
Oh, mr. Wilkinson,
won't you come in?
Thank you
kindly, ma'am.
Oh, won't you go
in the living room?
I'll get mr. Walker.
Fine and dandy.
Alex. Alex, darling.
Mr. Wilkinson's here
with the papers.
Uh, yes, of course.
Afternoon, mr. Walker.
Congratulations
to you, sir.
You have the papers?
Right here, ma'am.
Oh, but first, i wonder
if i could trouble you
for the use of
your telephone?
You see, i forgot
to tell my secretary
where i'd be,
and i'm expecting
a pretty important
call from out of town.
I'll call her for you.
Oh? Well, all right.
Well, in that case,
mr. Walker...
why don't you
use the dining
room table?
Fine and dandy.
After you, sir.
Make it as soon
as possible, darling.
We really have to leave.
Now, then...
as you can see right
here, mr. Walker...
well, i think i'd
better do it myself.
I have to tell
my secretary
some things anyway.
You sign right
here, mr. Walker.
Maggie? Jim.
I'm at henrietta
walker's house.
Would you put that call
through to me here
if it comes in in the next ten
or 15 minutes or so?
Fine, oh, and call
mr. Fisher
and tell him that escrow
has been approved
for 60 days and we have
the form ready for him to sign.
Right. Fine and dandy.
I'll see you,
maggie. Bye.
No, sir, we won't have
any trouble
selling this house
at all.
There something
you don't understand,
mr. Walker?
Uh, no, i, uh...
i think i'll wait.
Wait?
Yes, until
we return.
I want to
think about it.
But darling...
i just want to
think about it!
Alex.
I'm sorry
to cause you
so much trouble,
mr. Wilkinson.
Sure, sure.
You're positive?
I'm positive.
Well, all right.
I'll get in touch with you
on your return.
Please.
Well, have a nice honeymoon.
Oh, never mind,
miss lane...
mrs. Walker.
I'll pack.
Alex, alex,
you promised.
What do you mean?
You know what i mean.
You promised to
sell this house.
Oh, i'm not
backing down, virg.
I just want a little time
to think about it.
That's all.
What is there to think about?
Well, i just don't like
the idea
of people tramping
in and out...
that's just
an excuse.
That's not
the reason.
Oh, yes, it is, virg.
All right, never mind.
Just pack,
and let's get out of here.
What is it?
Couldn't...
i mean, couldn't we
live here, virg?
It's a pretty nice house...
oh, alex, no!
Don't just say no
without thinking about it.
We could redecorate.
I want to get
out of here.
I want to leave
right now.
Alex, you promised me
when your mother died,
you'd sell this house.
Well, she's dead.
Alex, dead!
She's been dead
for a year now,
and i waited that year
and all the years before-
12 years, 12 long years
of waiting for you.
Well, now, i want my own home.
I have a right to that.
Don't look at
me like that.
Don't look at me
as if you don't even know me.
Alex, please.
Please, don't do this
to me.
I love you.
I want to care for you
and make a home for you,
but our home, not hers.
We've waited
so long, darling.
How?
I know, you told me
she was sick,
and we couldn't...
shewassick, virg.
She lost her health
taking care of me
and this house for
more than 20 years.
My father deserted us
when i was two
months old, virg.
Two months old!
All right, all right.
Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
Virg.
I'm not going to sell
the house, virg.
We'll have it
redecorated,
maybe get
some new furniture.
We'll talk
about it later.
No, alex. I won't let you.
We'll get out of here.
I'll get my purse.
I won't let you.
I won't let you!
Alex! Alex!
No. No, you can't have him.
I won't let you have him.
He's mine now.
Mine!
Yes, he is,
because i'm
right for him.
I won't try to destroy
him like you did.
My love will
make him strong,
not weak,
not dependent.
Yes, it's true.
You've always known it's true,
and you hated me for it.
Well, your hatred
isn't strong enough now.
Your desire to dominate him
isn't strong enough.
He's not your
little boy anymore.
Leave him be.
You will not have him back!
This is not my doing.
Come back to me, mother.
I want you to.
Alex... not you.
Oh!
Can we go to the park
and then to the zoo
and have two
ice cream cones?
Oh, boy.
Go away, lady.
We don't need you anymore.
Exit miss virginia lane,
formerly and most briefly
mrs. Alex walker.
She has just given up a battle
and in a strange way retreated,
but this has been a retreat
back to reality.
Her opponent, alex walker,
will now and forever hold
a line that exists in the past.
He has put a claim
on a moment in time
and is not about
to relinquish it.
Such things do happen
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
The name "ray bradbury"
has become synonymous
with a new horizon
of american writing.
Next week onthe twilight zone,
we present
a typical bradbury tale.
It also has
typical bradbury ingredients,
including a grandmother
built in a factory.
Now, if this
doesn't intrigue you,
then i'm simply
not doing justice
to a most intriguing tale.
I hope you'll join us next week
for "i sing the body electric."
This is james arness.
You know, it's only a short hop
fromthe twilight zone
to dodge city ingunsmoke.
Saturday nights
over most of these stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org