Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Global 33, receiving okay.
Magellan, how about
a flight progress report?
Coming up,
skipper.
Global 33,
receiving okay.
We'll be about
four minutes
behind flight plan
at 30-degrees west.
Check. Captain,
gander wants to know
if you intend
an altitude change
after we
pass 30 west.
Advise gander negative.
Negative altitude change.
You'll be pleased to know
that thanks to the quality
of this aircraft
and the fine weather
and my brilliant flying
we'll hit idlewild
on schedule
if our speed holds up.
Send it in, wyatt.
Yes, sir.
Shannon, shannon,
copy, gander.
Global flight 33,
position 52 north
30 west, time 14:03.
Flight level 35,000.
Estimating 51 north,
40 west at 14:45.
Estimating idlewild 18:30.
Fuel remaining, 79560.
Temperature, minus 57.
Report received, captain.
How we doing
back there, janie?
Oh, your passengers
are highly content
but on behalf
of the stewardesses
i would like
to respectfully request
that we get to new york
as soon as possible.
One's going to the opera
two have
heavy dates
and the fourth is available
to any honorable
and single male crew member.
Oh, hold
it a minute.
Do you feel anything?
Feel anything?
No, what do you mean?
I don't know-
i felt something...
something funny,
like the sensation of speed.
I can't put my finger on it.
I guess i'm getting old.
True airspeed 470, we're level.
Suppose we picked up
a tail wind?
Yeah, maybe those
jet streams are tricky.
It's that crazy feeling
i can't shake.
I can't feel a tail wind,
but i feel something.
Everything looks fine.
Magellan, try and get me
a ground-speed check
with the doppler.
Indicates 900.
That's impossible.
I better check with loran.
What's going on?
Hold it a minute.
Skipper, loran indicates
a ground speed of 830 knots.
I never heard of a tail wind
like that.
Check it again.
See if you
can raise
weather ship
charlie.
Ask him for
a radar fix
on the ground-
speed check.
Magellan,
are you sure
about that
ground speed?
I'm not only sure,
but we're still accelerating.
980 now.
1,120.
1,500.
Global 33 tocharlie.
God in heaven,
i can't even keep up with it.
Global 33 to weather
shipcharlie.
Global 33
to weather shipcharlie.
What aboutcharlie?
Nothing, sir,
i can't raise them.
2,100.
Well, i hope the wings stay on.
Don't worry about the wings.
It's the true airspeed
that counts.
Ground speed means nothing.
Well, now, we just hit
one lulu of a jet stream.
Magellan.
My needle just reversed
past gander v.o.r.
How could we get past...?
Give me a fast position check.
Skipper, we are past gander.
We must be doing 3,000 knots.
Try to raise harmon control
or moncton or boston.
At this speed,
you might as well try
to get idlewild.
Harmon control,
this is global 33.
Harmon, do you read us?
Moncton.
Moncton, this
is global 33.
Boston.
Boston control,
this is global 33.
Boston, please
acknowledge.
Idlewild.
Idlewild, this is global 33.
Idlewild, do
you read us?
It's no soap.
I can't raise anyone.
You're riding on a jet airliner
en route from london
to new york.
You're at 35,000 feet
atop an overcast
and roughly 55 minutes
from idlewild airport
but what you've seen occur
inside the cockpit of this plane
is no reflection on the aircraft
or the crew.
It's a safe, well-engineered,
perfectly designed machine
and the men you've just met
are a trained, cool,
highly efficient team.
The problem is simply that
the plane is going too fast
and there is nothing
within the realm of knowledge
or at least logic
to explain it.
Unbeknownst to
passenger and crew
this aeroplane is heading
into an uncharted region
well-off the beaten track
of commercial travelers.
It's moving into
the twilight zone.
What you're about to see we
call "the odyssey of flight 33."
I hope you're proud
of the fly-boys.
I'm seeingthe
valkyrietonight.
Oh, janie.
I've always had
a thing about
valhalla.
Be a good egg and tell
me i'm going to make it
in time
for the curtain.
Let me put it to you this way:
I only hope that the valhalla
you're talking about
is at the metropolitan opera
house in little old new york.
Instead of...?
Instead of a conducted tour
through the real thing.
We're in trouble.
How bad?
They don't know yet.
Go ahead, serve it.
Paula, remember:
"Coffee, tea or milk?"
And with a smile.
You've got a deal.
You know, you talk
about ailments.
Well, i had an aunt
once in boise, idaho
had one of the
worst livers
in the medical
history of the state.
That woman, when she
passed on, rest her soul
would you believe it,
there were five
medical associations
who were bidding just to get
her liver in a bottle on display.
But her mother- that
was my father's sister-
she absolutely refused to
let them show her liver.
And it was like i said to
my late husband, you can...
what did you say you were, dear?
Group captain, madame.
I'm military attache to the
british embassy in washington.
Oh, isn't that
wonderful.
You know,
i had a nephew
in the navy
in the second world war.
Yes, he was...
he was on a
cruiser or a...
p.t. Boat, or
something like that.
Or maybe it was
a battleship.
Did you feel anything?
Well, i felt a little
queasy when we took off
but like my late husband
always used to say
i've got a stomach
that's just like...
it's odd.
It's very odd, indeed.
I have the strangest sensation
of speed.
Acceleration.
Oh!
Oh, dear,
terribly sorry.
Got a little nerves, miss?
Heavy date in new york.
Little shook up.
I don't blame
you then.
Another channel...
well, what about it?
Not a thing, captain.
Not a single thing.
Either everybody out there
is off whack- everybody-
or we are.
Well, check
your equipment again.
I checked it four times.
All right,
knock it off.
I might
as well try
to bull our way through and see if...
did we hit
something?
I don't know.
Check for damage.
Number three and four
are still on the wing.
They look okay.
Ditto one
and two.
Everything seems
to be in a piece.
Purcell, go aft and check for cabin damage.
Report back
right away.
Right.
I'd better get
on the horn
and calm
down anybody
that needs
calming down.
Tell the girls
to stay with it.
Right.
We're in trouble.
I don't know what
kind of trouble.
That light, that crazy light-
what was it?
Something we'll have
to find out-
quick too.
What was that shaking?
Turbulence?
I doubt it.
It was more like a...
like a...
like a what?
Like a sound shockwave
as if we'd gone
past the speed of sound.
You mean we hit mach one?
We broke the sound barrier?
But we didn't get
any mach warning bell.
We probably wouldn't have
not with a true airspeed
of only 470.
I don't know what it is.
I just don't know.
See, magellan's last speed check
was 3,000 knots.
We could have gone through
some kind of a sound barrier
but... no kind of
a sound barrier i ever heard of.
Magellan-
can you give
me a fix now?
Global 33 to
harmon control...
whatever that bump was, skipper
it's really knocked out
everything.
Global 33, moncton.
The altimeter and rate of climb
are steady, skipper.
Captain, i can't reach
gander, moncton or
boston or anybody.
Either they're off the
air or we are or both.
Hatch, give me
a sun line.
I'll need a
heading to idlewild
from our last
known position.
If we can't raise anyone,
we'll establish visual contact.
Skipper, you can't do that.
If we leave this altitude
well run smack-dab into the
middle of 20 other flights.
Have you got
any other alternative, craig?
Sooner or later,
we're going to have
to find a landmark
and go v.f.r.
Without radio contact,
we're deaf and dumb.
As long as we stay up here,
we're also blind.
There's no damage there, skip.
Everybody's shook up
and curious.
They're also plenty scared.
Them and me.
Well, "ours is not
to reason why."
Into the valley
of public relations.
Ladies and
gentlemen
this is
captain farver.
I want to assure you that
everything is under control
and there is no danger.
We encountered
a little clear air turbulence
and atmospheric phenomena
but there's been no damage
to the aircraft
except for some
temporary radio malfunction.
There's no cause for alarm
and i'll keep you posted.
If we run according to schedule
we should be landing at idlewild
inside of the next 40 minutes.
Thank you.
Purcell, what's the fuel?
71,435 pounds.
I don't feel that strange
sensation of speed anymore.
Magellan,
how about
that heading
to idlewild?
Part of this is
scientific, skipper.
Part of it's
kentucky windage.
Try 262, that's as
close as i can get.
All right, you all know
what we're up against.
We have no radio contact.
Apparently, we're out of touch
with all ground-radar points.
We don't know where we are.
We're not even sure
if we're on airways.
This beast gulps fuel.
We all know that only too well.
So we've got
one chance.
We'll go through
this overcast
and try to find
something that
looks familiar.
Uh... it's
very possible
that we might
hit something
on the way down
but it's a chance
we've got to take.
I wanted you to know
where we stand
so everybody keep a sharp
lookout for any other traffic
and keep your fingers crossed.
I guess a few prayers wouldn't
be out of order either.
All right, craig,
let's go down.
Hit the horn button.
Skipper?
I don't get it.
It happens to be
a fact, though.
That's manhattan
island down there.
Manhattan island?
How could it be
manhattan island?
Where's the skyline?
Where are all the buildings?
I don't know where they are,
but that's new york city.
One little item seems to be amiss.
The passengers...
yeah, i don't
blame them.
Well, we're over land.
I don't see any...
any what, janie?
Any city, right?
We don't either.
Now, that's manhattan island
down there.
There's the east river.
There's the hudson river.
That's staten island.
We've got all the
topographical clues we need.
The problem seems to be
the real estate's there
it's just the city and eight
million people are missing.
In short, there is no new york.
It's disappeared.
Skipper, verify something
for me, would you?
And in a hurry?
Look!
It's not possible.
What in the name
of everything holy
is going on?
What's the score?
We've been circling
for a half an hour?
They said they'd
keep in touch,
but not to come in.
Well, what do you
think, skipper?
Well, we've
flown over
what should be
schenectady,
albany
points north.
I'll give you a
surmise, gentlemen.
You may want to truss me up with ropes
but it's the only single
explanation i can give.
Somehow in some way we not only
went through the sound barrier
but we've gone back in time.
Well, what do we do about it?
Skipper?
Fuel is down to 49,435 pounds.
Then here's what we're
going to do about it.
We're going to push this baby up
until she's going as fast
as she can.
We're going to climb till we get
back into that jet stream
and then... we're going to try
to go back where we came from.
All right, craig.
Let's do it.
700 knots.
780.
800.
900 knots.
I think we're going to make it.
We're picking it up again.
Do you feel it?
Look, i know you've got
your hands full
but somebody get on the pipe.
I've got three passengers back
there that are nearly hysterical
and those two kids
back in the
tourist section
have half the passengers
climbing the walls.
We made it!
Look, we're back!
Ladies and
gentlemen
this is
captain farver.
We encountered some momentary
difficulty back there
but as you can see,
we're over new york city now
and should be landing
inside of just a few minutes.
Thank you.
What about
idlewild?
Nothing doing,
captain.
Our v.h.f.
Is still out.
Maybe their's
is out, too.
Try using a
high frequency.
I did already,
captain.
There's nothing
from idlewild.
What about
la guardia?
Somebody ought
to hear us.
La guardia
this is
global 33.
La guardia,
come in, please.
This is la guardia tower.
Who is calling, please?
La guardia, this
is global 33.
We're on the
northeast leg
of la guardia range.
Our v.o.r. And i.l.s.
Appear inoperative.
Request radar
vector to idlewild.
You request what?
Radar vector to
idlewild i.l.s.
What flight did you say
this was?
La guardia, this is
global airlines flight 33.
Now, stop fooling around.
We're short on fuel.
Global 33?
What kind of aircraft is this?
This is a jet aircraft.
Did you say ajetaircraft?
Let me handle it.
La guardia, this is a jet.
We have four,
big lovely turbines
and they're getting hungry,
running short on fuel.
We want a radar vector
to idlewild.
Do you have us in radar contact
or don't you?
I don't know who you are
and we don't know
anything at all
about radar or jets
or anything else
but if you're really low on fuel
we'll clear you to land here.
Captain, their
longest runway
is less than
5,000 feet.
Do you think we ought
to take a chance?
Global 33, you're cleared
to land on runway 22.
Altimeter 29-88,
winds south, ten miles per hour.
The captain is to report
to the c.a.a. Office immediately
after landing.
Roger, we'll
keep in touch.
C.a.a.?
They haven't called the
federal aviation agency
c.a.a. In years.
Now, we're going
down below, craig.
Hit the horn button.
Skipper,
do you know what that is?
I know exactly what it is.
It's the new york world's fair.
The new york
world's fair?
But that means
we'd be back in...
1939.
We came back.
We came back
but, dear god,
not far enough.
We can't land...
we can't land
at la guardia.
We can't land
in 1939.
We've got
to try again.
What about the passengers?
I think...
we better let them in on it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain.
What i'm about to tell you...
what i'm about to tell you
is something i can't
explain myself.
Your crew is as much in the dark
as you are.
If you look out from the
left-hand side of this aircraft
you'll see directly below
an area called lake success.
Those buildings aren't
the united nations.
They happen to be... they
happen to be the world's fair.
What i'm trying to tell you is
that somehow, some way,
in some manner
this aircraft has gone back
into time and it's 1939
but we're going to try
to increase our speed
and go back
through the same sound barrier
we've already done twice before.
I don't know if we can do it.
All i ask of you is that
you remain calm and pray.
A global jet airliner
en route from london to new york
on an uneventful afternoon
in the year 1961
but now reported overdue
and missing
and by now searched
for on land, sea and air
by anguished human beings,
fearful of what they'll find
but you and i know where she is.
You and i know what's happened.
So if some moment, any moment
you hear the sound
of jet engines
flying atop the overcast
engines that sound
searching and lost
engines that sound desperate
shoot up a flare
or do something.
That would be global 33
trying to get home
from the twilight zone.
Rod serling, creator
ofthe twilight zone
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
I've only got about 18 seconds
to tell you that next week
mr. Burgess meredith returns
tothe twilight zone
as mr. Dingle the strong.
He plays the role
of an incredible little man
who's given the strength
of about 500 men
and comes out of it as a kind
of 20th century hercules
and samson all rolled into one.
Its designed to send you right
from your set
into a fast bowl of spinach.
It's catching.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
be sure and see the colgate-
palmolive company's
new comedy show
my sister eileen
wednesday night on many
of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org