Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound...
a dimension of sight...
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Christie.
Honey, i want you to run
upstairs with your present.
Can't daddy see it?
Not right away.
All right?
Yes, mommy.
Hi.
Hi, daddy.
What did you buy?
Nothing much.
Go on, christie.
Wait a minute,
christie.
What have you got there?
It's just a doll, erich.
She doesn't need another doll.
She's had her eye
on it for months.
I thought we agreed...
christie,
show daddy your doll.
She's alive, daddy.
And her name is talky tina.
For heaven sakes, annabelle,
a doll like that could cost...
i put it on the account.
Tina does everything.
She moves, and she can talk,
and i just love her already.
My name is talky tina,
and i love you very much.
All right, how much did it cost?
I told you, i...
i know, you charged it,
but how much did it cost?
Erich, that's enough.
How much did it cost, annabelle?
Erich, i don't think
it's the price of the doll
that's upsetting you.
Now we'll get more
of that freudian gibberish
you've been getting
from her doctor, huh?
It isn't dr. Lubin's fault
she feels rejected.
My name is talky tina,
and i love you very much.
Will you shut that thing off?!
Oh, erich, how could you?
My name is talky tina,
and i don't think i like you.
Talky tina,
a doll that does everything,
a lifelike creation of plastic
and springs and painted smile.
To erich streator,
she is a most unwelcome addition
to his household-
but without her
he'd never enter
the twilight zone.
My name is talky tina
and i think i could
even hate you.
My name is talky tina,
and you'll be sorry.
Why, erich?
I don't like what it says.
You didn't have to throw it.
It has quite
a vocabulary.
Here...
listen.
My name is talky tina,
and i love you very much.
Yeah, well, that's not
what it said a minute ago.
I don't know how much more
of this i can take.
Exactly what is
it you're taking,
annabelle?
Your anger
toward christie.
I know you're having a
difficult time adjusting to her,
but i can't let you
treat her this way.
She's my daughter, erich.
I love her.
"I love her."
But i don't love her.
I'm only her stepfather,
and i'm incapable
of loving children
because we can't
have any of our own.
Isn't that what you're
saying, annabelle?
Erich, believe me, it's not.
You could love christie,
i know you could
if you'd give yourself
half a chance.
Good. I'm glad i'm not
the cold, cruel ogre
that mommy and
daughter think i am.
I appreciate all the
faithyou have in me.
Erich, please
give us a chance-
christie and me.
I know you got more
than you bargained for
when you married me.
Two for the price
of one, wasn't it?
But we'll do anything
to make you happy- both of us.
Daddy?
I'm sorry, daddy,
if i made you mad.
It's all right,
christie.
It's all daddy's fault, okay?
Sure, daddy.
Here, dear.
My name is talky tina,
and i love you very much.
Be a good girl, tina,
and eat your supper.
Eat your own supper,
christie.
I didn't know
your doll could wink.
Tina can't wink, daddy.
Really? I thought...
never mind.
Where'd you buy her?
Mason's.
She'll be a good playmate
for christie.
Mm-hmm. Lacking a brother
or sister, you mean?
I didn't say that.
But that's why you bought
the doll, isn't it?
Sort of a reminder?
It hadn't occurred to me,
but if that's what
you want to think...
it's linda.
Are you through
with your dinner?
Yes, mommy.
May i take tina?
Not outside.
You can show her
to linda later.
My name is talky tina,
and i'm beginning to hate you.
My name is erich streator,
and i'm going to get rid of you.
You wouldn't dare.
Oh?
Wouldn't i?
Annabelle would hate you,
christie would hate you,
andlwould hate you.
Just seeing
how it works.
Ow!
So you have feelings.
Doesn't everything?
Then i can hurt you.
Not really,
butlcould hurtyou.
Threats from a doll.
Who are you
talking to?
Oh, here.
The game's over.
Game?
Come on, annabelle,
get off it.
How dense do you
think i am?
I wish i knew
what you were talking about.
I admit i don't know much
about modern times
like putting walkie-talkies
in dolls...
walkie-talkies?
Get off it,
will you, annabelle?
I mean, all that stuff
about hating me
and that last bit about,
uh, feelings-
"doesn't everything?"
You belong in comedy.
I think i'll have more coffee.
Linda wants
to see tina.
All right, dear.
My name is talky tina,
and i love you very much.
Isn't she
sweet, daddy?
You can think
whatever you want to,
but it's not true.
I'm not playing
a trick on you.
Go ahead, pretend.
But i know there's
a microphone around here.
You and christie are trying
to get even with me,
isn't that it?
That's ridiculous, erich,
and you know it.
Is it?
Then how come the doll
doesn't talk to me
when you're in the room?
You're really serious.
You really mean it.
Of course i mean it.
So tell me.
There's nothing to tell!
All right, don't tell me.
Keep your secret.
But you'll be sorry.
Christie?
You are going to be sorry.
Where's tina, daddy?
I wouldn't know.
You had her, daddy.
Go ask your mother.
She's already asked me.
Hmm. And what did
you tell her?
That i don't know
where she is.
Do you, erich?
Where is she, daddy?
Well, now, if your
mother can't tell you,
then neither can i.
Tina must be somewhere
about, christie.
Let's see
if we can find her.
Yes, mommy.
Hello? Hello?
My name is talky tina,
and i'm going to kill you.
Who is this?
Annabelle?
Hello?
Where is she?
She's still looking.
I don't mean
christie.
We haven't found the doll,
if that's what you mean.
That's exactly
what i mean.
You knew i put her
in the trash can.
You what?
But she's
not there now.
Erich, how could you?
I've had enough
of this nonsense.
A joke is a joke
but you're carrying
it too far.
Me?
You!
And christie!
Will the two
of you stop it?!
Erich, i haven't
seen the doll.
I haven't even
seen it since dinner.
I swear it.
You're telling the truth?
You didn't take it?
I didn't take it.
But i think it's dreadful,
your putting it there.
But who?
The phone call.
What phone call?
You were on the extension,
you said...
what are you
talking about?
Didn't you do it?
Do what?
No, it couldn't have been you.
How could you have made
the phone ring?
I mean, there are ways, but...
erich...
the telephone rang.
I answered it.
The doll's voice
was loud and clear.
It said, "my name is talky tina,
and i'm going to kill you."
What?
Would i lie?
Erich, i don't
know what to say.
Well, the doll's disappeared.
If it wasn't you,
it had to be christie.
Erich.
I told you
you'd be sorry.
Christie.
Wake up, christie.
Daddy?
Go back to sleep,
christie.
I want my tina.
I'm going to borrow
tina for a little while.
Tina belongs to me.
Go back to sleep!
What's happening?
The doll was
in her bed.
She's the one who's
been doing it.
Daddy, daddy, please.
I'm not your daddy!
There, there.
Die.
You'll die.
I thought you said
you had feelings.
I can stand it if you can.
Erich?
Erich, what
are you doing?
What i have to do.
Erich, don't.
Leave me alone.
What are you doing?
What do you think
i'm doing?
But why?
How could i live with you
after what you've done?
I had to- the doll.
You had to, to show your hatred
for me and christie.
Now, look, annabelle.
That doll talked to me.
That doll said things
no doll should say.
I had to get rid of it.
You've become
a stranger to me, erich,
a sick,
neurotic stranger.
You're filled with blind,
unreasonable hate.
You better see
a good psychiatrist.
I couldn't have imagined it.
Tell him you tried
to kill a doll.
I couldn't...
what did you do
with it?
I'll give it back.
I'll give it back
to christie.
Will that
solve things?
I don't know, erich.
My name is talky tina,
and i don't forgive you.
Shut up.
Please, shut up.
Tina.
Oh, tina.
What is it?
I heard something.
Erich, i don't
hear anything.
No, stay there.
Erich!
Erich.
My name is talky tina...
...and you'd better
be nice to me.
Of course, we all know
dolls can't really talk,
and they certainly
can't commit murder.
But to a child
caught in the middle
of turmoil and conflict,
a doll can become many things:
Friend, defender, guardian.
Especially a doll
like talky tina,
who did talk
and did commit murder-
in the misty region
of the twilight zone.
And now mr. Serling.
Next ontwilight zone,
a journey into a future moment,
a nightmarish,
frightening moment in time,
when man sits in his own rubble
and surveys the legacy
he's left to himself.
James coburn and john anderson
star in
"the old man in the cave."
Recommended viewing for the more
imaginative amongst you
onthe twilight zone.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org