Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
I can't decide...
eight or 12.
I think 12 might
suit you better.
What do you think, marilyn?
Hmm?
You weren't
even listening.
I'm sorry, mother.
I don't understand you, darling.
Most girls are thrilled when
it's time to pick a pattern.
You haven't
even looked
at the ones the
bureau sent over.
Oh, i looked at them.
I remember how excited
i was before i was done.
I couldn't sleep for nights.
I finally chose number 12.
I guess that's
everybody's favorite.
Aren't
you excited?
Marilyn, what are
you looking at, dear?
You, a picture
of you before.
Oh, dear.
It is you,
isn't it?
Yes, that's me before
my transformation.
I was a sight,
wasn't i?
Mother, i think
you were beautiful.
Well, i certainly don't.
Am i very homely now?
No, darling, not to me.
But afterwards,
you'll be beautiful.
Mother, if i didn't want
the transformation,
i wouldn't have
to have it, would i?
What are you talking about?
The transformation is
the most marvelous thing
that could happen to a person.
Well, i could wait
a little while, couldn't i?
Don't worry, darling,
you're just nervous.
What you need is a
glass of instant smile.
Just think,
very soon now
you can look
like that.
Won't that
be wonderful?
You rang, mrs. Cuberle?
Lana.
Pardon me... lana.
I don't know why teaching
you people to use first names
is such a problem.
A glass of instant smile
for marilyn, please, grace.
On second thought,
make it two.
Yes, ma'am.
Lana.
What's so terrible
about being beautiful?
After all,
isn't everybody?
Given the chance,
what young girl
wouldn't happily exchange
a plain face for a lovely one?
What girl could refuse
the opportunity to be beautiful?
For want of a better estimate,
let's call it the year 2000.
At any rate,
imagine a time in the future
when science has developed
the means of giving everyone
the face and body he dreams of.
It may not happen tomorrow,
but it happens now,
in the twilight zone.
Who is it?
Hi, uncle rick.
Take it easy with
that uncle rick stuff.
Are you trying to
make me feel old?
I'm sorry, i forgot.
Now, young lady,
what's all this i've
been hearing about you?
You know, honey, your
mother is very worried.
I don't want
to be transformed.
I want to stay ugly.
Oh, you're not ugly,
you're just...
not beautiful.
Well, i wouldn't
exactly say that.
It's just that, uh...
you're different.
Sit down here.
Marilyn, your father
was transformed.
Yes, number 17
just like you.
A very popular
number these days.
As a matter of fact,
it has been for 20 years.
He wouldn't have settled
for anything less.
But is that good?
Being like everybody-
isn't that the same
as being nobody?
I think it's time
you tell me
where you're getting
these radical ideas.
Daddy once said...
your father was
a handsome man.
But he thought
about things
and he read books.
We talked a lot,
just the two of us.
Everybody talks.
I mean about
real things
not just about
electronic baseball
or super soccer
and where to buy
your clothes
or how to fix
your hair.
Is that bad?
Liking sports,
buying new clothes?
No, of course,
it isn't
but there's got
to be more to life.
You don't feel
very well.
What you need
is a nice cup
of instant smile.
I had a cup
of instant smile!
I don't feel like
smiling all the time.
Sometimes i want
to cry or frown.
Won't you understand?
Marilyn, you are
a very sick girl.
It's been very nice
talking to you, valerie.
Thank you.
Hi, marilyn.
Hi, valerie.
Are you two
going out?
I don't think so,
mrs. Cuberle.
You promised
to call me lana, remember?
Oh, yes. Lana.
Well, i know you two
have a lot to talk about
and i'm due
at culture class.
Bye.
Good-bye.
She told you, didn't she?
Yes, she did.
Don't you think you're
being awfully silly?
No. There's no law, is there?
But it isn't as if
it hurts or anything.
When they did mine,
i didn't feel a thing.
I know that.
Well, you like the way i look,
don't you?
I like you, val, we're friends.
I liked you
before the transformation.
But you're missing the point.
It's like getting
a new hairstyle
or new clothes or something.
You just look better.
I'll look like
one of those drawings
that the bureau sends over.
But they're all beautiful.
What's wrong with that?
It is wrong, valerie.
How will you know me?
I mean, how will anyone know me?
I don't want to look
like everyone else.
I want to look like me.
And i'm not going
to let them change me.
I won't let them change me.
Valerie,
please help me.
Please.
Doctor will
see you now.
Ah, come in, please, lana.
Thank you,
doctor.
Come,
marilyn.
And this
is marilyn.
Sit down,
sit down.
I'm sorry to have
to bother you, doctor.
It's such a silly
thing, really.
Not at all,
not at all.
I see you're
18 now.
It must be
just about time
for you to,
uh...
ah! I see
you've already
received notice.
That's why
we're here.
Of course.
You mustn't worry, lana.
Marilyn is like the rest
of them nowadays.
I am?
And it's our fault really.
You see, we haven't given
her any definite reason
why she must wait
until the age of 19.
You see, she looks
at you, lana,
and the
other women
around her
and then
at herself
in the mirror.
Doctor...
from pure perfection
of body, face, limb,
pigmentation,
stance, carriage,
she looks at herself
and she's horrified.
Isn't that so?
Of course.
You see, the poor child
says to herself
why should i be so hideous?
So awkward,
oversized, unbalanced,
so full of revolting
skin eruptions, eh?
In short, lana,
our marilyn is tired
of being a monster.
Dr. Rex, you
don't understand.
What's that?
She isn't anxious.
I don't want to have
the transformation.
You what?
I can't understand.
She never said anything
about it before.
Is this true?
Yes.
She doesn't
give any reasons.
Yes, yes.
Now, marilyn,
suppose you tell me
all about it,
in your own words.
I don't know.
I just don't want the change.
You understand, of course,
that the transformation
has become a normal part
of growing up.
It's a sign of maturity.
What, being like everyone else?
Marilyn...
would you mind
if i conducted an
experiment with you?
Purely for
my own records.
This way, please.
Sit right down
here, please.
Now, marilyn,
you must try to understand
the transformation is
not merely desirable
from an aesthetic
point of view.
But experience
has shown us
that it plays a
very important role
in psychological
adjustment.
Now just hold your head
very still, please.
This won't hurt a bit.
There we are.
That's all
there is to it.
Yes.
Lana, you have no idea what
triggered this resentment?
I can't imagine.
She's never shown
much interest.
It never
occurred to me.
I see that
your husband died
in the ganymede
incident.
Five years ago.
Did you and he ever
have an occasion
to discuss this matter
between yourselves?
Yes, he was opposed
to it at first.
But he finally chose
number 17, your number.
Ah, i see.
Marilyn, you can
come over here now.
We're quite
finished.
Now, marilyn, i take it
that you were quite fond
of your father.
Yes.
And you
no doubt
respected
his opinions.
Did he ever say to you that
the transformation was bad?
No, not exactly.
What did he say to you?
He said... he thought
it was tragic.
My husband had some
rather nonconformist ideas,
but it was just talk.
He had the highest physical
and psychological rating
with the rocket service.
Yes, yes.
Lana, this case
is extremely unusual.
I'm afraid that
i shall require more time
to examine the matter further.
Suppose i get in touch with you?
You find out
what's in there?
What's
that?
Did you find out
what's inside of me?
Yes, indeed.
Your general intelligence
rating is quite high.
Your social adaptability
is good.
Your powers of reasoning,
quite normal.
Then why can't i make up
my own mind?
Marilyn, please.
Why are you forcing me
to do something i don't want?
You can't make me
do it, can you?
Nobody can
make me do it.
Now, now,
my dear child.
No one has ever
been forced
to take
transformation
if he
didn't want it.
You see, the
problem is simply
to discover why
you don't want it
and then to make
the necessary
correction.
Right in here, please.
What place is this?
Marilyn cuberle.
Come in and sit down, please.
There's nothing
to be frightened of.
Who are you?
Sit down, please.
I am professor friend,
sigmund friend.
You must call me
professor sig.
Dr. Rex has told me
about you.
I am here to help you.
Help me?
To help rid you
of these fears
of this necessary...
that isn't true.
They're
not necessary.
This is very necessary,
very important step
in your life.
Why? Why does everyone
want to force me
to do something
i don't want to do?
But for your own good.
Why else?
Why else would the state go
to such trouble and expense?
Many years ago, wiser men than i
decided to try and eliminate
the reasons
for inequality and injustice
in this world of ours.
They saw in physical
unattractiveness
one of the factors
which made men hate.
So, they charged
the finest scientific minds
with the task of eliminating
ugliness in mankind.
But i'm not ugly.
I'm not pretty,
but i'm not ugly.
But to others you are.
Not to people who love me.
There is more to it
than that, of course.
As we learned to reshape
the features, remold the body,
we also learned to eliminate
most of the causes of illness
and thus to prolong life.
Before the transformation,
you could have expected to live
70, 80, perhaps 90 years.
But now you can live
twice that long.
Perhaps
three times.
This is a good
thing, is it not?
Yes...
your mother, ah,
she is lovely, is she not?
At one time,
her body, her face,
might already be
showing signs of age,
of decay.
You would not deny your mother
her youth, would you?
But you could do that anyway,
couldn't you?
Keep me young
without changing me.
I wouldn't mind just that.
But someday you might
and that would be too late.
You see, the transformation
must be performed
when the body and the tissue
are at the proper state.
No, i'll never change my mind.
I've thought about it
and i never will.
Why?
Have you ever read shakespeare?
Who?
Or keats or shelley?
Those books were banned
many years ago.
Where did you find them?
My father gave them to me
and lots of others.
Aristotle, socrates,
dostoyevsky.
Did you know that dostoyevsky
was an epileptic?
He was ugly, he was deformed,
but he wrote about beauty,
about real beauty.
I must warn you,
this subversive...
these men wrote about life
and about the dignity
of the individual human spirit
and about love.
This is enough!
The introduction of smut
into this interview
will not help your case,
young lady, not at all.
May i go?
Yes, certainly, i have
arranged a room for you.
You will be quite
comfortable.
I don't want
to stay here.
I want to go home!
Your mother
will be informed
and you will be
allowed visitors.
Come, my dear.
Why do i have
to stay here?
I am afraid that
for the time being
you must let us decide
what is best for you.
We won't
hurt you.
We're going
to help you.
This way, lana.
She's right
in here.
Marilyn?
Marilyn, you
have visitors.
Mother?
She was upset
last night.
I gave her
something
to help her
sleep.
She's all right,
isn't she?
You haven't
done anything?
Just a mild
sedative.
Now if
you ladies
will
excuse me.
Darling, we'd have
been here sooner
but the doctor said
you were sleeping.
Do you feel all right?
Yes.
Hello, valerie.
Hi, honey,
what happened?
Nothing.
They just wouldn't
let me go.
Oh, mother, they're
going to do it anyway.
They're going to
make me do it!
No, marilyn, dr. Rex
promised, remember?
He was lying!
Lying, but why should he?
He has to say that
to keep people from finding out
the transformation will be done
whether you want it or not.
I don't see
why you're unhappy
when all they want to do
is make you pretty.
But that's not true!
Last night, before
i went to sleep,
i remembered something
that father said.
He said, "when
everyone is beautiful
"no one will be
"because
without ugliness
there can be
no beauty."
Mother, don't
you understand?
They don't care whether
you're beautiful or not.
They just want everyone
to be the same.
"They"?
Who are you
talking about?
I'm terribly
sorry,
but i'm afraid
it's time
to leave now.
Oh, well.
If it's
all right,
i'd like to talk
to marilyn.
Just for a
few minutes.
Don't worry,
darling
everything's going
to be all right.
I've been thinking
about what you said.
I mean about what
your father said
and... well,
i don't see why
you're so concerned
about him.
He's dead.
I mean, surely
you've had
other fathers.
My mother's been
married 11 times
and personally
i've liked the
stepfathers better.
Valerie,
please don't.
Look, i know you've
had nine fathers
since the first one.
Everybody marries
everybody these days.
Valerie, stop.
I just don't see how
anybody can stay married
to the same husband
for a hundred years.
Besides, i've heard that
your father was pretty dull.
Valerie, stop it!
Stop talking about my father!
Can't any of you understand?
I loved him.
I cared about him.
He was good and he was kind
and he cared about me;
not what i wore,
not the way i looked
but what i thought, what i felt.
He cared about himself and
his dignity as a human being.
Valerie, he didn't die
in the ganymede incident.
My father killed himself.
Because
when they took away
his identity he had no reason
to go on living.
I just don't
understand you, marilyn.
Valerie...
can't you feel anything?
Well, of course, silly.
I feel... i feel good.
I always feel good.
"Life is pretty, life is fun
i am all and all is one."
You can't understand, can you?
What?
They can't
understand.
They can't understand.
Come in,
my dear.
We've been expecting you.
Sooner or later,
everyone wants to be beautiful.
Where's
your number?
She's chosen
number eight.
Excellent,
excellent.
I just love
your suit, val.
Lana, val!
You're just
in time.
It's all
over, doctor?
All over.
Is she
all right?
She's fine.
You'll see for
yourselves.
I've been
so worried-
not being able
to talk to her
and she seemed
in such a state.
Well, it's
as i told you.
Occasionally,
a person has
difficulty adjusting
to the idea.
But we've
improved methods
since the old days
and now it always
turns out well.
Never fails.
It's complete.
Mother!
Mother, val.
Look at me.
What do you think?
You're beautiful,
marilyn
just beautiful.
And the nicest
part of all, val-
i look just like you.
Portrait of a young lady
in love-
with herself.
Improbable? Perhaps.
But in an age
of plastic surgery,
body building
and an infinity of cosmetics
let us hesitate
to say impossible.
These and other
strange blessings
may be waiting in the future
which, after all,
is the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Earl hamner, jr. Brings his
typewriter and his fertile mind
back intothe twilight zone
next time
with a program about visitors.
On the surface
they're beatniks-
a few raunchy looking characters
on motorcycles
draw into town one day.
But once you meet them,
you won't forget them-
they're quite different
from what they appear.
Onthe twilight zone,
lee kinsolving, shelley fabares
and michael forest
star in "black leather jackets."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org