Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
The time is 1863,
the place the state of virginia.
The event is a bloodletting
known as the civil war
a tragic moment in time
when a nation was split
into two fragments,
each fragment
deeming itself a nation.
What is it?
I thought
i heard something.
Yanks?
I don't hear 'em no more.
Dauger, you figure
this would fire
if you was to press
the trigger?
I reckon.
What's the idea,
paradine?
The idea is, dauger,
you ain't a right arm to me
or a left arm.
You're just
some extra baggage
that breathes hard
and splits my rations.
You figure you'll shape up
by the end of the war?
I can't help it!
It used to...
it used to be i never
give it any thought.
It used to be like
it was some kind of game
we was playing like kids.
King of
the mountain.
Hide and go seek.
Blind man's bluff.
But it ain't that way
anymore, paradine.
I seen too much
of this business.
I was at the second manassas.
You haven't got
a nerve in your body,
have you?
Just as many as you, son.
From head to boot.
Only i don't concern myself
as much as you.
You're worrying about dead men
and lost battles.
That's just too much area
to fret in.
I'm worrying about two scouts
on a mission,
and a dirty piece
of brown paper.
It says the yanks are going
to take up a position
in the chano valley.
We got to scout them
and report back
as soon as they get
into that town
down there below.
Yanks?
Yanks, probably.
Horses, positive.
How many?
It's a patrol,
i figure.
20, 30 men.
That's funny.
What is?
Well, i know
i heard horses,
and it's coming
from down there.
They're yanks.
Ain't no question
about that.
Listen, joe,
we're exposing ourselves here.
This is no place
to stand out in the open.
If they are yanks,
they'd be in that town
down there by now.
Be as noisy as
a county fair.
There ain't a
sound anymore.
Reckon i better
get down there
and take a close look.
Listen, joe...
let's pull out.
I don't like it.
You heard 'em.
We found out
what we had to find out-
the yankees are
in the valley.
So we go back
and report.
What's the point
in going down there?
The point is we got
to count their heads,
their horses
and their guns.
We got to get a look at
their regimental number.
That enough point
for you, mr. Dauger?
I don't care.
I just don't care
anymore.
I only got
one big mission left
and that's to stay alive.
All right, i say
we go down in that valley.
And we wave a shirt
and throw down our carbines.
Mr. Dauger, i
extend my sympathy
so long as your yellow
eats at your insides.
But when it crawls
into my bivouac
and tries to climb
up on my horse,
i withdraw my sympathy
and give you the
back of my hand.
So far, you and me pledge
nothing to the confederacy
except a lack of sleep
and empty bellies.
But there's a couple
of hundred thousand others
pledged
a lot more.
You're making
it appear
like they did it
for nothing.
Now you stay here.
If you hear a shot,
you get back to the lieutenant
at a fast gallop
'cause that will mean
they're down there in force.
And you tell him what happened.
If you haven't heard from me
in 15 minutes,
you get back
there anyway.
Listen, you going
down there alone?
Just me and this brave horse.
For want of anything else.
This is joseph paradine,
confederate cavalry,
as he heads down
toward a small town
in the middle of a valley.
But very shortly,
joseph paradine will
make contact with the enemy.
He will also make contact
with an outpost
not found on a military map-
an outpost called
the twilight zone.
Hey!
Hey, yank!
Sleeping.
Must be sleeping
or are you dead?
Are you dead?!
Plague maybe.
Some kind of sickness.
But that would take hours.
You wouldn't all be like this.
Not all at the same time.
Must be asleep.
No wounds.
Not a sign of blood.
Wake up.
Go on.
Wake up, go ahead.
You aren't dead.
None of you are dead.
Wake up, yanks!
None of you are dead!
All right, yanks,
you're all my prisoners!
Come on, yanks!
You're all my prisoners!
Well, you come
to the right place.
You sure come
to the right place, boys.
Food, clothing.
Ammunition.
What you got
is what we need.
You hear me, yank?
You come
to the right valley.
Nothing around here
but hungry confederates.
I don't understand.
I just don't understand.
What's happened to you?
Why are you...
why are you all quiet like this?
None of you can speak?
None of you can move.
First meat i've had
in a couple of months, you hear?
Wind... must be the wind.
It has to be the wind.
All right, in there,
you'd best come out now.
You hear?
You'd better come out now
or i'm coming in.
Oh, well, old man.
You don't know how close
you come to dying just then.
Now, you'd better tell me
just who you are
and what you're doing here.
I was just about
to ask you for the
same information, son.
When i first seen you
coming up the street,
i thought you
was a yank.
You don't know how close
youcome to dying.
What was you going to use,
grandpa, that book?
That's a pretty heavy thing
to be throwing.
This book,
but i wasn't aiming
to throw it...
just use it...
like i used it on them.
I done that, you know.
Put them all to sleep.
You don't believe
me, do you?
You think i'm lying.
I ain't
called you no liar.
Something happened
to 'em,
but there must be
some natural explanation.
They just couldn't...
"natural explanation."
Now, don't that take all.
This here's
what done it.
This here book.
That wasn't
bright of you.
bright of you at all.
Listen, old man.
You may be
harmless enough,
but i got no time
to fiddle around
with black magic
or any other
old men's games.
Games?
Games, you call it?
When there in front of you
stands the enemy?
Not even a twitch?
Not even a move
in the eyeball?
Well!
"Ye soldier, conjured here
"in the name
of the prince of darkness,
ye shall remain
silent and..."
now, listen, old man...!
How 'bout it now, johnny reb?
You believe me?
I reckon you
believe me now
being as you can't
move a muscle.
Being as you
can't speak even
a word out loud
you're just going to have to
stand there and listen to...
listen to me speak at you.
Oh, i know you
can still hear me
'cause i only used
half the power.
My name's teague.
I lived down yon by the creek.
I'm a witchman,
like my pappy 'fore me.
He was the seventh son
of a seventh son,
and i was his seventh son.
I know conjure stuff
forward and backward
and up and down.
It's my living.
And then the yanks come
and all the people
run afore 'em... 'cept me.
Invaders!
Tyrants!
Thieving skunks to boot!
But i fixed them.
I didn't do no la-dl-da.
I opened the book,
and i read the words,
and you can see
what happened to them.
Now... now, you listen
to me, johnny reb.
Your... your secession-
you fight the yanks.
Now, you be good and
don't give me no argument-
blink your right eye.
Now you'll be able
to move again
as soon as i
read the words.
"Ye soldier,
conjured here
"in the name of the
prince of darkness,
ye can now move and speak."
Hypnotism.
Hypnotism?
Hypnotism?!
This is conjure stuff.
And what i done
to them yanks,
i can do to the
whole union army-
freeze 'em all
in their tracks.
I can open up a
path to washington
so that bobby lee
could ride in there
with three confederate
troopers and take over
the whole country.
Magic.
You claim it's magic.
I don't claim it.
I say it.
Itismagic.
It's what i read in the book
and now... you seen it.
You felt it.
You mean you could...
you could do this
to the whole
union army?
Could and would.
Why don't you, old man?
Why don't you?
For one good reason,
one good reason only.
I'm goin' to die.
Mm. I'm goin' to die
afore the sun goes down.
I got a feelin' in my bones.
I can smell death,
and hear it comin'
on a white horse
galloping straight at me,
galloping, galloping
straight at me.
Old mr. Death
come to pluck me
out of the livin'.
So i ain't goin'
to be around
to do what's got to be done.
I'm leaving it
up to you.
Me?
I can tell about a man's looks,
his eyes, his head,
hold on his weapon.
I can tell all about that man...
and i'm choosing you.
You can find everything
you need in this book-
spells, talisman,
curses, everything.
Here.
Take it.
Don't seem right.
Don't seem right at all.
There's something...
something unclean,
like being in league with the...
that's it.
You got it right, johnny reb.
You said it like it's got
the devil.
That's who you're
in league with,
the devil himself.
That's who we'll have fighting
the devil.
The devil.
Halt. Who goes there?
Paradine,
troop scout.
Advance and be recognized.
You've been gone a
long time, paradine.
We give you up,
dead or prisoner
by this time.
Neither, lieutenant.
Not time for either
of it, it appears.
Well, a man's got to do
his reading, don't he.
Well, out with it, man.
What'd you see?
More'n you'd believe,
lieutenant.
Where was their advance party?
We haven't heard a sound
from that valley all day.
Their advance party's
in that town,
and the main body's
spread out behind.
Are you drunk or something?
Now, there hasn't been a sound
from down there all day,
not a sound.
Lieutenant, you got
every right to call me mad,
but the reason
you didn't hear 'em is...
is they're all asleep.
Put to sleep by magic-
black magic.
It's right here
in this book.
A little old man by the name
of teague- he done it.
Paradine, the
order's out.
You're to take
yourself to bed.
You're to sleep
the night.
Make your report to
me in the morning.
This is my report, lieutenant.
Where's mallory's troop?
They went up the north ridge
late this morning.
Yeah, there's a group of yankees
camped up there, wasn't there?
Company strength at least,
wasn't there?
That's what we figured?
But what's that got to do
with all this?
On the way back here,
lieutenant, i...
i... i opened the book,
and i read from a page of it.
Halt. Who goes there?
I conjured up a spell, and i...
and i turned it in the direction
of that ridge.
Mallory, paradine says...
l-i just seen something
l-i can't explain
no more'n any of my men
can explain it,
but they seen it too.
We was walking up that ridge
in the scrimmage line
scared out of our boots,
'cause it was so quiet.
We thought them yankees
was waiting for us
just beyond the parapet.
Yeah, they was waiting,
all right-
standing straight and tall,
guns to port,
frozen like statues.
Dead?
Not dead.
Not dead
and not alive.
Just frozen stock-still
like rocks.
Lieutenant, this done it.
Paradine, this is
the devil's work.
Well, what's this
all about?
This book- an old man
give it to me in town.
It is the devil's work.
I know that.
But maybe it's time
we called muster on the devil.
Maybe it's the only
thing left for us.
We ain't got enough guns.
We ain't got enough food.
We ain't got enough of anything.
We're losing, lieutenant.
The confederacy's
cracking up into little pieces
right in front of our eyes.
It's bleeding to death
every day.
We ain't got enough blood left
to make a change.
I don't know much about satan,
but this cause of ours is...
is dying right in front of us.
Paradine, open up the book
and read from it out loud.
Make it good for every
union soldier in the field.
Freeze 'em. Put 'em
into the earth or something,
but make it good.
"Satan... satan,
i call upon you,
"and in so doing
i revoke the name of..."
go on, joe, read it.
He calls upon us to
revoke the name of god.
Leave it be, dauger.
You said yourself
it's the only thing
we got left.
He's right, paradine.
God help us,
thatisall we have left.
What do we call 'em?
Damn yankees,
don't we, lieutenant?
That's the phrase,
ain't it- "damn yanks"?
If i read aloud
from this book,
it'll be the confederacy
that's damned.
It's that book
or it's the end.
Then let it be the end!
If it must come,
let it come.
If this cause is to be buried
let it be put
in hallowed ground.
Let it be put
On the following morning,
sergeant paradine
and the rest of these men
were moved up north
to a little town
in pennsylvania,
an obscure little place
where a battle was brewing,
a town called gettysburg,
and this one was fought
without the help of the devil-
small historical note
not to be found
in any known books
but part of the records
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week onthe twilight zone
we once again borrow the talents
of mr. Charles beaumont
who's written a script
especially for us
called "the jungle."
Now this is designed
for the reasonably
impressionable amongst you
who find nothing to laugh about
when somebody mentions
the words "black magic."
Mr. John dehner stars
in another small excursion
into the darker regions
of the imagination.
Next week, "the jungle."
This is james arness.
You know, it's only a short hop
fromthe twilight zone
to dodge city ingunsmoke.
Saturday nights
over most of these stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org