Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
She's all set,
mr. Radin.
How about the
sound system?
You check that out?
She's all
ready to go.
I don't know where you
got your sound effects
but you'd swear
a bomb was exploding.
I mean a big bomb.
That's precisely the way
it's supposed to sound.
That about do it,
mr. Radin?
That about does it.
You got quite
a setup here.
This part of
the illusion too?
No, this room is
not an illusion.
I venture to guess
that it's the best
designed bomb shelter
on the face of the
earth- who knows?
The hydrogen bomb
is not an illusion.
But tonight it's
for gags, huh?
Something of the sort.
A practical joke,
let's say.
You can say
that again.
When they start
those sound effects
and that stuff
on the screen
you'd swear the world
was getting blasted.
That's the idea.
I have three guests
coming this evening;
rather special
guests.
You did this to fool
three of your friends?
Must be kind of
special friends.
They are; they are, indeed-
very special friends.
What you have just looked at
takes place 300 feet
underground,
beneath the basement of
a new york city skyscraper.
It's owned and lived in
by one paul radin.
Mr. Radin is rich, eccentric
and single-minded-
how rich,
we can already perceive.
How eccentric and single-minded,
we shall see in a moment,
because all of you
have just entered
the twilight zone.
Good evening, friends.
Just step across the hall to
the door straight ahead of you.
Please come in, if you will.
Sit down, make
yourselves comfortable.
Please sit down.
How good of
you to come.
Colonel hawthorne,
mr. Hughes,
mrs. Langsford.
It's radin,
isn't it?
Aren't you paul radin?
You have an excellent
memory, reverend.
And you, colonel,
do you recognize me?
I believe i do.
Served under me once,
didn't you, radin?
I did indeed, second lieutenant,
infantry regiment
under your command,
africa, 1942.
I recall it vaguely.
I seem to recall
something else too.
It's not surprising it
doesn't flood back to you.
You had a few thousand
men under you.
I was only one.
But then again, you didn't
court-martial all of them.
That distinction
you reserved for me.
Ah, yes, i do recall.
You refused to lead
an assault on a hill;
refused in the face
of a direct order.
The delay cost us
almost a company of men.
That was your contention
to the court-martial board,
and so i was stripped of rank,
dishonorably discharged.
You were fortunate,
mr. Radin.
Were i to have
dictated the sentence
i would have had you shot.
I'm sure you would have,
colonel.
I'm sure you
would have.
But what a wretched host i am
to neglect the lady present.
Mrs. Langsford.
Do you recall
who i am?
Of course,
i do, paul.
I taught you
in high school.
I don't forget
my students.
Oh, sometimes the names
and the faces get confused
but if i prod my memory
i usually can connect
a name and a face-
and, in your case, a character.
You flunked me, mrs. Langsford;
dressed me down
before an entire class;
called me names, humiliated me.
Well, let
me say again,
how good of
you to come.
I'm delighted
you accepted
the invitation.
Invitation?
The request that i come here
was an ultimatum.
Your chauffeur said
it was a matter
of life and death.
Well, yes, yes, indeed.
That's the way it
was broached to me.
I was having my dinner
and my wife mary went
to answer the door,
and when she came back,
she had such a strange
expression on her face.
Ah, mr. Hughes,
you've never ceased
to be a bit on the wordy
side, now, have you?
It's odd, really, how changeless
we remain over the years.
But then again, i suppose
certain lifetime habits
are not easily put aside.
Paul, perhaps you'd be
good enough to tell us
why we've been asked
to come here.
I'd be delighted to.
But first,
can i get you something?
A highball, perhaps...
or a cup of coffee?
Reverend, how do you
take your coffee?
Habits, mrs. Langsford-
the incredible
persistence of habits.
You call me paul, as if
i were still sitting
in the front row
in your classroom.
But what about you,
mrs. Langsford?
A nice cup of tea?
Thank you, no.
Oh?
How about you, colonel-
a tot of rum, perhaps?
I would appreciate
if you made your point
and let us leave.
You've obviously called
us here for something
and i would welcome
hearing whatever it is.
How staunchly military, colonel.
Drive, drive, drive!
Get up against that objective
and wipe it out.
Red flag in the map
and troops
out of the sun.
The nerves of steel
and a concrete head.
That will
be all, radin!
Colonel, you are
no longer in command.
I'm in command here
and what i command
is your attention.
I called you
three here
for a very
specific purpose.
I want to settle
three old scores
but will do it
in chronology.
My dear old schoolmarm
shall begin-
that staunch and
intrepid educator
that looks so
out of place
without her
severe spectacles
covering severe eyes
looking out of
a severe face
and possessing
that vast prerogative that comes
from the school board,
and the vast courage
that comes with pitting all her
wits and instinct and knowledge
against captive children.
Are you finished, paul?
My dear schoolmarm,
i've hardly begun.
Well, then, may i make
an observation?
Just a comment
on how incredible
this whole thing is
that a man like you,
a millionaire three times over,
an important man who walks
with kings and heads of state
and industrial
tycoons-
that such a man should
have a mind so tiny
that it could brood
over a high school incident
of 20 years ago
and let it fester inside you
as you seem to have done.
I have never liked humiliation,
whether it happened 20 years ago
or in the past ten minutes.
Humiliation?
All right, paul, let's
talk about humiliation.
Let's talk about
your humiliation.
Mr. Radin was caught
cheating in
an examination.
Not a crime,
of course,
but perhaps a bit indicative
of the character
of the person who does it.
And when he was accused
of this act,
this cocoon-
soon to become tycoon-
tried to plant his crib sheets
on an innocent student.
How right you are,
mr. Radin, that i stood you
up on your feet
and in front of
the entire class
i told you exactly
what you were.
But no room was there
then, mrs. Langsford,
for a moment of compassion,
for an iota of sympathy
for a poor, frightened,
desperate boy.
Mr. Radin, i've dealt
with frightened and desperate
children all my life.
And it may surprise you to know
that i've lent them
more of sympathy
and of compassion
than i have lent
them of knowledge.
But neither sympathy nor
compassion can be handed out
wholesale,
like cheap bubble gum.
The recipient must
be worthy of them
and you never were.
You were a devious,
dishonest troublemaker.
And in spite of
all your millions,
it's my guess you are still
devious,
you are still dishonest.
And i've no doubt, even now,
you're
a troublemaker.
You haven't changed,
mrs. Langsford.
Mr. Radin, obviously
many years have passed
between now and the time you
felt you'd suffered indignities
at our hands,
but what's to be gained by...
a great deal can
be gained, reverend.
A very great deal.
You, for example, accused me
of a lack of character,
put a scandal over my head,
destroyed my reputation.
Yes, i remember.
A girl, mr. Radin,
a girl you drove to suicide.
Because even at
that early stage
you were not a man who held
honor in very high regard.
You can go
to the devil, reverend!
Radin!
And you, too, colonel.
Tonight,
my friends,
you will all
go to the devil,
and that is not a
figure of speech!
Do you know why i built
this room down here?
Those walls are 18
inches concrete with
reinforced steel.
And around them,
six inches of lead.
I have my own generator
system, my own air system.
Yes, and out there,
beyond that door,
a storeroom the size
of a warehouse.
You understand
logistics, colonel.
Does it occur toyouwhy i
should have gone to all this
trouble and expense?
To begin a vigil, my friends.
The long wait and the countdown.
Yes. I have walked
with kings and tycoons,
as you perceive, mrs. Langsford.
I have walked with them,
and i have listened to them.
I keep abreast of the times,
and usually well ahead of them.
I know things
that are going to happen.
I pay for the service.
48 hours ago
i received a most
interesting bit of news,
something that
perhaps only six men
in the world know of...
the world is coming
to an end this evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
At 11:45, there will be no
more city, no more country.
At 30 minutes after midnight,
there will be no more world.
They are going
to bomb us,
and we are going
to bomb them.
By dawn, there will be nothing
left but rubble and bodies.
And in a few moments
it will all begin.
You'll be hearing
sirens very shortly-
that's the red alert.
That means their missiles
are on their way.
Ours will follow
soon after.
And you are to
survive, mr. Radin?
Is that the idea?
I am to survive, mr. Hughes.
I am 300 feet underground.
And what about you, reverend?
Do you wish
to survive?
Do the rest of you
wish to survive?
Or am i to be
the only pallbearer?
This is your civil
defense announcer.
Repeating, the air defense
command has just declared
a take-cover signal.
This is not a practice warning,
not a drill.
An attack by enemy forces
is expected at any moment.
You must seek the nearest
shelter immediately.
If you are in your home,
go to your prepared shelter
or to the basement.
If you have no shelter
or basement,
go toward the center of the
house, to the first room
or hall
that will put as many walls
as possible between you
and the outside of the house.
Take your radio with you.
If you are in any other type of
building, go to the basement
or lowest floor and get as close
to the center of the building
as possible.
...leave your shelter until told
it is safe to do so.
This is not a test.
This is a real take-cover...
comments?
Perhaps a little military
sophistry now, colonel.
A quote from
general grant.
Or you, reverend,
something enriching
from the gospel.
Such silence, mrs. Langsford?
Nothing in that vast repertoire,
that pilgrim's progress mind
of yours,
to handle
the situation?
A mental eraser to
wipe out reality?
I've got to
get to my wife.
By all means, reverend,
get to your wife.
Hold hands and
die together.
You turn my stomach,
mr. Hughes.
"Get to your wife."
That's not what's
on your mind.
What's on your mind is
what's on the colonel's mind
and the schoolmarm's mind.
Your precious hide,
your sanctified flesh.
That's what preoccupies
you at the moment.
If i'm to die tonight
i want to be with
someone i love.
"Somebody i love..."
how theatrical!
But more burlesque
than legitimate.
Have the decency, reverend,
to depart this earth
with just a fragment of
the truth in your mouth.
Tell me to my face
that you're so scared,
so miserably frightened,
that you'd sell
your wife by the pound
if it meant
your own survival.
If those were the last words
i spoke before i died,
they would also be
the worst falsehood
i ever uttered on earth.
Now, will you open this door?
Will you let me leave now?
How did you
know, radin?
How could you
possibly have known?
What difference
does it make?
If he'll let
us leave now
perhaps we can
reach our homes
before it happens.
My dear friends, shall we drop
the pretenses now?
Shall we, all of us now,
tell the truth?
I told you
how this room
was constructed-
steel, concrete and lead.
It may be the only place on
earth where you can survive.
Now, what is this nonsense
about going back to your homes?
Do you mean to say that you
would walk out of here and die
when by simply sitting
here you could live?
Are we to understand,
mr. Radin,
that you will permit
us this luxury?
You will allow
us to stay?
Of course, colonel.
As a matter of fact,
it's precisely why
i've asked you to come.
Each of you in his own way
has tried to destroy me.
But i'll not repay
the compliment.
That is to say, i will not
require an eye for an eye,
nothing as primitive
or as naked as that.
What is your price,
mr. Radin?
I'd be interested.
The colonel would
be interested.
I presume the reverend
and the schoolmarm
would be interested.
I submit,
dear friends,
you're not
just interested.
It's probably the only
thing in god's earth
that has any meaning
left at all.
But the price, colonel...
you will beg my pardon,
you will ask my forgiveness,
and, if need be, will get
down on your hands and knees
to perform the function.
"Pretty please
with sugar on it."
How's that?
Speak up, teacher.
"Pretty please
with sugar on it."
It's what children say
to exact a favor.
I don't want your
favor, mr. Radin!
Let me out of here!
If i'm to spend my last
quarter hour on earth
i'd rather spend it
with a stray cat
or alone in central park
or in a city
full of strangers
whose names
i'll never know.
The door, radin.
Will you open
the door now?
Open up, radin.
You're too blind
or you're too stupid,
because none of you
seem to understand.
All you have to do-
literally, all you have
to do- is to say a sentence.
Just a string of
silly, stupid words.
Like a command, colonel,
or like
a lesson, teacher,
a prayer, reverend.
All you have to say
is you're sorry.
All right,
you want to die, fine.
But you'll be back
inside
five minutes.
There's the elevator!
Take it!
Take the farce
to its conclusion.
Go up into the street
and see the panic
and the frenzy
and the horror.
And then come back down
here to your salvation.
Or you can watch it all
down here on that screen.
You can see it all happen,
the whole thing.
Watch the world being
shoveled into a grave.
It's your
last chance.
It's your last chance,
i mean it.
Tell me, reverend, is
life so stinking cheap
that you can throw
it down a drain?
Life is very dear, mr. Radin,
infinitely valuable.
But there are other things
that come even higher.
Honor is one of them-
perhaps the most
expensive of them all.
Amen.
Try not to get
too lonely, mr. Radin.
Use mirrors.
They may help.
Put them all
around the room.
Then you'll have the company
of a world full of radins.
It'll be a fantasy,
of course,
but then your whole life
has been a fantasy,
a parade of illusions-
illusions about what
people have done to you,
illusions about what justice is,
illusions about
what is the dignity
of even the
lowest of us.
A fantasy,
mr. Radin,
and now you can have
it all to yourself.
No, it's not true,
it's not a fantasy.
No, it's not a fantasy!
This is your civil defense
announcer.
Our military authorities have
just ordered a take-cover alert.
Attack by enemy forces
is imminent.
Take cover immediately.
If you are in your car driving
away from your city, continue.
Keep on driving.
Do not stop.
When movement is
no longer possible,
seek the best available refuge.
That's enough!
If you are outdoors on foot,
hurry to the nearest shelter...
that's quite enough!
Anybody?
Anybody.
Please...
somebody...
hey, mac, mac.
Had a little
bit too much?
Hey, mac.
I didn't want
it this way.
Let me take
you home, mac.
I didn't want
it this way.
No, somebody, please.
Mac...?
Anybody, won't
somebody listen to me?
Go on now, move along.
Move along, please.
There isn't a thing
here to worry about.
Move along, please!
Please, move along,
please, please.
It's okay now.
You're gonna
be all right.
We're going
to help you.
Isn't there
anybody left?
Nobody?
You're gonna be
all right.
Nobody!
Now, go on,
break it up.
There isn't a
thing here to see.
Go on, go on.
Nobody.
Nobody...
oh, god...
god...
mr. Paul radin,
a dealer in fantasy
who sits in the rubble
of his own making
and imagines that he's
the last man on earth,
doomed to a perdition
of unutterable loneliness
because a practical joke
has turned into a nightmare.
Mr. Paul radin,
pallbearer at a funeral
that he manufactured himself
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, through the good
offices of mr. Charles beaumont,
we take a walk
in some dead man's shoes.
It's the story of a hobo
who takes some shoes
off a recently-deceased hoodlum,
and then discovers
that if the shoe fits,
you have to wear it.
And in this case, you have to do
as the shoes do-
go where they tell you to
and then perform some services
above and beyond the norm.
I hope we see you next week
for "dead man's shoes."
Seat belts can reduce serious
injury by one-third.
Does your family have the
security of seat belts?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org