Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Paper, paper,
get your paper!
Get your paper!
Paper!
Paper, paper!
Get your paper!
Late sports final!
This must be
your lucky day, mister.
That'll never
happen again
in a million years.
You miserable,
dirty, lowdown...
if liz and eddie split up,
then liz can marry rock
and eddie can marry tuesday.
Uh-huh.
Oh, dear! Terribly sorry.
If he hits me, i'll die.
Easy, mister.
Are you all right?
Just lie still.
We'll get a doctor.
Doctor? Oh, no, no,
i don't need a doctor.
Just help me up.
No broken bones...
no scrapes
or scratches.
I seem to
be all right.
You can't know
how sorry i am, sir.
Well, there's
no harm done.
If you were hurt,
i could never forgive myself.
You clumsy idiot!
I wish you'd broken
your fool neck.
What did you say?
Are you certain
you're all right, sir?
L-l-i think so.
Thank heaven
for that.
Lamebrain!
With your asinine jaywalking,
you took ten years off my life.
Mr. Hector b. Poole,
resident of the twilight zone.
Flip a coin
and keep flipping it.
What are the odds?
Half the time it'll come up
heads, half the time tails.
But, in one freakish chance
in a million,
it'll land on its edge.
Mr. Hector b. Poole,
a bright human coin
on his way to the bank.
It's 9:10, hector.
Of course, felicia, baby.
You know i love you.
But how would it look?
I can just see
the headlines now:
"Prominent banker divorces wife
to marry chorus girl."
Oh, no, no, no, felicia, baby,
you misunderstand.
I didn't mean it
the way it sounded.
Yes, yes, yes, that's right.
Look, how about
this weekend, huh?
Just you and me, huh?
Yeah, yeah. Come in.
Hold on. There's
somebody at the door.
Yes, uh... what
is it, poole?
Mr. Bagby, i would
like to explain
why i was late
this morning.
Yes.
Sir, a very strange thing
happened this morning. I...
well, as you know, sir,
my record for
promptness is spotless.
I pride myself on
my attention to duty.
Yes, poole, we're all aware
of your devotion to the bank.
Get on with it,
you simpering idiot.
Do you think she's going
to stay on the line forever?
If you ruin
my weekend,
i'll string you up
by the thumbs.
Your weekend, sir?
Spoil your weekend?
What are you mumbling about?
Weekend?!
Can he know about felicia?
Impossible!
I've been
so careful.
So discreet.
You had something
to tell me, poole?
Poole?
Poole!
Those dodgers think
they can steal second
any time they want.
Well, they won't steal
a bag of popcorn
with that southpaw
pitching today.
Whois
pitching today?
What? What did
you say, hector?
Oh, nothing.
Nothing at all.
Good morning, sir.
Everything in
apple pie order, i trust?
Yes. Thank
you very much.
I'll bet this
grinning ape
is the one who sent me
that overdrawn notice.
No, sir.
I work over there
in the accounts section.
Poor mr. Poole.
He looks
tired and pale.
Mr. Poole?
Mr. Poole.
You know mr. Sykes
of ajax cement?
Yes, yes, mr. Sykes.
His loan has
been approved.
Will you see
that the papers
are properly signed?
Also that the
check is made out?
Certainly, mr. Graham.
Won't you sit
down, mr. Sykes?
Thank you.
Oh, a business loan
for $200,000.
That's quite a sum.
You expanding,
mr. Sykes?
That's right.
That's wrong.
Well, which is it?
Pardon me.
Oh... nothing.
Uh... mr. Sykes,
you are aware
that this loan must
be completely repaid
within 90 days.
I certainly am.
If i bet
the money right,
it could come to
well over a million.
I could pay
back the loan
and have enough to keep
ajax out of bankruptcy.
I'll put half of it
on lucky lady
in the sixth
and split the rest
between nimble runner and
crinoline at five to one.
Nimble runner?
Five to one?
What did you say?
Now, look here,
young man!
Oh, mr. Sykes, i was
just trying to...
what's going on, mr. Poole?
Anything wrong, mr. Sykes?
Well, mr. Bagby,
he just told me
he's borrowing this money
to bet on the horses.
I said nothing
of the kind!
Nimble runner,
five to one.
He's mad!
Poole! Doubtless
there's been a mistake.
Well, there certainly
has been a mistake.
If you'll come into my office,
i'll correct it at once.
I'll talk to you
later, poole.
Mr. Bagby...
poor mr. Poole.
You do all the work
around here,
and get none
of the credit.
You should speak up more,
and assert yourself.
But i guess that's not
in your nature.
But i hope mr. Bagby
is easy on you.
Good morning,
mr. Poole.
Miss turner...
yes, mr. Poole?
Well, uh, please don't
be offended but, um...
well, i, uh, i would
like to thank you
for your, uh...
kind thoughts.
Well, i don't think
i quite understand,
mr. Poole.
Romancing the help,
mr. Poole?
Well, who can blame you?
Miss turner
is the prettiest girl
in the accounts section.
Which is saying
absolutely nothing.
I haven't seen such
an aggregation of beasts
since the last time
i went to the circus.
Not much chance
for socializing
around a bank,
is there?
This one is
probably a tiger
under the proper
conditions.
All the sweet,
prim types revert
to the jungle
once more.
You did that
deliberately.
Well...
i'll see you
later about this.
Good for you!
He certainly
had it coming.
I suppose i should
get back to my desk.
401, 402, 403...
20 years at
the same desk.
It isn't fair.
Ah, but they'll
be sorry
for their
treatment of me.
Yes...
at 4:30 this afternoon,
i'll go into the vault
like i always do.
I'll take my
briefcase with me,
and no one will
suspect a thing.
I'll fill my briefcase
with currency,
and be on ship to bermuda
by nightfall.
They'll all be sorry.
Yes, indeed.
I wonder how long
it will take them
to discover that
the money is gone.
Good night.
Hector.
Well, one more
day nearly done,
and no notches
on the gun.
You wouldn't use
that gun, would you?
What do you think i got it
on my belt for, hector?
Hold up my pants?
Miss turner...
may i talk to you
for a moment?
What i have to tell
you is very important.
Yes, mr. Poole?
Well...
i wish we could
talk someplace
where it's
more private.
Mr. Jones'
office is empty
since his transfer.
That is a good idea!
Is something wrong?
Dreadfully wrong.
Miss turner, i keep hearing voices
- people talking.
Their lips don't move,
but i can hear
their words clearly.
I've got this
ringing in my head.
Miss turner, i can
read people's minds.
Think something,
anything at all.
This is a strange
approach.
Why did it
take him so long
to gather up
his courage?
Well, it just
happened this morning.
Now, miss turner,
you may think that...
you may think that
i'm crazy but, uh...
i have reason
to believe
that someone plans
to rob the bank
this afternoon.
Oh, well, if someone's going
to rob the bank this afternoon,
you should do
something about it.
But what if i'm
wrong, miss turner?
You have a responsibility
to the bank.
To the stockholders
and depositors.
I'd better talk to
mr. Bagby right away.
What is this,
poole?
I'm worried
about you.
I've always
considered you
one of my best men.
Why, poole?
Tell me why.
We lost the ajax
cement account
because of
your nonsense.
Something
wrong at home?
Something bothering
you, poole?
Come on, tell me.
I don't quite know
how to tell you
this, mr. Bagby.
Speak up, poole.
We're all with you.
You won't believe it!
Nonsense. Of course,
i'll believe it.
Tell me anything.
Feel free.
Mr. Bagby...
mr. Smithers is planning
to rob the bank!
What did you say?
Mr. Smithers is sitting
at his desk right now,
planning to
rob the bank.
Well, i...
old mr. Smithers?
Old mr. Smithers.
At exactly 4:30,
he's going to
go to the vault,
fill his briefcase,
then he's taking
a boat trip to bermuda.
Tonight!
Smithers is one
of our oldest
and most trusted
employees.
He was here
when i came here.
I absolutely refuse
to believe that...
hold it.
Wait a minute.
Who's the man who ends up
stealing the company funds?
Isn't it always
the most trusted employee?
The man you least suspect?
The man who's been
reliable for years
until that one moment
when everybody relaxes?
Good man, poole.
I wish it weren't
true, mr. Bagby.
I've always admired
mr. Smithers.
I wouldn't have
believed it
if i hadn't overheard
him planning it myself.
No time
for sentiment, now.
Quick, now.
What's his plan?
Well, at
exactly 4:30...
it's time.
He's going to close
the drawers on his desk...
close up his books...
he'll stand up.
He'll pick up
his briefcase.
He'll go to the vault to check
up, just as he always does.
He'll be back
there alone,
only this time things
will be different.
When he comes out,
his briefcase will be
packed to the brim with...
jim.
Here, here.
What the...?
Just open the briefcase
and dump the contents here.
Your great mistake,
mr. Smithers,
is assuming that
we were all asleep.
A very great mistake!
As a matter of fact,
i've had my eye on you
for a long time.
Travel folders...
a sandwich...
socks.
Where's the money?
Is everyone going insane?
What money?
Poole...
where's that idiot poole?
Here, sir.
He was going
to steal the money.
He was going to take
a boat to bermuda.
That was the story, huh?
Well, mr. Bagby,
i heard him.
And who was he talking
to, mr. Poole?
Well, he wasn't exactly
talking to anyone.
He was... well,
he was thinking.
Please forgive us all,
mr. Smithers.
I should have
known immediately
that what i was told was
impossible on the face of it.
Poole?
I'm fired.
That's right.
Clean out your desk
at once.
Mr. Smithers, i don't
know what to say.
I...
i am sorry.
How did you know?
How did you
know, mr. Poole?
It's true,
of course.
I was thinking of
filling my briefcase
with the
bank's money.
Yes.
It's a little
dream of mine.
Have you ever had
a dream, mr. Poole?
I have.
I don't always plan
on bermuda though.
Sometimes, it's siam, fiji.
Beautiful,
exotic places
where there are
no books to keep.
Where i'm not a little man
with no future and no past.
Yes, mr. Poole...
yes.
But i'll never
go through with it.
You know why?
I've lived with
it too long.
I'm old and
set in my ways.
And besides,
mr. Poole...
i guess i'm a coward.
It doesn't matter,
mr. Poole.
A man with
your ability...
hearing people's thoughts-
strange delusion.
But, with proper
medical care,
it will go away.
Miss turner, it
is not a delusion!
There. You see?
Icanread
your thoughts.
Until this morning,
everything was
normal. I washappy.
At least i wasn't
unhappy. And now this!
It's like seeing people
with their clothes off.
I never imagined
people were like that.
You know, we do things
without thinking
about them at all.
And we think things
without having the...
slightest intention
of doing them.
Well, at least i've
learned one thing:
People are not like you
think they are at all.
Mr. Poole! Thank heavens
i caught you.
Ajax cement
was just on the phone.
Mr. Sykes
has been arrested...
for gambling with company monies.
Yes, i know,
mr. Bagby.
I tried to tell
you that earlier.
$200,000. if that loan
had gone through...
pardon me.
Uh, poole...
about your job.
It's still available
if you're interested.
If you can really
hear me, hector,
you're wasted in that job.
Everyone knows
you should be in charge
of the accounts
section.
What do you say, poole?
Mr. Bagby...
everyone knows i should be in
charge of the accounts section.
What?!
And that would mean
he'd move into
mr. Jones' old office.
That'd mean he'd...
i'd move into mr.
Jones' old office.
Now, look!
This is absurd.
What am i standing
here wasting time for?
Felicia is
waiting for me.
Man, oh, man, what a weekend
this is going to be!
Now, see here, poole!
Don't let him
bamboozle you.
Stand up to him.
He needs you more
than you need him.
Mr. Bagby...
let's get down to
business, shall we?
Business?
What business?
The business of
felicia and your wife.
Yes, i know all
about it, mr. Bagby.
I know where you're
meeting her and when.
Impossible. No one
knows about the trip.
The trip, mr. Bagby?
A word to the wise.
Am i right?
All right,
poole, you win-.
In charge of the
accounts division,
and office
next to mine.
You won't say anything,
to anybody, will you?
Not a word.
Not, not, not, not
a word, mr. Bagby.
Mr. Bagby, um...
there is one more thing.
At the bank's expense,
i'd like you to buy
a round-trip ticket
to bermuda.
I'd like you to
have it made out
in the name
of l.j. Smithers.
I think
he'd like that.
Are you out
of your mind?
Mr. Bagby,
remember.
One ticket
to bermuda.
Shall we leave,
miss turner?
I'd go anywhere
with you,
but i wish you'd
call me helen.
May i see you
home... helen?
Of course,
you can, hector.
What do you think
i waited for?
Paper! Get your
late afternoon paper!
Latest stocks!
Paper!
Why'd you do that?
I've had that coin
standing there all day long,
and nobody even
touched it until...
oh, hey, it's you-
same guy.
What do you think
about that?
You're the guy
who stood it up,
and you just
knocked it down.
Talk about
coincidence.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Listen...
it's gone.
It's gone!
Helen, helen,
think something.
Think something!
Helen, i can't
hear anything.
I think it's gone.
Isn't that great?
Isn't it wonderful?
Nothing.
Helen... helen!
Helen, listen.
I can't hear anything.
I can't hear a thing
you're thinking.
Can't you?
One time in a million,
a coin will land on its edge.
But all it takes to knock
it over is a vagrant breeze,
a vibration or a slight blow.
Hector b. Poole, a human coin
on edge for a brief time...
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
the creator oftwilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
This is room 22.
And, on the other side
of its doors lies an adventure
that is as fascinating
as it is inexplicable.
It's a story that comes to us
from mr. Bennett cerf,
who describes it
as an age-old horror tale
whose origin is unknown.
We've dressed it up
in some hospital wrappings,
and enlisted the performance
of miss barbara nichols.
Next onthe twilight zone,"22."
Be prepared to be spooked.
It's that kind of story.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
see the newandy griffith show
each week
over most of these stations.
Consult local listings.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org