Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Short.
5-0.
That's right, still.
They say that's their limit.
Hello.
This is baker company f.o.
You've wrecked
some rice paddies,
you've knocked down
a grove of palm trees.
What we're trying
to figure out is
if there's something
in your religion
that says you're not supposed
to send a shell
into a cave.
How's that?
Yeah, we can bypass it.
Well, look, all
you've done so far
is ruin some real estate
and kept some japs awake.
Anybody back there
figure out how long
it takes the enemy
to die of insomnia?
Yeah.
Yeah, all right.
Okay. Well,
keep in touch.
Hey, sarge, what goes?
They're going to
fire for effect
until late
this afternoon.
If they can't
smoke them out,
maybe we'll bypass it.
Yeah.
Well, that's what
i like to hear.
Amen.
Well, i feel
better already.
I've got no big yen
to run into
anything anymore,
not at this
stage of the game.
Let's go up.
You don't think
they'd expect us
to go at that
frontally, do you?
When two air strikes
and an afternoon
of lobbing shells
doesn't accomplish anything,
you better start
counting your cartridges
because we are
the bottom of the barrel.
When they can't move
an enemy with the big stuff,
that's when they call out
the queen of battle-
the everloving infantry.
Yeah, well,
what do you think?
A month? More? Less?
I don't know.
We got them ringed.
They're finished on okinawa.
The trouble with these
little bandy-legged buzzards
is that they just don't know
when to quit.
Look at them.
They're in there,
holed up in that cave,
beaten, sick, starved...
and yet there's no one in there
to tell them that the war's
over for them.
Those poor guys.
It's august, 1945,
the last grimy pages
of a dirty, torn book of war.
The place is
the philippine islands.
The men are what's left of
a platoon of american infantry
whose dulled and tired eyes
set deep
in dulled and tired faces
can now look toward a miracle-
that moment when the nightmare
appears to be coming to an end.
But they've got one more battle
to fight,
and in a moment,
we'll observe that battle.
August, 1945,
philippine islands.
But in reality it's high noon
in the twilight zone.
Which one of you is
sergeant causarano?
That'd be me.
I'm lieutenant katell.
I'm taking over the platoon.
What's your situation here,
sergeant?
Well, we're observing
for a mortar company,
lieutenant.
That cave down there-
a bunch of japs
holed up in it.
We've been trying to
get them out of there
for two days.
Nothing doing.
Your binoculars, please,
sergeant.
Tough little item.
Looks like we'll have to do
a little mopping up
by ourselves.
Sir?
We'll go at it frontally.
Move right in there
and wipe them out.
Hey, lieutenant,
you sure you got
the right platoon?
What about it, sergeant,
can we go it alone?
Go it alone?
Pardon me, sir,
but you've just inherited
a pretty good outfit,
but we're notthatgood.
This is infantry,
not kamikaze.
I told you he had
the wrong platoon.
I think he's got
the wrong army.
Your name is what?
Watkins, andrew j. Watkins.
Are you accustomed
to talking to an officer
lying on your back?
I'm not accustomed
to talking to
an officer any way.
We lost the last three
we had,
and there's usually
a little space of time...
well, you've been
assigned another one.
You've got to learn
to live with him.
We'll start off with
a little reminder.
When you talk
to an officer,
you stand up on
your two feet.
We've been in
the line 33 days.
We haven't had
much sleep.
You have my sympathy,
sergeant.
My job is to lead this platoon,
and i intend to lead it my way.
When i tell you to jump,
you'll jump.
If i tell you to stand up,
you'll stand up.
If i tell you to head
toward that cave,
that's exactly
what you'll do.
Begging the lieutenant's
pardon...
sergeant?
What are
your orders,
lieutenant?
We'll have to go right
in there and wipe them out.
What about it,
sergeant?
Are you asking my opinion,
lieutenant?
I'm willing
to discuss it.
Well, chronologically,
lieutenant,
first thing you should do
is take that gold bar
off your helmet
and take the one
off your collar
and put it
in your pocket.
The japs may be
half-beaten, half-starved,
but they're not dumb.
They're tough
and they're shrewd
and they got eyes.
We lost three platoon officers
because they made
slight motions of commands
with their hands,
and that's what
the japs look for-
the guy in command.
I intended to
remove the insignia.
Now what about
attacking the cave?
Well, maybe we'll
have to do it eventually,
but the war
isn't going to end
before dinnertime.
I say we sit on it
the rest of the day
and see what
some 105's can do.
Maybe you're right.
But it strikes me
we could move in there
and wipe them out
inside of an hour.
Lob grenades in
and pulverize them.
Lieutenant...
how long have you
been out here?
What's that got to do with it?
Not a heck of a lot, i suppose,
but you talk like
it's a football game
and this is no football game.
It's one long, hard gut ache
with a lot of torn-up,
mangled guys.
It's going to take a long time
for us to forget it.
You have to remember,
lieutenant,
you haven't
been shot at yet.
And you haven't
shot anybody either.
You got here ahead of me,
i'll concede you that,
but when it comes
to killing japanese,
i think you'll find me a
pretty efficient officer.
That's a filthy
piece, soldier.
I want clean weapons
in this platoon
because we're
going to kill japs.
That's my job.
This outfit
better shape up.
This one is
bloodthirsty.
You don't think
he'll want us
to scalp them?
No sleep or no guts,
which is it?
You're tired of
killing japs, is that it?
Or you just got
no stomach for it?
Lieutenant...
we're about
24 months up on you.
Now we've seen enough dead men
to last us for the rest
of our lives.
The rest of our lives,
lieutenant, and then some.
Now, you got a big yen
to do some killing?
Okay,
we'll do some killing for you,
but don't ask us
to stand up and cheer.
Causarano.
Those flamethrowers
arrive yet?
Yes, sir.
Figure we can move in
behind the next barrage
and get within 50 yards
of the opening.
Those flamethrowers can do
a lot of damage, can't they?
They can, indeed, sir.
What about
the phosphorous grenades?
I'd hate to
be hit by one.
Check with company
about the time
of the next mortar barrage,
and we'll move in there.
You're going to have
to double-time
this one, sergeant.
That is, if you're going
to keep up with me.
Yeah.
Well?
Nothing, lieutenant.
I'm not your
cup of tea,
am i, sergeant?
You got a little bit
too much vinegar
for me, lieutenant.
Look, we could
bypass them.
There aren't
20 japs in there,
and they're sick
and half-starved.
But they're japs.
They're men,
lieutenant.
You've got a funny
group here, sergeant,
and you're the oddball
of the bunch.
If i had to size you up,
i'd say you've either
got battle fatigue
or you're chicken.
Well, maybe neither
and maybe a little
bit of both.
I don't know, but
the way i size you...
go ahead, sergeant,
how do you size me up?
All right. You're
a pea green shavetail
just fresh
from some campus.
You're afraid
you won't bag your limit,
or worse, all shook up
because somebody might spot you
as a johnny-come-lately
instead of a killer of men.
I think that
ought to do it.
You asked me, you're
going to get it.
You want to prove your manhood,
but it's a little late
in the day,
and there aren't many choices
left as to how to do it.
It all boils down
to that lousy cave
full of sick, pitiful,
half-dead losers
and a platoon of
dirty, tired men
that have their craw
full of this war.
You're a lousy soldier,
and that goes
for the rest
of these poor, sick boys
you want me
to bottle-feed.
When you fight a war,
you fight a war.
And you kill until
you're ordered to stop.
I got your message,
lieutenant.
There's always someone like you
that sneaks in
before they close the door
to grind an ax before he gives
that final order.
What's your pleasure,
lieutenant?
How many men have to die
before you're satisfied?
Offhand, i'd say all of them.
No matter who they are
or where they are,
if they're the enemy,
they get it!
First day of the war
or last day of the war,
they get it!
Lieutenant yamuri,
you dropped
your glasses, sir.
Lieutenant yamuri, sir,
that was exceedingly
brave, sir,
trying to get at
the americans that way
and single-handedly.
)
The americans?
Those are americans
in the cave?
Yes, sir.
We figure there are
20 or 30 of them.
Most of them wounded.
Are you... are you
all right, sir?
Where are we?
Who are you?
Who am i, sir?
Sergeant yamasaki.
Are you all right,
lieutenant?
Are you...
feeling well?
Where are we?
I asked you a question.
Where are we?!
Why... why...
corregidor, sir.
When?
When, sir?
You mean, what is
the day's date.
May 4, sir.
It can't be may.
It's august.
August 6.
I... humbly ask
the lieutenant
to forgive me,
but i must
correct him.
The day is may 4.
May 4, when?
What year?
The year 1942.
Is...
is the lieutenant
all right?
Perhaps... perhaps
a touch of malaria.
What did you call me?
You called me
by a name.
Lieutenant
yamuri, sir.
I called you
lieutenant yamuri.
by your name, sir.
No.
No!
What happened to me?
What's going on?
What happened?
Yamuri,
are you sick?
I require an answer,
lieutenant.
I asked you
if you were sick.
We shall be moving out shortly,
and if you are too ill to move,
we shall
leave you here.
Leave me here?
We have
no transport
for the wounded,
lieutenant.
We shall shortly move up,
and you shall remain here.
My name is not yamuri,
i swear to you.
Something's happened.
My name is not yamuri.
My name is...
i'm all right.
Forgive me, sir.
I'm all right now.
You what?
I was feverish for a moment.
I'm all right now.
You sure?
Yes, sir.
Very sure.
Sergeant...
we move out
in five minutes.
Yes, sir.
Be ready
in five minutes.
Unfortunately, the artillery
was unable to do its job.
We will attack the cave
in force.
Prisoners, sir?
What?
Are we to take
any prisoners
if any surrender?
If any do, i suppose we can.
Yamuri...
take the first
section.
Move forward
very quickly.
Drop down 50 yards
in front of
the opening.
Watch for
my signal.
We will cover you
with automatic fire
before you make the attack.
Then section
two and three
will follow you in.
Understood?
Yes.
I didn't hear you.
I understand, sir.
Your section, sir.
You said
there were wounded in there.
I think so,
lieutenant.
When they ran inside,
they were carrying each other.
There are no more
than 20 or 30 men inside.
It shouldn't be
too difficult.
Americans.
20 or 30 americans.
I didn't hear
what you said, yamuri.
What did you just say?
There are wounded
in there, sir.
Perhaps...
perhaps what?
Perhaps we can let them
surrender or perhaps...
or? Or what?
Or perhaps we can
leave them there-
bypass them.
Bypass them, lieutenant?
Is that tactical?
Or is that some sudden
nugget of compassion
that you have unearthed
in your fever?
But they-they
are wounded.
They can't do
us much harm.
Neither can they
sink a battleship,
but nevertheless,
we have to destroy them.
A reminder, lieutenant-
the identity
of the men in the cave,
they are americans,
they are enemy-
healthy, wounded,
walking or lying,
they are the enemy.
The japanese army
does not bypass.
The japanese army attacks.
They japanese army
wipes out its opponents.
But they are
wounded, sir.
They are wounded
and beaten.
Lieutenant yamuri,
odd that you
should require this reminder,
but the comparative health
and well-being of the enemy-
his comfort
or his discomfort,
the degree of his anguish
or his incapacities-
have no more bearing
on a military action,
a tactical move
or a decision of command
than the fortunes
of an anthill
that you step on
when we move out to attack.
They are the enemy.
They are american.
If, when we enter the cave
and they are lying
on the ground,
i can assure you
i will have
no more compunction
about making them
a head shorter
than i would stepping
on that anthill.
But they are men.
They are enemy,
and this is war,
and in war, you kill.
You kill, lieutenant.
You kill until
you are ordered
to stop killing.
You kill until you
are ordered
to stop killing.
No!
Sections, assemble.
Sergeant yamasaki,
you will handle
the first section.
Sergeant hiro,
you will take
the second section.
Lieutenant ishimoto,
yours is
the third section.
All right?
We move out.
I will take care of
you when we return.
Captain!
What you do to those men
in the cave...
will it shorten the war
by a week,
by a day, by an hour?
May i ask the captain
what is his pleasure?
How many must die
before
he's satisfied?
Offhand, lieutenant yamuri,
i would say all of them.
I don't care where they are
or who they are.
If they are the enemy,
they are to be destroyed.
First day of the war,
last day of the war,
we destroy them!
Any time you say,
lieutenant.
Form lines for
the duck shoot.
Causarano...
something happened.
Something...
lieutenant katell.
Orders, lieutenant.
They want us
off the hill.
Who says?
Colonel hardin
at headquarters.
The air force
dropped a bomb
on japan
this morning.
They call it
an atomic bomb.
Hello. What's
all this about?
They figure the bomb
will end the war
in a of couple days.
They want the units
to pull back
and see
what happens.
Let's get ready
to move out of here.
You with us,
lieutenant?
Yeah, i'm with you.
Is it something,
lieutenant?
Yeah, it's something.
Well, i
wouldn't fret.
There'll
be other caves
and other wars,
other human beings
you can knock off.
I hope not.
God help us, i hope not.
"The quality of mercy
is not strained.
"It droppeth as the gentle rain
from heaven
"upon the place beneath.
It blesseth him that gives
and him that takes."
Shakespeare,
the merchant of venice,
but applicable to any moment
in time
to any group of soldiery,
to any nation
on the face of the earth,
or, as in this case,
to the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, an excursion into the
shadowland of the hereafter.
Miss gladys cooper
and mr. Robert redford
combine sizeable talents
to bring you a script
by george clayton johnson
entitled, "nothing in the dark."
The dark, in this case,
being the little nooks,
crannies and closets
of those regions
presided over by mr. Death.
I hope you'll be with us next
week for "nothing in the dark."
Our population's expanding
faster than our colleges.
For more classrooms
and finest professors,
help the college
of your choice.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org