Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
My son is coming to get me.
Good-bye.
Good luck.
I didn't say i'd come
and get you, dad.
I said i'd come
and we'd
talk about it.
Five... ten...
15... 20... 25...
30... 35... 40...
45... 50...
55... 60...
65... 70...
75... 80...
85, 90, 95, 100!
Here i come, ready or not!
Hey, mister.
That's our can.
We're playing.
Hey, mister.
Sunnyvale rest,
a home for the aged-
a dying place-
and a common children's game
called kick-the-can
that will shortly
become a refuge
for a man who knows
he will die in this world
if he doesn't escape
into the twilight zone.
...75, 80,
85, 90, 95, 100.
Here i come, ready or not.
Give that can!
Listen to them.
How can a man think?
They aren't supposed
to play on the grounds.
The children?
Are they hurting anyone?
Old people
need their rest.
Let them play
someplace else.
They got playgrounds.
They got homes.
Well, it's the grass, ben.
Kids can't resist going
where the grass is.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Your own son turns against you.
Well... the boy
has got a lot of problems.
It's a small house,
and the second baby
is on the way.
It was a foolish idea thinking
i could move
in on them.
They don't want
an old duffer like me underfoot.
No... this place is
good enough for me.
Listen to 'em.
It's enough
to wake the dead!
Oh, ben, they're
playing kick-the-can.
Don't you remember?
Oh, we used to play
it all the time.
Oh, we were running
and shouting...
and all that noise.
Well, you can't
stop kids
from playing
kick-the-can.
It's like statues and...
and hide-and-seek.
It's in their...
their blood.
It's a...
a special summer ritual.
Five, ten, 15,
20, 25, 30...
did you ever
stop to think of it?
All kids play those games.
And the minute they stop,
they begin to grow old.
It's almost as though playing
kick-the-can keeps them young.
You ever notice that?
Say, you don't believe
in magic, do you?
There... there was a time
that you did.
You know, we've known
each other ever since...
oh, i can't remember.
Ever since we were
a couple of towheaded kids.
And you believed
in magic then.
Me? Magic?
Yes, you did.
When we walked on different
sides of a street lamp
you'd say,
"bread and butter."
When your baby
teeth came out
you put them
under the pillow
for the tooth fairy.
Yeah, you believed
in magic.
What happened, ben?
What changed you?
Was it time that did it?
Or was it something else?
We grew up, that's all.
Everybody gets older.
Maybe there are...
people who stay young.
Maybe they know a secret
they keep from the rest of us.
Charles.
Maybe the fountain of youth
isn't a fountain at all.
Maybe it's a way
of looking at things...
a way of thinking.
Charles, stop it.
You're an old man,
you understand?
Your youth has been gone
for 60 years.
What i mean is, uh...
you've lived a full life,
charles.
Don't go sloppy now.
Don't spoil it
by acting like a nut.
But it's all so clear.
It makes sense.
Can't-can't you
see it, ben?
Oh, no, you were quite right
to come to me.
When he acts like that,
l-i feel i don't
know him at all.
Well, mr. Conroy,
when people grow old,
truly old,
they begin to act
a little peculiar.
Now mr. Agee, for instance.
Some way he got ahold
of a few firecrackers,
and i found them
trying to set one of them off.
Now he could've gotten hurt.
Every time
one of our people goes senile,
i get a little cold inside.
When i first
took this assignment, i was 32.
Now i'm 43.
Everyone grows older,
mr. Conroy, even me.
Nyeah!
Oh, what's wrong
with you people?!
Can't you show a little life?!
Are you the ones
who skipped rope?
And hunt for polliwogs?
Huh?
And run through sprinklers?
Run through sprinklers.
Hey!
What are you going to do?
Why, that's the
silliest thing
i've ever seen.
Oh! Oh!
Let him drown himself
if he wants to.
Come on in!
The water's fine!
Mr. Whitley!
Come on, get out of there.
Mr. Whitley,
what's the matter
with you?
Here, now you
get him inside.
Fresh clothing,
and get him to bed!
I was afraid something
like this would happen.
In the morning,
i'll have to put him
in a special ward
for observation.
We're going to isolate him
for a while.
That'll kill him.
Senile?
Me?
Put me in a
special ward?
Alone?
Show them
you're all right.
Cut the crazy talk.
Act like everyone else.
Oh, what a choice.
To keep an attendant
from pawing at
my pulse all day
i have to sit
like a... vegetable
on that porch.
I'm trying to help you.
Now, keep on like this
and they'll put you away.
Use your head.
Maybe you're right.
Come. Come.
What is it, fire?
Shh!
Hmm? Huh?
Wake the girls.
Call mrs. Summers
and mrs. Worcester.
It's important.
Huh?
Psst! Psst!
What are we
doing here?
I'll catch
my death.
We ought
to be in bed.
What would
mr. Cox say?
Well, he'd say
being awake
is dangerous
and silly.
He'd probably say
we're crazy.
Well, maybe
you got to be a little crazy
to make the magic work.
Remember how we used to do it?
We'd sneak out at night
when the weather was like this?
And we'd play kick-the-can.
Oh, everybody
played that game,
or hide-and-seek.
Yeah, seems like
a million years ago.
Say, you know something?
I was the fastest runner
on our block.
When we would play kick-the-can,
i was never "it."
Look how i've changed.
I remember.
We all get old.
It's the running
i miss most.
Me, too.
I think if i could
only run again
then growing old
wouldn't be so bad.
People getting on
need their rest.
Well, we can't
run fast or far
but... well, we can move
and there are trees and bushes.
Maybe if the hunted
are handicapped
so is the hunter.
Us?
Children's games?
Yes, that's the secret.
Don't you see?
The secret of youth.
Say, you know
i was the fastest runner
on our block?
You can't beserious.
He isn't serious.
You bet i am.
Look!
Think! Feel!
Here, hold it.
Doesn't that wake some
sleeping part of you?
Listen.
Can't you hear it?
Summer... grass...
run... jump... youth!
Wake up!
Oh, this is your last chance.
I can't play kick-the-can alone.
Charles.
What are you doing?
Aw, ben.
Come with us,
out on the lawn.
Me?
Yes, you, ben.
We've always done
everything together.
Let's not stop now.
Come. Come with us, ben.
Come play kick-the-can.
Charles.
Come to your senses.
Ben, you're afraid.
You're afraid
of a new idea.
to look silly.
You're afraid
to make a mistake.
You decided
that you were an old man
and that has made you old.
Iamold,
and so are you, charles,
that's a fact.
Fact.
Your bones are old,
and they'll break
if you try to run with them.
Your heart is old
and your lungs are old.
You're used up.
Worn out by a lifetime.
Sit down, charles.
You're tired.
Sit down.
I can't.
Charles.
I've got to find out, ben.
Help me.
There is magic in the world.
I know there is.
When i fell in love with mary,
kissed her for the first time,
that was magic.
When my boy was born,
Friendship is a magic thing.
Maybe i'm right, ben.
Maybe kick-the-can
is the greatest magic of all.
All right, ben,
i'll do it
without you.
Mr. Cox!
Mr. Cox! Mr. Cox?!
Mr. Cox! Mr. Cox!
What is it?
Hurry, stop them.
What are you
talking about?
They've all
gone outside.
Well, why?
To play
kick-the-can.
Now, calm down.
What'll he do when
nothing happens?
He really believes
he'll be young.
Charlie's it.
Hurry.
Now, where?
On the front lawn.
...20, 25,
30, 35,
4o, 45, 50...
55, 60,
65, 70,
75, 80,
85, 90...
where are the old people?
What are these kids
doing here?
I told them
not to play here.
Go on, kids!
You'll wake everybody up!
Ready or not, here i come!
Maybe whitley took them
around to the back.
One, two, three, you're out.
Charles.
Charlie, is that you?
Is that you,
charlie?
Charlie, it's me, benny.
Charlie...
take me with you.
Take me
with you.
Charlie,
wait for me.
Wait.
Last one into the forest
is a rotten apple!
No, charlie, no.
Wait for me.
Olly, olly oxen free.
Charlie... it's me.
Listen, i'll bet
whitley's taken them
all down
to the orchard.
Come on.
Look all you want, mr. Cox,
you won't find them.
Olly, olly oxen free.
Sunnyvale rest,
a dying place for ancient people
who have forgotten
the fragile magic of youth.
A dying place for those
who have forgotten
that childhood,
maturity and old age
are curiously intertwined
and not separate.
A dying place for those
who have grown too stiff
in their thinking
to visit the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week onthe twilight zone,
we roll in a musical instrument
purchased in this store.
Now there are pianos and pianos,
but this one was manufactured
in our own very strange,
unpredictable factory.
It comes to you via the
typewriter of mr. Earl hamner
and it boasts a collection
of oddities and oddball doings.
Next week,
you can roll up the rug
as we bring you
"a piano in the house."
Radio free europe needs
your help to fight communism.
Give now to radio free europe.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org