Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it
is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Okay, and thank you for calling.
Yeah.
We'll be watching.
That was
colonel connacher, honey.
He says daddy is just fine.
Will he... will he
be going up soon?
In just about
an hour.
That's what
colonel connacher said.
Do you want
to go back to sleep?
I don't blame you.
I can't sleep either.
I'll tell you what.
I'll make some
coffee for me
and some cocoa
for you.
And you wash your
face and hands
and comb your hair.
And then we'll turn on
the television set, okay?
Okay.
Be safe, bob.
Be safe, darling.
And come back.
In the vernacular of space
this is t minus one hour-
60 minutes before a human being
named major robert gaines
is lifted off from
the mother earth and rocketed
into the sky
farther and longer
than any man ahead of him.
Call this one of the first
faltering steps of man
to sever the umbilical cord
of gravity
and stretch out a fingertip
toward an unknown.
Shortly, we'll join
this astronaut named gaines
and embark on an adventure,
because the environs overhead-
the stars, the sky,
the infinite space-
are all part
of a vast question mark
known as the twilight zone.
Huh. Pulse normal?
Reasonable.
Someplace between
nonchalance and panic.
I know the feeling.
I called helen. She's fine.
Says to tell you
they'll be waiting.
Bless you for that.
Do you have any messages
for the angels?
Hmm... give them a kiss for me-
any that you meet.
On my last orbit, i'll lasso
a pair of gossamer wings
and ship them down
to you air express- collect.
Kind of an odd feeling,
knowing i'll be moving
around the earth for a week.
That's progress.
Gus grissom went 302 miles,
glenn made three orbits,
schirra handled six.
And you, bobby boy, are
going to go round and round.
And, when you come back down,
maybe we'll be that much closer
to filing a claim
on some more sky.
Good luck, buddy.
Thanks, bill.
Thanks a lot.
This is capcom.
Time is now at
t minus one minute
and counting.
Better hurry.
This is capcom.
The mx ten countdown
is now t minus
25 seconds.
T minus 20 seconds
19...
18...
17... 16...
15... 14...
13... 12...
11...
ten...
nine... eight...
seven... six...
five... four...
three... two... one...
zero.
Go ahead, ten.
We read you loud and clear.
Zero g, and i feel fine.
Spacecraft is beginning
to turn now.
Roger.
Turnaround has started.
Spacecraft is almost over.
I can see the booster just
a couple of yards behind me.
It's quite a sight.
Roger, ten. We still
read you loud and clear.
Next transmission, bermuda.
Roger. Understand
next transmission, bermuda.
Phebus ten, bermuda.
Capcom tech on hm.
Phebus ten,
this is zanzibar captech.
We have solid
telemetry contact.
Phebus ten.
Capcom calling phebus ten.
We now have i.o.s., over.
Phebus ten, your
voice transmissions
are starting to
fade very badly.
Capcom, capcom,
this is phebus ten.
I've lost contact with you.
I've lost radar here!
I've lost radar!
We don't have
contact here, either.
No contact at all.
Capcom tech calling phebus ten.
Capcom, capcom,
this is phebus ten.
Open the blinds,
nurse.
Yes, doctor.
Well, how
about it, gaines?
Can you talk?
Sure.
Sure, i can talk.
Hey, billy.
What happened?
Well, we were waiting
for you to wake up
to tell us, bob.
Tell you?
I can't tell you anything,
i blacked out.
We lost you
on radar
and radio.
Absolutely
no contact.
It boils down
to this, gaines-
you're the only one
who can explain it.
I can't explain anything.
I had an odd sensation.
Last thing i remember
is the 15th orbit.
After that,
i don't remember anything
except this bed.
I couldn't reach
the cape at all.
I kept trying.
Why don't you let him
get some sleep?
I think he'll feel
a little clearer later on.
I won't be any clearer
than i am right now.
How could you lose me on radar?
Bill, do you mean to tell me
every single tracking
station blacked out?
Really, gentlemen, i...
just one last
question, please.
Bob, there's
only one way
you could head
back toward earth.
That's just to spiral in,
and then head for water.
Your spacecraft
was found, intact,
46 miles from where
you were launched.
Intact, bob,
on the ground.
There was no evidence
of any damage,
not even a dent.
Somehow, some way, you
brought that spacecraft in,
and you landed her.
Tell me how.
Would you please explain to me
how you performed
an absolutely impossible act?
I didn't.
I had nothing
to do with it.
I blacked out, general.
I simply blacked out.
There was some
factor up there,
something which i had
no control over,
something which must have...
must have taken over for me.
Hmm. Okay, uh...
we'll talk
about it later.
This whole thing is
temporarily classified-
i mean everything about it.
We'll simply make
the statement
that he regained
entry and he landed.
He's shaken up but
not seriously hurt.
And that's the feed.
No extensions,
no enlargements
beyond that
simple statement.
After we've been
able to probe this
thing a little while,
we might be able
to come up with
something we can let go.
But, in the meantime,
it's a one-line release.
"He got
back down." unquote.
You get some
rest, bob.
Talk to
you later.
Yeah, you, uh...
sleep it off.
There's an explanation
for everything.
Well, don't worry about it now.
You're, uh, all doped up,
and you're also dead tired.
You sleep it off,
and i'll see
what i can do
about getting you a
leave to get on home.
So rest easy, pal.
Bill?
All along, i thought
there was some kind
of malfunction up there-
fuel or propulsion
or just communication.
Maybe the malfunction
was closer to home.
Maybe it was
right up here
between my ears.
Maybe astronaut robert gaines
went off the tracks.
Maybe he couldn't
cut the mustard.
Look, you talk like that-
you think like that-
and you'll come around
to believing it.
And that's stupid, bob.
We're dealing with
nine natural laws
plus a whole string
of imponderables.
And reasons are going
to come out-
legitimate, rational reasons.
Now, you just lie there
and breathe through your nose.
I'll call
helen again
and tell her
you're resting
and you'll
be home soon.
Will i? Will i be home?
Yeah. Unless you persuade
all the people around here
that you need an attendant.
Dream good.
I'll see you later.
Well?
Oh, it'll all come
out in the wash.
Will it?
Let me tell you
something, colonel...
a man is sent up into space,
and then he orbits.
There are only three ways
he can break off contact.
One is ionization,
and that didn't occur.
The other is sunspots,
The third is the man's death,
and he's lying there
on that bed
breathing five by five.
All right, i'm waiting
for a fresh alternative,
one i can take
without flinching.
One maybe i can repeat
to the president
without worrying about him
sticking me in a rubber room.
What happened to gaines?
Where was he
for six solid hours
when nobody in the world
could find him?
How did he make a reentry
without burning up into a flake?
Sometime we'll
have to ask him.
Give her my love.
Thanks for services rendered.
I'll talk to you later.
No question about it.
Home, james.
Welcome home.
What's the matter, bob?
Is that what you
did for therapy
while i was gone-
put up that fence?
What do you mean?
That fence wasn't there
when i left last week.
Are you kidding me?
That fence was there
when we bought the house.
Outer space does things
to memories, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, so it appears.
America's latest manned
orbital spaceflight
ends on a note of mystery today.
With a cloak of secrecy being
placed over the entire project.
Millions were watching
the orbital flight
on television when, suddenly,
the pictures were interrupted
with a terse announcement
that no further coverage
would be forthcoming.
General stanley eaton
announced late this afternoon
that further information
would be forthcoming
at a later date
but that, for the moment,
all aspects
of astronaut gaines' flight
would continue
to be top secret
pending further
investigation of data.
You got any more
coffee out there?
I'm making some.
It'll be better in a minute.
I'm going upstairs
and put on a bathrobe.
I'll be right back.
Do you want maggie
to go get it for you?
Both you and maggie
have been treating me
like a cross between
an eccentric millionaire
and a piece
of fragile dresden.
I'll get my own
bathrobe, woman.
Be right back.
That's funny.
Some chicken colonel
back at the base
is going to be running
home in his undershirt.
Bob, your
coffee's ready.
You want us to
bring you up a cup?
No, honey. I'll be right down.
Want to hear something funny?
I ran off
with somebody's shirt-
a full colonel's, no less.
Bob?
What?
Are you all right?
Helen...
without trying
to scare you,
and without trying
to make you wonder
whether i've still
got all my marbles,
i'd like to ask
you a question.
What is it?
When i left-
when i walked out of here-
what was my rank?
Your rank?
What was my rank?
What do you mean?
Wasn't i a major?
Haven't i been
a major for 13 months?
Are you serious?
No, i'm playing games with you.
Helen, i want you to tell me.
You're a colonel, bob.
You're a
full colonel.
You've been a
colonel since
last march.
Last march?
Last march.
I want to say
something to you now.
I, um...
i don't know what
happened up there.
I have no idea.
But, uh...
i know you
don't want
to talk
about it-
that's why we haven't
said anything- but, uh...
something must
have happened, bob.
Some delusions.
Some distortions.
Like that fence
outside the house.
I don't remember it.
And yet you said
it had been there
when we bought
the house.
And that business
with bill connacher.
He told me he called you
before the flight.
He made it
a point to tell me.
And then, afterward...
afterward, he said
there'd been no such
phone conversation.
It's unimportant.
It's insignificant, really.
And yet...
and yet it all
seems to be part
of some sort
of crazy pattern.
Something is very wrong,
because he did
tell me he called.
That fence wasn't there,
and those eagles have never been
on my collar before
because, when i left
here, i was a major.
You, um...
you told me once
that there are whole
areas of space medicine
that we know
practically
nothing about.
Phenomena and
reaction patterns
that can only
be guessed at.
I'm sure this
is one of them.
I'm sure there's nothing
wrong with you but a...
couple of fixations
that are going
to go away with time.
Now...
let's go downstairs
and have a cup
of coffee.
And don't let
a white fence
and a promotion end
the world for you.
If that's as far as it goes,
i'll try not to.
But what if...
what if other things...?
Um...
i'd like colonel
william connacher, please.
I was, uh...
i was just, uh...
going to call
bill connacher
to ask him
if he'd like to...
like to what?
Come over for dinner.
Bob, i, uh...
i just called bill
to have him give me
some reassurance.
I remember that...
that he said once
that there are some aspects
to prolonged weightlessness
that makes...
look, really, like i
said, i'm all right.
It's you people
i'm worried about.
Now, where's
my coffee?
I'll get it for you.
Don't break any more
saucers, mother's helper.
I'll try not to.
Helen?
Helen, i think it'd
be a whole lot better-
a whole lot better- if we
dropped all the pretenses.
If you think there's something
wrong with me, just say so.
And honey,
i'd consider it
a real favor-
a major favor- if you wouldn't
walk past me on tiptoe
with forced smiles
and "there's nothing
wrong with you" dialogue.
All right?
All right.
Ahh!
I helped mommy
make the pie.
You know, someday, i'm going
to lose you to a navy ensign
who'll marry you
for your father's money
and your cooking.
Now, honey, you know
i don't take sugar.
Maggie...
honey, what's
the matter?
Nothing.
Nothing's
the matter.
Maggie, here.
Tell daddy
what's the matter.
Daddy...
daddy, you're different.
Well, how, honey?
How am i different?
I don't know.
I don't know, but you are.
Youaredifferent.
You're very different. There...
there's something
wrong.
Maggie!
What does
she mean?
I don't know.
What does
she mean?
What does she mean,
i'm different?
Well, am i?
Am i, helen?
Have i changed
somehow
between now
and when i left?
I can't...
i can't
explain it to you.
I don't know how.
I have changed,
haven't i?
There is something
different about me.
The child sensed it.
You have, too.
You have,
haven't you?
Yes, i have.
How?
I...
i don't know. I...
i just don't
know. It's...
it's just that you're...
you're not the same somehow.
You didn't have to
call bill connacher.
That wasn't necessary.
Tomorrow i'll turn myself in
for psychiatric help.
I don't know what it is
that happened.
Something did.
Something is
tearing us all apart.
Something so remote, we can't
even put it into words.
Something...
something, until we
find out what it is,
it's going
to wreck us, helen.
Ivan, there was nothing
he could tell you
that occurred in space
that could give us some key
or something to all this?
Nothing that he
could relate to me.
I wouldn't recommend that
he remain here, however.
For the time being,
i'd like to treat him
as an outpatient.
Have him come in
at intervals,
but in no way suggest
to him that he's in
an aberrant condition requiring
psychological treatment.
This is one
of those instances
where the psychology
of the situation
requires
very careful handling.
We're right back
where we started, then.
Uh... mrs. Gaines, i don't
mean to sound callous.
He's an exceptional gentleman,
that husband of yours.
I think he'll be out
of the woods in no time.
My concern happens to be,
very specifically,
a space project, not a man.
I understand, sir.
Mrs. Gaines,
what about that fence?
It was there when
we bought the house.
And when did he seem
surprised that it was there?
The moment that he came
home yesterday morning.
Really a very strange
collection of delusions.
A white picket fence...
a story...
his own rank...
and the last thing he said
was he doubted very much
if president kennedy
would pin any medals on him.
President who?
Kennedy.
Someone named john kennedy.
Who's john kennedy?
Someone who
colonel gaines has decided
is president of
the united states.
And i share your bewilderment.
I never heard of him either.
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
It isn't easy to say.
Well...
if it isn't
easy to say,
then it's
better said,
so get it out.
Maggie's
noticed it, too.
Noticed what?
That there's something...
there's something
differentabout him.
It's something i can't
put my finger on, but...
there's some...
there's something different.
Suggesting what?
Suggesting nothing.
Something or everything.
What can it suggest?
Simply that there's
a man in my house who...
a man in your house who what?
The question is, a man
in my house whoiswhat?
Better, a man in
my house who is who?
I think you just overshot me,
unless i'm reading
you very wrong.
No, maybe you're
reading me very right.
Reassure me, bill.
Tell me that,
uh... this thing
my daughter and i
have this ice-cold
feeling about is way off.
Tell us that we're
just being carried away
by his problem.
Tell us...
tell us...
tell us that the
man in this house
is bob gaines.
Hello, bill.
How are you?
Fine.
I just dropped over
to see how you were.
Me?
Well, that depends.
Depends on just what are the
current standards for sanity-
the acceptable outer limits.
I've been going over a set
of encyclopedias up there,
and jotting down some notes.
I've uncovered some
very revealing items.
There are some pretty
basic historical facts
that simply don't jibe.
For example,
it talks about
a man named anderson
who was sent
by the united states government
to supervise the construction
of the panama canal.
So?
So, i never heard
of anyone
named anderson.
It happened
to be a man
named goethals.
It also talks about an american
ace named eddie rickenbacker
from world war i
who was lost on a raft
in the next war and never found.
That's right.
He crashed, and that
was the end of it.
But that wasn't the end of it.
The raft was found.
Rickenbacker was saved.
He became the president
of an airlines company.
I've got dozens of items
like that.
Men talked about
who never existed.
Men who existed
and not even mentioned.
Historical events that i know
happened a certain way
somehow, according to
the encyclopedia,
didn't happen,
or happened another way.
The things i remember
are not delusions.
They're the legitimate
recollections of things
as i remember them.
But somehow, some way,
this world seems to have
turned upside down for me.
Well, not in
every way, you understand.
Uh... by and large,
the people are the same.
The names,
the streets,
the mutual recollections
we all have
of people and events.
It's as if there were...
there were another world
parallel to mine.
As if this world
were almost a twin,
except for
some minor differences
that happened somewhere
along the line of evolution.
Bob, for the
love of heaven...
do you want to follow
that line of reasoning?
Because, if you do,
there are a couple
of built-in conditions
that go along with it.
Conditions that
i don't think you
or anyone else
wants to admit.
First and foremost,
they happen to
be that if all
this is true-
if you suddenly uncovered
a theory
that there are two earths,
two sets of people,
two histories-
and you somehow, inexplicably,
crossed over to
the other dimension-
then you're not
who we think you are.
And we're not
who you think we are.
Maggie?
Bob!
Let's get it out,
shall we?
I'm so sick of
tiptoeing and whispers.
Maggie!
Come down here, baby.
Come down right away.
Honey...
think this over
before you answer...
but answer.
Who am i, honey?
Tell mommy and colonel
connacher who i am.
Bob, please.
No.
Now, sweetheart...
you say whatever's on your mind.
Tell them who i am.
I don't know who you are.
Maggie, this
is your daddy.
This is
your daddy.
He's not my daddy.
I don't know who he is.
Oh, that wasn't fair.
You've taken a little
child, impressionable-
you've superimposed
on her your own doubts.
I've done nothing
of the sort.
I merely let her
say out loud
what helen's been
thinking all along.
And, heaven help me,
what i've been thinking.
What you've just
told me is fantastic.
How can you possibly...?
It's incredible.
Incredible.
I helped build that spacecraft.
I know it very well.
And this one
is not the same one
we sent off.
It's almost
a twin to it,
down to the very
last nut and bolt,
but it's simply not
the same spacecraft.
It's a different vehicle.
It's almost as if it came
out of the same mold,
but every now and then-
in the wiring,
in the control panel
and in the structure-
there's a tiny
insignificant alteration.
You add them all up
and you come up with one
very irrevocable fact:
Colonel gaines went up
in one spacecraft,
but he's obviously
come back in another.
That leaves us
with two alternatives.
Colonel gaines
actually blacked out
and has no knowledge
of what occurred.
Or two:
Colonel gaines is not
who we think he is.
Colonel...
i want you to examine
this vehicle carefully.
I want you to be
able to say to me,
without a single
shred of doubt,
that this is the spacecraft
you were sent up in,
and the spacecraft
you came down in.
This is of the essence now.
Phebus ten, bermuda.
Capcom tech m.h.m.
You understand me?
What?
What's the matter with you?
Bob, what the general
is trying to get at
is that there are
delusions that a man
can suffer under stress.
Now, all we want to do now is
try to retrace the chronology
from the blastoff
through the orbits.
And we want you
to check over
this capsule.
I am talking about
a microscopic check, now, bob.
We want to make
absolutely certain
that we can separate
what is delusion
from what might
conceivably be
an incredible
series of events.
The weather in the recovery are
is excellent.
Bob, what's the matter with you?
Three-foot waves,
only one-tenth cloud coverage,
ten miles visibility.
Don't you hear that voice?
Phebus ten, phebus ten...
capcom tech, do you read me?
Don't you hear that voice?
What are you talking about?
What voice are
you talking about?
Leave the retro package on
through the entire reentry.
Gaines will have to override...
that voice.
...to 0.05...
that voice!
Retract the scope.
Do you read?
Don't you hear
that voice?
Recommend you go
to reentry attitude and...
we'll give you the countdown
on retro-sequence time, bob.
You're looking good.
We have only 50 seconds
to retrograde. Over.
I'll give you a mark.
45...
mark.
I am on 8scs now,
and backing it up manually.
30 seconds, bob.
Capcom, this is phebus ten.
The retro warning is on.
Roger, bob.
Leave your retro pack on
through your pass over texas.
Do you read?
Roger.
Five... four... three...
two... one... fire.
Retros are firing.
I'm starting my reentry now.
I'm going to fly by wire.
I'm down to 15% on manual.
Capcom, this is phebus ten.
It's a real fireball out there.
How are you doing?
What's your general condition?
How are you feeling?
I'm feeling... i'm feeling fine.
Condition is good.
There's an awful lot
of fire out there.
Capcom...
one last question:
Go ahead, bob. Go ahead.
Who's the president
of the united states?
Say again, would you, bob?
We don't think we
got that. Say again.
Who is the president
of the united states?
It sounds like you're
asking who the president is.
That's precisely the question.
I hope you said kennedy.
Open the blinds, nurse.
Yes, doctor.
Our wandering boy is awake.
Bill.
Right here, buddy.
How you feeling, gaines?
That depends.
Did you hear that last
question i asked up there?
Just before reentry?
You asked who
the president is.
Was that some
sort of a gag?
I didn't hear the answer.
It was no gag.
President kennedy.
You were only gone
two days, major,
not two years.
What happened on that
second morning, gaines,
about your 15th orbit?
We lost all contact
with you for a period
of almost six hours.
No radar, no contact at all.
We couldn't find out
what was wrong here.
And we asked you that question
several times
after we picked
you up again,
but you ignored it.
Six hours?
That's how long it took.
Then you came back in
loud and clear.
I think later, sir.
Right now, i think
he should rest.
Bill...
something...
something
happened.
I know you're not
going to believe this.
I'm not absolutely certain
that i believe it myself.
There's another dimension.
I don't know how it exists
or where it exists.
But there's another world,
parallel to ours-
the same people,
the same places,
most of the same
chronology of events.
Except, now and then,
there's something
a little bit
different.
How do you know
all this?
Because i was there, general.
I was there for almost a week.
That's impossible.
We only lost you
for about six hours.
We had contact with you
all the rest of the time.
I can't help that, sir.
During that six hours,
i lived out a week.
Doing what?
Looking at our counterparts.
Looking at us.
Us?
Us, as we exist
in a parallel world.
One that exists alongside,
but which we can't see.
The world i stumbled into.
I don't know how.
Some kind of
space-time continuum,
some warpage.
There's a doorway
up there somewhere into it.
It exists.
Every now and then,
i think it's possible
for somebody to fall through it,
and i did.
How did you get back, bob?
I don't
even know that.
All i can remember is running
toward the spacecraft.
Then... i was up there again...
and then i was back here.
Well...
bob, i think, uh...
sleep on this for a
little while, will you?
Why?
Because...
i think, uh... this may
just be a delusion.
Delusion?
Bill, i can recount
to you every minute
and everything that happened.
Every line of dialogue,
every person that i met.
I could recall to you
the streets,
the places, everything.
This was no delusion.
It was no dream.
I have no proof.
I've told you that.
Mm-hmm.
Well, um,
okay, major...
we'll talk
about it later.
Did anybody
phone helen?
She, uh... asked what
you wanted for supper.
Will i be
able to leave?
At least for an overnight.
Mm-hmm.
I want you back first thing in
the morning for some critique.
I want to have a look
at those psychiatrists' faces
when you start talking to them
about parallel dimensions.
Meanwhile,
get some rest, major.
One last question.
Be my guest.
If we each have a counterpart,
and you saw them,
where was yours, bob?
I don't know,
but he was a colonel.
A full colonel.
I hope he got back,
'cause he has
a very beautiful wife
and a very lovely
little daughter.
I hope he got back.
What do you think?
Uh-uh.
I don't think.
Not on this one, sir.
What kind of trauma...?
Something to set him
tilt like that? I...
can we call
it "tilt," sir?
Oh, what else?
Another dimension?
Another world
parallel to ours?
Call that rational?
Up there, who knows
what's rational
and what isn't?
We don't even
know the rules, sir,
let alone the facts.
We're...
we're like little ants
that have just
made it to the desert.
Now we say we've
conquered the sahara
and we haven't
conquered anything.
We're only starting to find
the mysteries, general.
We haven't even
begun to solve them.
We're going to do
a lot of groping
through a lot of dark nights,
through a lot of dark space,
before we find the clues,
let alone the answers.
We've got a long
way to go, sir.
Okay.
General?
There's a message
from capcom, sir.
I'll give it to you
as we got it.
It doesn't make
much sense.
Let me be the judge of that.
What's the message?
Capcom reports telemetry
with an
unidentified space vehicle.
What?
Yes, sir.
They had voice communication
for about a minute and a half.
The spacecraft identified
itself asastro seven,
and the person
in it said-
what'd he say?
What'd he say?
He identified himself
as a colonel robert gaines.
He asked for
reentry data.
Colonelrobert gaines?
Yes, sir.
Then we got some garbled stuff,
and then nothing.
And then what?
And then nothing, sir.
We lost the visual sighting.
We lost all voice.
The thing just disappeared.
Get a transcript
of everything
that was said.
Have it brought
to my office.
And keep trying
to raise, uh...
whoever it was.
Yes, sir.
We're still trying.
Good. Uh... you
keep me in touch.
Yes, sir.
Well, bill...
you certainly were right
when you said we
haven't even begun.
We don't have
all the answers.
We've got
a long way to go.
What's on your mind?
One thing. I'd
like to tell
astronaut gaines
that his proof
just showed up
on a radar screen,
however briefly.
Yeah. Be my guest.
Do me a favor,
would you, honey?
Tell me who i am.
What, daddy?
Thank you, honey.
That's all
i need to know.
Welcome home.
It's good
to be home.
Major robert gaines,
a latter-day voyager just
returned from an adventure.
Submitted to you
without any recommendations
as to belief or disbelief.
You can accept or reject.
You pays your money,
and you takes your choice.
But credulous or incredulous,
don't bother to ask anyone
for proof that it could happen.
The obligation's
a reverse challenge-
prove that itcouldn't.
This happens
to be the twilight zone.
A new author joins the ranks
of thetwilight zonecrew
when john furia jr. Gives us
several stunningly new twists
to a classic character
in "i dream of genie."
Join howard morris,
patrica barry and loring smith
as they take their trip
into the twilight zone.
Who...
who... who...?
Who were
you expecting?
Who...?
I'm a genie in a lamp.
That's who.
Aladdin, magic,
the whole bit.
If... if you
are the genie,
then i must be the
master of the lamp.
Big deal. Master of the lamp.
All right, you got yourself
a free wish.
I can't believe it.
Anything i want
in the whole world.
Anything.
But only one wish.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org