Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
How long is this
going to take?
Like i told you, nobody
stocks fuel pumps around town.
I'll have to send
into dayton for it.
How long will that take?
Oh, three, four hours.
Better figure
on four, to play safe.
Four hours?
Crazy.
Let's get
some lunch.
Lunch? We can homestead.
June, croon, honeymoon.
Quiet.
Don't think i should phone
the office again, huh?
You are going
to lose that promotion
if you keep
pestering them, lover.
I'm going to
lose it anyway.
Ah, that's
a fine way to talk.
And i thought i married
a man with confidence.
And who is
the best man for the job?
Me, but...
but?
But thompson
has seniority.
Aw! Doesn't mean a thing.
Little miss sunshine.
That's me.
Bread and butter.
Yes, dear.
Just trying
to save your life.
Shall we?
Let's have
some music, don.
Great.
I thought we came
in here to eat.
Yes, we did.
Shall we sit here?
Well, what have
we got here?
"The mystic seer."
The what?
Let's try it, shall we?
Have you got
a penny, honey?
I think so.
What'll we ask it?
I don't know.
I got it.
What?
Does anything exciting
ever happen around here?
"It is quite possible."
The hand belongs
to mr. Don s. Carter,
male member
of a honeymoon team
en route across the ohio
countryside to new york city.
In one moment,
they will be subjected
to a gift most humans
never receive in a lifetime.
For one penny, they'll be able
to look into the future.
The time is now, the place is a
little diner in ridgeview, ohio,
and what this young couple
doesn't realize
is that this town happens to lie
on the outskirts
of the twilight zone.
Howdy.
Hello.
What'll it be?
I think i'll have a tomato
and lettuce on whole wheat
and some
iced coffee, please.
I'll have the same.
I've got
some very good
chicken-fried
steak out there.
No, thank you.
No?
No.
You finished
with that?
Yes.
Oh!
Good, hmm?
Great. He must have
siphoned it out of a swamp.
What are you doing?
Getting some pennies.
What are you going
to ask it now?
What else?
Am i going to be promoted, for pete's sake.
Hey, look.
What?
"It has been decided
in your favor."
Ah! You see,
your worries are over.
I think i'll phone.
Honey...
well, i was
going to anyway.
Wasn't i?
Hello,
operator?
Give me
main 1-8-9-9-7
in saint louis,
please.
That's
right.
How much?
75 cents?
Honey, you got another quarter on you?
Is this call necessary?
Here you are, operator.
Hello.
Connect me with mr.
Welden's secretary, please.
Keep your
fingers crossed.
I'm doing it up here.
Hello.
Hello, pauline?
It's don.
Fine. Fine. And you?
What's the secret word, pauline?
I did?
I made it.
Oh...
thank you, pauline.
Yes, we'll send you a
postcard from new york.
As soon as we arrive.
Good-bye,
and same to you.
Good-bye.
I made it.
Oh, darling,
i'm so proud of you.
You're now looking
at the world's youngest
office manager.
And i'm happy to say
i told you so.
And so has he.
Yeah? Well,
i told you first.
I think we ought
to celebrate.
Here's a dime
for the jukebox.
Some success music.
Or "the triumphal march."
Don't know that
i can find it here.
Crazy.
Oh.
Thank you.
You ain't going
to like this
as much as you would
that chicken-fried steak.
We'll bear up.
Ah...
office manager.
I think it's wonderful.
Let's ask him
something else.
He really came
through on that one.
Why don't you ask him
why he didn't warn us
that the whole-wheat
bread is stale?
"Does he/she
love me?"
I know the answer
to that one, huh?
"Will i become rich?"
I know the answer
to that one, too.
I'm going to be the world's
first millionaire accountant.
Office manager.
Right.
Is it really going
to be four hours
before we get
out of here?
"You may never know."
What does that mean?
Who knows?
He does.
Mm-hmm...
but it'll cost you
another penny.
I'm an office
manager now.
What do you mean,
"we may never know"?
No, that's not a "yes"
or "no" question.
You mean something will
keep us from knowing?
Something will
happen to us?
"If you move soon."
What does that mean?
Well, he's a mystic.
What do you expect?
Oh, i can see
i'm going to have to be
the frugal one
in our family.
Just one more.
You mean, if we're
not supposed to move,
we're supposed
to stay here?
Just one question
per penny, please.
"That makes a good
deal of sense."
How long should...
no, uh...
should we stay here
until 2:30?
"Try again."
Should we stay
in here until 3:00?
"There's no question
about it."
Don, let's take a look
around the town, hmm?
Every answer seems to fit.
You're joking,
aren't you?
I mean...
don, no more.
If we don't stay
in here until 3:00,
something bad
will happen to us?
Oh, don,
for heaven's sakes.
Read it.
"Do you dare risk
finding out?"
Don, let's go.
Well, i haven't finished
my sandwich yet.
Don't you want
some ice cream?
Can we go now?
Don't you want
something cold to drink?
Please, let's go.
All right.
Say, can
i have my check?
You don't need a check.
I know what you had.
80 cents,
$1.10,
$1.60,
with three cents tax.
Here. Keep the change.
Well, thanks.
And come
on back, now.
Hot, hot, hot.
Yeah.
Maybe it won't take
them four hours
to fix the car.
You think?
Maybe.
Don, you didn't
really want
to stay in there,
did you?
No.
Honest?
Well, why was
it so specific?
Specific?
Sweetie...
"if you move soon."
"That makes a
good deal of sense."
"Try again."
"There's no question about it."
"You may never know."
"Do you dare risk finding out?"
Don, it's just
a napkin holder
in a little cafe
in ridgeview, ohio.
Oh, i know,
i know.
All right, what about
my promotion, then?
Didn't it tell me, "it has
been decided in your favor"?
Isn't
that...?
Oh, forget it.
I suppose i'm just being stupid.
No, you're not.
You're just...
don't say it.
Superstitious.
It's like you married
an alcoholic, isn't it?
Only, instead of bottles
in the chandelier,
it's rabbits' feet
and four-leaf
clovers
in my pockets,
in the car...
and...
and you're all mine.
Whatareyou doing?
What?
Well, you keep
looking around as if...
do i?
Youareworried.
You're worried
about that...
oh, don, i wonder
when you act like this.
I'm sorry. I'm not trying
to upset you.
I know you're not.
Doesn't change
the facts, though.
What facts?
Six straight answers.
Oh, don, please!
Oh, stop treating me like
a retarded child or something.
I didn't make
those answers up.
Wait, don.
Wait.
We can
make it.
You all right?
Quite a moment.
If you hadn't pulled me
out of the way
of that car,
one squashed honeymooner.
Come on.
Well, where
are we going now?
Oh, we're not going
back to that...
why not?
All right, i admit it was
a strange coincidence.
If it was a coincidence,
what are you worrying
about us going back, then?
I'm not.
So stop worrying.
Just the same,
you will admit that,
for a coincidence, it
was pretty far-fetched.
Maybe.
Well, someone's
sitting in front
of our mystic seer.
Don?
Why don't you
try this one,
or one of the others?
I'm sure that...
don?
What?
Look at me.
Well, you... you really
don't think that that...
that gizmo can
foretell the future, do you?
It foretold ours.
How? How did it?
Well, back already.
What will you have?
Honey?
Oh, i'll have some iced coffee, please.
And how about you?
The same.
Um... all right, how?
When that car almost hit us, it was 3:00-
exactly when
that machine said.
Don, yousaid 3:00,
not the machine.
Youdecided
to sit in here
as long as we did. You.
Oh, this is ridiculous.
Can't you see that
youmade up all the details,
and all that that...
that thing did
was give back
generalities?
What are you getting
so upset about?
You. That you could
even consider the possibility...
will... will
you listen...?
Will you listen?
Excuse me.
Yes?
Can you give
me some pennies?
Oh, sure. How many?
Ten.
Thank you.
Come on.
Yes, sir.
Did you know
about the car
almost
hitting us?
"What do you think?"
Will we reach new york
all right now?
"Your chances are good."
Very precise.
Honey, what
do you expect?
A slip should
come out and say
"hiya, donsy and patsy,
so how's by you?"
Excuse me.
I never said these slips
were made
for us personally...
i heard!
Don...
don't you realize that...
you could get
the same kind of answers
from any one
of these machines in here?
Try and see.
The same kind, maybe,
but not the same answers.
Will it still
take four hours
before the car is ready?
Hey...
"it has already
been taken care of."
Swell.
Let's go, then.
Mister...
your car's ready.
Got a lucky
break.
Found a fuel pump
right here in town.
Last one
they had, too.
Figured you'd
be walking around
a couple of hours
before you finally
came to the garage,
so i come looking for you.
Thank you.
We appreciate it.
We'll be right over.
Okey-doke.
Coincidence?
Yes.
All right, then you
ask it some questions.
Or are you
afraid to?
All right.
Will we reach columbus
by tomorrow?
We're not going
through col...
"if that's what
you really want."
Will i ever be married?
"The answer to
that is obvious."
It's not possible
to foretell the future, is it?
"That's up to you to find out."
You're just a stupid
piece of junk, aren't you?
"It all depends
upon your point of view."
I don't want to stay
here anymore, don.
Even if it's true?
Especially
if it's true.
What are you
talking about?
I think youare
afraid of it.
Not of it.
Of what, then?
Don't you know?
Are we always
going to live
in saint louis?
Are we going to live
in the east?
Are we going to
live in the west?
Are we going
to live
in this
country?
Don...
don!
What?
Let's go.
No.
Are you just going
to stay here?
I don't know!
Oh, sweetheart,
listen to me.
Please, if you love me,
just listen to me.
No, you listen to me.
This machine is
predicting our future.
Do you think i could
just walk away from it?
I'm not talking about
that machine anymore.
I'm talking about you.
Are you just
going to sit here
and let that... that...
that thing
run your life?
Run my life?
Isn't that exactly what
you're letting it do?
Don, it made you call
the office before.
It made you stay here
instead of leave.
It made you afraid
to walk down the street.
And now it's telling you
where you're
going to live.
Why, it's as if every
superstitious feeling you ever had
is wrapped up
in that one machine.
It doesn't matter
whether it can
foretell the future.
What matters is whether
you believe more in luck
and in fortune than
you do in yourself.
Well, you can decide
your own life.
You have a mind-
a wonderful mind.
Don't destroy it
trying to justify
that cheap, penny fortune
machine to yourself.
Pat...
we can have a... a
wonderful life together
if we make it
wonderful ourselves.
I...
pat...
i don't want to know
what's going to happen.
I want us to make
it happen together.
Don't cry, darling,
don't cry.
Is there something wrong?
No, no, no,
it's all right.
Don't cry.
We'll go, we'll go.
You're right. I'm a jerk.
No, you're not.
You're wonderful.
Yes, yes, i am.
I'm the world's
biggest jerk.
Come on, let's go
get our car.
Yes, that's right.
Let's go get
our car and...
we'll drive
out of this town
and go where we want to go
anytime we please.
Oh...
oh, don, i love you.
I love you, too, baby.
You keep
the change.
Thanks!
Come on
back, now.
Go ahead.
Can we ask some
more questions now?
Do you think we might
leave ridgeview today?
Is there any way out?
Any way at all?
Counterbalance in the
little town of ridgeview, ohio.
Two people permanently enslaved
by the tyranny
of fear and superstition,
facing the future
with a kind of helpless dread.
Two others facing the future
with confidence
having escaped
one of the darker places
of the twilight zone.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
be sure and see
the colgate-palmolive company's
new comedy show
my sister eileen.
Wednesday night on many
of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org