Previously on "Pan Am"...
Let's keep it in New York,
Ginny. Monte Carlo was a lark.
She does have a way
about her.
I love her.
I've fallen in love.
What if I could tell you
something about someone
you're very close to?
Don't pose.
I don't suppose I could...
make it up to you?
Could make you a list.
I'll get you a pen.
My mind is full of you.
Are you in danger?
Tito has put an entire nation
in danger.
You want me to spy for you?
For us.
Welcome to the big leagues.
I think I'm in love.
And you, beaute?
Yes. They're beautiful.
They're so...
I was going for heavenly.
A "female as
the visible manifestation
of the deity's presence
on Earth "kind of thing".
Graham, these portraits
are remarkable.
And you're an artist.
A true artist.
You've been holding out
on me.
Excuse me?
You never mentioned
you had an interest.
In photographers?
I mean... in photography?
I'm just a beginner. I...
Me and my instamatic.
But these... these are...
Inspiring.
I thought shooting girls
serving appetizers on a plane
was your specialty.
Well, appetizers
are in back.
Well, now I see the problem...
Laura was wearing
far too many clothes.
- Maggie!
- I suffered through it.
Well, it's a great show, Graham.
Thanks for inviting us.
Thanks for coming.
Laura, um,
can you take a cab home?
Yes, sure.
The girls that do this...
Who are they?
Friends, models,
and, uh, they're not girls.
They're... women.
Right.
They're not embarrassed?
No, they're liberated.
But you can't see
their faces.
Anonymous can be liberating.
For them, it's an experience
of self-expression.
I never thought I'd wish
I wasn't going to Rome.
This is all your fault.
Rome? Not so special.
Pantheon? Colosseum? Vatican?
That's no big deal?
Well, you haven't seen
my country.
Croatia is better
than all of Europe combined.
I'm really sad for them.
You know? I-I pity their shame.
I think you're jealous.
Of Italy? Ha!
Or maybe you're just full of
nationalistic pride like us yanks.
Well, yes and no.
Niko, I've been afraid to ask,
but I've wanted to...
Have you ever thought about
the desirability of living here?
You're trying to tempt me?
No.
Yes.
We have freedom here, and...
We have decency.
Decency?
Desirability?
Sounds like you're
describing yourself.
If you're going to Rome,
you should practice
your Italian.
I'll test you.
Translate this...
"La Croazia e molto piu bella
di Italia"...
"Croatia is much more beautiful
than Italy..."
"E tu sei piu bella..."
"And you are
more beautiful..."
"Di qualsiasi altra Donna
in qualsiasi posto."
"Than any woman anywhere."
I don't believe this.
This... what you're doing...
It makes no sense!
Ginny, calm down.
That's rich!
You break up with me,
and when I react with
understandable astonishment,
you tell me to "calm down"?
I thought we'd... we'd have to be
a couple to break up.
So what?
I was just a good time?
Is that what
you're telling me?
Yes, Ginny,
that's what we were having,
a good time.
And I'm pretty sure
I was a piece on the side.
Are you missing something?
Was I unclear when I said
"I love you"?
I'm sorry.
Perfect.
How perfect!
I tell you that I love you,
- and you tell me you're sorry.
- I-I am.
You're sorry, all right.
You are a sorry, sorry man!
Would you keep
your voice down?
Aren't you and Everett
just two peas in a pathetic pod?
"Yes, no, come, go."
Everett should have
known better.
About what?
Don't be dense.
I brought champagne
and I said the words,
"I'm all yours."
You left him?
He had his chance,
and he blew it.
I thought we had
a future together, Dean.
I thought
this was what you wanted.
You didn't
leave him for me.
And I never made you
any promises.
That's right. You just
strung me along, didn't you?
You did a fine job
stringing yourself along
without any help from me.
What are you, crazy?
Pan Am
S01 Ep 13 - Romance languages
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
And I can't find a replacement.
The boy can't fly
unaccompanied.
I liked this job.
I'm on the Rome flight.
Why don't I escort him?
Is that allowed?
It is now.
I was hoping you'd say that.
I know.
I'm sure
my fellow stewardesses
would appreciate
separate hotel rooms.
It would make a nice change.
Let me see what I can do.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Morning.
- Bonjour.
- Thank you.
Have you seen
the flight manifest yet?
She isn't on it.
Neither is he.
We do have
a plane full of clergy
for the second
Vatican council.
Chances are good
the flight is serene.
Are you two married?
No.
We're not married, no.
Because I'm available.
You must be Charlie.
Oui. Bonjour,
je m'appelle Charlie.
Bonjour, Charlie.
Je m'appelle Colette,
et voici notre capitaine.
How are you, Charlie?
Morning, captain.
Pleasure to meet you.
Careful there, sport. I gotta
fly the plane in a few minutes.
Sorry, sir. I'll take it easy
on you next time.
Right this way, monsieur.
Please, allow me.
What a gentleman.
Merci.
Hold it right there!
You got my watch?
May I help you with something?
I will be right back.
Why me?
"Why you" what?
Why do I always get stuck
with the honeymooners?
The future honeymooners?
The pretend honeymooners?
Do you need me
to take care of something?
No! I don't!
Laura, what's wrong?
Sex.
Did you see them?
What?
The couple in row 9.
They're almost having sex
in their seats.
Right next to a nun.
They're still at it.
They're getting
kind of acrobatic.
Well,
at least they'll be able
to confess their sins
immediately.
Sin? Where?
How did... they should have spent
their airfare on a hotel.
They're so passionate.
I'm envious.
- I...
- No.
I want details.
I can't wait anymore.
Do you feel different?
Maggie, it's... private.
That's what girlfriends
are for.
Grazie mille.
A pickpocket
and a linguist.
You speak Italian also?
Well, I'm not fluent yet,
but I'd like to be.
I'm partial
to the romance languages.
As am I.
They are... poetic, no?
Yes. And they make sense.
Unlike English.
I don't get it.
Why isn't it dead like Latin?
It's a mystery.
How did you do this?
I like close-up magic.
It's fun.
Something to do
when I'm on my own,
which is a lot.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Then again,
"transcontinental divorce"
has a nice ring to it.
I'm sorry to hear that,
too.
Give it back.
Keep an eye on this one.
He's a scamp.
Excuse me!
Sister Mary Agnes really needs
to use the lavatory.
How long has it been?
17 minutes.
There have been...
Noises.
Dear.
I'm sorry.
Could you please...
Finish up?
Is this beyond
your station, child?
Would you like me
to speak to the pilot?
I'll say one thing for her...
She's got a pretty good arm.
I got one word
for you... jujubes.
No, I know where
you're headed. Skip it.
I'm not headed anywhere.
I've said all I need to say.
No, you're dying to say it.
That I told you so?
I would never say that.
You got nothing
to be ashamed of.
You went
a respectable distance,
considering the mink
was off-the-charts crazy.
Why are the crazy girls
always the most fun?
Let's get
something straight.
They are all crazy.
All you can do is choose
a degree on the crazy-o-meter.
I need some turbulence.
Why?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are experiencing turbulence.
Please take your seats.
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm worried.
Everything.
I...
I spent some time
with a man...
Last night.
What exactly are you saying?
Does that mean
what I think it means?
Laura, did you lose
your virginity?
Expensive piece
of equipment.
That happens to be
an essential tool of the trade.
That's how you get
the film off the spool
in total darkness.
So you just
feel your way around?
Gotta know right
where everything goes.
That's the "soup."
Not edible.
Stop bath, fixer,
rinse bath,
we have to be very gentle.
Coax the paper
with a delicate touch.
Timing is... everything.
The temperature
has to be... ideal.
I'd,
I'd like to try it someday.
Developing.
You should. I insist.
Bring your film back from Rome.
We'll develop it together.
Really?
There's a statue
you shouldn't miss.
Two lovers.
Intimate, yet visceral.
A romance and passion
alive in stone.
It'll change your life.
Non se l'aspettava stasera.
He's only authorized
to be released to his mother,
not the housekeeper.
His mother is away overnight.
So tell her
that the boy knows her.
Allora... lui la conosce,
va bene?
She isn't coming, is she?
Your mother is not coming,
no.
But hopefully, they'll release
you to your housekeeper.
Parent trap again.
Dad put me
on an earlier flight.
He probably didn't remember
to tell my mom
I was coming in so soon.
It's not the first time.
They don't talk much
since they got divorced.
You don't have to wait.
I'll be fine.
I didn't get
to pick a card.
Looks like trouble to me.
Alzarzi. Possiamo andare ora?
Vieni. Vieni.
- You can go with her.It's all right.
- Thanks, Laura.
Affrettatevi!
Bye. Thanks for everything.
I had a swell time.
Bye.
Hey, Charlie...
Would you care to have
dinner with us this evening?
We need
a transcontinental tour guide
to recommend
the perfect place.
Sure.
I guess that'd be okay.
We'll give you two a lift.
We'll drive, yes?
Grazie.
Mille grazie.
She doesn't understand.
It's my park ride out there
without the amusement.
Surprised we made it back
in one piece.
Rome traffic is notorious.
Yeah, so is that housekeeper.
Charlie is quite a character,
no?
Yeah, I like the little guy.
I'm gonna keep an eye
on my wallet tonight, though.
Wanna fill me in
on the joke?
Not here.
Uno, due, tre.
Don't you already
have one from Rome?
It's a gift.
A friend of mine
will find it very amusing.
The second Vatican council.
I feel like we're
a part of history.
Change is in the air.
Yes and no.
Women only get to watch.
It'll be a miracle
if there's a positive stance
on birth control
any time this century.
You used precaution,
didn't you?
Damn it, Maggie!
Sorry, sorry.
Tick-a-lock.
I'm gonna grab a cappuccino.
Maggie, what's your pleasure?
I'll have an espresso.
Laura,
hot chocolate, right?
No, I'll have
an espresso, too.
Are you sure you don't wanna
start with a latte
and work your way up?
Espresso, please.
Break up with Niko Lonza.
Who is that man,
and how does he know me?
Not CIA.
Most likely Niko's people.
Niko's people? Why?
Betting they don't want him too
tempted by the Western world.
Meaning me?
Especially after his little
unauthorized escapade in Belgrade.
Richard, am I in danger?
They are trying
to scare you, not hurt you.
That's not what I meant.
I meant...
Is my cover blown?
Am I going to
end up like Bridget?
Richard?
Richard, please,
I can't disappear.
- Please insert 2,825 lire...
- Richard, are you there?
For one more minute.
- Si prega di inserire...
- God, Richard...
Shoot! Richard!
I'm here.
Kate, listen to me.
It is unlikely
your cover is blown.
I will investigate
on our end,
but I'm fairly certain
that as far as anyone knows,
you're a stewardess.
"Fairly certain"?
I wanna see you as soon
as you return to New York.
I don't know
what else to say.
I would never have told you
to come all this way.
Which is why
you didn't ask.
Ginny, sit down.
Would you sit down?
Ginny?
Would you like
something to drink?
I'm sorry.
I really am, but...
It's still over between us.
Hi.
Thanks for being here.
I'm feeling more calm now.
Much better.
I don't know
what possessed me.
I was... I don't know.
It's humiliating.
Talk about betting
on a lame horse,
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I wasn't trying
to prove a point.
It just happened.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
So you're still ending it?
Nurse! Nurse!
I just need a few minutes.
Do you mind waiting outside?
I need to send
a cablegram, please.
Do you have a fever?
No, not yet.
Just hope I'm not coming down
with something crummy.
You're smart
to get some rest.
Tell the little man
I'm sorry.
I'll take care of it.
I'm sure Charlie
will understand.
Thanks.
Feel better.
Yeah.
Buona sera.
Sei un fiore squisito.
Grazie a voi.
Che tipo di Fiore?
Una rosa.
Tu sei bella.
E ti piace il...
Attenzione.
Wait.
You're right.
Let's go find the bedroom.
I...
- I should go.
- Go?
Did I cross
the line or something?
I mean, you seemed...
I'm not ready. I'm...
I'm not ready.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
Anyway, I...
I-I like, you. I...
No need to explain.
My mistake.
I didn't realize
you were so... young.
I'm sorry.
I was... I was trying
to be quiet.
Hey there, Cinderella.
I'm guessing you had fun.
You look appropriately
disheveled.
I'm just gonna take
a quick shower.
This is big news.
Are you okay?
Sure.
Come on, sweetie.
Don't keep me in the dark.
How was it? Or should I say,
how was he?
He was fine.
I-I'm sorry.
I just don't really wanna
talk about it right now.
You don't really
wanna talk about it.
I can respect that.
I think you made the perfect
choice for your first time.
He's mature, handsome,
probably good
with his hands.
Was he considerate?
Was it torrid?
Good night.
"Filetto mignon."
Sounds good
in Italian, too.
You picked a lovely spot.
I'm sure our captain will be
sorry he missed this.
Yeah, but it's okay.
You're not too disappointed?
Everyone knows
three's a crowd.
Besides, candlelight looks best
on a beautiful girl.
Buona sera, signora.
Buona sera.
Signor Charlie,
your companion is molto bella.
See?
Luigi agrees with me.
We'll have a bottle of the...
Old red wine
that you decant at the table.
Very good, sir.
Mi scusi,
perhaps I'll have
a glass of Chianti instead?
And perhaps
you can have a taste.
I think you're the oldest
12-year-old I've ever met.
I'm almost 13.
Do you enjoy school?
It's taking forever.
Wish I was done already.
When you're a grown-up,
no one can tell you
what to do or where to go.
It's funny.
I wouldn't have predicted it,
but there are things I miss
about being your age.
Penny for your thoughts.
It's just
that when you're older,
you'll wish you had
less decisions to make.
That's a good trick.
I've got another one.
Yeah?
Close your eyes.
Charlie, no.
How'd you know I was here?
I didn't.
But I should have guessed.
Ginny called me
early this morning.
Sorry.
How was, uh,
how was dinner last night?
Unique. Growing pains.
I'm not sure
I handled it correctly.
I'm not entirely convinced
I did, either.
Is she all right?
Yeah.
No.
I don't... I'm not...
I'm not sure what to do.
Why does she wanna see you?
I'm about to find out.
May I come in?
If you want.
I'm happy to see you
look as well as you do.
When you called, I was...
Eight letters.
Begins with "B."
Plural. Describes all men.
"Buffoons." "Bastards."
What to choose?
I'm sure the nurse
could find you something
much better to read.
You have an innocent face.
Anyone ever told you that?
Is that a compliment?
I like you, Colette.
So the question of the hour,
of the minute...
Does Dean?
Captain Lowrey and I
are friends. Nothing more.
Damn.
I can't believe that
I'm actually disappointed.
I liked having
a face on the crime.
T.W.A.!
I had to fly T.W.A.!
Captain Lowrey,
I'm so glad you're here.
Mr. Henson.
Look, how is she? I mean,
what the hell happened?
Wait, wait, wait,
just let me...
Let me catch my breath.
That woman is going to be
the death of me.
The whims, the demands,
the athletic assignations.
You know, I'm not...
I'm not so young anymore.
Still, the last part
of her wire was cryptic...
"Lost a fight
with a window"?
I mean, can you shed
some light?
Must have killed him
not to fly Pan Am.
And what did you hope to gain
by bringing him here?
Pistols at dawn
might be exciting.
I want no part of this.
I don't want to be alone.
There. I said it.
I can't be alone.
I... I can't.
I've been you,
in your situation,
more times
than I care to count.
You've been on this ride?
Someone leads you on and
then throws you away?
I think I fell in love
with the idea of love
as much as anything else.
It's easy to do.
It helps you feel safe.
But as much as
we wish we could,
you can't force someone
to love you.
We had a falling out
two nights ago, she and I.
But why come here?
Why Rome?
Because the truth is, sir...
Ginny and I became involved.
"Involved."
Is that what the kids
are calling it these days?
She followed me to Rome
after I broke things off.
I-I regret my actions
more than I can say.
I bet you do, buddy boy.
I bet you do.
I bet you think that this
information is surprising to me.
Don't be an amateur,
captain Lowrey.
Why do you think
Ginny and I fought?
Everett knows.
I never said "boo."
He found out on his own.
Some little friend
of yours, apparently.
A stewardess?
Who?
He never said.
Someone who needed a favor.
Worked out
just peachy for her.
For me not so much.
After that, he tried
to rein me in.
But why won't
he leave his damn wife?
He's here now.
Seems to me
nothing has changed...
Unless you want it to.
You're not
her first dalliance, captain,
and you won't be her last.
But a pilot from my own company?
That is an unusual
and unwelcome departure...
One that will soon
be permanent.
I'm sure
there's another airline
that'd be delighted
to have you.
And I'm sure having
a wife and a mistress
must be
extremely complicated.
I confided in you.
I told you I loved her.
Hey, that's perfect,
because I don't.
Look, I may be foolish,
but I am not a fool.
Okay. Then I suggest that
you stop playing me for one.
Now I'm...
I'm done conversing.
I said she's yours.
Now what's it gonna be?
Mr. Henson?
Second door on your right.
Ginny is quite desperate
to see you.
Captain Lowrey,
I hope your health improves.
Another Bourbon, please.
Colette, je suis desole.
I'm sorry, Colette.
Je suis vraiment desole.
Charlie?
You frightened me.
Good.
I'm glad you're scared.
What are you doing here,
Charlie?
I came to tell you
that you're a phony.
- A big fake.
- Charlie...
What? I'm leaving.
We're through.
Charlie, please sit down.
Don't go yet.
I'd like to talk to you.
I like talking to you.
Nobody ever does...
Unless I do
those stupid magic tricks.
Charlie...
I'm sorry I embarrassed you
at dinner.
It wasn't my intention.
Grown-ups don't really don't
really know everything.
You don't think I know that?
I wish I didn't have
any parents.
Charlie...
Never wish that.
They never want me around.
If you only knew
how much I wish
I'd had parents
to be mad at.
Am I forgiven?
Okay.
You know the trouble
with magic tricks?
There is no surprise
for the magician.
He knows how it ends.
You don't want to be young
because you don't like
the way things are.
I don't blame you.
But one day, you'll wake up,
and you'll be all grown up.
It's inevitable.
And all the rest...
It will be a surprise.
I have some magic.
Do you wanna see it?
Please?
Okay, sit.
Part of magic
is suspense
and expectation, right?
What could it be?
Voila.
I didn't want
to forget you.
And I won't.
That's a promise.
I think it's this way.
Is your knee okay?
Do you wanna go back?
No, it's okay. I didn't
wanna miss this beautiful day.
This is the place.
That's it!
That's the sculpture
Graham told me to find.
Have you ever felt
like that?
Yes.
Here. Sit down.
What?
And hold still.
Kate.
Stop taking care of me.
I didn't lose my virginity,
and I'm sick to death
of never knowing
what to do or how to be.
I had my chance to be
a modern woman,
and I just acted like
a stupid little baby.
Did I get it all?
No, just...
Just... yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
I wanted
my first time to be special,
but Greg never pressured me,
and now...
Now what? Will... will it turn out
to be some man I barely know?
Maybe I'm over-thinking it.
Maybe I should just
get it over with.
There's something to be said
for practicality,
but being a modern woman
isn't about losing
your virginity.
Do you remember that to-do list
I had in high school?
Well, that was on my list.
Who?
Do you remember Clayton?
From junior French club?-
I cornered him
under the bleachers
in a football field
after a sock hop.
You did not!
Yeah, we were hopeless.
Tangled in my crinolines,
and his boutonniere
kept stabbing me.
No.
You know, gave it
the old college try.
Stop, stop.
That's probably what
I should have said.
Laura.
Just follow
your instincts.
You'll know
when it's right.
I-I don't need to know
what happened in that
room with Ginny.
Good.
But I'm... pretty sure that
I should be saying "thank you."
No, not really.
Well, they're together now.
They always were.
Some people can play at love
like it's a sport...
A game. It's not.
Well, regardless,
the "thank you" stands,
all right?
- I'll see ya.
- See you.
5 loose cups on the floor,
row 10.
The chocolate twins.
And three empty vodka bottles...
Their mother.
I meant to say this before,
but congratulations.
For?
Your job...
You saved it.
I thought all was lost.
They just needed
a little persuading.
I didn't think anyone could
persuade the base manager.
Did you secure
all the stemware?
I know how much this job
means to you.
You must have been
so frightened.
Desperate, even.
What did you say to him?
Not much. The usual...
Smoke and mirrors.
I should've guessed
you would have a trick
up your sleeve.
A little something extra.
What do you mean,
something extra?
The usual...
Maggie's magic.
Who knows
what any one of us
would have done
in your situation?
All looks good. I'm off.
"I'm terrified, Niko.
It was awful.
What do you think it means?"
Try it again.
Kate, can you do this?
When you say it,
- believe it.
- I believe it.
And so will he. I know him.
He will be upset.
Niko's people want him
to toe the line.
And you want him to be
upset with his people.
It'll help him.
It'll help you,
is what you mean.
Us. And in this case,
it is the same thing.
So I deliver
their not-so-cryptic message,
and then what happens?
Wouldn't an ordinary girl
run from all this?
You want me
to break up with him?
I want you to tell him
what a frightened girl
would tell him...
That you need some time
to collect yourself.
How much time?
Depends. We'll see.
You might be back on the job
before you know it.
Kate?
What is it?
Are... are you okay?
You sure I didn't wake you?
It's only, uh, 7:00.
I always look like this
when I've been in the darkroom.
Come out like a bear
who's been hibernating.
Thin and hungry.
Fur all matted,
disoriented.
I brought you something.
Yes. Rome.
Did you, uh,
find that sculpture?
I did.
And?
Is your camera handy?
It's always handy. Why?
I wanna feel how liberating
anonymous can be.
Are you sure?
No. But I'm gonna do it
anyway...
If you're fine with it.
Is it warm enough for you?
No, I've got it.
This is
about self-expression.
Understood.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com