Previously on "Pan Am"...
- You're gonna meet Kennedy?
- Tomorrow in Berlin.
The secret police,
they know who I am.
Go to the U.S. mission.
If you go there, you can defect.
You have no idea
what you've done
nor what it takes
to keep a cold war cold.
You're different
from other girls.
Ask what you can do
for you country.
Freedom has many difficulties,
but we have never had to put
a wall up to keep our people in.
Thank you.
Who's up for a debriefing?
- Ugh.
- We just got home.
New York is a city of the world.
Oh, no,
not that skinny boy
who can't carry a tune.
Bob Dylan is an artist.
I'll bet money he'll be famous.
I'll go.
No, we have a date
with the laundromat,
and we depart for Iceland
in 36 hours.
Thank you very much,
miss Ryan.
I miss Bridget.
She was never too tired to play.
Has anyone heard from her?
- No, not a word.
- Strange.
Good evening, ladies.
Good night.
Will wonders never
cease? She's still talking.
She'll come to her senses.
- She already did.
- What do you know?
It's the boy wonder
and his first officer.
Howard.
Tucking him into bed, Ted?
Right after I finish
cutting your food, captain.
With your family connections,
I would have thought
you would have been the one
to jump seniority.
Have you read the paper?
It's 1963.
A new generation leads.
Careful, son.
The fierce itch of ambition
can be hard to scratch.
We'll suffer through it,
captain.
Uhh! Oh!
Laura! Let's go!
We're late!
- I can't find my mittens!
- Will I need long underwear?
If you'd make a list,
you wouldn't be scrambling!
Just hurry up. We're late.
I hope you're not lugging
all that on a subway.
Well, if you would like
to hail us a cab...
At your service.
Richard.
Do you have an extra pair
I could borrow?
You won't need mittens
if I leave you behind!
- Okay, okay!
- Did you get any of my messages?
Did you forget the part about us
only contacting you? Taxi!
I know, but I wanted to explain
what happened in Berlin.
I'm well aware
of what happened.
I got stuck
with the paperwork.
But you can sleep at night.
It was for a good cause, right?
Kate, you you disobeyed
a direct order.
I know. I overstepped.
It won't happen again.
I understand you saved
a girl's life,
but you need to understand
that you are of no use to us
if we can't rely on you.
You can.
I have really gotta
learn how to whistle.
Ah. Here we go.
Thought I was losing
my touch.
So... will I get
another assignment?
One sec.
I need you to keep
your eyes open in rangoon.
The agency might need you
to run an errand.
But we're not flying to Burma.
It's Reykjavik
and then onto Scandinavia!
- Found them!
- I'll be right down!
Laura?
I said I'm coming!
Forget your mittens!
Uh, grab a swimsuit!
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Come on. Who did you
bribe in scheduling?
It was a lucky guess.
That we'd be rerouted
to the orient?
That I might need
a bikini.
Anyone up for a swim?
Maybe in a year or two.
I may cool off in a few minutes.
Careful. She placed third
in the Connecticut junior high
freestyle state finals.
Only by a reach.
I have abnormally long arms.
Oh, perfect. Reach over there
and pass me that cocoa butter.
It's right next to you.
I'm situated.
Allow me.
My friend and I were hoping
you could settle a bet for us.
Yes, it's true.
Guarantees deep,
lingering color.
Ohh.
We heard a rumor
that Pan Am stewardesses
checked into the hotel
last night.
Well, we heard a rumor there was
a naval wedding this morning.
One of our R.I.O.S.
You're stationed here?
Saigon. We're teaching
the South Vietnamese how to fly.
Ahem.
Oh, sorry, friend.
Are they with you?
- For the day.
- Lucky man.
You used to be a Navy man
once, Ted, weren't you?
Everybody has to earn
their wings somewhere.
Ah.
Former aviator?
- Current.
- He's our first officer.
A co-pilot. Good for you.
I earn five times more
flight hours, uh, in Pan Am
than I did in the Navy,
and you can't beat my crew.
It's tempting. I'll have
to consider it when I retire.
Well, that'll give you plenty
of time to get up to speed.
I could fly that boat
blindfolded tomorrow.
By the time you work
on your I.F.R. booster
instrument rating,
you'll be wearing bifocals.
Missed your calling, buddy.
Should've been a comedian.
Missed his calling all right.
Why'd you leave the Navy?
- Look, don't worry about it.
- Aren't you boys hot in those uniforms?
Maybe they can't swim.
We're in the Navy.
Well, there you go, Laura.
One of these gentlemen
will race with you.
Oh, I wasn't looking to race.
Are you sure? 'Cause I'll
give you half-a-lap head start.
Loser buys drinks?
Take this to Jakarta.
Come on, Laura!
- Come on now!
- Come on! You're beating him!
Come on! You got it!
I won?!
Oh!
Was there ever
any doubt?
What's going on over there?
Battle of the sexes.
Oh. Best one win?
Of course.
Oh, I won!
Apparently, the secret is being
endowed with monkey arms.
I'm so happy
she could amuse you.
- I'm being ironic.
- Laura's a gem!
- Did you see?
- I saw.
Where'd you get that camera?
Did you get a picture?
Oh, I missed it.
I'm sorry.
Drinks all around!
You didn't even give me the full head start.
You didn't need it.
Mayday! Mayday!
Aah!
Help!
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're just crossing over
the equator.
We'll be landing in Jakarta
in just under an hour.
Did I do something wrong?
I mean...
No, not at all.
Well, they knew I could swim.
We told them.
You were swimming.
He was trolling.
Oh. Well,
Maggie said that...
Maggie likes to stir the pot.
It's her hobby.
Uh, you have the pilots'?
I do.
No, no,
Sputnik was a good thing.
So it was a good thing.
The Russians beat us
into space.
We needed a kick
in the pants.
Some kick.
They got the first man
up there, too.
We could have beaten them
in two and a half months
if we didn't wimp out and send up
that monkey.
Coffee, gentlemen?
Please.
- Wasn't it a chimp?
- Like I said, a monkey.
Yeah, right, so...
No, none for me, thanks.
So you look before you leap,
right?
You're learning, captain.
Bridget. You leapt. She loped.
Thank you, Sanjeev.
Completely forgotten.
Say...
Did Bridget,
you know, help you?
Jump the line.
What line?
The line
to that captain's chair.
I just thought
maybe Bridget had a connection
before she went Houdini.
British aristocracy
or something.
Ted, the world does not work
that way for most people.
Tell that
to the 65 Pan Am first officers
with more seniority
than you.
Oh, so you counted.
Rough guess.
Does that include you?
Look, don't get me wrong.
I think you're a fine pilot.
I'm just not buying
this whole new image thing,
not with your ugly mug.
Or...
That chip on your shoulder
doesn't leave any room
for captain's stripes.
Yeah, maybe.
But seriously,
how'd you jump the line?
Well, why didn't you?
At ease, lieutenant.
We'll make this quick.
In the matter
of the 12 September crash
of the Juno-V3 interceptor,
piloted by
lieutenant Edward Vanderway...
Excuse me, sir.
Is this a finding?
I haven't completed
my testimony.
We have your statement.
Is it deficient in some way?
No, sir.
Then in the absence
of any clear mechanical failure,
this inquiry finds...
Sir, with respect, as I've
told you, I'm a test pilot.
My job is to push aircraft
to the limit
in search of
possible mechanical failure,
in this case, I found one.
My I.A. was stuck
at 90 degrees left.
No evidence
of an altimeter freeze.
The V3 cockpit is scattered
all over the Atlantic.
I repeat... no evidence.
My testimony as a pilot
and officer
in the United States Navy
is evidence.
And your bar tab
the night before is evidence
that the Navy got less
than your best that morning.
That was over 12 hours
before I flew.
That's well
within regulations.
The aircraft failed, sir.
Lieutenant, your presence here
today requires you to listen,
not to argue.
While the absence
of clear mechanical failure
suggests the primary cause
of the Juno crash
to be that of pilot error,
this inquiry requires further
investigation and deliberation
and recommends
lieutenant Vanderway
be placed
upon administrative duty
until the matter is resolved.
Dismissed.
He's a looker, ain't he?
Is there any chance you all have
a television set around here?
- Yes, we do.
- All right.
Jakarta...
Coming up in the world.
But it is not working
right now.
Or not.
What's wrong with it?
I don't know, sir.
I'm sorry.
Well, where is it?
Maybe I can fix it.
You just go down the stairs,
you turn right,
and you keep going
all the way back.
Okay, okay.
Oh, it's so foreign!
How did you get here so fast?
Oh, Mr. Rickshaw knew how
to beat the traffic.
You should have tried one.
So that's where
my scarf went.
Oh, you had two.
J-just ask.
I-I thought I lost it,
and you should be wearing
a white scarf in uniform.
I know. I forgot it.
That's a demerit.
I made a list
of the attractions
we can see while we're here,
and I think if we don't
leave soon, then I'm...
I think you're
a bit jet-lagged.
Why don't you just
rest here for a few minutes?
Well, Maggie said that Jakarta
is excitingly unrefined.
I tell you what.
I'll go pick up our per diem
and get a few tourist tips,
and then we'll head out.
Okay.
Promise not to see anything
without me.
I'll keep my eyes shut.
Laura?
Make no sense.
What this word?
Uh, it's, um, "souvenir."
Sou-ve-nir.
"Richard. Want souvenir?
What destination? Kate."
Yeah.
You wait?
Sorry?
You. Wait. Reply.
Uh, yes, I will wait.
Thank you.
5 pieces of page paper.
2 rupiah each.
Here's what you need to know.
Lizards... good.
Leave 'em alone.
They eat the mosquitoes,
not you.
If you say so.
- We are definitely
- not in Kansas anymore.
I can't believe you touched it,
you weren't scared at all.
Aah!
Snake in the bathroom!
What do we do?
Okay. Okay.
What? What?
We get outta here.
Get dressed,
and I will
meet you downstairs.
Oh, uh... m-Maggie?
Hi. Excuse me.
Um, I have to get going.
Can I just come back later?
Tomorrow.
No, no, no.
I'll just come back later.
We close five minutes.
What?
No, no, no.
I need that reply now.
You have U.S. dollars?
Thank you.
You won't find this place
in the tourist book, huh?
Bir, silakan.
I can order beer
in 15 languages.
Really?
Well, don't be too impressed.
After that, my repertoire tops
out at "where's the bathroom?"
Ah, the scent
of youth and freedom.
Intoxicating.
Thank you.
Yes, we are
the American dream.
But, alas, merely your fantasy.
Dominoes?
Block dominoes or "gaple."
Serious stuff.
High stakes. A lot of fun.
You know how to play?
I know how to win.
Pull up a chair.
Ready for rematch?
Oh, yeah.
How have you been?
On a winning streak.
Oh, yeah, till I got here.
Okay.
Okay, you go now.
Make no sense...
"If you drop camera,
it break."
"Drop camera harta karun laut"?
Oh. Excuse me! Excuse me.
Uh, do you know
where harta karun laut is?
Green door.
This is the best
chicken curry in Indonesia.
Thank you.
How much money
do you have left?
Not much.
Don't worry. I'm flush.
Which one of those varmints
looks tougher to you?
What, the chicken?
Well, they're cocks.
It's a big difference.
Oh.
At least the loser tastes
pretty good, don't you think?
- Let's go dance.
- Let's dance.
Laura?
Oh, God.
Oh, Laura.
Ohh.
Hello?
Excuse me.
Yes?
Uh, excuse me.
Uh, did my sister leave
a note for me?
Room 212?
Sister?
- Yes, sister.
- Uh, my sister. Room 212.
No.
Oh, dang. Almost had it.
Ted. Ted, have you
seen Laura?
Uh, no. Can you hold this
for a second?
I can't believe
she didn't leave a note.
Where'd... where'd she go?
If she needs a spanking,
I'm your guy.
I know. I know.
Restricted airspace.
What's our motto?
Go native!
You got it, sister!
Kate? Look.
I'm practically a native.
Yes, Colette told me.
She saw you and Maggie
out and about.
Oh, we had the best time.
Maggie knows everything about
everything and then some,
and look what she made me buy.
Mom will flip.
Laura, is there a camera
in your bag?
Yes.
- Ohh.
- I borrowed it.
- I hope you didn't mind.
- Great. Just... just give it to me.
I... we just left in such a hurry.
I didn't... just... no, it's...
Just give it to me.
I'm... I'm... I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Hello?
Uh...
Um, are you in there?
Ohh.
I don't... have any money.
You're late.
Snake's gone.
I got
housekeeping to take it.
They didn't seem
very apologetic.
Said it wasn't poisonous,
like we could know that.
You just took off.
You just took off,
without a care in the world...
Well, there was a snake. I...
Room in shambles.
Oh.
I should have left a note.
Do you have any idea
how worried I was?
I mean, what...
What were you thinking?
Maggie just came in.
It all happened...
You know, Laura,
you weren't thinking...
And you sure as hell
didn't give me a second thought.
We might as well just be
back home, you know?
You just skimming by,
and me paying for all
of your mistakes.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to worry
about you,
and I don't want
to take care of you.
Who's asking you to?
I don't seem to have
a choice.
Kate...
You're not even giving me
a chance.
To do what, Laura?
To be me?
In case you've forgotten,
I got this job
on my own merits.
Then act like it.
You want to get out.
You... you want to have a job.
You want to see the world.
That is great,
but do you know
what that makes you?
A grown-up, so grow up.
It's so easy for you.
No one ever expected
anything from you.
Excuse me?
You always got to do
exactly what you wanted.
Yeah, Laura, I did!
I did. I did what I wanted.
I did what I really wanted to,
but now...
Now I'm doing
what you wanted...
And you still don't
want me here!
No, Laura, I just want you
to stand on your own two feet!
I am trying!
You're wearing bunny slippers!
Well, I like them!
You don't have to!
...As the elevator door closes
and slowly starts up
the, uh, the entry tower.
Booster locked
and ready to go.
Then light that sucker.
And once again,
he wastes no time in...
Did you close down the bar?
Wouldn't be the first time.
Carrying his portable cooler
and walks into the van...
Is that the, uh, latest
in tropical evening wear?
Following him
into the transfer van.
Paradise not
what you expected?
Through the gates...
I'll tell you
if you tell me,
and we'll both deny it
in the morning, hmm?
All right.
You go first.
I killed a man in amarillo.
You did?
Rube.
Brat.
I don't need anyone else
telling me
I don't know anything.
Aha. A clue.
Cooper will be up 136...
What are we watching?
"Mercury 9" live liftoff.
Sending the first man
into outer space
for more than a day.
More time than land.
Oh, come on! Not again.
Technology versus Ted.
Round six!
- Anything?
- No.
Ohh! I will not be bested by
some tubes and wires from 1952!
Oh, w-wait. Wait.
Oh, we got something?
Yes. Uh...
No. Wait. A little... yes.
Yes, it... well, it...
It's sort of working.
- Story of my life!
- Mine, too.
Okay, there!
Oh! Oh.
Oh, can you turn up
the volume, please?
Uh, you... look, you sit.
I'll hold this.
Oh, thank you.
Ohh.
Will it fly by us?
Oh, maybe...
In about 45 minutes,
but it's more like falling
than flying.
Earlier than he was
yesterday morning.
Oh, we lost it.
Oh.
Hey, oh. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Freeze!
Right... there.
I wish I had my camera.
Don't say the word "camera."
Here we go.
Four... three...
Two... one.
Ignition. Liftoff.
Liftoff.
04 after the hour, liftoff.
All systems appear to be
operating properly.
This is Mercury control.
The trajectory looks a-okay
at this time.
- Roger.
- You look good here, Gordo.
Roger. Feels good, buddy.
I bet it does.
They offered me
honorable discharge.
It's the least
the Navy could do.
I'm opting to decline it.
And the devil did grin,
for his darling sin is pride.
That aircraft had
a bum gyro, dad.
Everything has limits.
Even you.
Here's a thought.
I'll make a call.
No.
No, you want to fly
a few more years
before you settle down.
I'll put in a word
with Juan Trippe at Pan Am.
I am a naval aviator.
I do not need your help
flying commercial.
Former naval aviator.
Not yet.
Dad, I-I, uh,
I need you to get
your engineers to take
a harder look
at the gyro on the V3.
It's been taken care of.
So there was something
wrong with it?
Tell the Navy.
They can reopen my inquiry.
My company's contracts
with the Pentagon
are up for renewal
next year.
Contracts?
Oh, dad. Um...
This is my last shot
at the space program, so...
It's over, son.
Accept your honorable discharge
honorably
and get on with your life.
Plenty of blue skies ahead,
Teddy.
Ooh! Time?
Two minutes, seven seconds.
Ugh! I'm slowing down.
Do you really walk off the plane
without your girdle on?
We are in the tropics.
That's no place
for the shackles of propriety.
You know she got grounded
for that.
Do you see
a grooming supervisor anywhere?
Oh, don't worry.
Kate's not a tattletale.
Ladies and gentlemen,
there's some weather on
the ground in Hong Kong harbor.
We're gonna experience
a few bumps on our descent.
Too bad.
The view is usually spectacular.
Well, she doesn't have
a camera anyways.
I plan on getting my own.
Oh, good.
Is this fight about a camera?
- No.
- Yes.
- Oh.
- Tug-of-war. Must be nice.
You're lucky, no?
Flying together?
I suppose we are.
It's hard to fly
with your wings clipped.
What does she mean by that?
Laura, what have you been
telling her?
Nothing, I...
I didn't have to.
You're the one
who does all the telling.
Yes?
Got it.
Maggie.
Hmm?
All I'm trying to do is help
Laura get up to speed...
I was joking.
And you're not helping.
Aren't I?
She is inexperienced
at everything.
She hasn't done a thing
on her own.
Well, maybe she should.
Pan Am is
the ultimate new beginning.
Let her begin.
Better batten down
the hatches.
Hmm?
Heavy crosswinds.
Clipper Two,
over heading Sierra-Lima-beacon,
descend to 2,000 and cleared
to intercept localizer
for approach.
Clipper Two, do you copy?
Answer him, will ya?
Roger that,
Kai Tak approach.
Have you ever
done this before?
What, land it
in poor visibility?
The Hong Kong approach.
First time
without training wheels.
Yeah, so never
with these crosswinds then.
Piece of cake.
Captain,
airspeed 2-0-0 knots.
Damn, who designed
this approach?
Satan.
Clipper Two,
call checkerboard in sight.
Roger. Call checkerboard.
Okay, I have checkerboard
in sight. Flaps to 30.
- Checkerboard in sight.
- Flaps to 30.
Altitude, uh, 1,000 feet.
Where... uh, uh, what was
our last wind speed?
225 degrees at 20 knots.
20 knots. Abort. We need
to abort. Let's circle around.
The weather's not getting
any better.
Tell the tower we're landing.
Are you nuts?
Hey! Do it.
Cleared for 1-3.
Clipper 2-2.
At this airspeed,
with that crosswind,
you're gonna land in the water.
I don't plan on maintaining
this airspeed.
We're at our crosswind limit.
At! At, not over.
Captain, do you want me
to take over?
No! I want you
to shut the hell up!
Oh! Oh!
Oh.
Here we are.
Good news...
my circulation has returned,
and I didn't soil myself.
That was quite a landing,
captain.
I'll be at the bar...
until tomorrow.
Yeah.
That was quite a landing.
Glad you agree.
There were 128 souls
on this aircraft.
Yeah, that I got safely
to the ground.
We could have gotten safely
to Singapore.
Well, we got safely
to Hong Kong.
We were one short and curly away
from landing in that bay.
The only time we were
in any danger
was when you were
distracting me.
Look, you're my friend, Ted.
I like you.
We can joke around
in the cockpit.
We can hang out
on the ground,
but you make no mistake.
I am in charge in the air,
and what I say
and what I do is the law.
There's no discussion,
no second-guessing.
And a sky God is born.
Hey, call it
whatever you want.
You either accept it,
or you need to get another jet.
A good captain respects
and utilizes
the expertise of his crew.
And a good first officer knows
exactly when and where
to offer it.
Where the hell
are all the umbrellas?
Do you think you're special?
You thin you're the only guy
that can make that landing?
I-I was a test pilot.
I can land
an anvil on a postage stamp
in the middle of the ocean.
That's not the point.
No. The point is, you think
you're in the wrong seat.
Yeah, I am.
Okay, well, you either need
to let it go,
or you need to call your daddy
to get you one of your own.
Two days. It's been two days.
Are you actually gonna let us
land in New York
without telling us
how you got that shiner?
Yeah, did some jerk
sucker punch you?
Guess we're
on a need-to-know basis.
3,000 feet.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain speaking.
We are making our final descent
into the New York area.
I want to thank you
for flying Pan Am.
For those of you
that have traveled with us
from the Orient...
Welcome home.
So... are we going
for cocktails?
Well, Kate will say no.
But what do you say?
Night, boys.
Ladies.
Pan Am
flight 36 from London Heathrow,
pick up your baggage
at carousel 4.
- Sorry, sir.
- I'll be right there.
All right.
Ted.
Right place
at the right time.
That's how I jumped
the line.
I was downtown,
headquarters,
and I got stuck in an elevator
with Juan Trippe for 11 minutes.
I figured...
I had nothing to lose,
so I told him
what I thought about
his pilot seniority system,
and I asked him,
I said, "do you want to be
part of the past,"
"or do you want to be part
of the future?
"You know, World War II vets
versus what's happening
right now with you and me...
The jet age?"
Sometimes
you just got lucky.
No, we make our own luck,
captain,
sometime you just gotta
step up.
Yeah.
Buy you a drink?
- Twist my arm?
- Please, no more violence.
And about that...
You work on your hook.
What?
Well, a little ivy league.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- There you are.
- Burger medium well.
The jakarta cablegram office
was not a model
of efficiency.
It took hours
to receive your reply.
I got to the drop
as soon as I could.
It was across the street.
You were six hours late.
But I made it, right?
You got the camera.
Yes, miss Cameron.
You made it.
These, um...
They didn't ruin anything,
did they?
Just
your sister's reputation.
We're getting her
out of your way.
I bet your pardon?
Your sister.
Can't have her impinging
on your ability
to function covertly.
I'll have her reassigned.
You won't be flying
together anymore.
No.
She's not in my way.
She's perfectly capable.
I can assure you
that my sister is not
and will not be a problem.
Laura?
Hi, dollface.
Well, it ain't much,
but it's home.
Welcome aboard.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com