Previously on "Pan Am".
Why don't you came out of the fog,
captain?
- Do we have an affirm here?
- Yes, of course.
- It's the vice-president.
- I don't plan on telling him.
- Will we go for a ride?
- Think I've already been taken for one.
Will be a man on your next flight.
Nico Lonza.
We need fingerprints.
- After you.
- Pardon me?
We'd all like to know how your wings
will act these days.
Miss Ryden, I can continue
our conversation
with your supervisor
upon of her return.
You kept this up,
you're not came be
around much longer.
So what do you say?
Am I a Pan Am material?
My shoes and socks, too?
Remarkably comfortable,
I must say.
Well, I'll have
to buy you a pair.
Mm. Men's socks...
The way to a woman's heart.
Mmm.
Promise not
to have too much fun in Rio?
What am I gonna wear?
What I did... it was stupid,
miss Havemeyer. I apologize.
I was attempting
a little levity, uh, stupidly.
And at my expense.
At the expense
of Pan American world airways.
- How did I hurt Pan Am?
- My ability to effectively...
Never mind.
You're right.
I made a mistake.
I will never do it again.
As this is one
of several infractions,
your file will be sent
to the base manager.
Excuse me.
Are you firing me?
The matter is now
under review...
Please. I have worked
my entire life to be here.
And until an official decision
is made, yes, you are grounded.
But I have a flight
to Brazil in two hours.
We'll find a replacement.
Who can speak Portuguese?
Maggie.
- Whoa, Maggie, watch out.
- Oh.
Ohh. Whoa.
You almost stepped in it.
Yeah. Nothing new.
Hey. I tried you at home.
You were pulled
from the Rio flight.
No, not yet. Mrs. Olcott said
that I could still...
Not you, Maggie. Kate.
Me? Uh, why?
Headquarters can't find
your smallpox vaccination.
Uh, d-do you want to see
the scar?
They suspect
it's their mistake,
but they still can't let you fly
until it's sorted out.
Could be a good thing.
Your landlord called.
There's a busted pipe
in your building.
Uh, d-did he leave a name?
Richard something.
Mm-hmm.
What's with
the photographer?
"Life" magazin
they're doing a follow-up piece
of their April profile...
"Day in the life
of Pan Am stewardesses."
Really? Our crew?
Uh, don't get too excited.
He's specifically here
for Laura.
Sprung it on her
ten minutes ago.
Huh. The powers that be are just
full of surprises this morning.
And I'm off to deal
with a plumber.
Mm.
Take care of my sister.
Oh, don't worry.
I won't leave her side.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
More ginger ale for you,
Mrs. Brous?
Yes, but this time
with a little Bourbon.
Two fingers.
As soon as we're airborne.
Sorry.
A little Pan Am posterity.
Best opening line I've had
in months.
A book?
But not just any book.
"The feminine mystique."
You actually read
the whole thing?
Didn't skip to the answer key
in the back?
Half a million copies sold,
and to whom?
Women,
and understanding women
is the best way to get women.
You understand women?
Oh, less than ever, but at least
now it sounds like I do.
Mink. 12:00.
You're flying
your paramour down to Rio?
Good morning.
Welcome aboard.
Well, thank you.
Hello, miss Saddler.
Captain Lowrey,
you remembered me.
I'm flattered.
And I'm surprised to see you
flying with us again so soon.
It seems I can't get enough
of your Pan Am service.
Well, we'll try not
to disappoint.
I'm counting on it.
Love the uniform.
Colette, I need you
to switch to economy.
Laura's in first.
I'll cover both.
Covering both
or covering the photographer?
I'm in need
of a little public relations.
Is that how they call it
these days?
Management and I have
a small difference of opinion.
Anything serious?
No, just my usual pickle.
- Okay.
Order up.
Oh.
Not again with that book.
Takes me out
of this place.
So does that door.
Outside that door is
a crazy father
in a trailer
with two flat tires.
In here,
at least everyone's pretty,
all their clothes are
beautiful,
and none of the parties
serve beer.
Books make me sleepy.
Nao Leia. Trabalhe!
Voce e uma garconete terrevendo.
How about some English?
I don't speak Portuguese.
This is America.
You bad waitress.
You pick up.
You mean boss.
You hold horses.
3 cents? 3 cents?
I live off my tips.
I grasp that.
Really? You grasp that?
What was wrong with my service?
The service was adequate.
Then why didn't you leave me
an adequate tip?
I didn't want
to encourage you.
I drove my first truck here
right after the war,
and, uh, Rose in there
served me coffee, black.
I was saving up to go
to school on my G.I. bill,
but 14 years later,
I'm still driving a truck.
And she's still pouring Joe.
Wait!
Stop! Wait!
I'm coming with you!
Stop! I'm coming!
August in New York.
Even the flies are sweating.
Smallpox? Really?
I could have just told them
your results were back,
set their inquiring minds
aquiver.
- Why did you pull me from my flight?
- Why haven't I heard from you?
I haven't had anything
since Monte Carlo.
Haven't you?
Your friend at the united nations...
Niko Lonza?
I've seen him a few times.
You said he wasn't the target.
At the time he wasn't.
Lonza works
at the Yugoslavian consulate.
Their president, Josip Tito, has
been playing us off the Soviets.
How does that involve
Nik... Mr. Lonza?
Your Niko's leaving town
this week, diplomatic business.
We need the wheretos
and whatfors
and where he stands
politically.
We never talk politics.
Here's your chance.
An amusement park?
Go play some hooky
with your communist friend.
Weather in Rio de Janeiro is a lovely
72 degrees.
Should be a nice break
from the New York humidity.
Again...  Don't pose.
I don't know how not to.
Excuse me.
You looked totally natural
in that cover picture.
Because I didn't know anyone
was taking it.
Hard to surprise you here.
Where am I gonna stand?
They told me
this wouldn't happen,
- if at all, until next month.
- What can I say?
Your Pan Am brass suddenly
wanted this in Rio.
If I may, mister, uh...
"Graham" will do.
Well, Graham,
if you want to see more
of the candid, spontaneous side
of the Pan Am stewardess,
you really need to see us
out of uniform.
Out of uniform?
Oh, don't get ideas.
I mean Rio. I've made a list.
Shopping,
the beaches of Ipanema,
the botanical gardens,
a night of samba, bossa nova.
Ambitious list.
You should see
the one I sent Santa.
Look, Laura's a little uncomfortable
with too much attention,
but she listens to me.
I can make this easier
for both of you,
if you could do a girl a favor.
I've worked
with temperamental before.
I meant me.
Laura was three weeks out
of training when that cover
landed her a spot
on this brand-new clipper.
Maybe you could rinkle
some of that fairy dust my way
and help me get out
of a jam?
Hey, I'm just a guy
with a camera.
Who decides
where it's pointed.
Nice maneuver,
but you'll never give him
the slip at 30,000 feet.
I can't understand why
they couldn't pick
someone with more experience.
Experience is overrated.
Maggie, I need your help
with a woman in 11C.
She wants something
but only speaks Portuguese.
Whenever I have to do something
I really don't want to,
I pretend I'm playing a role,
like an actress in a movie.
Give him a little...
Bete Boop?
Brigitte Bardot?
- Bardot's a blonde.
- Not originally.
- Oh.
- Hello, ladies.
I know that I shouldn't, but I'm
just going to poke my head in.
Do you want me to take
anything in to the pilots?
Uh, I-I don't think so.
Roger that.
Should I have stopped her?
She is Mr. Henson's secretary...
And Mr. Henson is
a Pan Am vice president.
Oh.
If that woman is
Henson's secretary,
then I'm his dog Walker.
- 11c?
- Portuguese.
"Movie. Fred and Ginger."
15 letters.
Mm. Easy. "Flying down to Rio."
Is that whole puzzle about Rio?
Okay, smarty-pants.
"'Hunchback' in Portuguese."
Nine letters.
Sanjeev covers
the hunchback stuff.
Corcovado.
- Gold star, captain Lowrey.
- Corco-what?
Corcovado...
That beautiful mountain right
in the middle of the city.
The one with big Jesus?
I'm always afraid we're gonna
fly right in him.
I think big Jesus
is where my boss
wants to take some
of the pictures.
That would be
Mr. Henson, vice president?
He's gonna be in Rio?
Oh, he's already there...
Preparing or something.
"Life" magazine photo shoot
with one of the stewardesses.
And that's why
you're headed down.
Well, you know these V.P.s.
Can't blow their nose
without a gal and a steno pad
by their side, so here I am.
Yes, here you are.
Keeping that for yourself,
are you?
Maybe it's for
a special girl back home.
You say that because you know
how competitive I am.
It's for my niece Magda.
In Yugoslavia,
we don't have bears.
We have wolves.
You're going home?
Yeah, to Zagreb,
just for one week.
You will miss me?
Is that a command
or a question?
Both.
- A fortune-teller.
- Let's get our palms read.
I don't need to come all
the way to America to be swindled.
Well, that's too bad.
A gypsy woman once told me
I'd fall in love
with
a dark, handsome stranger.
And instead you're stuck
with me.
You see?
Anyone can read a palm.
Bad news?
A secret.
Which one?
Any one you want to tell me.
Here? You want to ar
a secret?
We could always leave it
to the gypsy.
Here is a secret.
My mind is full of you.
I go to sleep this way.
I wake up this way.
You follow me like
a ghost...
Which is no good.
No good?
With a ghost,
I can't do this.
Mm.
And the bear is yours.
You aren't following me,
are you?
I was about to ask you
the same thing.
Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
Allow me.
You didn't, by any chance,
arrange this, did you?
Right next door. I'm good,
but I'm not that good.
I hope you and Henson
aren't the noisy type.
Or that foolish.
Well, you're certainly
not that forthcoming.
Nine hours ago, it's all tickle
tea and socks.
There's no mention of Rio,
no mention of Henson.
And if I had?
Then I might have discouraged
you from flying Pan Am today.
Well, then I guess I am
that good.
Monte Carlo was a lark.
It was wild,
and by some miracle,
we managed to swerve around
the accident in the road,
but Rio... Rio is the accident
waiting to happen.
Let's keep it in New York,
Ginny.
We can read the road signs.
We can speak the language.
Hit with common sense,
the mighty warrior falls.
Kate specifically asked
for an alligator bag.
I
think we got enough shopping.
Now I'm wasting film.
I haven't even bought
anything yet.
What was wrong with the clutch
with the big buckles?
Genuine alligator "style"...
If "style" means plastic.
Will Kate even know
the difference?
Meanwhile, somewhere people
are dancing the bossa nova.
I-I'm sorry.
You... you two go ahead.
Kate never asks me
for anything,
and I really want to do
this for her.
I thought we had a deal.
I'll get her back on track.
Meet us by that big red canoe
we saw in 15 minutes.
But not much longer.
Life is waiting.
Did we mention
we're stewardesses?
We can tell everybody
on the plane
how to find your shop
or tell them to stay away.
- Pan Am?
- All day long.
So we'd like the real thing
but for the plastic prices.
Tudo bem.
Stick with me, kid.
I know the lay of the land.
Drop slips are red.
Folder.
Add slips are blue.
Blue folder.
We usually hire a student
for this job,
but they can be
so unreliable.
What's this folder for?
That's a request
for transcripts.
That gets walked down
to Harvey in records.
Now he will probably offer
you an official degree
for your phone number.
You want to avoid him.
And where is he exactly,
so I can avoid him?
Main administration building.
Oh.
I need to drop a class.
Roxanne Gibson.
Oh, world literature.
It's a shame.
Oh, I know. Professor Kolker
is supposed to be wonderful,
but it interferes
with my job.
You're a stewardess?
Yes. Pan Am.
Guess it's a giveaway.
Oh, it's more than that.
The way you carry yourself.
Pan Am training... confidence,
leadership, and diplomacy,
all done with style
and poise.
Poise.
Anyway, I work Friday flights
so I can fit in classes here,
but I have to sacrifice
world lit.
Mm. Red slip.
I'll take care of it.
Don't you have more important
things you could be doing?
Welcome to world literature.
As I call your name,
respond not with "here"
but with the title of the one
book that you would request
if you we shipwrecked
on a desert island.
From that, I will extrapolate
and perhaps judge you.
Marnsdale.
"A farewell to arms."
Cheer up, Barnsdale.
Lareau.
"Tropic of cancer."
Well-played, Lareau. You're on
a desert island, after all.
Gibson.
Roxanne Gibson.
"The Great Gatsby."
Torn between the lunk
who opens your coconuts
and the man you left behind?
Oh, I'm not Daisy, sir.
I'm Gatsby.
Ah. In love with
what she can't have.
You do realize you end up shot
to death in your own pool?
Not before I throw
some truly fabulous parties
at my tree house, sir.
"Damn the torpedoes."
I like that.
I can't believe the texture.
You know genuine
when you feel it.
Come on. This way.
And this? I never thought
I could afford to replace Ted's.
How can that man make a profit
selling a Rolex so cheaply?
I'd say he got the "fell off a truck"
discount and passed it on thus.
Hurry up. Graham's waiting.
You mean they're damaged?
You didn't notice that nothing in
that stall was in its original box?
Wait. They're stolen?
I bought a stolen watch?
You want me to give
a stolen bag to my sister?
It's not like we stole them.
Maggie.
Well, if we hadn't bought them,
someone else would have.
Don't look guilty.
Uh, so I-I figured, uh,
right out of the gate
at the airport, go for it.
She worked for, um,
A-Aerolinhas...
Brasil...Eiras or something.
Isn't that a cargo carrier?
That was my opening line.
Oh, yeah. "Ola, senhorita.
I would like to show you
my very heavy cargo."
These Brazilian women...
They don't understand me.
It's pitiful. It's pitiful.
Captain Lowrey.
You're right, Ginny.
It is the good captain
and his merry crew.
Miss Saddler. Mr. Henson.
Good evening.
Mr. Henson,
good to see you, sir.
Good to see you, too,
Vanderwill.
Vanderway. Or Ted.
Whichever.
We thought you all might like
to join us for dinner.
If you haven't eaten.
We're all here, right?
Well, I-I'm afraid
you're going to have to make do
with the good captain
and miss Valois. I have, uh...
An assignation?
You know these
Brazilian girls.
One strike left
with the bases loaded.
Well, swing away,
by all means, Vanderwick.
Yeah.
This is swell. Shall we?
What if
they cut off our hands?
We're in Rio,
not Saudi Arabia,
and we didn't steal
anything.
Tell them that.
Tell them anything.
You haven't said a word
in our defense.
That's because there's
nothing to defend.
They don't know our purchases
fell off a truck.
Then why are we here?
For whatever reason
they come up with.
Loitering, probably.
Loitering? We were shopping.
We need to call Pan Am.
Pan Am?
Yes. Yes. Pan Am.
Hotel Intercontinental.
Maggie, he obviously wants
to clear things up.
He obviously wants a bribe.
Look, this happens.
They pull two girls
into the big, scary jail
in the hopes of getting
a payoff.
Well, it worked. I'm scared,
so let's pay them off.
We don't have enough on us,
and everybody we know
is out for the evening
so if we just keep
our mouths shut,
they'll let us go, okay?
I am supposed to meet
the photographer and Mr. Henson
first thing in the morning.
Go over there right now,
find out how much they want,
and then tell them we need to make
a long-distance call to New York.
Kate can wire the money.
I can't do that.
We...
Maggie, I don't want
to spend the night in j...
I mean, I actually
can't do that.
I don't speak Portuguese.
But... but that's one of your languages.
I've heard you speak it.
A few words.
I can tell officer Roberto
what a bad waitress he is,
if you think that'll help.
You're a fake.
It was the best of semesters.
It was the worst of semesters.
Yes, these grades are final.
No, you may not question them,
nor may you grovel.
No hysterics.
How about
dignified weeping?
Jane Austen would not approve.
But Jane Austen didn't
have to pull
three all-nighters
before finals.
I doubt miss Austen
would blanch
at a little academic critique.
Why then, I wonder,
did she write under a pseudonym?
Who in this class
would understand her motives
better than you, Roxanne?
You would have gotten an "A"
on the exam.
In fact, you did well
the whole term,
or rather...
Somebody did well.
It's my work.
And you are whom? Roxanne?
Susan? Marjorie?
Did you really think
you could keep this up,
sitting in on classes,
masquerading as other girls?
I was working
at the registrar's office.
People kept dropping
these wonderful classes.
All I did was pick them up.
You're not even enrolled.
You have any idea
how much trouble you're in?
Gatsby, indeed.
You're smart.
You're a hard worker,
well-possessed.
Make someone see that.
To Pan American world airways.
- Pan American.
LA meilleure compagnie aerienne
de tous Les temps.
Ooh. The best airline
that ever will be.
Mm. I didn't know
you spoke French.
Oh, gosh, no.
What did I say?
Almost exactly what I said.
But you notice the difference, though?
No accent.
That's why you're
a vice president.
And you, captain,
are an excellent pilot,
and there is nothing wrong
with that.
To captain Lowrey.
No, no, no, no, no.
To... to Air Force training.
"Yes, sir!
No, sir! Right away, sir!"
All that authority crap. I would
have put a gun in my mouth.
And yet you are authority.
Everywhere
but in the cockpit.
Ooh. I think
I've waited almost too long.
I'm going
to the lite girls' room.
I'll go with you.
First, where is
that waiter?
I'm going to get us
some more eau-de-vie.
That's French, right?
Oui.
- Be right back.
- Yeah.
I don't know how
you handle the travel.
Oh, you seem to travel
quite a lot.
I don't know how the hell
I handle it.
Well,
you know what they say.
Plenty of water.
No.
Plenty of Ginny.
Oh, don't play confused
on me now, captain.
I think we both know that Ginny is not my
secretary
I... sir...wh..what...
two people do on their own..
No, no, no. Don't call me "sir."
Call me Henson.
Ginny is
over-the-rainbow wacky.
And intoxicating.
Um, I-I wouldn't, uh...
She does
have a way about her.
Most men wouldn't understand
why I... I love her,
but you, captain,
I'm guessing you are
a man who does.
With this faith,
we will be able to transform
the jangling discords
of our nation
into a beautiful symphony
of brotherhood.
With this faith, we will be
able to work together,
to pray tog...
Excuse me.
We were watching that.
Brave man.
Reminds me of my cousin.
Men like that don't live
too long in my country.
It took a lot of years
to make that speech possible,
and even now...
Yeah, but still,
so many people came to listen.
Here in... in America,
there is... there is hope.
You don't have hope
for Yugoslavia?
It... it is static...
And worse, I'm static.
I thought
Tito was making changes.
Oh, changes, yeah,
but, uh, for the better?
Where's the music?
We need some music.
- You're choosing?
- Oh, I'm paying. You're choosing.
Something new,
for a new day.
Okay. "Roy Orbison.
The Beach Boys. The Chiffons."
Chime in.
You see anything you like?
"Walk like a man"?
Oh, yeah.
Frankie Valli & the 4 Seasons.
- Any good?
- It's really good.
Okay, before I invest my nickel,
you tell me how it goes.
I am not singing.
Pay your money
and take your chances.
Should I take you home?
It seems like something's
bothering you.
The people in that square...
They face great risk
for what is right.
They walk like men.
Niko, in my experience,
you know,
life changes every minute.
If there's something
you want to do,
it's never too late.
Dean.
Dean, it's me.
Dean, I'm so sorry.
It was such a stupid idea.
Dean.
This isn't necessary.
Necessary? You mean like
how fluency in Portuguese
is necessary for stewardesses
who claim to speak it?
You know, food must taste great
from a silver spoon...
Necessary, so you can, say,
serve drinks, offer directions,
or, I don't know,
talk your way
out of police precinct
in Rio de Janeiro?
Atencao.
Eu gostaria de telefonar
para os estados unidos.
Minha Irma vierma
LA e tem o dinheiro.
Dinheiro.
Thank you.
Nos gastariamos de pagar e...
Where's your photographer now?
Ted!
Oh, I'm just dying to know
how you ladies pulled
this one off.
Ah. There we go.
I never thought I'd be able
to afford to replace yours.
Oh, you didn't have
to do that.
You were so sweet to...
Okay, okay. Can you just
get us out of here?
Just be grateful I happened
to be striking out
at the hotel bar
when these gentlemen called up
asking to speak
to the Pan Am boss.
Suficiente?
Excuse me. Pan Am?
There you are.
I'm Maggie Ryan.
I'm sorry, miss Ryan.
The interviews
were from 3:00 to 6:00.
Oh, please! I-I came
all the way from Tacoma.
I'm afraid
we've found our girls.
Well, I would have made it
on time
if it weren't for the accident.
A logging truck...
The bindings came loose,
and timber
was raining from the sky,
and I had to stay
until the ambulances came.
You would be surprised
how few people know how
to staunch the flow of blood.
Well,
that's very impressive.
But as I'm sure you're aware,
the Pan Am stewardess is,
over all things...
Cultured.
I've had my heart
broken twice, mister...
Claymore.
Once by a boy named Chip
and once by a man named
F. Scott Fitzgerald.
And I wasn't even
an English major.
World history...
That's my passion.
My transcript, hot off
the presses of the Berkeley's
registrar's office.
I saw to it myself.
Well, you've got gumption,
miss Ryan.
And poise, Mr. Claymore...
That Pan Am poise.
I did a stint modeling
the latest fashions from Paris.
But the thing that irks me
about modeling...
What really riles me...
That it's all about the body
and nothing at all
to do with the brain.
I think women should be
acknowledged for their brain.
I-I see you took some Spanish.
Hmm.
Unfortunately, we have a surplus
of Spanish speakers.
Limpar a bagunca
na mesa nove?
- Catalan?
- Portuguese.
- You're fluent?
- Here's thing.
I've been training
my whole life for this job.
I know both elbow grease
and elocution.
But I think the most important
thing for a Pan Am stewardess
is that she be good company
for the journey
and a fast friend.
I'm sorry for that.
No, I hate to see you
this upset.
My cousin has been put
on a show trial.
You know what that is?
It's a favorite practice
of Tito's regime.
The defendant has little-to-no
opportunity to justify himself.
My cousin... he was forced to sign
a statement under duress.
He was tortured?
He'll be found guilty.
I must go to Belgrade
and do what I can.
But what about Zagreb
and your family?
It'll have to wait.
Niko, are you in danger?
Tito has put an entire nation
in danger.
"Chief architect"
of the "second Yugoslavia,"
and yet his dreams
are not for his people.
I must go and try
to help my cousin.
This might be the last time
I'll ever see him again.
Niko...
My mind is full of you,
too.
Maggie, those cops were lucky
ere wasn't a fork around.
Don't start in on me, okay?
I know. You warned me before,
and I didn't listen.
Whoa. That was me saying hi.
You girls did your time,
paid your debt to society.
Tell that
to the base manager.
I thought we kept him
out of this.
Not the one in Rio, Ted.
You mean New York?
You mean that base manager?
Ted...
I disagree with your politics,
your attitude toward women,
and, well...
You as a person in general,
but... you show up.
You come through,
and not everything does that,
so...
Thank you.
Maggie, what is going on?
Maggie?
Are you sure you don't need
a few more plane photos?
I have plenty.
I didn't mean to abandon you
at the beach, honest.
Well, even coco chanel only
stood me up for three hours.
You shot Coco Chanel?
Almost. She, uh, ran off
with an alligator bag.
I don't suppose
I could make it up to you.
I could make you a list.
I'll get you a pen.
Oh.
Sorry.
Mr. Henson,
can I offer you anything?
No, thank you. I'm fine.
Then maybe you can help me
with something.
If a girl
was to find herself
in a little bind
with the airline,
would you be in a position
to perhaps put in a good word?
I don't get involved in personal
issues, if that's what you mean.
It wasn't even
a serious infraction.
I can't help you. Sorry.
Well... thank you anyway.
Did Graham get all
the shots he needed?
I owe him some time
in New York.
Well, I'm sure
it'll be fine.
You'll be
the model stewardess.
Well, that's funny,
coming from you.
I already apologized.
In what language?
Portuguese?
I didn't hear anything
that sounded like an apology.
No one ever had
any expectations of me.
Never thought
I could get anywhere...
Not my family,
not my friends.
But for some reason, I did.
Even though I didn't know
where "anywhere" was
or how I would find it.
Yet here I am.
I made a new me.
I took a lot of shortcuts,
I told more than a few fibs.
Every time I got caught,
I moved on.
Each close call was
a stepping-stone
to something better.
But this time,
there is nothing better.
This is it.
I can't lose Pan Am.
Why would you lose it?
The truth is,
I admire you
more than you know.
And I'm sorry, Laura.
He was flying to Zagreb,
but he changed his plans.
Belgrade.
His cousin's on
"show trial" there.
Anything else?
He's not a communist.
They don't all carry cards,
you know.
He hates Tito,
admires Martin Luther King,
and he even likes
Frankie Valli & the 4 Seasons.
The part about Tito
is interesting.
He said that Tito's dreams
were not for his people.
Daring words
for a diplomat.
He must trust you.
He shouldn't.
Sounds like he's working
for the wrong people.
Is that what this is about?
You want him to spy for you?
For us.
You'll have
to tread lightly.
Turning a target into an asset
is about patience and control.
For now, just keep
building on that trust.
You want me to turn him?
Welcome to the big leagues.
Richard, no.
I'm a-a courier, remember?
I... this is...
I can't do this.
With the way Niko feels
about Tito,
how long do you think
he's going to last?
Dean.
Everett's inside.
It's fine.
Ginny, let's give this
a few days.
You were right.
Rio was...
I was the accident
waiting to happen.
And the dinner... I'm...
I'm sorry that I put you
through that.
I know you are, but...
But this is not the
time to talk about it.
I don't... I don't wanna
sneak around anymore.
Neither do I.
I don't... I don't wanna
pretend anymore.
I can't pretend anymore,
Dean.
Not when
I've fallen in love.
Margaret.
Margaret, before you go,
the base manager's
expecting you in his office.
- Already? Now?
- I'm sorry.
Margaret?
Now.
Okay, um, tell him
I'll be there in a minute.
Mr. Henson, I hate
to bother you again,
but if you would reconsider
helping me out...
I already told you,
I don't get involved in...
What if I returned
the favor?
Saving your job
is more than a favor.
What if I could tell you
something
about someone
you're very close to?
Miss Havemeyer.
Miss Ryan, I heard
you made a new friend
on your flight home
from Brazil.
I try to make friends
wherever I go.
I can only imagine.
Bem-vindo.
Como eu posso o ajudar?
Welcome. How can I help you?
Bem-vindo.
Como eu posso o ajudar?
Como eu posso...
Welcome. How can I help you?
Bem-vindo.
Como eu posso o ajudar?
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Is massive.
...Ls true.
Is stimulating.
...Ls helpful.
Volunteering...
Volunteering builds
a better community.