Previously on "Pan Am".
You're always disappearing
on me. Marry me.
I-I can't say "yes" now.
Bridget?
You and I finally make it
to Paris!
- Are you going my way?
- Sometimes the stars align.
I work
for the U.S. government.
A Pan Am stewardess
can travel all around the
world without suspicion.
They wanted you to deliver this
so that you would see
what happens
when you don't follow orders.
What are you doing?
Mind if I sit?
Uh, no, not at all.
The newsstand
at my station was out.
At least they had
"Popular Mechanics."
That's... good.
What's happening
in the world?
The... president is going
to Berlin.
Right, right. First visit
since the wall went up.
Have you ever been?
To Berlin? Oh, uh, sure.
I've... I've been a bunch of...
I'm going again soon.
There's
this good little bookshop
on Friedrichstrasse.
They sell first editions
of Nietzsche.
"The will to power,"
"der wille zur macht"...
Terrific read.
And that's where I start?
A map of Berlin
with the exact location.
Buy the book. Bring it home.
That's it?
Tell the clerk, "ich bin hier
um ein buch zu kaufen."
Ich bin ein...
Ich bin hier...
Ich bin hier um ein
buch... buch... buch zu kaufen.
Maybe work on that.
Oh. Here's your stop.
- Have a wonderful time.
- Congratulations.
Attention, please.
Pan Am flight 32
is now ready for boarding
at gate 11.
Flight 32 is now ready
for boarding...
Berlin?
Is it as beautiful
as it is in the pictures?
I can't wait to find out.
Arriving passengers
on flight 9 from Lisbon...
How have you flown
this whole time
and not gone to Germany?
It's a mystery.
That's right. You were pulled
into Japan last time.
Yes. I'm overdue,
but today is the day.
Good morning, Colette.
Good morning.
Here you go, sir.
Ready for Germany?
That's the rumor.
Are you preparing to toast
the president?
With anything but whiskey.
I'm laying off the stuff
for a while.
Are you?
Oh, yeah, and cigarettes.
I've been told
that they lead to dancing.
I'm surprised you remember.
I remember I had
a lot of whiskey...
And stepping on your foot.
But you seem to be walking okay,
so I guess, uh...
It was a moment, captain,
a nice moment,
but that was all.
You've never done
a press charter?
I've never done
a charter, period.
You just gotta keep the drinks flowing...
Keep their cigarettes lit,
and you'll be fine.
That's very helpful.
Thank you, captain.
I do what I can.
But he's right.
Journalists can be
seasoned travelers,
and seasoned travelers
can be particular.
They need food they can eat
with one hand,
and they expect to be treated
as though their work is
the most important work
in the world.
You girls gossiping
about the pilots again?
Journalists.
Oh, right. I blame them
for our 24-hour layover.
Oh, that's just enough time
for Kennedy
to speechify a little,
give the wall a good kick.
Farm boy, I pegged you
as a Nixon supporter.
Eh, they're all the same.
How fashionably cynical of you.
Oh, is he knocking
the wall over?
No, he's going
to kiss it.
Kennedy loves the wall.
He loves communists.
He loves their cigars.
We have that in common.
That's all you know
about him, isn't it?
Yeah,
what do you know about him?
Maggie was a precinct captain
for his campaign.
Oh, so you've met him?
No, but I'm going to.
You're gonna meet Kennedy?
- That's right.
- When?
Tomorrow in Berlin.
Good luck with that.
Journalists.
You think one of them might
know the president?
A paper, sir?
Can I get you anything else
to drink, Mr. Manchester?
No, but you can take
this away.
Too salty for my taste.
A simple pastry will do.
Uh...
When you get a chance,
I'd love your autograph.
You are aware that
I'm not a movie star
or a baseball player?
I've met them.
What they have to say
would not fill a column inch
in the newspaper of record.
May I have my pastry now?
Pastry on the way.
I thought you could use
another pillow.
I'm sorry. What?
Oh, you're all hunched over.
Oh. Thanks.
My pleasure.
I'm sorry.
Do you happen to write
for the "Village Voice"?
I do.
Mike Ruskin.
I recognize your picture
from the column.
What's a Pan Am stewardess doing
reading the "Voice of Bohemia"?
Oh, what should I be reading,
the "Ladies' home journal"?
Oh, th...
I'm Maggie.
Pleasure to meet you,
Maggie.
So I take it you're covering
Kennedy's speech?
Yeah, the "voice" thought
it would be worth the dough
to send me in person...
Context, atmosphere,
actual reporting.
Well, most everything is better
in person, don't you think?
I do think.
Uh, are you going?
Dying to, if I could get
a good seat.
Oh. Right.
Um, look,
I-I wish I could sneak you
into the press section,
but, uh...
Oh, no, no.
How could you?
But if you're looking
for atmosphere,
you should let
me and my girlfriends
show you around Berlin.
Ich bin hier
um ein buch zu kaufen.
Ich bin hier um ein buch
zu kaufen.
Zu... zu... zu kauf...
You've come to buy a book?
You speak German.
Here's a tip.
The more you sound like
a barking dog,
the more
they'll understand you.
Do you need a landing card?
Ah. Yes.
Pen?
I understand the communists
are hanging red banners
on the Brandenburg Gate.
God forbid they allow us
a peek at east Germany.
That seems a little paranoid.
Welcome to Germany.
- Welcome to Germany.
- Thank you very much.
Welcome to Germany.
Thank you for flying Pan Am.
Don't make any plans
for tomorrow morning.
We have a date
on the Kurfurstendamm.
What's that?
I have no idea,
but my new friend Mike
wants to go.
It's like
the Madison Avenue of Berlin.
You want to come?
Oh, I would love to,
but... I'm... I'm meeting
a friend of my own.
Oh, okay.
Well, then do you want to meet
up for the president's speech?
Absolutely. It's a date.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Thanks.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Thank you.
You sure?
No.
I owe you an apology.
I didn't mean
to embarrass you.
Well, what...
What are they gonna do?
Are they gonna kick us out
of the country?
We're leaving.
It was a terrible mistake.
What,
the party or the singing?
Coming to Berlin...
At all.
It looks like somebody had
a little too much fun in Berlin.
Uh, veni, vidi, vici.
Well, I came, and I saw.
I definitely didn't conquer.
And no one feels sorry
for you.
It wasn't pity
I was looking for.
No kidding.
I'm just gonna go fly
the plane now.
Where is Maggie?
Oh, she's not gonna make it.
What do you mean,
she's not gonna make it?
Is she all right?
Yes. N-no. No.
She's s-sick.
A stomach problem.
I mean, a headache.
But I saw her in the concourse
ten minutes ago.
Right, well,
she ate something bad,
and it just... it hit her.
Bratwurst, I think.
I thought you said
she had a headache.
Okay, I don't understand.
Where is Maggie right now?
Today...
In the world of freedom...
The proudest boast is,
"Ich bin ein Berliner."
Flight time to New York
tonight will be just under
seven hours.
Still, I hope you enjoyed
your time in Berlin,
and I don't mind speaking
for myself
and our entire flight crew,
when I say that this was
quite a day for us.
That will be one
for the history books.
What?
You're voting for Kennedy
in '64, aren't you?
I'm going to kill Maggie.
Time for us to start
watering down drinks.
And plan on how
we are going to kill Maggie.
Are you girls having
a party back here?
We're a stewardess short
on a plane
full of drunk journalists.
Oh, Maggie stuck it to me, too.
She stole my cigars.
You know how I like to stock
up on Cubans in Berlin.
"Ich bin ein Berliner."
See? Right there.
He said, "I'm a Berliner."
No, in German a Berliner is
a jelly doughnut.
He did not say,
"I am a jelly doughnut."
Check
your German dictionary.
Hey, before you go,
I just gotta ask.
What?
Did Maggie pull it off?
It's like the 4th of July.
On another planet.
This is another planet.
"Deutschland Uber Alles."
"The edge
of a new frontier."
Oh, you're quoting him now?
Who?
Kennedy. What...
You're in love with him,
aren't you?
Ask what you can do
for your country.
Uh, I know what I can't do...
Get you seats
in the press section.
What if I slip you into
first class on the way home?
Can we do that?
Extra roast beef,
unlimited liquor.
Come on, Michael.
What's it gonna take?
Besides that.
It's Mike,
a-and you're not press.
Who cares?
Just say that I am.
I'll help you
with your article.
The new frontier?
Hopes and dreams in the "Village Voice"?
Well, what do you need,
the smart, countercultural,
antiestablishment take?
Smart would help.
So Kennedy will come to Berlin
to make a speech, sure,
but it's not like
he's knocking down the wall.
Wait. Maggie, you don't
really think that.
No, but his readers might,
and it's not like
you can go wrong
telling people exactly
what they want to hear.
Ah, so you're a politician now?
I'm whatever I need to be.
The line about
knocking it over...
I could maybe use that.
Sind sie die amerikanerin?
Pardon?
Sind sie hier
um das buch zu kaufen?
Uh, ich bin hier
u-um ein...
No, I-I'm here to buy
a book.
Los, steig ein!
What? N-no.
"Der wille zur macht,"
Nietzsche.
- I have it, okay?
- I have your book.
Get in the car.
Schnell! Steig ins auto!
Wait.
I was supposed
to buy this book
in the... I-in the store.
I know.
I couldn't make the drop.
What happened?
STASI, the secret police...
They infiltrated my network.
The STASI are
in West Berlin?
They were just at our hostel.
They know who I am.
Then they know your car.
Pull over.
Uh, wait. Wait, wait.
What are you doing?
Come back!
Come on!
Now what?
Where do we go?
You're asking me?
You're CIA, right?
No. No. Y-yes.
I mean, I'm just...
I was just supposed
to buy this book
and bring it back
to New York.
I'm a courier.
So am I.
I'm just a translator.
I crossed the border
with an east German journalist
for this speech.
This is
my third assignment.
This is my second.
We have to keep moving.
I can't go back.
If they find me,
they'll kill me.
Okay, you get out of town...
Uh, a bus, a train.
And go where?
Berlin is surrounded by east Germany.
Uh... uh, the embassy.
We can get you
to the U.S. embassy.
There is no embassy!
Oh, no, no, no.
I mean, uh, the mission.
You... you go
to the U.S. mission.
You go there.
- You can defect.
- Your president is here.
No east German will get past security.
That's them,
the secret police.
Ohh.
I don't know what to do.
Why didn't you keep
the taxi you came in?
What? There are no taxis.
I had to walk.
There will be a bus here
in, like, five minutes.
How many people are going
to this speech?
Um, some random number
between 100,000 and a million.
Is that your expert opinion?
Crowd counts
are meaningless.
Tell you what. You pick
the number. I'll print it.
100,002.
I'm not very ambitious.
Uh-huh.
Oh, before I forget...
Ohh. Thank you.
It's my pleasure,
Maggie, really,
but I didn't have a choice,
did I?
Of course you did, Michael.
What's that?
That's
the president's itinerary.
Do you have one?
Uh, "Village Voice,"
remember?
Hey.
Hi there.
Did you just pickpocket me?
- No.
- Yes.
Artful Dodger,
meet George Manchester.
Oh, we've already met.
Maggie Ryan
from your flight over.
The stewardess.
Maggie's a little obsessed
with the president.
Well, there's a party
for him at the U.S. mission.
Need a date?
Hey, I just got you
a press pass.
It's invitation only.
Maybe if I bring
a couple girls,
like getting into a nightclub
in the city?
That would work?
There are certain things
about Kennedy...
That are not to be shared
with the civilian population.
Oh, come on.
The other girls...
Would they be stewardesses?
Smuggling an asset...
That's a bit above your
pay grade now, isn't it?
Her cover has been blown.
She has no other options.
She needs to defect.
She wants to defect.
17 million east Germans
want to defect.
That's what the wall is for.
Yeah,
but she works for our side.
As a low-level courier.
I am a low-level courier.
We're not going to risk
our entire east German operation
for someone
who can be replaced
by a 15-year-old
with a bicycle.
Is that
what you think of me?
Let it go, miss Cameron.
She could be killed.
That's not your problem.
What did he say?
He's working on something.
- Hey there.
- Hey, captain.
Have you been outside yet?
It's a madhouse.
That's a fancy envelope.
Well, it's a fancy party.
Gotta do the old grip and grin
at the U.S. mission...
You know, butter up some
German government officials,
so Pan Am can expand
their Berlin hub.
I'll never understand
why rich folk love to make
small talk with people
they're never gonna meet again.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to offend.
No, no. You didn't.
Your ancestors probably
danced at Versailles.
No.
Come on. What were they?
- No.
- Barons, counts, dukes?
- No. I don't know.
- Or just... so you're the...
You're the great-great-great
granddaughter of Louis the...
No, no.
I didn't have any family.
None?
So how old were you
when the Nazis occupied
France?
I was 3.
But I don't think about it
most of the time.
Everyone lost people.
We were all the same.
I wasn't a special case.
Kate, are you there?
We have to leave now,
if we want to see the speech.
Laura, I'm sorry.
Uh, you're gonna have
to go without me.
What? Why?
Would you...
Yeah, just hold on a second.
You should go.
Hello.
Isn't it time to leave?
Colette.
You should go.
No, I'm staying with you.
Is Laura with you?
No. Go, or they'll know
something's wrong.
Kate?
Uh... yes.
We're coming right down.
Okay, um, you wait here,
and I will be back as soon
as I can.
What kind of something?
Kate?
Laura, I'm...
I'm coming now.
I'm sorry. What?
What kind of something are
they working on?
Um, I don't know.
He didn't say.
Did they teach you to lie?
'Cause you're not very good
at it.
Um, I-I think they went
this way!
We have to stay together,
or we'll lose each other!
Whoa.
This is nuts.
Which way should we go?
All I can see are shirts!
Ted, do you think all
the streets are this way?
Ted, what are you doing?
Scouting.
You look like gene Kelly!
Good thing it's not raining!
Good thing he's not singing.
Do you want the bad news
or the bad news?
Sind sie amerikaner?
- What?
- Amerikaner?
Oh, yes. We're Americans.
Wir lieben euch.
Wir lieben die amerikaner.
Kennedy!
Danke. Danke.
Wollen sie ihn siehen?
Uh...
Uh, konnen sie uns helfen?
Ich bringe sie hin.
Oh.
Kommen. Kommen.
Ted, look! Come on, let's go!
Ted, get down from there!
Oh.
Ted, let's go!
All right!
Kommen sie.
Eine bessere auf sicht...
Oh.
Kommen sie. So sicht.
Kommen sie.
I am proud to come to this city
as the guest
of your distinguished mayor
who has...
Oh, he started. He started!
There are many people
in the world...
Kate! Kate!
Colette!
I'll meet you up there!
Or say they don't...
Kate!
What is the great issue
between the free world
and the communist world.
Let them come to Berlin.
No, no, no!
Okay!
Aah!
Not gonna lose you now.
Today in the world
of freedom...
Kommen sie. Schnell.
The proudest boast is...
Kommen sie. Kommen sie.
Schnell. Ohh.
"Ich bin ein Berliner."
Kommen sie. Schnell.
Kommen sie.
Hier. Kommen sie. Hier.
Schnell, schnell, schnell.
Thank you.
Freedom has many difficulties,
and democracy is not perfect,
but we have never had
to put a wall up
to keep our people in,
to prevent them
from leaving us.
Though a city
that has been besieged
for 18 years
that still lives
with the vitality and the force
and the hope
and the determination
of the city of West Berlin.
While the wall
is the most obvious
and vivid demonstration
of the failures
of the communist system
for all the world to see,
we take no satisfaction in it,
for it is an offense
not only against history,
but an offense
against humanity...
Separating families,
dividing husbands and wives
and brothers and sisters,
and dividing a people who wish
to be joined together.
Kate!
Where is everyone?
I don't know.
When are they getting bac?
I don't know!
Will you stand still
a second?
What do you want?
We're going to a party
for Kennedy.
Ohh. Why?
Because he's the president!
I just want
to shake his hand.
It's at the U.S. embassy.
The mission.
Kennedy loves stewardesses.
I figure,
if we go as a group,
we have a pretty good chance
of getting in.
Uh, we fly out tonight.
Uh, we should all go
in our uniforms.
What? No!
I'm not wearing my work clothes
to meet Jack Kennedy.
You said that
he likes stewardesses.
No, this is my plan.
You are not going to...
Maggie, he likes stewardesses.
Let's show him stewardesses.
We're Pan Am,
and who can turn down
Pan Am?
See if you can convince
the others.
Anke.
I found someone who will
smuggle me across the border.
Uh, does he have papers for you,
uh, forged identification?
I'll be hiding in his trunk.
- No.
- I can't stay here.
That's a terrible plan.
I have no choice.
Yes, you do.
I can get you out.
How?
Perfect.
Wow. We really are alike.
I don't know
if this will work.
There's only one way
to find out.
Let's take her
for a test spin.
Kate.
Oh, hello.
Is this the friend
you were visiting?
Uh, y-yes.
This is Greta Mueller,
out of the Berlin hub.
Uh, Greta,
this is my sister Laura
and our friend Colette.
A pleasure.
Arriving or departing?
Uh. . Athens. Later.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh, guess what?
Maggie's bringing us
to a party for Kennedy
at the U.S. mission.
Tell Colette
that she has to come.
You have to come.
You loved his speech.
I did?
Well, I-I saw you crying
while listening to it.
No, I wanted to catch a nap
before we fly out.
A nap?
This is history... the time we met
the president in Berlin?
He's not my president.
The truth is,
is we need you.
The bigger the group,
the better chance we have
of getting in.
You're all going?
Yes. Oh, and Maggie wants us
to wear our uniforms.
Oh, uh, I think
the dry cleaning ate mine.
Oh, no.
Do you have a spare jacket?
How did the hotel lose
your shoes, too?
I just left them outside
my door for a shine.
So much
for German efficiency.
All right.
They're checking guests
at the door.
Put on
your best Pan Am, girls.
Excuse us. Sorry.
Entschuldigen sie.
Okay, as soon as you get in,
wel l find you a case officer
or a state department official.
But remember, you're having fun, so...
smile.
Sorry we kept you waiting.
The crowds...
Worse than New York.
We're here
as representatives
of Juan trippe
and the airline, Pan Am.
Name?
P-a-n-a-m.
Stewardesses.
How did you make it past
the front gate?
"Ich bin ein Berliner,"
right?
Excuse me.
So did you grow up
here in Berlin?
- Mm.
- Oh.
Have you been
to this building before?
Mm-hmm. My Uncle used
to deliver bread here,
before they divided Berlin.
I came with him sometimes.
What was it then?
It's the headquarters
for the German Luftwaffe,
uh, Air Force.
So... do you know
if there's a side door
or a back entrance
or something?
What did your parents do
during the war?
What do you mean?
Are they okay?
Did they survive?
Yes.
How?
What did they do?
Colette.
We don't like to talk
about the war.
But you delivered bread here,
to the Luftwaffe.
We had a family bakery,
that's all.
That delivered bread
to the Nazis.
Colette.
There's Dean. Dean!
- Over here!
- Hey, girls.
We're with him.
Dean! We came to meet you.
I'm sorry about that.
George Manchester.
He knows everyone
and hates communists.
I can't do this part
with you,
but tell him that you're
an east German asset
who needs protection,
and he can get you
to the right people.
I'm shaking.
You have gotten this far.
Thank you.
Go.
Anke.
Smile.
Dean, have you seen
the president?
Uh, I only got
a brief glimpse.
Where is he?
He's come and gone.
Apparently he had
a whole circuit lined up.
What?!
I'm sure he would have
loved to meet you,
but he's got a lot going on.
Well, when did he leave?
Just now.
Like, a minute ago.
Which way did he go?
Maggie,
I'm not in charge here.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
- You can't go out this way!
- Hold these!
Stop!
New friends or old friends?
Yeah, Colette,
this... this is, uh, Otto...
Rontegen...
The German Aviation Authority.
And, uh, Peter Newberry...
U.S. State Department.
Ah, the international
Pan Am stewardess.
That is me.
Guten tag.
Guten abend.
Didn't you say you were
flying out tonight?
Oh, it's a special occasion.
A glass of champagne's not gonna hurt.
Uh... no.
Ah.
It's a very special occasion.
Noch einen, bitte.
Ich muss
meinen kummer ertranken.
You speak German very well.
I was forced to learn
when I was a child.
But that is water
under the bridge,
now that the Germans
and Americans are best friends.
We do share a common enemy.
Mm.
Convenient, is it not?
That's politics, right?
Politics?
No, it's a miracle.
One clever speech
by your president,
and the whole nation is
instantly absolved.
Excuse us, gentlemen.
We, uh, need to prep
for our flight.
I'm sorry.
Did I spoil your party?
I meant, congratulations.
I'm sorry.
Let me make it up to you.
I thought I was clear
on the phone.
You were.
I just didn't agree.
Well, it's not your place
to disagree.
You do what you're told.
So you're saying
to just follow orders?
Yes.
You're actually saying
that here?
This is how wars are won.
Do you have any idea how many
people have risked their lives,
so that you could carry
that book?
I know that she did,
and I know that
she was going to be killed
for trying to help us.
How do you know
she wasn't lying?
She wasn't.
Mm.
I just heard my president
promise the 2 million people
in this city that
we wouldn't abandon them.
You brought an East German spy
to an American consulate
in your uniform.
I know what I did,
and I take
full responsibility for...
Miss Cameron, you have
no idea what you've done,
nor what it takes to keep
a cold war cold.
- You should be proud.
- You got so close.
- Close is nothing.
- Close is meaningless.
You got into the press section.
You got into the mission.
You can tell the boys that.
I don't care
what the pilots think.
That's not why I...
What is that?
That... is "Air Force One."
It's still here.
He's still here!
Ohh!
What are you doing?
Cover for me.
I'm not gonna make our flight.
What?
I'm gonna meet him
right here, right now.
Wait!
What do I tell everyone?
Make something up!
Something German!
Wait! Have you seen Ted?
Where's Ted?
Why?
He has something I need.
You're not on this flight.
What are you doing here,
miss?
My name is Maggie Ryan.
I worked
on Kennedy's campaign.
I logged more hours
than any other volunteer,
and as a reward,
I was supposed to meet him,
but I took a bathroom break
when the deputy field director
came for two minutes,
and suddenly Marcia Phillips
was going instead of me
even though she only did
half the hours I did.
I just...
I just wanna thank him
for making me realize that each
of us can make a difference.
I just wanna shake his hand.
Well, you've certainly got
a lot of enthusiasm.
Thank you.
But you haven't been vetted.
I'm a Pan Am stewardess.
They vetted me!
I got him cigars!
Cubans!
His favorite.
What?
Cubans... his favorite.
Tell me your name again.
Maggie Ryan.
Okay.
Wait here.
Cigars for the president.
She wants to give them...
Welcome to New York.
- Thank you for flying Pan Am.
- Thank you.
Can't beat that humidity.
Berlin not as entertaining
as you thought it would be?
I took a shot.
Can you blame me?
I mean, look at you.
Let me take you to breakfast
and apologize.
Good night, Mr. Vanderway.
Yeah.
Yeah, good night.
You know...
You're different
from other girls.
Thank you.
Hi.
You wanna share a cab home?
Oh, I have a couple things
to wrap up at operations.
Is it okay if I meet you there?
Sure.
When the Nazis took over,
my parents made plans
to flee.
They dropped me off
with a neighbor
and promised
they'd come back to get me.
But they never did.
Never could.
And the people who brought us
into the apartment
were so warm...
And magnanimous.
Your president tried so hard
to lift their shame.
But they should feel shame.
I came to Germany to forgive.
But I still hate them.
And I don't know how to stop.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
forr www.addic7ed.com