Previously on "Pan Am"...
Do you not wanna get married?
You need to decide,
because this is your life.
I wanna see the world.
I'll become
a Pan Am stewardess.
"Upon boarding,
passengers are greeted
"by the international
beauty and Grace
known as the Pan Am stewardess."
- Are you wearing your girdle?
- Yes, ma'am.
Oh.
Pan Am
flight 292 is now boarding.
I didn't know you'd be
on this flight.
What a coincidence.
I didn't know you were married.
Should we spike his
food or his drink?
Both.
I work for the U.S. government...
Intelligence.
You fit
the profile perfectly...
Beautiful, well educated.
The Pan Am stewardess can
travel all around the world
without suspicion.
And I have the perfect cover.
- Marry me!
- I can't say "yes" now.
Bridget.
Bridget arranged
that meeting in Rome.
She had an eye for talent.
"Had"?
Am I her replacement?
Hello, miss.
Couldn't help but notice
your predicament.
Unfortunate, no?
Are you going my way?
Ah, it depends.
Where you going?
Me? Paris.
You've gotta be kidding me.
I'm going to Paris.
You don't say.
Sometimes the stars align.
Say, I could give you
a lift...
Oh.
But I'll have to warn ya.
You'll have
to cook my dinner,
bring me coffee,
make occasional small talk.
Some steep demands.
It's a long walk to Paris.
Fine. On one small condition.
- I swear, just another minute.
- Laura!
I couldn't find my blue shawl.
Did you pick it up from home?
I don't know. I couldn't see
through all the smoke.
Smoke?
Yes,
mother was breathing fire.
- Right.
- What, are you moving to Paris?
Well, I wanted to have plenty
of room to bring things home.
And you couldn't find
your steamer trunk?
Oh, I almost forgot.
I have something for you.
Can't it wait?
No, it'll only take a second.
Here.
What is it?
Remember this?
We did it.
We're really going, together.
How did you get this
out of your room?
Did you call daddy?
And risk mother finding out?
No way.
I had Maria send it.
Wow.
It's a sad day when your maid's
more accepting than your mother.
But it's not a sad day.
It's the best day
in a long time...
The day you and I
finally make it to Paris!
You have to stay
on the right side of the road.
I'm French, not English.
I'm fairly confident
this is a bad idea.
Oh, come on.
What are you afraid of?
Where do I start?
No, before we do this,
do you have any questions?
Only one.
How fast does it go?
That's the wrong question.
We had a deal!
Thank you.
You have your license on you,
right?
What license?
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Did you know
there are 2,000 windows
in the palace at Versailles?
Maybe you shouldn't
read and walk at the same time.
Ooh, pardon.
And over 2,000 acres
of formal garden.
No kidding.
Laura, there you are.
In body.
Her mind is elsewhere.
I'm cramming for Paris.
Go ahead. Quiz me.
Uh, height
of the Eiffel Tower.
324 meters.
Built by...
Gustave Eiffel.
Well, that oughta come in handy.
Colette!
Thank you again.
I'd like to say "anytime,"
but... no.
- Bye.
- I'll see you soon.
I salute you, captain.
Oh, not now, Sanjeev.
Very impressed.
Sanjeev?
Back on the horse.
No, I'm not back
on the horse.
Understood.
Mmm, the pain au chocolat
at fauchon patisserie
near Madeleine.
Definitely amazing,
but not the best.
What's the best?
A la mere de famille,
en montmartre.
Les orangettes enrobees
de chocolat.
I wanna try everything.
You'd be advised to limit
yourself to one, miss Cameron.
You've gained
another pound.
Do we need to revisit
your personal weight limit?
Oh.
No, miss Havemeyer.
Attention, passengers...
Miss Cameron,
you have a call.
Redheaded Cameron.
Pay phone. Your father.
Daddy?
Okay.
I'll see you on board.
You're next, miss Ryan.
Oh, please. After you.
Pardon me?
Well, I think
we'd all like to know
what you're weighing in at
these days.
I assume that
if there's an ideal weight
for serving drinks, then surely
there's an ideal weight
for looking down one's nose.
- Maggie, it's okay.
- No, go on, please.
I'll be gentle.
Don't believe a word
she says, Mrs. Havemeyer.
Maggie promised
to be gentle with me,
and I assure you,
it's a bald-faced lie.
I'm sorry you had to witness
miss Ryan's insubordination,
Mr. Vanderway.
And I'm sorry
that I have to steal
this insubordinate stewardesses
away. They're late.
Or I can let operations know
that there was a delay.
No delay. Miss Ryan and I
can continue our conversation
with her supervisor
upon her return.
Oh, thank you so much.
Daddy?
Not exactly.
Richard.
I'm glad you're here.
I need answers
about Bridget.
Your predecessor
isn't your concern.
A stewardess
can't just disappear.
Quitting is one thing.
Vanishing is another.
All of Pan Am is buzzing.
Pan Am is buzzing,
or you're wondering?
- Both.
- Take this.
Keep it in your purse.
Do not open it.
This isn't another test,
is it?
Your contact will find you
in Paris
and identify himself using
the hour-of-the-day exchange.
You remember it?
Hour-of-the-day exchange.
Yes.
Uh, they ask for the time,
I give it in hours.
They repeat it back wrong,
I correct them.
They thank me,
and I give them the package.
What time is it?
1800 hours.
Ah, that's 7:00, right?
You're supposed to
correct me.
I'm sorry.
Uh, 1800 hours is 6:00, sir.
Give me the box back.
No. I mean,
I can handle this.
If you can't remember
your basic training...
I can handle this. I just
need to go now. I'm late.
Au revoir.
Thank you.
- Where have you been?
- Where's the manifest?
There you are.
No, no, no.
Oh, God.
Kate, what is it?
It's mother.
Mother?
Is something wrong?
Yes.
She's on the plane.
You're not
the least bit curious?
No.
Not a tiny bit curious?
She disappeared.
- Nope.
- 'Cause if a guy's not on a new horse,
chances are he's still thinking
about the old one.
And you, Sanjeev,
know how to beat a dead horse.
3-minute pee.
He's still on Bridget?
I'm just saying, I'd be curious.
- I'm not.
- Good man.
In case you do get curious,
let me tell you something.
When it comes to women...
Listen up, folks.
Sanjeev's sharing pearls.
Yeah, I'm taking notes.
There's always a friend
who knows. Always.
So if a dame left you
without word...
No "it was fun,"
no "we'll always have Paris,"
you'd go searching for her?
I didn't say that. Hell, no.
There you go.
That is, unless...
She was the love of my life.
What kind of name
is "Metropolitans," anyway,
for a brand-new ball club?
Stengel didn't do too bad
for your boys in the Bronx.
Until he went senile.
- Dinner already?
- Well, a deal is a deal.
And who benches Whitey Ford
until game...
Three? What deal?
Now what do we have here?
Oh, evening flights have
their advantages.
I think I'm looking at one.
Oh!
Prosciutto, pate,
escargot?
You've already got
my attention.
Serve me an aphrodisiac,
I might just fall in love.
It has been known to happen.
Careful. I'm a glutton.
Oh, I noticed.
- I have no idea.
- She hasn't spoken to me since I left.
Then what
is she doing here?
Are you two still hiding?
Daddy didn't tell you?
Daddy?
He just called you
on the pay phone.
Oh, uh, yes, he needed me
to buy him some...
French cheese.
Cheese?
Mom's on her way to kill me,
and he wants cheese?
You know,
as Pan Am employees,
you can have your parents
fly for free.
We are not
telling her that.
- No.
- She's that bad?
She should have saved the fare
and flown her broomstick.
Well, one of you is gonna
have to face her.
Colette's by herself
in economy.
Two out of three.
No.
Kate, please.
I can't do it.
What else is new?
Order up here.
Did daddy yell?
No. He calmly threatened
to call the state troopers
and report his car stolen
if we didn't turn around
and come home.
- And mother?
- Indisposed, apparently.
Oh, God.
What have I done?
You were honest with yourself,
and you stood up
and claimed a stake
in your own life.
I didn't stand up.
I ran away from my own wedding.
Can you imagine a look
on Greg's face?
Would you rather be
at a reception right now,
feeling trapped
and forcing a smile?
All right, then.
Let's order some pie.
They're gonna disown me.
Okay, let's get
something straight right now.
I am the black sheep
of the family.
Today is hard to beat.
You forget that I drove
the getaway car.
I robbed the bank.
And I told mother
that I hypnotized you.
See?
You know, she might actually
believe that.
Yes.
You had to think about
it, didn't you? No.
Mm-hmm.
No.
Well, at least you
didn't walk away empty-handed.
What do you think it is?
A toaster, I hope.
Well, we can't keep it.
- Why not?
- Mother.
I think that ship
has sailed...
No. Mother... she's here.
Quick! Hide! Oh.
Oh, God.
What are you doing?
Hide! Laura, she's
already seen the car.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Stay here.
Get her in my car!
No, mother!
Kate, I was starting
to get worried
I was on the wrong plane.
Hello, mother.
What's bringing you to Paris?
I thought you said her name
was Laura.
This is my other daughter,
Catherine.
You have two daughters
who are Pan Am stewardesses?
I suppose I'm blessed.
Oh, yes. I see the resemblance
to her sister.
- Laura's been back here?
- No, dear.
The "Life" magazine.
You brought your own copy.
What does she want?
- She didn't say.
- It's not a coincidence.
Are you insane?
She needs
new reading material.
The Life" magazine
she's been waving around
is over a month old.
Oh, no.
Oh, yes.
And she's all yours.
Hello, Mr. Elkins.
You've learned my name.
It's my job to know the names
of everyone in first class.
Really?
Do you know that
my favorite color is blue?
I believe
the lavatory's open.
I'm not here
for the lavatory.
Then can I help you
with something?
I might need
a cigarette later.
Of course.
I'll bring one to your seat.
I like the way that uniform
leaves just enough
to the imagination.
I imagine
you'd be much more comfortable
in your seat.
Not interested in comfort.
Aah!
I am not included
in the price of your ticket.
There you are, and with
my favorite drink, I see.
Sorry it took me so long
to get back here.
I was... up to my ears
in roast beef.
It's all right.
You're here now.
Only for a moment, actually.
I... there are things I'm
supposed to... have a seat.
Okay. Um...
I... yeah,
I suppose things can wait.
If you're gonna tell me
what a terrible daughter I am,
I wish you'd just go ahead
and do it.
What?
I know how angry
you and daddy are,
and... I'm sure
you're mortified
by what Mrs. Metcalf
and those other D.A.R. gossips
must be saying, but I just...
I miss you.
But then why haven't
you called?
I... I sent you a letter,
and you never called, not once.
I suppose I was hoping
you'd come home,
that you would need me,
but...
I was clearly wrong.
I do need you.
I need you so much.
Well... that makes me
very happy.
And as for Mrs. Metcalf
and the D.A.R. ladies...
This handled things
quite nicely.
I'm the new belle of the ball.
Really?
How much had he had
to drink?
Does that matter?
We need to report him.
Well, I can't
exactly do that.
Why not?
I sort of... stabbed him
with a serving fork.
You stabbed him?
You did what?
Shh!
Maggie was accosted
by a passenger.
And you stabbed him?
It was more of a poke
than a stab.
Is that him?
What is he doing?
Having second thoughts
about molesting stewardesses?
- I need a band-aid.
- Hold on, sir.
We have to take care
of him, or he'll report you.
Yeah, and after inviting
miss Havemeyer onto the scale...
Okay,
I'll get the first aid kit.
The first aid kit?
What for?
Someone's bruised ego.
Can I help you?
Um, since the plane
isn't full,
I was wondering if I could
move my mother to first class.
- Sure.
- Absolutely not.
I'm gonna let you two
sort this one out.
First class?
You're the one who sent me
back there.
Yeah, scared to death.
Now you're upgrading her?
Can we get you
anything else, sir?
A tourniquet, maybe?
Am I missing something?
Besides the fact that mother
is a master manipulator?
Kate.
Evening, girls.
Captain.
Air sick.
Could be a while.
I think the, uh,
economy lavatory is free.
- That's okay.
- I'll wait.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Everything okay back here?
Absolutely. Right as rain.
Surprised you haven't
asked to take the helm yet.
Oh, the night is young.
I hear you've had
a rough evening.
Not very friendly, is he?
No.
Do you have big plans
for Paris?
Little ones.
Wander the streets,
take in the sights,
the smell.
The smell?
Yeah. Smells like home.
What about you?
Big plans?
I was thinking of looking up
a friend I met at a club once.
I don't remember it
having a smell.
Oh, no, with clubs,
it's more about the sound.
You've been practicing
at home.
With my pillow,
but she's all left feet.
Bridget! Ca va?
Gaspar!
Quel plaisir de vous voir.
Ah, Dean, this is Gaspar,
an old friend.
Gaspar, c'est mon
petit ami, Dean.
- Ah.
- It's nice to meet you.
Tout le plaisir
est pour Moi.
Merci.
Shame he had to kiss
and run.
He's bringing us champagne,
darling.
Mm,
friends in high places.
C'est un tres bon ami.
I'm sorry.
You're English, yes?
Is my French accent
that terrible?
On the contrary.
You're just that beautiful.
Hey, slow down there, buddy.
With all due respect,
of course.
Of course.
Would you happen
to have the time?
I'm afraid my French
is bloody awful.
It's 2230.
Half past 11:00?
10:00.
Of course.
Never was good
at military time.
Enjoy your evening.
You're a lucky man.
You know, I haven't heard that
since my boxing days.
What?
- Boxing?
- Well...
- 2230.
- What are you, a general?
No. Right now I'm a girl in
need of the powder room,
and I shall leave you
in the capable hands
of monsieur Gaspar.
Bridget, you can't,
because I can't speak... French.
Monsieur, je vous sers?
Ou bien preferez attendre?
Uh, yeah, it looks great.
Thank you. Merci.
That's good. Thanks.
Monsieur, vous-n'etes pas
satisfait de ce choix...
- Excuse me.
- Monsieur!
Hey! Excuse me.
- Hey!
- Monsieur!
- You okay?
- What the hell did he say to you?
- Nothing.
N-nothing happened.
Wait here. I'll be right back.
Dean! No!
He was only being a boor!
Dean!
She'll be
screaming in about five minutes.
Can you heat this up
for me?
Miss?
Oh, absolutely.
Consider yourself lucky.
She actually bit me once.
- Did she draw blood?
- Only a couple of pints.
So how do I report her?
Is there a form I fill out?
A telephone number?
I'll take care of it.
Throw her over my knee if I have to.
I'm serious.
I didn't pay $350 to fly to Paris
and get stabbed by the help.
- You didn't pay for...
- She'll be disciplined.
I guarantee you.
What are you drinking?
Scotch.
Maggie, what do you say
we fetch Mr. Elkins here
a single malt
before landing?
Make it a double.
She'll bring it to your seat...
With bells on.
Call me
your guardian angel.
Or superhero. Your choice.
Shouldn't you be preparing
for landing?
Maggie, that man was
gonna have you fired.
I made him go away
for the cost of a drink.
It cost a lot more than that.
You never have to see him again.
Yeah, but I have to see you.
I like you.
You speak your mind,
and you're a scrapper,
but frankly, you keep this up,
you're not gonna be around
much longer.
You have to be smart.
He's in 3D.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain speaking.
Sunrise is in 15 minutes,
and we'll be landing
shortly after.
Hope you all had
a pleasant flight...
Mother's made reservations
at 7:00 in Montmartre.
Time to feed
the prodigal daughter
her fatted calf.
For all three of us.
Oh, no. For all two of you.
Kate, I think she's lonely.
She'll talk to you.
From wayward daughter
to ambassador
in one transcontinental.
I'm impressed.
She bought a ticket.
She came all this way.
That's a big gesture.
Sure is. She's never
gotten on a plane for me.
I'm sure she's wanted to.
No, I'm sure she hasn't.
Did she tell you that?
If you only had
ringside seats.
Did she ask you
to clean out her closet,
or did you volunteer?
Was bridge club canceled,
or were you lying in wait?
This is serious, Kate.
What Laura did
is selfish and irresponsible.
took real courage.
I admire her for it.
Running out
on a houseful of guests?
Poor Greg is devastated.
I wouldn't blame him if he were
through with her for good.
I didn't say
she had good timing.
She seemed perfectly content
until you arrived.
Clearly, you weren't
looking closely enough.
Cold feet are nothing new.
Reconsidering marriage
doesn't mean she has to
move to Manhattan.
Mother, Laura's reconsidering
her whole life.
Don't you understand that?
And you're advising her?
Absolutely.
Ohh. You'll be off flying
around the world.
What is Laura gonna do
in the city alone?
Laura plans on
flying around the world, too.
She's gonna tag along
with you?
Mother, Laura's applying
to Pan Am.
No, no,
you're not taking her.
Taking her?
No one is taking her, mother.
If the life we've given you
isn't enough, fine,
but don't infect
Laura with your...
with my what?
- Dissatisfaction.
- Dissatisfaction?
I rode an elephant
in Bangkok last week.
I watched the sun set over
Patagonia the week before that.
Which is not nearly as
interesting as you think it is.
How would you know?
You don't even have a passport.
If you wanna trot
around God-knows-where,
throw your education away
to serve coffee to strange men
and that sort of thing,
I can't stop you!
What is
"that sort of thing"?
But Laura is different.
You mean special.
She's impressionable.
She wants
out of this driveway.
She wants a taste
of something bigger.
She needs me.
Laura will be fine.
How do you know that?
Because I needed you, too!
And I'm fine.
Ugh! All right! All right.
You're still sleeping?
I could be.
It's 5:00 P.M.
You flew all night,
slept all day. Paris awaits.
Is Colette here?
She's still sleeping.
- No, no.
- No, I'm awake now.
You sure?
Yeah, you're right.
Paris awaits.
About that... I, uh,
did a little wandering.
Had some trouble finding
that nightclub I mentioned.
Mm, do you know the name?
It's Palace or...
Chez Palace, maybe.
Everybody keeps directing me
to Versailles.
Oh. Placette. It's famous.
Placette. And that explains it.
In St. Germain.
6th Arrondissement.
Great. Thanks.
Was there something else?
Truth is, um...
I could use a favor.
The concierge said Cafe Canard
should be right down there.
Oh, and we need to remember
to get some French cheese.
Cheese?
For daddy.
Kate said he wanted cheese?
I doubt that, dear.
Mother?
You can't give up on her.
Oh, I don't intend to.
Trust me.
Good. You know,
because the three of us
can fly anywhere you like.
We can...
We can explore
the whole world together.
The whole world
is an awfully big place.
Do you think
there's room for one more?
Yes, we're allowed to get
tickets for daddy, too.
I wasn't talking
about your father.
You brought Greg?
Now, Laura,
he's a good man,
and he loves you.
And you loved him enough
to want to marry him.
So all that stuff you said
on the plane...
Kate was right about you.
I meant what I said, but Greg
deserves an opportunity to...
Laura!
Laura?
What did she do?
Oh.
As you remembered?
Well, it's not quite as busy.
It's early.
I came here first
when I was 19
with a boy
who was an artist.
He fed me drinks until
I agreed to let him paint me.
How'd that come out?
Mm, depends on your taste.
He was a surrealist.
I had four noses.
Yeah, but think of all
- the smelling you could do. - Oh.
My favor...
Uh,
it wasn't getting me here.
Bridget introduced me
to this place,
and I think the... maitre d'
is a good friend of hers.
And you came to ask him
if he knows where she is.
Yeah, but the only problem
is that...
You don't speak French.
Yeah.
Let's see what
he has to say.
Garcon?
Mademoiselle, bonsoir.
Bonsoir.
Vous connaissez Bridget Pierce?
Bridget? Oui, oui.
No.
Mais vous devez bien
vous souvenir de lui?
Non, je vous l'ai deja dit.
J'en suis desole.
- So what... what is he saying?
- He doesn't remember you.
- But he remembers Bridget, right?
- Yeah, they're old friends.
Okay, so does he know
where she is? Do...
Et Bridget? Pouvez-vous
me dire ou Elle est?
Le capitaine
l'a demandee en mariage.
Why is he laughing?
Pas etonnant
qu'elle ait disparu.
Pourquoi vous dites ca?
Bridget aime bien
ses petits copains,
mais son mari... Elle l'adore.
What... what is it?
What'd he say?
Colette?
He said... she may like
her boyfriends,
but she loves her husband.
You had to do it,
didn't you?
Kate, Laura running from
her problems doesn't solve them.
Oh, you were so close.
You were so close
to getting your daughter back.
Which one?
The one you want.
I want both of you.
No...
Pardon me.
Might you have the time?
It's 2100...
Hours.
It's good to see you.
Bridget, where have you been?
Nowhere. I'm a ghost
at the moment.
Why didn't they tell me
I was meeting you?
Do you have the package?
A gift.
How ironic,
considering what
I've had to give up for it.
Dean.
How is he?
It isn't the first time I've
heard of a secret marriage.
For girls who want
to keep working,
it's the only way.
Dean...
I saw the way
she would look at you.
Okay. Let's get you home.
What's inside?
My future.
Couple of months ago,
I was meant to take a picture
of a man at a local airport,
but I missed him.
So I tracked him down on my own,
and I got the shot.
Dean was with me
when I dropped off the film...
It's nice to meet you.
To the C.I.A. liaison
at a Parisian nightclub.
Champagne?
All routine
until a mi-6 agent appeared
and told me
that I'd been compromised
whilst taking the picture.
At first
they deactivated me,
and I resumed
my normal life.
But eventually,
it was decided...
That for my own safety,
I should become...
Elizabeth Reese
of Kansas City, Missouri.
Good God.
I mean, where on Earth
is Missouri?
Bridget, I'm so sorry.
They wanted you
to deliver this
so that you would see
what happens
if you don't follow orders
to the letter.
But I have another
unauthorized message.
You volunteered for this.
They will let you out.
The thrill of it...
The good that you hope
you are doing
is not worth
losing everything, Kate.
But I don't want out.
Does that mean I'm crazy?
No.
It means I was right
to recommend you.
You'd think I would have
practiced what to say next.
Where are the flowers?
Oh, I gave them to an old lady
in the lobby.
They were a bad idea.
They were nice.
The old lady
was very excited.
Hugs, messy kisses.
Exactly what I was
hoping for, really.
Just... not from her.
Greg.
I am so sorry.
I really meant to marry you.
I did.
But then suddenly,
I put on that wedding dress,
and I thought, "here I go."
My last great adventure.
And then I realized...
I was only 22, and I'd hardly
had any great adventures.
You don't think starting
a family is an adventure?
Well, sure it is.
It's just not...
Paris.
You still finish
my sentences.
You are still the prettiest girl
I have ever laid eyes on.
You need to let me go.
When I was 15,
I read a story in "Boys' Life"
about climbing Kilimanjaro.
And it seemed about
as far away as the moon,
but I mowed lawns all summer
so that I could make the trek.
Saved almost $300.
Wasn't enough by a long shot,
but I put it in the bank,
and I swore that someday
that money would go
towards adventure.
And what did you
spend it on?
A ring.
Th-that's not the point.
The point is, if what
you're leaving me for is...
Kilimanjaro?
Then bon voyage, Laura.
Safe journey.
Well, I don't understand
a word you're staying.
Hey! Hey! There she is!
The tenderizer.
Come on! That was funny.
Hey, I-if you lost your key,
you're welcome to stay with us.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I got you a little present.
You know, I actually
learned something today.
Don't... piss off...
Maggie Ryan.
I know what my job is.
For the price
of their ticket,
businessmen get to flirt
with pretty women.
And I can handle flirts.
I can handle
the personal grooming checks,
the weigh-ins, the boozy jerk
that crosses the line.
But what I can't handle
is that you made it okay
for him to try that again
with another girl.
M-Maggie...
What do you want?
One stamp.
It's impressive.
Look at the date
it was issued.
The summer
I became stewardess?
I tried.
I need you, too.
We were supposed
to take a right
at Rue chat qui danse.
You're laughing at me.
The French girl who got
lost in France? No.
You're the one who wanted
to wander.
Besides, I wasn't lost.
No, I was bewildered
by the moment.
Shall we?
How do you say "lost"
in French?
Perdu.
I am... Perdu.
No. No.
Nous... sommes perdus.
We... are... lost.
What are you doing?
Nous sommes...
Dancing.
You smell like
whiskey and cigarettes.
And you smell like Paris.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com