Previously on Mad Men...
Are you leaving me?
We're leaving each other,
just like you said.
And who's that woman,
your other wife?
I ended up married to her because
I ran away to join the army.
You want me to work up an entire
corporate image campaign for 10 dollars?
How much do you want?
How much you got?
When a housewife has a rapid weight
gain the cause is usually psychological.
This can never happen again.
What?
No, of course. I...
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
How is fishing competitive?
Man versus fish?
- No.
- Morning.
Man versus man.
The weighing, the measuring.
Got to respect anything
that rewards you for silence.
Come on.
Morning, all.
My mother always said
good news could wait.
But I spent an hour and a
half on the phone last night
with my new best friend
Victor at the New York Times.
Gonna get a paper route?
No, they're doing some literary
profile on hip agencies.
- Hep. - After an hour of invading
the details of my life--
You shouldn't start it
with the mayflower.
Anyway, I told him
to get in touch with you.
He wants to see
what we've been up to.
I'll have Joan put it together.
And don't worry about
an interview.
He seemed to be only
interested in talking to me.
Sterling Campbell Draper
Pryce, may I help you?
And this one.
That'll do it.
Peggy really got
buried with Heinz.
Yes, they are mostly
Mr. Ginsberg.
Look at all the great work you've
done as creative director.
Look at all these voices,
all this talent.
You really should put
the letter in there.
Should I?
That was a year ago.
As far as the world knows,
it wasn't really an ad.
It's something to talk about.
We're still suffering for it.
Might as well get
something out of it.
Leave 'em.
Look, JC, if you golf with me you're gonna
win every time. No, because I'm terrible.
Okay.
Get Max Rosenberg on the phone.
I thought your tailor
was Italian.
I met him at the Javits
fundraiser.
He's got a piece of business.
It's a Jewish wine.
- Why not bring it up at new business?
- Why?
Don't you think we're capable
of doing this on our own?
Mr. Campbell is very good
for our business,
but this requires your finesse
and, frankly,
your semitic wife.
Bert, how do you not know
I'm getting a divorce?
Not Mona, Jane.
Jane and I
are getting divorced.
Already?
How Jewish are they?
You know, "Fiddler on the
roof," audience or cast?
The company is Manischewitz.
Max will know.
You can't blink.
Try to keep your eyes open
so the sting
from the air comes in.
Like this.
Daddy, don't forget
the colored pencils.
Whining is not gonna get you anything.
I'm crying because I need them so
badly for my family tree project.
- Dinner's at 7:00?
- You're gonna work all day?
It's 3:30.
- Bye, boys.
- Bye-bye.
How'd you do that?
Just keep 'em wide open and think
about something that makes you sad.
They're probably
tying their shoes.
- That's what it always is.
- I can't sit here all day.
I thought you could
park anywhere.
Betty, I'm not an ambulance.
We're double-parked.
What do you think
you're doing, pal?
Okay. Jesus.
Just go get 'em.
I'll circle.
The doorman said
you were downstairs.
- Where's Megan?
- I don't know. In the bathroom.
Hurry up, get everybody.
Bobby, Gene, mom's here.
Come on.
Oh!
Uh, we were waiting.
And they buzzed you.
Henry's double-parked.
I'm sorry.
I've lost track of the time.
Don's late.
This is quite an apartment.
Thank you.
I think you've seen most of it.
- Bobby, come on.
- I'll go get them.
Daddy was supposed to bring
the colored pencils.
I'll buy you some.
Let's go.
Okay, goodbye.
Bye.
This is irritating.
I'll see you in two weeks.
Goodbye.
A trail of Sno Balls
leading to bigger sales.
A frozen machine that
makes money for vendors.
Now, if it's for
the customers, the kids,
do they get to
work the machine?
Find out.
A snowman...
On the beach.
A Sno Ball's chance in hell.
They don't melt.
They're refreshing
for the damned.
They're sinful.
The Sno Ball is the sin
that gets you into hell.
They're sinfully delicious.
Jesus, not bad.
Just put gene to bed.
I'll be right up.
Everyone loves the cartoons
in the New Yorker.
And I thought we could
do that kind
with the guy crawling across
the Sahara dying of thirst--
The long beard,
the tattered shirt.
Only there's four guys
and each one has
a thought bubble above him.
"Water, water,
water, Sno Ball."
- What's the line?
- Doesn't need one.
Well, if you want to stay
with the New Yorker thing,
maybe some kind
of cryptic joke.
- I already have the joke.
- Okay. Your turn.
Ahem. As much as I hate
following another comedian,
Sno Ball,
because it's for kids,
demands a big, loud joke.
"Hit me in the face with
a Sno Ball" is the tag.
And the picture is someone getting
hit in the face with a snowball.
Not the drink, an actual
round, white, messy snowball.
And when I say someone,
I mean a cop,
school teacher with glasses,
businessman, Indian chief.
Anybody kids hate.
And maybe a pig.
Why a pig?
I don't know,
but everybody laughed.
Great, so that's a way to go.
I agree.
Also, Sno Ball comes
with its own slogan
because when you
think of a snowball,
there's a 90% chance you think
of its chance in hell.
Oh, right.
That's true.
So I picture this devil
with a mischievous smile
on his face,
sipping a Sno Ball in front
of the flames of hell.
The cup is beading
with condensation.
And in your head
you hear his voice,
"Yes, even me."
Wow.
That's actually good.
I'm glad I could surprise you.
No, it's just damn impressive
you could not write for so
long and come back with that.
- It's good to know.
- Thank you.
- It's great.
- I'm working on the line.
I'll do the rest of it.
That's the easiest part to change.
So let's run
with both of these.
May I?
Judy Steckler,
half-pound loss.
That's so good.
We both had a good week.
I don't know what happened.
I just wasn't
that hungry this week.
Oh, stop it.
You're here. You came.
This meeting can start
to define what is a good week
and a bad week in our lives.
But there are good weeks
and bad weeks
for thin people, too.
Coming to weight watchers
is not just a chance
to feel better about yourself.
It's a chance to share
so that if, for example,
you're someone like me,
you don't stuff yourself
just to keep from telling
your family your problems.
How was your week, everybody?
Betty?
Uh, well,
I had a bad week out there
after having
a good week in here.
Could you stand up, sweetheart?
Uh...
I, you know, had a...
A very trying experience.
I was in an unfamiliar place
and I saw--
Felt a lot of things
I wish I hadn't.
And I lost a half a pound.
And I feel like I should
pat myself on the back
because it was really hard.
We always talk about
our goal in pounds,
but that's not
all it is, is it?
Thank you, Betty.
Anyone else?
Katherine with a "K."
Burke Devlin will never be a stranger in
Collinsport. Just do what you're told.
But the way he looks at Vicky--
I know what that means.
Who was she to him,
Mr. Collins?
I've heard her name
too many times.
What could that miserable
schoolmarm offer him that I can't?
I'll kill myself!
I will!
Who the hell is this woman?
She's a new character.
She's a cook and she's in love.
She's insane.
She needs a drink.
They want you to be emotional.
You haven't even seen the show.
I've seen a soap opera.
I don't think
I've seen one this bad.
And isn't this supposed
to be scary?
I didn't come
for an acting lesson,
but thank you for
making me more nervous.
Come on, we used to
laugh about this together.
You'll go in and turn
that Chuck into Tenderloin.
You know what?
It's just so easy for you
from your throne
on 73rd and Park.
Some of us act for a living and
we wait tables when we don't.
- That's not fair.
- No, it isn't.
What do you want me to say?
That I'd kill for an audition
in this piece of crap?
I would.
Are you happy?
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm nervous.
I haven't had a job in a while
and you're lucky, that's all.
I am.
I've got to go.
I've got a shift.
What should I bring
for Thanksgiving?
Something sweet.
Mr. Ginsberg is here to see you.
I like the connect the dots.
What's it end up being?
Actually, it's reminiscent
of certain experiences
for some people.
Have a seat.
- Michael, can you keep a secret?
- Nope.
I need you to do some work for
me on a prospective account.
It will involve
a client dinner.
And murder.
You're not going to dinner.
What I need from you
is a couple of ideas
for a company called
monarch wines.
The brand is Manischewitz.
- You assume that I'm Jewish.
- Stop talking.
They make wine for Jews.
And now they're making one they
want to sell to normal people.
You know what I mean--
People like me.
I think they're open
to anything,
but it has to be cheap,
surprise, but impactful.
Bring me a couple of
your best by sundown Friday.
I have done a little research.
You know, I work
for the agency.
And I don't know I want
to keep a secret from Don.
You know Don--
Tall guy, short temper.
For the purposes of this
dinner these are my ideas.
If it works out, Don will
obviously pick you for it
- and you can come up with them
all over again. - Yeah, but why?
Well, Michael,
when a man hates another man
very, very much,
sometimes he wants to know
that something is his,
even if in the end
he has to give it up.
You really do hate Campbell.
I don't devote the energy
to hating people anymore.
It's for Mr. Cooper.
And what's for me?
It's a lot of work.
My paying clients might suffer.
Jesus, I am bankrolling
this entire outfit.
Say 100 now
and 100 Monday morning.
You wipe your ass
with 200 bucks.
Here, take it.
I've got to start
carrying less cash.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I can't eat fish
five times a week.
I'm sorry.
I don't want you
to go to bed hungry.
I don't do it all the time.
Go to sleep.
You better take it out.
Sit down.
This is nice.
Don't know that it's nice
that I've driven you to this
because I can't control myself.
Sweetheart, it's got
nothing to do with you.
Well, what is it?
Nothing.
I've just been
putting it together
that this job is a dead end.
Does Lindsay want someone
else for the campaign?
Lindsay's not running.
He keeps saying that,
but, you know.
Betty, I'm the one
who keeps saying it.
Turns out he's the one
who means it.
He wants to wait until '72,
but now's the time.
Once he's out, rocky will
get the nomination.
Rocky can't run.
He's divorced.
Nobody cares anymore.
He just got reelected governor.
I bet on the wrong
horse, Betty.
I jumped ship for nothing.
This is a setback.
You're always thinking
about other people,
and then you're angry because
no one's thinking about you.
But I am.
It's so easy to blame
our problems on others,
but really we're
in charge of ourselves.
And I'm here to help you
as you're here to help me.
We'll figure out what's next.
What time is it?
Midnight, I think.
Can I count it as tomorrow?
Okay.
Now.
Hello?
- Hello.
- What do you want?
I want to have dinner.
Is that a good idea?
You know what, Jane?
When we took LSD,
you swore to me that you would
always be there for me.
Stop telling me things
I said that night.
Like I know I didn't promise
to remarry right away
just to save you alimony.
No, this is true.
And I have a very painless exercise,
which is taking some extremely
important clients to dinner
and having you on my arm.
Why don't you ask Joanie?
She's a professional something.
Because they're dying
to meet you.
You'd like them.
It's a dinner.
I'll owe you.
I want you to buy me
a new apartment.
What's wrong with
the one you're in?
Your mother is my landlord.
And honestly,
it has a lot of memories
and it's painful to be here.
And I feel like I can't
start a new life
until I start a new life.
This is the most expensive
dinner in history.
Really? Because I found
the perfect one.
Well, you're lucky
I called, then.
Fine.
Have your lawyer tell my lawyer
what time dinner is.
I don't know, I feel like one
of us should say thank you.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
You can't be here.
I missed you.
And I kept thinking about you.
I thought you were
done with me.
I forgot you.
And then I saw you in the
New York Times Sunday magazine.
- Can I go watch TV?
- Did you finish everything?
Yeah.
You can check it.
Yeah?
I just might do that.
My God, are you still
working on the tree?
All they care about
is the names.
Well, I have questions.
Do Megan and Henry get branches?
Of course. They get a branch off
of us because we're your parents.
What is this mess?
You carry this around
with you every day?
This goes in your math folder.
This goes in your spelling.
Is this what
you're doing in class?
No, I made it at daddy's.
Well, it's very nice,
although I don't know
why he's smiling.
"Lovely Megan,
I went to buy a light bulb.
When I get back,
I'll see you better.
Love, Don."
Everything looks good.
I'll take care of this.
You can go.
You know what?
Don't forget your daddy's first wife.
You're right here.
Elizabeth Hofstadt Francis.
No, your father had
another wife before me.
He did?
I'm surprised
he didn't tell you that.
Megan helped me.
Just put it down.
It's Anna Draper.
She's a deceased.
And turn it in already.
I don't want another
call from school.
Who is she?
I don't know why Megan didn't tell you.
Ask her.
Oh. Okay.
Hey, I've got an office
just across the ladies' room
from the insurance
company next door.
- At least you're over here.
- I'm the head of my department.
And I've been working
very hard and doing very well
and nothing has changed here.
It's a lot of empty promises.
What were you promised?
Hello.
It's a mess in there.
Both campaigns draw you in, but in different ways.
This one's a series.
If Harry rolls it out right, you
wonder who's gonna get hit next.
- That's great.
- And this one pulls you in
as you hear the evil voice
inside your head.
"This could
change everything."
I think the devil is clever.
"Snowball's chance in hell"
and so forth.
But I think the getting hit in the
face has a loud, juvenile quality
that makes a Sno Ball seem
more fun than a soft drink.
Also, they kept talking
about refreshing,
and this one is literally
a slap in the face.
The devil could
be a series, too.
We could see what he's up to
in different situations.
And it's got the heat that
Warren talked about for thirst.
This one's funnier.
Let's lead with that one
and take them both.
- Great.
- Funny stuff. Really good work.
- Thank you.
I've got drinks.
- Take these to full color.
- Absolutely.
- What time is it?
- Bye, creative.
"Look on my works,
ye mighty, and despair."
You should read the rest
of that poem, you boob.
Come on.
Here.
Bye-bye.
Sally?
- Sally.
- Bye.
Have fun.
Come on.
Let's go.
Do you want me to make you something?
You haven't eaten.
I told you I don't
want anything.
Why are you being
so nasty today?
Because you're a phony.
Hey, you don't talk
to me like that.
- Who is Anna?
- What?
You acted like
you were friends with me.
But you really do
whatever he says.
And guess what.
You're not special.
And neither was Anna.
Where did you hear that?
You were my friend first.
Who told you about her?
Someone who doesn't lie.
Someone who didn't just pretend
to care about my school project.
Sally, listen to me.
I wasn't lying.
I just-- I didn't think
it was my place to say.
Everybody knows.
You're a little girl.
And it's complicated.
Fine, just keep
digging yourself deeper.
I don't know what
your mother told you,
but your father and Anna got
married to help each other.
They never lived together
and they never had any babies.
- Honest.
- So why did he marry her?
It was a long time ago.
And back then it was the only
way to help each other out.
So why did he marry you?
- Talk to your father.
- I don't want to.
And don't tell him I asked.
I mean it.
Are you going
to make yourself cry?
I am your friend, you know.
Ooh, Judy Steckler--
May I?
Lost a full pound.
Good.
What a nice way to end things.
I don't know what happened.
No, it's good.
Betty, you know maintaining
is better than gaining.
It wasn't even a full week.
Now everyone deserves
a round of applause.
You came on a Saturday.
This is the best thing you can do with
the challenge of Thanksgiving ahead.
And we know it's not
just the meal.
It's the cooking, right?
You have to taste everything.
We're supposed to be
thankful for this,
but the food is just a symbol
of all the other things.
We should fill ourselves
with our children,
our homes, our husbands,
our health, our happiness.
So who has a plan for how
they're gonna handle the day?
And the day before?
And let's not forget
about leftovers.
Just wanted to make
sure she was asleep.
What's going on with her?
She asked me about Anna.
Betty obviously told her.
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
But I think I handled
the situation as best I could.
Who the hell told you
to say anything?
What are you doing?
- Damn it, this has nothing to do
with you. - Keep your voice down.
I'm not gonna let her keep
getting away with this crap.
You're just gonna
make it worse.
And let her keep sticking
her fat nose in my business?
- Let it go. - Yeah, and what
am I supposed to say to Sally?
Nothing. I promised her
I wouldn't tell you.
Jesus, who's the child here?
Get your hand off the phone.
You think this is an accident?
If you call her, you're giving
her exactly what she wanted--
The thrill of having poisoned
us from 50 miles away.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what else to do.
I'm sorry about that.
Hey.
I didn't think
anybody'd still be here.
I'm gonna leave in a minute.
You come to steal something?
Nah, I'm doing
some work for Roger.
But I'm not supposed
to tell anybody.
It's a wine.
He's trying to reel them in.
Wants to look smart
at the meeting.
- And he asked you?
- What can I say?
I have gifts and I'm grateful.
Well, just so you know, he's not going
to pay you if you tell everybody.
He already did.
Maybe I'll throw some of it
your way if you tell me
what you think.
I don't care.
- Hello. - The article came out
and we're not mentioned.
- What?
- It's a bullshit piece on the usual assholes.
He compares them
to philosophers.
Hold on.
Page 52.
170 is the kicker.
Jesus, they look like
Peter, Paul and Mary.
Why are they picking them?
I don't know and I don't care.
Maybe that's the problem.
You were the one who talked
to him for an hour.
I thought he was your best friend.
You obviously made no impression.
- He's a rat bastard.
- You know what?
Don't wake me up and
throw your failures in my face.
It's Sunday, for Christ's sake.
Sally, get back here.
Boys, back to your room.
Get over here.
- Do you have something
you want to ask me? - No.
You do but you thought
it'd be better to ask Megan.
She wasn't supposed
to say anything.
And what was she supposed
to do exactly?
Not lie again.
Well, I'm sorry.
I know it's my fault
that you even have to think
about things like this.
- You're a little girl.
- I'm not a little girl.
Well, then you should realize that your
mother doesn't care about hurting you.
She just wants to hurt us.
- Are you done?
- No.
Anna and I were married
because of a law.
It wasn't romantic.
She was a friend.
And I would have told you
all about her, but she died.
Is she the woman whose house
we went to in California?
The one who called you dick?
Yes.
And I really wish
you'd met her.
Now, you realize an adult
would apologize to Megan even
if telling her was an accident.
Okay.
Go hang up the phone
in my room.
Anything for me in there?
Why don't you have
Ginsberg get your lunch?
That Mohawk work I did
for you was great.
And I kept it a secret, which is
more than I can say for Ginsberg.
It's Manischewitz.
He was perfect for it.
I'm sick of hearing
people think that way.
I'm not an airplane either.
I can write for anything.
You know, in the old buildings,
they used to have
an executive elevator.
You are not loyal.
You only think about yourself.
Were we married?
Because you're thinking
about yourself, too.
That's the way it is.
It's every man for himself.
Quaid's department
developed Sno Ball,
and he will remind you.
We've got Bob Dennison, who
speaks for the local bottlers.
We'll also have Michael Lloyd
and Warren Kent,
who deal with
the local retailers.
- You want me to get those?
- I'm not taking two.
Sally?
Sally, get in here right now.
That was Mrs. Engel.
Apparently you got an A+
on your family tree.
She thinks you're really
turning things around.
It's just a drawing.
Well, I'm very proud of you.
You should thank Megan
for her help.
She helped you, didn't she?
I guess so.
She just told me
the same stuff you did.
Oh.
Really?
You asked her about Anna?
Yes. Daddy showed
me pictures
and they spoke
very fondly of her.
I guess you've earned some TV.
So I pulled over to
the side of the interstate
and I let him out with
his luggage and everything.
He is not related to me.
Siegel's a very common name.
You wouldn't want to think everyone
named Rosenberg is related to you.
I didn't want to say it.
Lord knows there's been plenty
of prejudice in this country.
But growing up in Manhattan,
I've always envied the humor,
the closeness, the way your
people keep track of each other.
So you married
your way in, huh?
I've always thought
Jewish women
are the most beautiful
women in the world.
Now that's a sales pitch.
- I'm sorry I'm late.
- This is my son Bernard.
We're still on drinks.
Roger Sterling, this is my wife Jane.
- Bernie.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry about that.
I took the boat out.
- We got stuck.
- Really? What kind of boat?
No, you two can discuss
the details later.
My dad doesn't like yachts
because last time he was on one,
he rode steerage.
And look where you are now.
I've been trying to find out
what Roger thinks,
but he wanted to wait for you.
I wanted to wait for dessert,
make sure you liked me.
What's not to like?
As I understand it,
you're trying to get Manischewitz
into the hands of different
kinds of people.
So to us, it seemed
the key was, well, different kind
if you ever look at the side of
a bus, it's a moving billboard.
The passengers can't see the ad, but
everyone can see the passengers.
The idea was to put a picture of the
bus seats on the side of the bus
right below the window
where the real people are,
show the bottom halves
of their bodies
with a case of Manischewitz
under each of their seats.
So it looks like whoever's riding
the bus has bought the wine.
Isn't that clever?
So you thought that up, huh?
Well, I engaged some
of our creatives ad hoc
in anticipation of this dinner.
I figured even if you didn't like it,
you could see what we were capable of.
- I know it's good.
- Do we need menus?
- I do.
- I'm getting the Chateaubriand
if someone will
split it with me.
I thought you liked
the crabs Rangoon here.
I just had some.
So, Roger, what kind
of boat do you have?
Am I the only one who can work
and drink at the same time?
- What happened?
- They laughed,
they bought it
and we already celebrated.
I'm only here because I've got
three hours left on the coast.
- Hot damn!
- I knew it.
Hold on.
We work our ass off
and we don't even warrant a call?
Blow by blow, please.
Don pitched the hell out of
it, they said it was clever.
And apparently kids like devils
in cartoons as I predicted.
Oh, really?
They didn't like the other one?
I don't know.
He left it in the cab.
Are you kidding me?
They never even heard it?
We made a sale.
Anything else?
I'm going to order some dinner.
Sure. He's gonna
be useless tonight.
So, you suddenly have no problem
telling people I'm Jewish?
You going to meet Bernie?
What?
No.
So you're not gonna call him in two
days and tell him we're separated?
You had your chance
to say who I sleep with.
Well, you're supposed
to help me land this.
So if something goes on
between the two of you,
you'd better pretend
you're still married.
I promise, bubala.
I'm sorry.
The least you can do is show me what the
better end of this deal looks like.
- What do you mean?
- The apartment.
Show it to me.
When else am I
gonna get a chance?
I'm not moved in.
I just got the key.
Has a lot of potential.
You think so?
I have missed you.
Roger, wait.
What?
I'm surprised
you're working today.
We roll out all
our business this week.
Well, I'm just gonna spend as
much time as I can with my girl
before I'm trapped with
my family over the holiday.
You know what, Howard?
Why don't you spend
Thanksgiving with her,
and I'll go to your house
and screw your wife?
Are you kidding me?
Good luck with that.
But I guess the grass
is always greener, right?
I know you saw me.
I thought you were
hiding from someone.
That was a bold
last-minute decision
going with your idea.
I thought it was more
what they wanted.
Well, we'll never know,
will we?
Because they never heard mine.
Look, I don't like going in
with two ideas. It's weak.
And you don't wanna be weak,
so you picked yours.
And they bought it,
which is our goal, isn't it?
What do I care?
I got a million of 'em.
- A million.
- Good.
I guess I'm lucky you work for me.
I feel bad for you.
I don't think about you at all.
- Morning, Mr. Draper.
- Morning.
I used the toothbrush in there.
I hope it's yours.
Why did you do that?
Jesus, it doesn't belong
to the dead guy, does it?
It's pink.
I told you why I wanted this
apartment and you ignored me.
I hardly ignored you.
Now this is no different
than the last place.
Really?
I think it's nicer.
Not anymore.
You ruined this.
Shit.
You get everything you want
and you still had to do this.
You're right.
I don't know why I did that.
I feel terrible.
Smells good.
I just got off
the phone with Julia.
- She got the part.
- Good for her.
She asked me to buy champagne.
And you will because
you want her to be happy.
It's hot as hell in here.
Turn on the air.
It's on full blast.
Go get ready.
- Open the door at least.
- No, don't.
The radio said there's
a smog emergency.
The air is toxic.
I don't want that in here.
That is
a good-looking bird.
Mommy, wait. We're supposed to
say what we're thankful for.
She's hungry, Bobby.
No, I think it's nice.
Go ahead, buddy.
I'm thankful that
I have two houses
and they're both really big
and I got a new sled.
Doing well.
I am thankful that
I have everything I want.
And that no one else
has anything better.
Me, too.
Let's eat.
♪ don't go around moping
hoping happiness ♪
♪ will come ♪
♪ that's not the way ♪
♪ it doesn't pay ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ why don't you try to ♪
♪ take life the way I do? ♪
♪ let the whole world
sigh or cry ♪
♪ I'll be high in the sky ♪
♪ up on top of a rainbow ♪
♪ sweeping the clouds away ♪
♪ I don't care
what's down below ♪
♪ let it rain, let it snow ♪
♪ I'll be up on a rainbow ♪
♪ sweeping the clouds away ♪
♪ I have learned
life's lesson ♪
♪ fighters who always win ♪
♪ are those who can take it
right on the chin ♪
♪ and grin ♪
♪ and so I shout to everyone ♪
♪ find your place in the sun ♪
♪ up on top of a rainbow ♪
♪ sweeping the clouds away. ♪