Don?
What do you think?
Now, it may take a moment to get used to.
I told you, men don't like change.
Well, it's hard for me to judge
when I can't see a price tag.
A modern Chinoiserie breakfront,
a Dunbar, Japanese-influenced sofa,
silk Dupioni drapes, Murano vases,
and a classic Drexel end table.
- And what goes here?
- Where?
Right where we're standing.
Well, that's your hearth, darling.
That's the soul of your home.
People gather around a fire
even if there isn't one.
- So, Don?
- I think it's fine, Betts.
All you do at work all day
is evaluate objects.
I would like the benefit of your eye.
Move the end table and the lamp
to the other end of the couch.
I think he's right.
- Hot as hell already.
- Yes, it is.
I watched the sunrise today. Couldn't sleep.
- How was it?
- Average.
Ogilvy wrote a book. I got the galleys.
They want a quote or something.
Advertising's already up there with lawyers
as the most reviled.
This is not going to help.
It'll help him.
It's called Confessions of an Ad Man.
- I like the title.
- Please.
It's a book everybody writes,
only he got it published.
It should be called
1,000 Reasons I'm So Great.
- Is he publishing it himself?
- No, Atheneum.
I'll send it over. I don't want you to buy it.
I don't know where to put it, and you know
I wouldn't be able to tell you if...
There you are.
When do you want us
to move the meeting to?
- Mr. Draper?
- Move it? I'm 15 minutes late.
I told you I don't want them hovering.
If I'm late, send them away
and call them when I get here.
Mr. Draper, Conrad Hilton is in your office.
- Right now?
- He just walked right in.
- We were waiting and he blew right past us.
- Hold on.
Come back in 20 minutes.
- Did you offer him coffee?
- I did. He's all set.
You look great.
- Twenty minutes.
- You can take an hour if you need it.
- He wants to look busy.
- Move it.
Allison, hold all my calls.
Connie. What a great way to start the day.
- 9:30? It's practically lunch.
- Well, can I get you something?
I've got a personal matter.
It's not fit for the phone.
What can I do for you?
I don't know what I'm more disturbed by,
the fact that you don't have a Bible,
or that there's not a single family photo.
- I'm easily distracted.
- You should have those things.
They'll make you feel better
about what you do.
Start showing up on time.
Maybe I'm late because I was spending time
with my family reading the Bible.
Are you nervous, Don?
I'm finding you hard to talk to.
Well, you caught me by surprise, Connie.
I think you know that.
Now, you're a married man,
so you'll have to use your imagination,
but
I have this involvement.
I can't say it's perfect,
and my needs are being met,
but I have significant needs, Don.
- Do you catch my drift?
- Yes.
So what do I do
when my eye starts to wander?
Don't you have a coterie of trusted advisors,
friends, kings,
that might counsel you better?
I want you to handle the Waldorf-Astoria,
the New York Hilton and the Statler Hilton.
It's just New York,
but my eye has definitely started to wander.
I think that's a good start.
Retainer, etcetera, that's for lawyers.
Everything else will be like this.
Having me in your life
is gonna change things.
- I look forward to it.
- They always say that.
- A happy bunch.
- If you say so.
Young people give us energy.
Don't forget that.
I'll take it from here.
It's not much to start with,
but I look forward
to sharing my dreams with you.
Speak to you soon.
I cannot believe you just had a baby
and you redid your house.
Are you suicidal?
They were not
supposed to be simultaneous,
and the baby wasn't the one
that couldn't keep a schedule.
I'm assuming this meeting
means you're interested
in replacing Francine as secretary?
- I am.
- Good.
Because we waited for you
for our most pressing business.
The proposed 3-million-gallon water tank
will not only drain
the Pleasantville Road Reservoir,
but also blemish the natural
and financial health of our community.
Well said.
The Junior League needs to take over
this effort and explain the issues.
Now, first, conservation. The Silent Spring?
The majestic beauty
of the Hudson River valley.
Second, worthless real estate
on both sides of the river
because some industrial park
on Route 9 needs our water.
We need to go over
the Village Board's head,
appeal to the governor.
The Rockefellers own half the land here.
Real estate, that's scary.
I may know someone
in the governor's office.
Who?
His name is Henry.
You're gonna have to do better than that.
Henry Francis.
He's in the paper sometimes,
always right behind Rocky.
- What does he do?
- I'm not really sure.
- How do you know him?
- I met him at a party for Don's work.
Here he is. Oh, my, it just says "Advisor. "
Yes, I know who he is.
He used to be the Republican Party chair
for Westchester County.
- I know him.
- Well, call him, then.
I think we have a better chance
if Betty calls.
It's not adorable to pretend
like you're not adorable.
Call him. He's a big deal.
Miami is where we should start,
let it grow from there.
Ho-Ho wants it everywhere.
He just bought land in Seattle.
It's an indoor city.
As long as he keeps writing checks.
Look, do you want to
kill this thing in one blow
or do you want to
shear the sheep every year?
Whatever you want, Don.
You made it clear
you don't want to talk about it,
but at least tell us how you know him.
We ran into each other at a party.
That'll be all.
I know Roger will be the face of this thing,
but I wouldn't mind doing the legwork.
Pete, I think you're supposed to
bring in the account,
and I'm supposed to beg to be on it.
What happened
with North American Aviation?
It's going well.
My friend Russ,
who deals with McNamara's office
said the orders are through the roof
for helicopters, carbines
and especially jets for Vietnam.
I think I've convinced North American
they're going to need to spend more
if they want to get out of NASA
and into the Pentagon.
When they do, we can talk about Hilton.
Understood.
Oh, no. Yes, of course.
He's busy.
It's Wilson 4-8038.
Betty Draper. He can call me anytime.
It's a civic matter regarding Ossining.
Thank you.
Lunch!
Wash your hands, Bobby.
Draper residence.
Mrs. Draper, it's Henry Francis.
Yes, of course.
I appreciate
you getting back to me so quickly.
Stop it.
Could you hold just a moment?
I'm going to get on the extension.
Of course.
I'm going in the study. Hang up the phone.
Damn it!
- What is wrong with you?
- You said to hang up the phone.
After I pick up the phone.
Freeze.
Draper residence.
It's Henry again. We were disconnected.
I'm sorry about that. My son.
I know how that goes. How are you?
You must have had your baby by now.
Yes, I did. You remembered.
- What did you have?
- A little boy.
Can you get him registered by November?
I just realized, everyone who calls you
must want something.
Actually, I've been doing
most of the calling lately.
- What can I do for you?
- Well, we were hoping
you could stop the destruction
of the Pleasantville Road Reservoir.
- Who's we?
- I'm representing the Junior League
of Tarrytown.
They want to build a 3-million-gallon
water tank, and it's a very scenic area.
I know the area.
Well, it's practically
the governor's backyard.
That's true, but I grew up there as well.
- Really? Where?
- Mount Salem.
I'm heading upstate tomorrow afternoon.
Maybe I could stop by and take a look.
Well, tomorrow is Saturday.
No, of course. I work every day,
I forget other people don't.
No.
This is very important to me.
I think I could find the time.
- Is Swenson's Bakery still there?
- It is. And it has an air conditioner.
I'll buy you a cup of coffee, and then
we can take a hike to the reservoir.
- Is 3:00 too late for you?
- No, it's perfect. I'll make it work.
Well, I'll see you then, Mrs. Draper.
I can save you the trouble.
It's from him and it's expensive.
I'm going to fire her.
- What did you promise him?
- Who?
You're thick, do you know that?
That present, it's from Duck.
- Hermès. Nice.
- I hope yours is a different color.
"Elegance and success. Duck. "
I wonder who wrote that for him.
- I don't trust him.
- Why?
Because he wants us?
- We're very important here.
- Who is?
- Did he put you on Hilton?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Stop barging in here
and infecting me with your anxiety.
This is really beautiful.
He sent me a box of Cuban cigars.
Although I'm starting to think
they're not that hard to come by.
- Hilton Hotels? Did we get that?
- Do you live in a cave?
Conrad Hilton
came to see Don this morning.
- He was right there.
- Really? What was he like?
I only got a quick look at him.
He was skinny, like a cowboy.
My mother gave me his book. He's Catholic.
- It's going to be a huge account.
- Not as big as Lucky Strike.
But it would be nice to be playing
a little offense for once
instead of hiding from the FTC.
- He has a book?
- I really like this.
Look, I'm keeping this.
Duck said we're not tied together.
I'll keep my mouth shut
and you do whatever you want.
Do you know why
Duck doesn't work here anymore?
Because Don squeezed him out
when the British took over.
So what? Don didn't like him.
It's the world against Don,
and now it's someone else.
True, but Duck
would love to hit Don where it hurts.
Well, I'm not going anywhere,
and I'm not going to tell Don.
I'm not worried about you.
I'm worried about Duck.
Send it back.
When were you going to tell us about this?
I thought I'd let it be
an incoming phone call,
and then wait and see who took credit for it.
This is very exciting.
Despite its modest billings,
London is thrilled with Hilton's potential
for international growth.
Finally.
Huzzah!
If you don't mind my asking,
how did you make this happen?
We travel in the same circles.
Well, I don't know
if we should celebrate yet.
His lawyers called,
and there's a little matter of the contract.
Well, don't be afraid to push back.
I agreed to the New York hotels,
but everything else
should be under our terms.
I don't think you understand.
This is regarding your contract.
Or lack thereof.
It may seem like a formality to you,
but to Mr. Hilton it's a necessity that
all the principals in the firm be secured.
And honestly, I can't blame him.
- I'll give him my word.
- And he'll take it, but his lawyers won't.
Obviously, you'll want
your attorney to look it over.
That's Ben Michelson. It's fairly standard.
Three years, a non-compete clause,
a healthy raise.
That's very generous. I'll think about it.
I'm confused.
If someone handed me that contract,
I'd be filled with glee.
A three-year guarantee,
a $5,000 signing bonus? I...
- I've never seen that before.
- Well, we want to take care of him.
Look, I've gotten to know
Conrad Hilton a little bit.
And I think he'll enjoy
something he can't have,
and you should tell him
that it matters to me.
It matters to him.
Still, I don't think anyone told him
that it matters to me.
Well, this is the way it has to be.
And not just for Conrad Hilton,
but for Sterling Cooper.
I'd like you to take those papers home
for the weekend and think about that.
I'd be happy to.
I met him once.
He's a bit of an eccentric, isn't he?
Yes.
Oh, Jesus.
- Mrs. Draper.
- Mr. Francis.
I'm alone. I hope that's okay.
Oh, well. Actually,
my friend couldn't get away either.
- I appreciate your coming up.
- Please. I love coming back here.
- So much changes, so much doesn't.
- Like what? I'm interested.
Can I help you?
- Just an iced tea, please.
- That's fine for now.
- What was I saying?
- You were talking about coming back here.
Ossining has always been
a real mix of people.
Well, after living in Manhattan,
it wasn't my first choice,
but it's grown on me.
I lived in Manhattan when I was married.
It's okay for work, but I can't sleep
with all those people on top of me.
Like in a skyscraper. May I have a straw?
So, you have your folder.
I thought I'd just give you the literature
and a copy of the petition.
I don't know that I'm a great spokesman.
You don't have to tell me
how beautiful the reservoir is.
- I used to do jackknives into it.
- We drink that water.
I've looked into this for you,
and I'm afraid it's underway.
Oh, no. We're too late.
Maybe if you knew somebody
with some clout.
I don't even know what you do.
I'm a classic strategist, fundraiser,
maybe campaign manager.
- I'm waiting on that.
- And how do you become that?
- Give a lot of money?
- No.
No, I'm a lawyer, but I don't use it much.
We all have skills we don't use.
I was an anthropology major. Imagine that.
- Where?
- Bryn Mawr.
Well, you may be
saving your community right now.
I'm hungry. Do you mind?
- I don't know.
- Fine.
You can read from your folder
and watch me eat.
I'll have apple pie and...
Ice cream or cheddar cheese?
One of each.
Can we just get one thing out of the way?
I don't know what I can do
about the water tank.
Don't give up so easily.
What this really is, is a camera obscura.
We call it a sun scope.
And it allows us to look at the eclipse
without injury to our eyes.
- We didn't bring a scissor.
- I have scissors.
And squares of cardboard
that already have pinholes in them.
And if you really need some help,
ask your dads.
The eclipse is 22 minutes away.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
I could have gone golfing.
I had no idea this is what we'd be in for.
Go ahead. I'll take Ernie home.
You know, Francine taught school
when we were first married.
I used to love seeing her
standing in the middle of those little kids
like a telephone pole. Hey.
There you go.
Sally has a crush on her.
Why can't you stare into the eclipse?
What's it going to do, really?
I stare at the sun every day.
- You stare at the sun every day?
- Well, you know, look at it.
You know, I see her sometimes
when I'm out running in the morning.
- You run?
- Yeah, over by the high school track.
- Do you talk?
- No. No, there's an etiquette to it.
You keep to yourself.
And honestly, that's one of the things
I love about my run, is being alone.
That's hard to come by, you know?
Listen, I hate to disappoint you,
but I have to be on my way.
- That's too bad.
- I have to be in Albany for dinner.
His master's voice.
The governor.
"His master's voice"? It's an old ad.
I know what it is.
- What are you doing?
- It's the eclipse.
He made a contraption.
Don't look at it.
Are you okay?
I think so. I feel a little dizzy.
Take a deep breath.
Is that better?
So you never had time
to go to the reservoir anyway.
I only had an hour, but I figured...
That's what you need. A fainting couch.
What's that?
Victorian ladies would get overwhelmed
from corsets and things.
They'd need a place to lie down.
- How do you know that?
- I used to move furniture.
May I walk you to your car?
- I don't know. This is still a small town.
- No, of course.
- Mrs. Draper.
- Betty.
Henry.
So, that's a rain check for the hike.
I'll contact you as soon as I know anything.
You doing okay?
- You don't want to watch it?
- I will once it gets a little further along.
I don't know if you heard me before,
but it only happens once every 10 years.
You don't want to miss it.
- How's your summer going?
- It's good.
- Are you gonna take a vacation?
- I don't think so. I'll get August off,
then September I'm back at it.
It's all fairly prescribed.
Have you been here in August?
It's a ghost town.
- Where are you going?
- We'll be here.
So now I know that.
Most just come right out
and ask if I'm going to be around.
I was just making conversation.
You can change it if you want to.
You're all the same.
The drinking, the philandering.
They don't know that word.
Do you want me to leave you alone?
Just say so.
- It's hard because this happens a lot.
- Nothing is happening. We're just talking.
Okay.
And where I come from,
schoolteachers, especially, used to say
you shouldn't judge a book by its cover.
- So you're different, huh?
- Is that impossible?
You're all wearing the same shirt.
So how do people live elsewhere?
They don't have as much.
They don't get as bored.
I'm not bored.
Miss Farrell. Miss Farrell. I can see it. Look!
Let me see it with you. Show me.
Yes, is he in?
Tell him it's Peggy Olson regarding Clorox.
Of course.
Hello.
Miss Olson, what a pleasant surprise.
I haven't changed my mind,
and I'd appreciate you not sending things.
- Things you want to keep?
- I'm sending it back.
And I hope you take that
as a definitive answer.
I would if you already sent it.
Listen. I've been having meetings
at The Pierre all day, suite 600.
At 4:30, Hermès comes by.
Give it back in person.
- Why are you meeting at The Pierre?
- Have you been to Grey?
It's a Penn Station toilet
with Venetian blinds.
I can't do that.
You can and you will,
then I'll leave you alone.
Suite 600 at 4:30, not the other way around.
Please don't contact me again.
- How was your weekend?
- Short.
- What did Michelson think of the contract?
- He hasn't gotten back to me.
That's because he didn't get it. I called him.
Are you afraid you're going to have a boss?
You will, the client.
- It's not that.
- What is the problem?
You think you're more dangerous
without a contract?
You are, and it's affecting our business.
You're our David Ogilvy,
and if you let all the blokes at Putnam,
Powell & Lowe relax for three years,
maybe we could put your name out front.
After mine. And Cooper, probably.
Well, I'll let you get back to work.
All I need is a letter of intent.
Ben Michelson can rape us later.
Grunt once for "yes. "
The problem is, I don't know
if you don't want to do this here
or you don't want to do this at all.
Didn't we give you an office?
I just need a minute.
I need to send Martinson's to the printer.
Come on in.
So, do you know
who you're gonna put on Hilton yet?
No.
Well, I don't know
if they want a woman's point of view,
- but I read his book, and...
- Who told you
we were going to land Hilton?
Because we're not.
And I resent you bringing work
in here under pretense.
- I didn't.
- I didn't need to sign off on this.
I'm sorry if... I was excited.
And I heard there was
an amazing assignment.
And you thought you'd come in here
and ask for it because I never say no.
You say no all the time.
What do I have to do for you?
Peggy, tell me.
You were my secretary,
and now you have an office and a job
that a lot of full-grown men would kill for.
Every time I turn around,
you've got your hand in my pocket.
You want a raise. You want this account.
Put your nose down
and pay attention to your work,
because there's not one thing
that you've done here
that I couldn't live without.
I'm sorry, Don.
You're good. Get better.
Stop asking for things.
Close the door.
Draper residence.
Betty. Roger Sterling. How are you?
- I'm well, thank you.
- Is Don about?
No, he's not home yet. Shall I leave word?
Actually, Betty, if I could be frank,
it's important.
- What's wrong?
- Well, it's a little touchy.
I don't want to put you
in a strange position.
- What's wrong, Roger?
- Well, it's about his contract.
What about it?
Look, I know you have to be
on the same page as him,
and he's your husband.
But it's a lot of money, Betty.
- Three years isn't that long, you know.
- I'm sorry. What do you want?
I want you to see what you can do
to get him to sign it.
I know you're the woman behind the man.
Don is going to do
whatever he's going to do.
And honestly, I find it terribly disrespectful
that you would go behind his back.
- Easy, Betty, that's not...
- I have to go.
You missed Hermès.
I was going to give you 10 more minutes.
You came all this way, have a drink.
- What are you having?
- Whatever you're having.
- I'm not having anything.
- A whiskey.
- You are Don's girl, aren't you?
- I was raised on whiskey.
Sit down.
A few minutes of adult conversation,
and we both go home.
Grey has Hermès, Macy's,
H.J. Heinz baby food and Revlon.
- You need someone in a skirt.
- Everybody does.
Copy chief?
Maybe once they get used to you,
but definitely more money.
- Would I get to go to Paris for Hermès?
- They come here,
but you're not going anywhere
where you are.
- I can't.
- Okay.
Just so you know,
that's what opportunity looks like.
I'm just sorry
I won't be seeing you every day.
What are you doing?
I was just thinking about all the times
I've walked by you and didn't even notice.
How is that possible?
What do you want from me?
I want to take you in that bedroom,
lock the door,
take your clothes off with my teeth,
throw you on the bed
and give you a go-around
like you've never had.
Bobby, Sally, turn off the TV
and go upstairs.
- What's wrong?
- Roger Sterling called.
He pretended to be calling for you, and then
he started on me about your contract.
- What?
- Your contract, Don.
It was very uncomfortable.
- What are you doing?
- What do you think?
- I'm calling him.
- Don't.
Betts, don't worry about my job.
Why would I?
I don't know anything about it.
They offered you a contract
and you didn't say a damn thing to me.
I had to hear about it from him.
And why the hell won't you sign it?
It doesn't concern you. You're taken care of.
Why won't you sign it?
Let me explain something to you
about business,
since, as usual, you're turning this
into something about yourself.
No contract means I have all the power.
They want me, but they can't have me.
You're right.
Why would I think
that has anything to do with me?
It's three years, Don.
What's the matter? You don't know
where you're going to be in three years?
Good night.
I love the taste of liquor on your breath.
- Where you headed?
- Niagara Falls.
But we'll settle for the nearest motel.
Hop in.
Thank you.
- I'm Doug. This is Sandy.
- Nice to meet you.
- How far are we?
- A couple of miles.
You wanna know
why we're going to Niagara Falls?
- We're getting married.
- At Niagara Falls. Fancy that.
- People keep trying to talk us out of it.
- Why's that?
Well, we don't really
know each other that well.
Well, we knew each other
a little bit in high school,
and we're not really in love or anything.
I'm sure you have a good reason,
not that it's any of my business.
I'm not knocked up.
They're passing a law that if you're married,
they can't send you to Vietnam.
I don't know if you've served, mister.
I don't want to offend you.
Again, none of my business.
It's just I'm 1-A. I'm 22.
I can't get into school.
I kind of have a target on my back,
and for what?
I think they're really
gonna start sending people.
I have it on good authority that you're right.
Good authority? Are you a spook?
Nope. I'm in advertising.
No way. Now that's priceless.
- But you seem okay.
- Thank you.
It's a beautiful night. It smells good.
But everything smells good
when you're high.
That's true.
Listen, Cadillac,
we don't have gas money, but...
Yeah.
- They're reds. You ever had them?
- What are they?
Phenobarbital. They're my dad's.
Give me one. Make it two.
- Does he know how to dance?
- Who cares?
- How old are you?
- Nineteen.
How old are you?
- Why can't you go to school?
- Because it's a waste of time, man.
- You like to watch us dance?
- Yeah, you want to watch us?
A hillbilly knocks on the door
of his new neighbor's house.
"Howdy, neighbor," he says.
"In honor of you moving into the holler,
I'm gonna throw a party.
"There's gonna be a whole lot of drinking,
"a whole lot of dancing
and a whole lot of screwing. "
"Sounds like fun," the neighbor says.
"What can I bring?"
The hillbilly replies,
"You can bring anything you want.
"It's just gonna be you and me. "
What are you laughing at, Cadillac?
Look at you. Up to your old tricks.
You're a bum, you know that?
- No, I'm not.
- Conrad Hilton?
You wouldn't expect him
to be taken so easily.
- Shut up.
- You can't be tied down.
- That's right.
- Look at your hands.
They're as soft as a woman's.
What do you do? What do you make?
You grow bullshit.
- I gave him two.
- How the hell is he still awake?
Everything okay?
I'm worried that housekeeping
is going to come in.
I put out the sign.
I'll call them when we're done.
- I don't know.
- Come on. I love the morning.
What were you thinking? It's awful.
- It's an antique.
- We discussed this for months,
and we decided antiques were expected.
Look around!
You have ruined the whole room.
If you want to keep it,
please do not tell people I did this.
- Good morning.
- Fender bender.
I'm going to get coffee. Do you want some?
No, thank you.
Good morning, Mr. Draper.
- Fender bender.
- I'm sorry. Mr. Cooper's waiting for you.
Thank you.
- Good morning.
- Sit down.
What do you want?
Sacajawea carried a baby on her back
all the way to the Pacific Ocean.
And somewhere,
that baby thinks he discovered America.
You, Don, have been standing
on someone's shoulders.
We brought you in,
we nurtured you like family,
and now's the time to pay us back.
You can't go any further on your own, Don.
Would you say
I know something about you, Don?
I would.
Then sign.
After all, when it comes down to it,
who is really signing this contract anyway?
I don't want any more contact
with Roger Sterling.
Don?
I signed it.