Previously on Mad Men...
We're going to take
LSD with them.
You don't want to see
each other any more?
You always want to push the
button on the whole thing.
Grandma Pauline is still here
and I hate her.
Stay out of her way.
Are you leaving me?
We're leaving each other,
just like you said.
I'm not a word person
like you, people.
Your words are always
"I don't like it".
Don, you're gonna call back
the American Cancer Society.
What made you
suddenly write that?
It was an impulse.
I'll be able to drive
in a few years.
I can come and visit.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Hello.
Hey, it's your dad.
- Yeah?
- Hi, it's me.
Weeknight, nice.
Is Mrs. Francis
out with the mayor?
They went to Michigan
and they took baby gene
and left me here with Bluto.
She still smell like a toilet?
Yeah.
How's it going?
I'm supposed to be
studying for trig,
but, uh, I'm not in the mood.
Oh, come on.
Her again?
You'll see when you break up.
It hurts.
- Not for the girl.
- Shut up.
Aren't you going back to
the same camp next summer?
Did you go get
the spoonful album?
Hey, bishop, who
you talking to?
Your sister.
Just figuring out when we can ball.
It's on the radio all the time.
Sally, get your brother
and set the table.
Did you hear that?
- We're like her slaves.
- Sally!
Yeah, well, at least you don't
have to change gene's diapers.
No.
Fine, I'll eat by myself.
Oh! Ah!
- What happened?
- Oh, lord.
- Can you move?
- Are you okay?
- Oh, my ankle!
Okay, go get her some water.
I'm gonna call for help.
Bobby, go.
Why do you insist on carrying
everything yourself?
- The doorman offered.
- Why bother him?
- It's not that much.
- No, it is absurd.
- I see you brought work with you.
- It is my book.
I make an excuse of New York
to try and publish again.
Megan's excited about it.
My daughter pretends
to find interesting
what I find interesting
because she loves me.
Why are you carrying the bags?
Is Jonesy drunk again?
- So...
- Please speak English.
You like it?
I don't know.
It's exquisitely decadent.
- Well, it kind of came this way.
- No, it didn't.
Emile is confused.
His eyes and his politics
are having a fight.
Well, daddy, I want
you to sit down.
I'll fix you a drink.
I have a beautiful Dover Sole.
And I want you
to be on vacation.
Formidable.
Merci.
Save yourself.
Got a nice bottle
of cognac for later.
You remembered.
I see she's convinced you
that she's particular.
I'm the proof she is not.
Hello?
Sit.
I insist.
Now tell me all about
your adventures today.
Hold on, sweetheart.
It's Sally.
She's okay, but you
should talk to her.
So Uncle Arnold, huh?
No one went to the funeral, but
I knew you always liked him.
Has Margaret stopped
dancing on Jane's grave?
Well, she
hardly hid her feelings.
You didn't react that way.
No, but I have to admit
I'm surprised that you're
in such a good mood.
It's unsatisfying, actually.
I always thought
she'd leave you.
I've been wondering lately
if she was just an excuse
to blow up my life.
Are you seeing a psychiatrist?
No.
But I did have a, um...
Well, I had
a life-altering experience.
I'll bite.
Mona, I took LSD.
I went on a trip.
Of course you did.
You should really try it.
You have to.
You'd love it, actually.
So what's it like?
Euphoria and insight
and-- I don't know.
My whole life, people
have been telling me
I don't understand
how other people think.
And it turns out it's true.
Maybe I should try it.
So, these...
Are four members of
the American cancer society.
They're honoring Don for kicking lucky
strike in the balls with that letter.
Incredible.
And what am I supposed
to do with these names?
You remember when
we were first married
and you used to go to luncheons
and tell me about these
powerful men that I could meet?
And you ignored me.
When I was in the deepest
part of the trip,
the farthest away,
I was sitting in my bathtub
and I saw myself
at the 1919 World Series.
I was playing.
Aw, you finally got
to be a baseball player.
Yeah, but why that game?
Why that series?
Because that's when
it went bad.
I just realized
nothing I had was mine
because the game was thrown.
Oh, Roger, please don't feel
guilty about your advantages.
I, for one, am not gonna let
a bunch of dirty teenagers
in the paper disrupt
the order of things.
I'm not.
I'm trying to meet with Firestone.
It's a huge favor, I know.
But I lost everything
when we lost Lucky Strike.
I thought you married Jane
because I had gotten old.
And then I realized
it was because you had.
I haven't had
a heart attack since.
Well, I don't see
what the harm could be.
You are still
supporting all of us.
Thank you.
Whatever you can
find out by Friday.
You'd be surprised.
- Hello?
- We're in here.
Sally, Bobby, this is
Dr. and Mrs. Calvet.
- Marie.
- Emile.
- Un plaisir.
- Hello.
Hi.
Henry's mother broke her ankle.
- Oh, my goodness.
- That's terrible.
It could have been a lot worse.
Sally, you want to
tell them what happened?
She tripped over
one of gene's toys.
No, not that.
Sally called the police,
who called an ambulance.
And while they were waiting...
Sally, go on.
I put her foot on a pillow and
put ice on it and kept her calm.
- Oh, what a big girl.
- This is wonderful.
Sally doesn't like fish.
Well, as a reward,
I made spaghetti.
I always made Megan spaghetti.
That was her very favorite.
So, you two
will stay in the boys' room.
We can't put Emile
and Marie in the bunk beds.
I apologize,
but we had a long voyage.
Good night, everyone.
Do you give a lot of shots?
Oh, I am not a medical doctor.
I am a professor.
When you have a high
degree in any field,
they call you a doctor.
It's from the middle ages.
That's right.
Let me just make sure
mom got settled in.
So, is Mr. Heinz
a down-to-earth,
kind of steel-town,
German-Polish,
drinks-beer-out-of-a-can
kind of guy?
No, he's boring.
He's got a daughter.
I think that's where he
gets all his shitty ideas.
Oh, who finished the shrimp?
- I asked.
- You still hungry?
She's got to watch herself.
Too much Chinese and we'll
have to go up a cup size.
- Shut up.
- What are you talking about?
We've been working on playtex.
Peggy's got a way
with the equipment.
I'd love your opinion
on this, Abe.
Peggy, a traditionalist
in the bosom arena,
believes that we should sell
sexy bras to old ladies,
whereas I think we should sell
adult bras to young girls.
Abe agrees with me.
So does Don.
Well, it's not fair that just because
you're a boob-carrying consumer
that your opinion means more.
You know what? I should take off.
I've got a deadline.
And, honestly, I didn't
have enough dinner.
- I should go home.
- Oh, okay.
- I'll call you in the morning.
- Good night.
Mm-hmm.
He's too good-looking
for you.
My father won't care if he
finds out you read James Bond.
You know what?
This is a good book.
You should read it.
Your father said they'll sightsee
with the kids during the day
and watch them when we go out
with Heinz tomorrow night.
You'll have to give
me some cash.
He won't even buy
himself a pretzel.
And they can watch them the
night of the cancer dinner.
That's the whole reason
they came down,
- to see you get the award.
- They came to see you.
And your father's got a
meeting with some publishers.
One publisher.
We'll call the sitter.
Francis the talking mule?
Don't you want them to come?
I don't think anything's
gonna make him like me.
Because I'm his favorite.
Why do you think my mother
is so competitive?
I didn't see that.
Didn't you notice
she touched you
six times in an hour?
She's French.
No, that's not what that is.
Well...
Goodnight.
They'll be gone on Sunday.
Do you have a minute?
Lock that and get Dawn to hold
my calls so you can have five.
No, pervert.
This is about work.
I think it is, anyway.
I think I have an idea.
It might be really good.
But it might be terrible.
Well, you've established
a firm bed of insecurity.
Okay.
Last night when I was
feeding the kids spaghetti,
I realized that my mother
had made it for me
and that her mother
had made it for her.
And I got this picture
in my head of her becoming me
like with one of those
movie dissolves.
And then this morning
in the shower,
I realized you could
take it all the way back
to cavemen and then
do the middle ages,
the renaissance,
all the way up to now
and then the future,
like a colony
on the moon and you see
earth out the window.
That's very good.
But we don't sell spaghetti.
No, Heinz baked beans.
Oh.
It solves a lot
of problems, doesn't it?
My God.
Get over here.
No, I don't want
to change the subject.
I'm not changing the subject.
What are we showing tomorrow?
Human cannonball.
I mean, it's funny
and I loved it,
but...
Dawn, get Stan and Ginsberg
in here right away.
Oh, they're gonna hate me.
Tell them it was your idea.
You don't really want me
to do that, do you?
No.
"Kids want beans
and they have forever."
Oh, I had something like,
"Heinz beans,
some things never change."
Jesus, I think that's better.
- You rang?
- I'm gonna need both of you on Surrette.
We're changing Heinz.
Mr. Drexler for you.
Thank you, Patricia.
- Hello?
- How's Minetta tavern sound for dinner?
It's Thursday.
Not good.
- You're gonna eat anyway.
- Well, come by.
I'm not coming by. I can't talk to
you there and I don't want to wait.
Oh, okay.
I could meet you early
if I come back.
6:00?
7:00.
I'll see you there.
She couldn't have been
struck by lightning a week ago?
You think that's her idea?
What happened?
Boss's wife had an idea.
- Is it any good?
- It's better than what we had.
Good for her.
Come in.
I'm supposed to be in the
final mix for Vicks tonight
and I need to switch it.
It's very important.
Who scheduled it.
I have something else to do.
Well, that almost never
happens, so don't feel bad.
It doesn't, does it?
Can I have a cigarette?
Joan?
Do you want to close the door?
I thought everything
was going great, but...
Now I have this terrible
feeling about Abe.
I think he's gonna end it.
Why?
He wants to have dinner
and he knows
weeknights are hard.
And we just saw
each other last night.
And he wouldn't
take no for an answer.
Well, it's been my experience
that when a man insists on a meal,
he has something important to say.
It's usually a proposal.
Really?
Well, that's you.
Men don't take
the time to end things.
They ignore you
until you insist on
a declaration of hate.
Someone dumped you?
Peggy, I'm just like
everybody else.
If he's going to end it,
which I doubt,
you'll know what to do.
If he's going to propose, you'd
better have your answer prepared,
especially if it's no.
Gosh.
I should go home
and change, shouldn't I?
Or better yet,
go shopping.
So the mom's wearing
the glass space helmet
and the kid took his off
and put it on the table?
That way, the kid
can eat the beans.
And I thought you
could do the whole thing
with the same actors
playing mother and child.
Mr. Sterling's here to see you.
Oh, you two
are actually working.
Go break it into frames
and have Stan draw it up.
I've been working
this morning, too.
You mean you finished yours,
you're moving onto mine?
No, I've been in
the war room, Don,
preparing for the American
Cancer dinner.
Caroline went to the library and
got me pictures of these guys.
I'm $50 away
from a seating chart.
Look, I don't take
this honor lightly.
Good.
Say something like that.
Titans of industry
are giving you an award.
We are being lowered in a
bucket into a gold mine.
I'm gonna bring my pick and
crack something off the wall.
I don't think it's
that kind of atmosphere.
You actually saying that
with a straight face?
You forget why
you wrote that letter?
Are you forgetting you said
it would kill our business?
So you think cigarettes are bad
and so are the people
who sell them?
It's what they think.
Mary Lasker and the rest of
them know it as the truth.
It doesn't matter
why I wrote it.
You're right.
Who knows why people
in history did good things?
For all we know, Jesus was trying to
get the loaves and fishes account.
I'll do what I can, but I'm
not gonna go overboard.
My in-laws don't think
I'm Jesus.
They'll be clapping
and cheering.
They don't know
you're a hypocrite.
Megan's father is a communist.
- What?
- He's a socialist
or a maoist or some ideology
plus, you know, I'm
sleeping with his daughter.
So he'll see you shaking hands.
You know,
it's very interesting,
but a lot of times you think
people are looking at you,
but they're not.
Their mind's elsewhere.
Lots of people that haven't taken LSD.
Already know that, Roger.
You're gonna be like
an Italian bride--
People lining up
to give you envelopes.
- You look good.
- Thank you.
The steak is supposed
to be good here.
The menu's huge.
The service is incredible, but I told
them to leave us alone a second.
Can I get a drink?
Yeah, sure.
I guess I can get
somebody's attention.
No.
Forget it.
What do you want to say?
Okay.
I've been thinking about this.
We're at a place where
we love being together.
It always seems to be
some kind of pain in the ass
to be in the same place
when the lights go out.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, well,
I think we should
move in together.
I mean, how would
we ever do that?
Well, however you want.
I mean, I think your place
would be better.
It's because that's how I feel.
I just like the idea
of the two of us
waking up in the same
place every day.
The two of us writing
together in the same room,
looking at each other
every once in a while.
Grocery shopping.
Look,
I know it's a big decision.
So you don't have to say
yes or no right now.
Maybe we should order.
Oh, excuse me.
Yes.
You've made me so happy.
Me, too.
You still want to eat?
I do.
Actually, my father is on the board
of the American cancer society.
Although he said the voting
was unanimous for Don.
Well, that is quite an honor.
And as much as we
appreciate the invitation,
we're heading back
to Pittsburgh
the minute I leave
your office smiling.
You're really gonna rush off?
I think Ken got you tickets to the new
Edward Albee play.
- Oh, we saw it on Tuesday.
- You did?
Yeah, we came in
a couple days early.
Alice loves the city.
Did I not mention that?
No reason to, I guess.
Raymond, would you
order me a sanka?
I'm gonna freshen up.
And some dessert.
Come on, why not?
You know, I've always
wanted to eat here.
I thought it was just
for time life employees.
You know, I really enjoy
spending time with you.
I feel the same way, Alice.
I'm only saying this because Raymond's
putting on such a good show.
He didn't want to go to dinner.
He just wanted to
do it in your office.
He's a good man, I swear.
Of course he is.
I was really prepared
to not like you,
but you're so good
for that man.
- And you're so lively.
- Thank you, Alice.
I'm just saying I hope we
can continue to be friends.
No, see, the truth in packaging
bill they wanted to pass
would hit everybody hard,
but now there's no teeth.
So nothing should change.
We're getting fired.
Sorry, but we ended up getting more
dessert than we bargained for.
Who's up for a nightcap?
That's okay.
I think we're gonna turn in.
Do me the favor, Raymond.
You don't know this,
but you've rescued me
from a house full
of in-laws and children.
Can we get a bottle of
sauternes and six glasses?
I don't know. We have the early
meeting tomorrow and the flight back.
You know, Don jokes about
having a house full of people,
but he loves it.
Don?
Don, tell him about last night.
Oh, well,
we had three generations
under one roof--
Megan, her mother
and my 12-year-old Sally.
Sally won't eat anything,
as you might imagine.
Except beans, of course.
It's true.
They do like them.
Never had any worries
about that.
You should have seen it--
Megan bringing the pot in,
spooning them out on the plate,
her mother was smiling.
- What a darling scene.
- Actually, I didn't know
if I had done something wrong
because Don was staring at us.
But apparently
I'd given him this idea.
She did.
Don, you sure you want
to talk about this now?
Let him talk.
Obviously there's more to it,
but I think it would be
a series of one-shot
little movies.
One mother starting
in the prehistoric caves
serving beans to a shaggy
little boy by the fire.
Then a Greek woman
in a toga with
a little shepherd boy.
Then Marie Antoinette
to a little prince.
Mary Jane to a pioneer boy.
All the way through
the gay '90s to today
in a kitchen like yours.
Would it all be the same
mother and child?
We hadn't thought of that,
but that might work.
Tell him the rest of it.
Well, it goes past
present day to the future
to a little lunar kitchen with
the earth off in the window.
You know, futuristic
clothing, interesting bowls.
The kid has just taken off
his space helmet
as he takes a warm bite.
Oh, that's clever.
That was Megan's idea.
When Don told me, I thought,
we're all so busy
and we rush around
and it will probably
always be like that.
But a mother and child
and dinner--
That'll never change.
"Heinz beans,
some things never change."
- Can I get some more coffee?
- Shh!
I don't know what to say.
Let me think about it.
See the pictures.
Raymond, really?
It's beautiful.
And it's exactly--
I don't know.
Can I get the cream, please?
Well, we were dancing around
a few other things, too.
No, we weren't.
This is what you're gonna see tomorrow.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime idea.
Raymond, you could save yourself
a trip to the office tomorrow
or we can get in the
elevator, go down 11 floors
and show you
the work right now.
It's the future.
That's all I ever wanted.
Should we change that
sauternes to champagne?
Sure, why the hell not?
72nd and Park.
Do you know you're good
at all of it?
You had the idea
feeding me the pitch, knowing to
pull the trigger at that moment.
I was just gonna scream
in his stupid face.
I'm glad you didn't.
I love the way you sold that.
Oh, my God.
I want you.
But we have to go
back to the house
with the kids and your parents.
We can go back to the office.
Change of plans.
Back to time life, please.
There's champagne
in the conference room.
Don and Megan sold Heinz
last night over dinner.
But, by looking
at your fingers,
maybe you're not
in the mood to celebrate.
No, of course.
It was better than that.
Really?
We're moving in together.
He asked me.
Shacking up?
My goodness.
I know, but--
No, Peggy.
Good for you.
Really?
You're not just saying that?
No.
I don't know.
Sounds like he wants to be
with you no matter what.
I thought you were going
to be disappointed for me.
I think it's very romantic.
It is, isn't it?
We don't need a piece of paper.
I mean, not that marriage
is wrong or anything.
Greg has a piece of paper
with the US Army
that's more important
than the one he has with me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It is what it is.
I think you're brave.
I think it's
a beautiful statement.
Congratulations.
So Megan comes out and does a double
secret reverse to Don that it's over.
Then they just passed it back and
forth like a couple of pros.
- You weren't even there.
- Way to go.
You should be shaking her hand.
- It's just beginner's luck.
- Oh.
- I'm gonna go tell Peggy.
- Tell everybody.
You want the
pleasure of telling Lane?
No, you earned it.
Besides, we're still
at least 15 grand
out of pocket on the account.
Megan!
Congratulations.
- Oh, you heard.
- Yeah.
Joan told me Harry said
you signed Heinz.
I don't want to take
all the credit.
Why aren't you
jumping up and down?
I don't know what the Canadian
equivalent of baseball is,
but this is a home run.
- We have baseball.
- Well, this is a home run.
I know what you did
and it is a big deal.
And when it happened to me, they
acted like it happens all the time.
It doesn't.
I tried to crack that nut.
I mean, if anything,
I should be jealous.
But I look at you
and I feel like,
I don't know,
I'm getting to experience
my first time again.
It's a good day for me.
This is as good
as this job gets.
Savor it.
You're right.
I will.
Good morning, Emile.
Where is everyone?
The girls went out
and Bobby is helping me
fill my fountain pen.
Thanks, Emile.
Hello.
Bonjour.
Uh-oh.
It's not as bad as you think,
but it's pretty bad.
- Sally.
- Go ahead.
Papa, can I come with you to see
you get your award tonight?
Papa?
I don't know.
I got a dress.
Please?
Every daughter should get
to see her father as a success.
It's fine.
Sweetheart, of course
you can go.
Thank you, daddy.
Can I show you my dress?
Bobby, put that away.
You two watch TV or something.
What was that about?
My father went to his
publisher this morning
and was back within the hour.
And then he got on
the phone with claudette,
his latest grad student.
My mother walked in.
He was crying, apparently.
Well, he's got a lot
wrapped up in that book.
He should be crying
to my mother, Don.
Oh, right.
What about tonight?
They do this all the time.
They'll recover.
They always do.
Hurry, it's really hot.
Wait.
Hi, ma.
Come in.
Hello, peaches.
Abraham.
Hello, Katherine.
Oh, you brought dessert.
Just leave it in the box.
I'll take it out.
It's very delicate.
You want some sherry?
Sure.
Smells good in here.
Peggy made a ham.
It's my favorite.
Really?
- Are you babysitting?
- No.
- Hello.
Roger Sterling, this is Dr.
Emile and Marie Calvet.
You ladies look ravishing.
- Thank you.
- Can I get you a drink?
Uh, no.
I mean, yes.
But does anyone know
how to tie this thing?
- Here.
- I'm stag tonight
and my doorman
wears a clip-on.
I am surprised.
You seem like you were
born in a bow tie.
I didn't tie that one either.
Good evening, everyone.
My God.
Sally, you look so beautiful.
You're beautiful, sweetheart.
Don, there is
nothing you can do.
No matter what, one day
your little girl
will spread her legs
and fly away.
- What? It's true.
- Wings, daddy.
Take off the makeup
and the boots.
What? No.
Or you can stay home.
Fine.
This is the ballroom?
There's no staircase.
But here's a handsome prince.
Nah.
Hello, all.
Don't you look lovely?
I hope you don't mind if I steal
your father for a moment.
I'd love for you
to meet Ed Baxter.
- Ken's father-in-law.
- No, of course.
Megan, could you join us?
I got 'em.
Ed, Don Draper, his wife Megan.
Pleased to meet you.
Both of you.
I guess I should
thank you for this.
No, don't thank me.
I had to recuse myself.
But you write
some stirring copy.
Actually, Megan's a hell
of a copywriter as well.
Well, I should lie,
but Cynthia told me
all about your dinner.
- She's a natural.
- Thank you.
- Who's he?
- His name is Ed. He's at dow corning.
They make beautiful dishes,
glassware, napalm.
- Peter Campbell.
- Emile.
And his wife's name is Lillian.
- Don't forget that.
- I won't.
And those two over there, the
balding guy with Margaret Dumont,
he's at GM.
Where's your purse?
You're gonna be my date.
Every business card
I bring back,
you're gonna put it in your purse
and say "go get 'em, tiger."
- So I manage those accounts.
- I don't understand.
What do you do every day?
Well, what do you do?
You're a scholar
and an intellectual, right?
Yes.
Actually, from what I hear,
you're a bit of a trailblazer.
I don't know if that's true.
I bet the world would be better off if
they knew about the work you're doing.
You are very kind.
That, Emile,
is what I do every day.
Ah.
Shit.
I've got to beat the entree.
Cover me.
Your dad is very resourceful.
Please.
I got this.
I'm sorry, honey.
I wasn't gonna leave before dessert,
but this is taking a little
longer than I thought.
Well...
We have something
we want to tell you.
Really?
Abe and I are very
serious about each other
and we've decided we're
going to live together.
What?
Listen. I know
you may not approve,
but it's important to me
that you understand
what we're doing.
I will take
very good care of her.
You know what?
I'm gonna go.
What?
I need my cake.
Why?
Because I'm not
giving you a cake
to celebrate youse
living in sin.
Would you rather
I not tell you?
Yeah. You want to
stick it in my face?
Just lie. You think you're the
first ones ever to do this?
- Ma.
- What do you want from me?
I'm gonna get you a cab.
I invited you here as an adult
because I didn't want to lie
and I want you in my life.
Well, if you're an adult,
why do you care what I think?
I thought you'd be relieved
I wasn't marrying the Jew.
It has nothing to do with that!
It's my fault.
Because once your father died, there
was no one to set you straight.
I know what I'm doing.
And I think daddy would
want me to be happy.
No. He'd be mad at you
the same way I am
because you are selling
yourself short.
This boy, he will
use you for practice
until he decides to get
married and have a family.
And he will, believe me.
You want me to be alone?
You know what
your aunt used to say?
You're lonely, get a cat.
They live 13 years,
then you get another one and
another one after that.
Then you're done.
Thank you for dinner.
All of us here appreciate
your years of service.
Ooh, baked Alaska.
It's flaming, but they probably don't want
- to wreck the speeches.
- You're wrecking the speeches.
You're a mean drunk. You know that?
From the Sterling Cooper Draper
Pryce advertising firm...
- Oh, your daddy's next.
- Mr. Donald Draper.
Thank you.
Shouldn't I be at his side?
Go get 'em, tiger.
Can I see it?
Do you want it?
No, you should keep it because
it makes you really happy.
You know what makes me happy?
A beautiful young lady
who will someday
be wearing makeup,
but not today.
I got you a shirley temple.
It's time to start
tapering off.
And, Don, I promised Frank
from Ford over there
you'd come and say hi.
I'd buy you a drink, but I
think they're still free.
I have been watching
you all night.
You're so full of life
and ambition.
Well, I've gotten
a lot of rejection,
so who knows what I'm full of?
When I was younger,
it was my spirit
to try everything,
get a taste,
know what was what,
and never be sorry
for making the mistakes.
And then one day,
I made too many mistakes.
Where was I that day?
Inside you is a little boy.
Well, Marie, I woke up one day
and I realized at what point
should you ever stop trying?
I agree.
We should have
everything we want.
I'm going to the ladies' room.
Can you watch the award?
I got it.
Daddy, I'm glad you came.
Then why do you look so sad?
I'm not.
I'm just tired.
It's been a busy week.
Yes, you have
a big beans success.
Don't make fun, papa.
I know you don't approve.
Is this your passion?
Because you have changed.
I always thought
you were very single-minded
about your dreams and that that
would help you through life.
But now I see that you
skipped the struggle
and went right to the end.
It's not the end.
It's the beginning.
This apartment, this wealth
that someone handed to you,
this was what Karl Marx
was talking about.
And it's not because
someone else deserves it,
it's because it is
bad for your soul.
Don't beat me
with your politics
because you hate
that I love Don.
No, I hate that you gave up.
Don't let your love
for this man
stop you from doing
what you wanted to do.
- Excuse me.
- I've been telling Ken
you should get out of
your business altogether.
Why is that?
I'd introduce you to him,
but I don't want you
to waste your time.
He's on the board.
- He obviously likes my work.
- He loves your work.
They all do.
But they don't like you.
- What?
- This crowd,
they'll bury
your desk in awards,
but they'll never
work with you,
not after that letter.
I mean, how could
they trust you
after the way you bit the hand?
Oh, sorry about that.
You want another?
Yeah, sure.
Two.
- Excuse me, miss. Are you
finished with that? - Yes.
- Yeah?
- Did I wake you?
Yeah, but it's okay.
I get a lot of attention
every time you call.
People think
you're my girlfriend.
I'm not.
Why are you whispering?
I'm in Manhattan at my dad's.
Bluto broke her foot.
Spectacular.
Yeah.
How's the city?
Dirty.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com