Previously on
AMC's Mad Men...
You said that I
should see a psychiatrist.
Doctors must love that
they now have an answer
for I don't know what's wrong.
Jai Alai is leaving.
- What?
- It's over.
Debbie. In your
dorm, I know.
He's dad! And he's never
coming back! And nobody cares!
Stop it.
Look, Pete, we're gonna
resign the Clearasil account.
I hate it here.
Every time I go around a corner
I keep thinking I'll see my dad.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Donald draper's office.
In addition to the two major
Smokers and cold sufferers,
Is another group
that eats them as candy...
The technical term
is "hypochondriacs."
Donald draper.
Donald draper's office.
- Hello?
You said not to buzz you
all the time,
But I don't know
how else to do this.
- You have a phone call.
- You can buzz me
for a phone call.
Things like coffee
after I've said no,
You don't have to ask again.
You're always asleep in here.
Walter Hoffman
from "the times."
he's a reporter.
- What's it regarding?
- You want me to go ask?
I think we're done here.
"New York times."
- This is don.
- Hi, it's Walter Hoffman
from "the New York times."
I write
the advertising column.
I know who you are.
What can I do for you, Walter?
I just wanted to know
if you'd heard
That cutler, Gleason & Chaough
just signed clearasil.
I don't keep track of accounts
once we resign them.
I just think it's
kind of interesting
that first c.G.C.
Takes the jai alai
association from you
and now this.
- How do you explain it?
- I don't think about it.
Well, I talked to Ted Chaough
And he said, "every time
don draper looks in his
rearview mirror,
- He sees me."
You have a partners' luncheon.
- What's your point?
- Do you
have a response?
- On the record?
- Please.
I've never heard of him.
Anything else?
No.
Have a good day.
This Selma thing
is not going away.
You still don't think
they need a civil rights law?
They got what they wanted.
Why aren't they happy?
Because Lassie
stays at the Waldorf
and they can't.
Please tell me
I missed everything.
I now call to order
a meeting of the partners.
Sterling, Cooper,
draper, Pryce in attendance.
Everybody.
Very well then.
Mr. Campbell.
Sector laxative
has finally agreed
To produce
a television commercial
and test market it.
How'd you ease them into it?
Must've had to
loosen them up first.
We've had that client
for 18 years, Roger.
Pete has other news.
A deerfield chum of mine
roped me into a dinner
for the Asia society,
The result of which
was a series
Of interesting phone calls
and one lunch
Regarding the Honda
motorcycle company.
They control over 50%
of the U.S. Market.
I've seen them.
They're cute.
They're miserable at Grey.
Well, 50% of the market?
Who wouldn't be?
"where's my other half?"
They're taking meetings
and as of 9:00 this morning,
we're on the books.
$3 million in
potential billings
And they're venturing
into automobiles as well.
When can you bring 'em in?
Listen, let me spare you
the agony and the ecstasy
And tell you we are not
doing business with them.
Excuse me?
Look, I don't expect you
to understand this
Because you were a little boy,
But I used to be a man
with a lot of friends.
World war ii came
And they were all killed
by your new yellow buddies.
Look...
If Bernbach can do business
with Volkswagen, we can do
business with anybody.
The war is over, Roger.
Why don't we just bring
Dr. Lyle Evans in here?
That'll be enough of that.
Lucky strike is great.
Meeting adjourned.
We don't usually
put new business
to a vote, do we?
Does anyone really
have a problem with this?
No.
When can you
bring 'em in?
Immediately, if possible.
I don't want to lose our spot.
So far I've been
advised to read
The "the chrysanthemum
and the sword."
From what I can tell,
they have their own way
of doing business.
Bert,
I'm hoping you'll help us
navigate these waters?
I'll prepare
a few salient points.
Keep Roger out of the loop.
A rather exciting possibility.
Good work.
Joan, get everybody that book.
I at least want them
to see it on people's desks.
Who the hell
is Dr. Lyle Evans?
I have no idea.
The body of a 38-year-old
unitarian minister
Was cremated within hours
of his death last night.
He had been clubbed
by white men who resented...
- come in.
- Hi.
- Sally?
- Hello.
I brought my doctor Kit.
Whoa.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
Enjoy yourself.
Which one is it?
I mean, which restaurant
in case I need to reach you.
Benihana's.
You're going to see
a girl, aren't you?
Yes I am.
- What's her name?
- Bethany.
I don't like that.
Well, you don't have to.
Bed by 9:00?
How do I love thee?
Let me count the ways.
Jesus.
What did you do?
she looks like a mongoloid.
- Is it that bad?
- Bobby, go to bed.
- Sally, get over here.
- No.
- good night.
Come over here.
I'm not mad.
Come on.
Your dad is gonna kill me.
He's actually gonna kill me.
You have short hair
and daddy likes it.
That doesn't matter.
You're not allowed
to do this
And you know that.
Are you and daddy doing it?
- What?
- I know what it is.
I know that the man pees
inside the woman.
Where did you hear that?
A girl at school.
You should talk to your mommy.
I don't want to.
Well, you don't need
to know right now,
So stop changing the subject.
I'm sorry.
Do you understand
I'm in worse trouble
than you are?
I just wanted to look pretty.
Come on.
We're gonna try
and fix this, okay?
You're not impressed.
My hair smells like
I've been frying chicken.
stop it.
This place is very expensive.
That's not it.
It's just not very intimate.
Three dates in five months?
Don't think I don't know why.
If it isn't
the inscrutable don draper.
Ted.
This is my wife Nan.
- This is my friend Bethany.
- Ted Chaough.
- Don draper.
- Pleasure.
Pleasure.
We just booked Howard Moses
to shoot clearasil.
- You ever work with him?
- Not yet.
I thought I was clever,
but it looks like you and I
had the same idea.
- What are you talking about?
- What do you think?
Honda?
You think the rest
of these tourists
Are from j Walter Thompson?
I suppose it's possible.
The good news is it's
gonna be between us.
The bad news is
the best man's gonna win.
Enjoy your dinner.
- We will.
- Nice to meet you.
- What are you doing, Ted?
- Job.
- Who's he?
- He's a fly I keep
swatting away.
They haven't done half
of what we have.
The minute he declared
himself the competition,
Suddenly we were equal.
Well, as far as I'm concerned,
he's no competition at all.
Hello?
We're not gonna let is
spoil our evening, are we?
No.
Do you know how to use those?
Yes.
Think you could teach me?
What time did they go to bed?
I'm really really sorry.
- They still up?
- No.
It's just...
I was watching TV with Bobby
And I turned around
for a second
And Sally cut her hair.
What?
It's pretty bad.
I could've
just left them alone.
She was in the bathroom.
I didn't know.
You were supposed
to watch them.
Don't.
I finally got her to sleep.
Do you know the River of Shit
I'm gonna get from her mother?
I'm sorry about that.
I tried to fix it,
But you'll probably
need to take her to
the beauty parlor.
Why the hell would she do that?
She probably wanted to look
older like Hayley mills.
I don't know.
- I really shouldn't.
- Consider it severance.
- Look...
- I don't want
your advice, okay?
Good night.
it's probably
the kids.
- Hi, mom.
- Did you have
a nice time?
Yeah.
Take that hat off.
Let me explain, okay?
- What the hell
happened to you?
- Calm down.
- You cut her hair?
- No.
- I cut it.
I'm sorry.
- Hey!
Betty.
- It was an accident.
- Jesus.
Betts, is that necessary?
I'm really really sorry.
Damn right you're sorry.
Get up to your room.
- Hold on.
- No, now.
It'll be okay.
Bobby, take your
little brother outside
and play.
- You didn't have to hit her.
- You're right,
Because it doesn't
do anything!
You have picture day.
- Forget about
your sleepover.
- Kids do this.
- You never did this?
- All I wanted was to
have long hair.
In fact when my mother
was mad at me,
She would threaten
to cut my hair.
- Where the hell were you?
- Look, it just happened.
The sitter wasn't
paying attention.
You know what?
I don't want to know
about your life.
You can't even
watch them for a second.
It's like leaving them
with nobody.
Because you're
so good with them?
Take her to the hairdresser.
Goodbye.
- Betty.
Henry, I don't want to hear it.
I want him dead!
You don't think I feel that?
I was divorced, Betty.
My weekends with Ellie
were sacrosanct.
I probably paid for
a building in play land
And he couldn't
take a night off?
And who knows
who he had watching her?
Some secretary, another whore?
But...
That's him, not Sally.
Little girls do do this,
And not just ones
from broken homes.
I know.
I was impulsive.
I'll apologize.
Having had a girl this age,
I can tell you that punishment
will only make this worse.
So when you're
up there apologizing,
You let her know
that she's going to go
to the hairdresser
And she can go
on her sleepover.
Reward her?
- Really?
- Really.
You're soft, you know that?
There you are.
The Honda meeting's today.
And before
you bite my head off,
I'm up to date on the protocol
with the help of Cooper.
We don't have to do anything
but avoid criticizing them
or giving advice.
I ran into Ted Chaough.
How are they in this thing
and how could you
not know that?
This guy's drafting off of us.
For the record,
it's j.W.T., c.G.C. And us.
Now if you don't mind,
I have to get some gifts wrapped
And get these chrysanthemums
out of the building.
Apparently
they symbolize death.
So much conflicting
information.
Allow me to show you around.
Our offices are probably more
modern than you've seen,
But that's the kind
of company we are...
forward-thinking.
This is what we call
the creative lounge.
We can't tell you
how it happens,
But it does
happen here.
This is too difficult.
Well, tell them something.
This is Joan Harris,
our chief hostess.
I'd like you to meet
Ichiro Kamura
And Hachi Saito.
Nice to meet you.
I hope no one's taken
you to Benihana.
David Ogilvy.
I've got a very good list
of steakhouses.
Just ask.
Not very subtle, aren't they?
No, they are not.
We are most happily
looking forward
To presentation.
Not now, I hope.
We want more driver
for motorcycle.
And we shall endeavor
to make that happen.
And now that we are finished,
Please accept our modest gifts.
I cannot accept.
A small token.
No thank you.
Please.
You are our guests.
Thank you.
- Open it.
- No. Later, of course.
It's a cantaloupe.
Johnny Walker red.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know
this meeting was happening.
Then again,
I know how some people
love surprises.
I apologize, gentlemen,
But for some reason
I was not informed.
In fact, someone set
a long lunch for me
with Randolph.
Well, it was last minute
and now, unfortunately,
drawn to a close.
I have to warn you
they won't know it's over
until you drop the big one...
Twice.
The meeting is not over.
We have yet
to present the rules.
So now you're dictating terms.
Mr. Kamura, Mr. Saito,
this is Roger sterling.
This is their translator
Akira Takahashi.
We give each firm $3,000
For a competitive presentation.
In this packet
are the conditions
for the competition.
We don't want any conditions.
We want it to be unconditional.
Akira, go ahead,
tell 'em what I said.
Roger, stop it.
- These men are our guests.
- I know exactly who
these men are.
You think you can just
come in here and we'll
Fawn all over you?
We beat you
and we'll beat you again.
We don't want
any of your jap crap.
So sayonara.
If you could only know
my embarrassment.
His wife's very sick.
He's been drinking a lot.
You have our rules.
We very much look forward
to your prestation.
You don't get
to kill this account.
- Well, you know how they are.
Maybe it'll kill itself.
- Enough.
I'm not even talking
about money right now.
I'm talking about
the kind of work you
could do for those people.
Have you seen
that motorcycle?
They love design.
As long as my name's
in that lobby,
I get to choose whom
I do business with.
I've got a lot better reasons
than you had with Jantzen.
Jantzen was over.
I made a pledge
to a lot of men
you'll never meet
Not to do business with them.
Christ on a cracker,
where do you get off?
You know what?
You weren't there.
You weren't anywhere.
I'm sorry you can't understand.
It's been almost 20 years.
Whether you like it or not,
the world has moved on.
These are not the same people.
How could that be?
I'm the same people!
You don't think
I know what you're doing?
You're wrapping yourself
in the flag
So you can keep me
from bringing in an account
Because you know
every chip I make,
We become less dependent
on lucky strike
And therefore
less dependent on you.
- Why you little...
- Roger!
Get him out of here.
The rest of us are trying
to build something.
He's right.
Where would you hide a coin?
You'd spend it, wouldn't you?
Well, I do know where it is.
I'll tell you.
Then tell me.
I'll make
a bargain with you.
Let these two go.
Keep me. I'll tell you.
- Promise.
- No.
Then no deal.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Laura.
Go upstairs.
Hold still.
I'll get it.
What's the problem?
Is she sick?
I would've come and gotten her.
No.
The slumber party
ended early.
I'd like to speak to Betty.
Okay.
Honey?
Is everything all right?
No, it's not.
Could you leave us
alone for a moment?
I found Sally behaving
inappropriately.
What'd she do?
She was in our den on the couch
Playing with herself.
What?
I don't know what goes on here,
But that kind of behavior
is not allowed in my house
And certainly not
in the presence
of my daughter.
I am...
Very sorry for this behavior
And so is Sally.
I would've done the same thing.
Well...
I'm sorry about that.
I should go.
What is wrong with you?
You don't do those things.
You don't do them in private
and you especially don't
do them in public.
- You have nothing to say?
- I didn't do anything.
Don't you dare lie to me.
I'll cut your fingers off.
Go to bed.
We'll deal with
this in the morning.
What happened?
I'm mortified.
I'm so embarrassed.
what happened?
She caught Sally...
Playing with herself.
What's wrong with her?
That woman will tell everybody.
why is she doing this?
I told you if it got serious,
Ere is a solution.
I don't want to do that, Henry.
It's one thing after another.
What's wrong with her?
Maybe it's time
we let a professional
answer that question.
Henry...
I went to a psychiatrist once.
What?
Why?
Because I was unhappy.
And I don't think
it helps anything.
I hate to think how much worse
It would have been
for Eleanor without one.
They train them just for kids.
We got ours from the school.
I'm saying this
not because I'm so sure
There's something
wrong with her,
But I think this is
very hard on you two.
- When did you go?
- Years ago.
I was bored.
- Can we leave it at that?
- Of course.
Miss Blankenship,
any luck on that call
to California?
I'm sorry.
No answer.
Misters Peters and Pryce
to see you.
Send them in.
I think we're okay,
but everything they do
is inside out.
I got a call this morning
from my contact Masao
Telling me that the meeting
was a Margaret Dumont-sized
disaster,
But then... lane?
Then nearly
20 minutes later
Masao called me
And set a time
for our presentation.
Look, there's probably
a guy like Roger
at every firm.
They've outgrown it
and we haven't.
Roger has something to say.
Mr. Cooper
and Mr. Sterling.
I realize that I
should not at this point
Limit our potential clients
in any way.
Next account,
no matter what it is,
you'll have my full support.
And?
Look, I know it's an old one
And I have to let it go
just for my health alone,
And, uh...
well, hell, it's over.
Your contrition wouldn't
have gotten you out of this,
but you're lucky.
They called and gave us
an appointment anyway.
That means nothing.
- It's over.
- No, Bert, I said
we have a meeting.
It's most likely that
they are expecting us
to come in and resign.
How do you get there from here?
Have we received a gift?
We should have
gotten one yesterday.
I haven't.
Miss Blankenship,
have I received any
packages today?
Yes.
Could you bring it in, please?
It says "don" on it.
Give it to him.
"help me, Honda,
help help me, Honda.
Love, Teddy Chaouh."
- So there is no gift.
- That's how they work.
They want us to go in there,
bow down and beg them
to chop our heads off
Because we disgraced ourselves.
How could you admire
these animals?
Would you shut up?
They're businessmen
And you insulted them
to their face.
I'm expecting a child.
Jai alai, clearasil, now Honda.
Chaough wins another one
by default.
- He's not going to win.
- I'm not wasting
that appointment.
We need to do something
That will make them
notice us... fireworks.
- Do you have a campaign?
- No.
But I will
and we're gonna shoot
a whole commercial for it...
Something outrageous,
something graphic.
The rules limit us
to boards and copy.
It specifically says
no finished work.
Because no one's ever won
an account by breaking
the rules?
- Not with the Japanese.
- You're trying to tell me
If we put our backs into this,
we couldn't turn their heads?
$3,000 is all we have.
That should buy
about four seconds
of your commercial.
You don't think it's worth
going out of pocket?
What pocket?
A spec commercial
will eat up our ability
To pitch anymore
new business this year.
It's only March.
I would be willing to risk
bankrupting this place
If I didn't think
we were already dead
in the water...
But we are.
Come on, Bert.
- Hello?
- Am I catching you alone?
What do you want?
I prefer not to talk
about this on the phone,
But it's our feeling
that Sally needs to see
a psychiatrist.
Our feeling.
Why, because she cut her hair?
No, it's more
serious this time.
I'm telling you
because I found someone
through the school...
A children specialist.
What exactly did she do?
She set the house on fire?
She was masturbating, don,
in front of a friend.
Does that seem normal to you?
Really?
Boy or girl?
Jesus.
What's the difference?
The doctor needs
to speak with us,
Individually of course.
So you've made up your mind.
Why are you even calling me?
She's out of control.
I thought you'd be concerned.
I am.
I just don't know
that she needs a doctor.
Can't you talk to her?
You think I want this?
I don't know what else to do.
You know what kind
of little girls do that?
- Fast ones.
- She's 10 years old.
Well, don't think
she doesn't understand.
She understands
a lot of things
thanks to you.
- What?
- I don't care what you do,
But just don't do it
with her there.
You brought another man
into your bed,
Into her house.
You don't think she
noticed that?
One man, don.
How many have you had
in your bachelor pad?
That girl you had
watching her?
Who's she?
- I'm married.
- Jesus. You ever
hear yourself?
I'll give the information
to your secretary.
- Perfect.
- Good night.
- Oh-ho!
- Yes!
Have you seen these?
I'm trying to figure out
what makes it work.
I'm still wondering
what makes you work.
Joan, Pete, Peggy.
Don't touch it.
I want to see how
long it goes.
What's wrong?
"a man is shamed"
By being openly ridiculed
and rejected.
"It requires an audience."
What is that?
Fortune cookie?
It's from that book
you were all supposed to read.
Oh.
Apparently making a commercial
for the Honda pitch
- Would bankrupt us.
- And it's against the rules.
Forget the rules
for a second.
C.G.C. Is
the same size as us.
If we can't afford to do
anything, they can't.
So everybody's bankrupt.
Chaough said he's
in my rearview mirror.
Guess what?
I'm gonna make a left turn
right off a cliff.
All I have to do
is let chaough think
I'm making a commercial
And he'll make one.
- So what's our campaign?
- We don't have a campaign.
We're not doing anything.
He just needs to think we are.
So what?
He's going to
make a commercial.
What if it's fantastic?
He'll win the account.
Let me worry about that.
I know she's the best rep
there is, but she told me
you were unavailable.
I am.
Clearasil doesn't wrap
until Friday night,
But maybe
you could push it.
It sounds interesting.
Well, Howard,
I'm going to insist
- On your discretion
at this point.
- Of course.
It's going to be
four to five days.
- just a minute.
Could you get the door?
I'm sorry.
I thought we'd
put this in here.
Later.
- Sorry about that.
- That's okay.
- You didn't see that.
- No, of course not.
- That's draper, isn't it?
- Yes.
Anyway, it's 12 scenes.
One of them obviously
has a crowd.
You'll need to figure out
how to shoot on the Staten
island ferry,
To it and from it
and how you're going
to close fifth Avenue.
I'll be honest.
I'd give anything to do this,
But right now I'm too busy.
Anyway, you know
I'd much rather shoot
your Honda commercial.
I don't have one.
Why the hell
did they call you in?
- They know I've got you booked.
- How can they afford that?
Get that kid in here
who worked for draper.
Anticipation.
Suspense.
A Honda tears through
a subway tunnel,
The train nipping at its tire.
he keeps looking back,
The train roaring at him.
He's wearing a racing helmet.
And then you see him
head up the steps.
- Can they do that?
- Howard'll make them do that.
Then he gets out
on the sidewalk,
Stops, kicks down
the kickstand,
Takes off the helmet
And he is a she...
California blonde.
Hands down,
that's your best idea.
We'll bring
a guy to the pitch
in a racing helmet,
Have him take it off...
it's a sexy girl.
- What?
- We only have $3,000.
- We're not shooting Shit.
How long did you
work for draper?
A little over two years.
When you were in a bake-off,
he ever break the rules?
I don't know.
He wouldn't have
shared it with me,
But definitely
doesn't think the
rules apply to him.
He once disappeared
for a month.
Does he like to play games?
He's always thinking
on the edges of
where you are.
I don't know.
He's... he's a genius.
You ever talk that way
about me?
Why don't you go work
for your boyfriend?
Get out.
And give me 20 different words
for "pimples." out!
Call Barbara about
Howard here and contact
the city of New York.
We need a subway.
How are you doing?
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
We're, uh...
we're late.
No you're not.
Closed set.
Sorry.
oh, you scared me.
Who are you feeding today?
Royal traveller Samsonite.
This is like a coconut.
Be careful.
There was a trapeze artist.
He made more in an hour here
Than he makes in a week
at the circus.
Have you ever had this?
Sake?
No.
I don't know how people drink
the way you do around here.
I'd fall asleep.
What's it like being
a trapeze artist?
Or did you just ask him
about his luggage?
It's good.
He was surprisingly modest.
His father does it
better than him.
He actually said that?
Best part of my job.
You'd be surprised
what people will say
to an interested stranger.
Why does everybody need
to talk about everything?
I don't know but they do.
And no matter what happens
while they're talking,
When they're done
they feel better.
You have kids?
No.
Where's your husband?
I'm not married.
But you're wearing...
you're divorced?
No.
This is just a stop sign.
I walk into a lot of offices
And it's helped me avoid
a lot of distracting
conversations.
But you told me.
Do you have children?
I do.
Two boys and a girl...
One and a half, seven and 10.
I'm sure it must be hard
to be apart.
I don't see them enough.
And when I do,
I don't know what to do.
When I drop them off
I feel relieved.
And then I miss them.
I'm sorry.
It is not going well.
My ex-wife thinks
my daughter needs
a psychiatrist.
And I assume
you're against that.
I don't know.
Well, I can't say there's
any evidence to support this,
But I'm pretty sure
if you love her and
she knows it,
She'll be fine.
Well, thank you for the drink.
I should be going.
Fake dinner plans
with your fake husband?
Good night.
Now from what you told me
on the phone
This year s been quite
eventful for your family.
I know it seems fast,
But I felt children
had no concept of time
And Henry's
really taken to them.
He has a daughter
and she's such an
exceptional young woman.
Well, if you choose
to have Sally work with me,
I'd like to meet her
And then interview you
and your ex-husband.
Well, I doubt
you'll ever meet him.
That's his level of interest.
Is this most recent incident
of the most concern for you?
Well, I know the divorce
is mostly to blame,
But she's been different
ever since my father died.
He lived with us briefly.
They were very close.
I wish he had met Henry.
That's my husband.
They would've gotten along.
My mother...
I don't know.
My goodness, if I had done
what Sally did...
My mother was
very strict about it.
My brother, he saved his money
And bought a nudist magazine
And showed it to me.
My mother found it
and she nailed it
To his bedroom door.
What about you?
I was private
and mostly outgrew it.
I see.
- Dr. Keener...
- call me Dr. Edna.
That's what the kids do.
Of course I know
children do this...
But not in public.
I feel like Sally did this
To punish me somehow
for everything.
That must be
a terrible feeling.
It is.
You have to believe me.
I had to get divorced.
I felt it best for them
to have some stability
in their life.
In the end,
she doesn't understand
that it'll be better.
Sounds to me
like it wouldn't be bad
for you to talk to someone.
No. No, I'm okay.
Well, I think
it'd be helpful if you and I
were to meet once a month
Just to keep up
with Sally's progress.
Will you tell me what
she talks about in here?
No.
And the other way
around as well.
No, that's better.
So I think we should start
at four days a week.
Let me go get my date book.
- Where's your film?
- What film?
That's how you're shaking it?
- I heard it stunk.
- We didn't make one.
- It's too expensive.
- Well, then you're out
of luck, Donny.
'cause I sure wouldn't
want to follow what
I showed them
With a speech
and a couple of posters.
Sterling Cooper draper Pryce.
Donald draper.
Where is Mr. Cooper
And Mr. Campbell?
And white hair.
- And sterling?
- They couldn't make it.
You created this set of rules
To even the playing field.
It says specifically
no finished work.
I understand not everybody
has observed this.
I don't really
want to be a part
Of a competition like that
So I'm withdrawing us.
What'd he say?
He said he is resigning.
You did not honor
your own rules.
Thank you for thinking of us.
Good afternoon.
The voiceover announcer
for lucky has a severe case
of chest congestion.
Get the boy wonder on it.
- Greg, accounts?
- No, Pete.
Have a drink.
It'll make me look younger.
I'm not gonna watch you
feel sorry for yourself.
I feel sorry for all of us.
Don's over there
surrendering right now.
Would you stop?
There was a kid
on the destroyer...
P.F.C. Brycen...
And he was
an honest-to-goodness poet.
- And then during...
- Roger.
I don't want to hear it.
My husband's gonna be
in uniform any day now.
How do you think
he's gonna feel
When one day
some Pete Campbell goes
to some Vietnamese doctor?
Since when is forgiveness
a better quality
than loyalty?
Roger, I know it was awful
And I know it'll never seem
like it was that long ago,
But you fought
to make the world
a safer place and you won
And now it is.
You think so?
Really?
I have to.
- Anything else?
- No.
Good afternoon.
Your daughter's
psychiatrist called.
Lower your voice, please.
- congratulations.
I just spoke
with Mr. Saito.
It seems Honda was never
going to leave Grey,
But of the three princes
invited to meet the princess,
You were the most charming.
We're first in the door
on their little car.
- And c.G.C.?
- Out of the running.
We killed him.
That stunt you pulled
was unseemly.
- The only reason
I let you continue...
- let me?
Do you think Joan
can rent stage space
without talking to me?
I let you
Because I realized
that our financial future
Was related to
Mr. Chaough's demise.
So what is it?
Are you thanking me
or reprimanding me?
Let's not pretend
like this wasn't
a big risk.
We're thanking you.
Send over what
you have on the car.
It redlines at 9,500rpm,
But it only has 57 horsepower.
- What?
- It's a motorcycle
with doors.
The nice thing is
it has windows
So you can see your brains
spatter against it
when it crashes.
They're working on it.
Cheers.
Hello, Sally.
I'm Dr. Edna.
Why don't you come inside?
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com