Sounds like the place.
I couldn't believe there were
two parties on this block.
I have no problem with Negroes.
I'm just worried about the car.
We can still go home.
This was your idea.
It's important that
we're here, for you.
For the people that work for you.
Lovely, go easy on that.
Some of them don't feel that way.
Is my nose running?
- How are you?
- Hi.
Sorry about that, buddy.
What did you do with your coats?
We left them in the car.
When we called to get directions
from somewhere else in New Jersey,
Paul gave Harry the idea.
I took my purse.
I can smell alcohol, but I don't see it.
It's him.
It's a party.
Cosgrove's doing great.
Let's go get a drink.
I'm going to stay here.
Come with me.
So you work for these stuffed shirts?
I work with them.
Peggy. Glad to see a familiar face.
Yes. How are you?
Introduce us to your friend.
Eugene, whom I just met,
was telling me that at Princeton
Paul used to dress up like a girl.
According to him,
that's the way Shakespeare did it.
Looking stunning, as always.
Much too good for him.
What are you doing out here?
Not enough subterraneans
in the Village?
I'm here because this isn't
Greenwich Village.
This is America.
How do you get to the city?
The number 33 bus takes you
right to Port Authority.
Trust me, Montclair is the knees.
We have Globe Trotter Antiques.
We have the Wellmont Theater.
Silent movies with organ.
The Montclair Art Gallery.
George Inness. Have you heard of him?
Of course I have.
Come.
Enjoy.
Imbibe.
You're a button, you know that?
And you're drunk.
Can't get Donna here on my desk
because she keeps refusing.
You're not allowed to do that.
I can't feel my cheeks.
I can.
I feel them fine.
My mother says when you
can't feel your cheeks,
it's time to stop.
Well, what do I do with this?
There. That works.
Oh, my God.
Don't you and Kitty
have some place to be?
Apparently, when they say "on call,"
it does not mean "available by phone."
You have to be in the hospital.
I'm sorry he didn't make it.
I'm looking forward to meeting him.
I've been having this pain right here.
You've met him.
How could I forget?
Big, handsome, saves people's lives.
Why did you get the nice glass?
Because I have the Rhône Gallagher.
Fine. What is it?
There's a ship that went down in 1871,
and the casks of Rhône were on it.
It was a very good year.
And it sank,
and they washed up
on shore two years ago,
and they sold 180 bottles,
and I have one.
But not a sofa.
Joan, I want you to meet someone.
My baby... Sheila.
Sheila White.
Joan is our senior secretary.
Office manager.
Sheila's an assistant manager.
At the Food Fair in South Orange.
She's saving for school.
- Kinsey!
- What?
The man upstairs is here.
God?
No. It's Mr. Hoffenberg.
He wants to talk to you.
He smells marijuana.
Don't talk until I get back.
I'm serious.
I don't think we have
a Food Fair in Manhattan.
Is it a big market with a parking lot?
It is.
Well, one day you'll drive in
in a station wagon
and be a customer.
I grew up out here.
I've already been a customer.
It's fun to meet the boys,
put faces with names.
Well, it's good to see
you and Paul together.
I have to say, when Paul
and I were together,
the last thing I would have
taken him for was open-minded.
I love your purse.
Thanks. I just got it.
What's that?
Marjorie. Works at the newsstand.
I like.
But behind her.
You stole that.
That's from the office.
That dumb girl almost got fired.
But she didn't.
I'm a writer. I need it.
Hey, Brooklyn, come home with me.
Why not? I live alone.
Why should I?
Because I like you,
and we're having a good time,
and I'm a good kisser,
and you know you want to.
Eugene.
I'm in the persuasion business,
and frankly, I'm disappointed
by your presentation.
Come on.
Fifth Avenue's a parking lot,
in both directions.
Traffic makes the parade look bigger.
What parade?
Colonel Glenn.
It's incredible what passes
for heroism these days.
I'd like ticker tape
for pulling out of my driveway
and going around the block three times.
It's not like people were shooting at him.
I think he's a winner.
Square jaw, false modesty.
Looks like he just took off
his letterman jacket.
You going to go down there
with your autograph book at lunch?
Can I just fire everyone?
Excuse me!
This is a place of business.
Colonel Glenn will be on Earth
for the rest of his life.
Plane went down.
American Airlines
Flight 1 to Los Angeles.
Crashed in Jamaica Bay.
...had suddenly become locked
in a death dive into the bay...
There could be
a hundred people on there.
Just fell out of the sky.
...turn prescribed
by Idlewild Airport rules.
The Federal Aviation Agency
said there is no rational basis
for grounding the Boeing 707
as a result of the crash.
Federal Aviation
administrator Najeeb Halaby
- summarizing...
- Turn it off.
...of the investigation
said there was no...
Pull all Mohawk ROP.
And anything in production, stop it.
But it wasn't a Mohawk plane.
We don't want people
opening their morning paper
and seeing a Mohawk ad
next to a picture of a floating engine.
The rest of you, stop crying
and figure out how we're going
to hit the ground running
in three weeks with new work.
Excuse me.
Well, for one thing,
we should probably avoid
the term "hit the ground."
How about "Idlewild to Rockaway
in less than eight minutes"?
Answer the phone, sweetheart.
- Some of the passengers...
- Sterling Cooper.
...were on their way
to a golf tournament.
Apparently, the minute the plane hit,
the bay turned plaid.
Get back to work.
Jets are made for dropping
bombs on Moscow,
not French cuisine.
Although I like those
little girls they have.
You know, they're completely captive.
Mr. Phillips to see you.
Send him in.
Someone should tell Draper
to pull everything from Mohawk.
He knows that.
I just had an interesting conversation
with Shel Keneally.
He's inside of American Airlines.
Is the plane still crashed?
Shel was a client
when I was at Y&R in London.
We had some times together.
It's complete chaos over there.
They have any idea what went wrong?
None.
Normal takeoff, perfect weather.
The thing just nose-dived, exploded.
That's not comforting.
Shel says they're going to
need to make a fresh start.
Did he say "fresh start"?
A few times.
That is an interesting phone call.
Yes.
I can't talk right now.
Mr. Campbell, are you all right?
Mr. Campbell?
I'm sorry. Am I bothering you?
What's going on?
I just got off the phone with my brother.
It's the strangest thing.
Apparently, my father
was on that plane.
What?
My father, he was on the plane.
God, I'm sorry to hear that.
I don't know what to do.
I just saw him at the barber.
Paul Molé on Lex.
What does one do?
Make arrangements, I guess.
What am I supposed to do?
What people do.
Go home.
I don't even think
I know how old he was.
Someone's going to ask that.
I don't know. I suppose.
You know what?
I don't think I'm going to tell anyone.
Am I going to cry?
You just had a shock.
I wouldn't...
worry about what you're feeling.
Go home and be with your family.
Why?
Because that's what people do.
Is that what you would do?
Yes.
Really?
Everything's exactly the same.
You should go home.
What about the Stouffer's meeting?
I'll cancel it.
It's not hurting anything.
There's life, and there's work.
Hey, I got one.
"Mohawk Airlines...
when you need to make it
past Jamaica Bay."
How about "American...
pioneering vertical flight"?
Mr. Draper, Mr. Cooper
would like to see you.
I spoke with Hank Lamont
over at Mohawk.
How are they doing over there?
He says they can weather it out.
I always get the feeling
that man opens his front door
and money comes in.
Always cleaned me out.
Best poker player in the South Pacific.
Duck, tell Don here
about your phone call.
Well, I put in a call to check in
with Shel Keneally
over at American Airlines.
He used to run International.
We're old pals.
He picked up the phone?
What's going on over there?
Shel says it's bedlam.
Anyway, he was
quite clear about the fact
that they're going
to want to make changes
if they want the dust to settle fast.
What does that mean?
It means they'll be looking
for a new image
and thus a new agency.
What's it been, four, three hours
since the plane went down?
You'll have to forgive me
for not looking at a bunch
of bodies in Jamaica Bay
and seeing the opportunity.
Adding a few hours or a day or a week
doesn't make this any more
of an opportunity.
- We already have an airline.
- We don't have American.
That's right, we have
the one whose planes
didn't just fall out of the sky.
That's good.
I'm sorry. Is there an issue?
$1 million. $7 million.
Am I missing something?
Did you sign American
during this phone call?
No, but Shel made it very clear
that if we can get rid of our conflict,
he'd love to hear our ideas.
It's a serious foothold.
A foothold.
I'd do anything for a foothold.
This is how it works.
We got a regional airline
so we'd have a shot at a big one.
I know how you had it in your head.
The President of American Airlines
sees a Mohawk ad,
falls in love, and says
"Get me that guy."
I'm sorry it didn't play out that way.
Easy.
We have a good client who trusts us,
who likes our work,
who pays their bills on time.
They don't deserve
to be thrown out the door
for a wink from American.
I can't believe this.
Anything else?
He'll be fine.
I'll need to cancel
my reservations to Sarasota
and, of course, Andrew's return flight.
But l... Well, they can't possibly expect...
I'm sure that's taken care of.
Dunham's taking care of all that.
Bud's on the phone
with him right now.
I'm sure he'll forget something.
There's no way that he
can remember everything.
Bud's very good with things like this.
Is he aware there is no way
to have a funeral without the remains?
What's the difference?
You're right.
There's just so much to do.
What is that?
What?
That.
What is that?
Take it.
I want you to have it.
He was such a fine man,
so well-mannered, civic.
My father admired him.
What a nice thing to say.
I like to offer a nice
bouquet of thoughts.
Did you take care of everything?
They do this all the time.
- What?
- I took care of it.
Give me another one
of those, a big one.
Dunham had
some unpleasant news.
Dad was insolvent, broke.
Is there enough for a funeral?
As if the idea of a will
never crossed your mind?
We weren't going to get that.
You weren't.
What about her money?
The Dykeman Trust isn't
as solid as one would hope.
A lot of loans were taken
out by the president...
and recipient... Daddy.
Really? For what?
I asked Dunham
if there was a woman.
He said no.
It's all oysters, travel,
and club memberships.
Does she know?
You want to tell her? Go ahead.
Everything's been taken care of.
Boys.
Father called you salt and pepper.
That's beautiful, Dot.
Hi, Daddy.
I made you a ham sandwich.
What is this?
Carlton and Francine are
coming over for cards.
Oh, Bets. Didn't we just do that?
We haven't done it
since before Christmas.
And they keep inviting us,
and we never go.
- Can I play cards?
- I want to play.
I'm going to lie down for a minute.
I have the chenille bedspread on.
Pull it back or they'll see
the marks on your face
and know you were sleeping.
You can say hello to everyone,
then it's off to bed.
Muddled. That means smash it.
He'll be nicer on the second one.
You did a wonderful job on mine.
Thank you.
Go take Mommy and Francine's orders.
Bobby, that is your last one.
All right. Come on, go.
Watch TV.
They're growing like weeds.
That's true.
We have the Caruthers girl
over to baby-sit already.
Can you believe that?
I don't think we know her.
You'd remember.
Goes to lmmaculate Heart.
I've been out
of high school a long time,
but honestly, the way these girls dress,
and those uniforms.
Carlton.
What?
I'm enjoying this story so far,
but I have a feeling
it's not going to end well.
I think that Francine
brings her in to torture me.
I mean, everything I do
rubs her the wrong way.
I got rid of the apartment in the city.
I'm taking her to Nassau.
There was a pie
cooling in the windowsill,
and I'm not even
supposed to smell it?
It's Darkness at Noon.
- What do you want to hear?
- Now, come on.
Don't be like that.
Two Tom Collins.
Okay, you don't smash
the cherry on that.
Just plop it in at the end.
Try to keep it in the top of the glass.
Gin.
Oh, good, you didn't wait.
We couldn't. It's late.
Work.
Your hair looks nice.
It does,
and she fought with Mr. Pierre
every minute of it.
He's got some funny ideas.
You want something to eat?
No, thank you. I already ate.
Connie Griffin was in her yard,
hanging laundry in Bergen Beach.
She saw the whole thing.
Can you imagine?
WOR said there were
sharks eating the victims.
That's worth reporting.
You want toast?
Mama, I already ate.
You say you're coming to dinner,
and you already ate?
I came because I wanted to see you.
We never see you.
I'm here. Right now.
Such a pretty face.
Gladys Rhine was asking for you at church.
Babe saw your brassiere ads
in the newspaper.
You should see poor Donny.
His skin is horrible.
Clearasil.
- He's beyond that.
- It's a shame.
He's a handsome boy.
Lots of people was
asking me about you.
Doesn't mean the same thing
to me that it means to you.
I think your father would like it
if you lit a candle for him.
I pray for you.
You know she lies and tells people
you're out of town on business.
She has some made-up church
in Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania,
where you go to mass with a friend of hers.
No one asked her to lie.
She's not going to be here forever.
Would it kill you to go?
I don't want to.
And I'm capable of making
my own decisions.
Really? State of New York
didn't think so.
The doctors didn't think so.
Did you bring the vacuum?
Yes.
Did you empty the bag?
How do you let her get away
with making a bid of 150?
She usually overbids.
How was I supposed to know?
I do not overbid. I'm cautious.
I hear it's going to be
a row of apartments
all up Cedar Lane.
No more cedars.
No parking around the school.
You know, I could've had
that property for a song?
A song and a half, tops.
I thought he was crazy,
but there you go.
I'm sure we have
something else to talk about.
Did you hear about that jetliner?
Terrible. It's terrible.
I was supposed to fly to Cleveland.
Now I can't. I have to take the train.
Nine hours.
You have got to be kidding.
Sorry.
I love the train. You do, too.
Bobby.
Go back to bed.
I'm scared. I heard something.
Everything's great. Go back to bed.
Bobby.
Come on.
Do what your mother says.
When I was a child,
I would've been way more
afraid of my father
than of going to sleep.
I hated going to sleep
when I was a kid.
But I bet you did when you were told.
With a stack of comics and a flashlight.
I don't care what they do
when they're up there.
I just like a few hours of quiet.
Ernie tests my patience.
Said he saw a ghost.
He was scared.
He's a little liar.
He is?
He drew the most amazing picture
of George Washington the other day.
His teacher was so impressed,
she put it up in the hallway.
It really looked like him.
Well, obviously.
Because he brought it home,
and I noticed the exact same
image of Washington
on the cover of one of his books.
He had traced it.
What happened?
He brought a book to school
so he could trace it?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe they had it there.
I mean, the point is it was dishonest.
My whole art department
is run on tracing paper.
Why reinvent the wheel?
I've got the rest.
I don't care about tracing.
What about all
that praise he accepted
for something he didn't do?
Well, the book says they
start fibbing at this age.
They want to see if they
can make it come true.
I don't need a book
to know what little boys do.
You have anything you want me
to take back to the library?
Anything you want me to pick up?
No. I have to renew
The Agony and the Ecstasy.
It's taking forever.
I should go. I have to work tomorrow.
Busy bee.
Aren't you going to say good night?
Hi, Aunt Peggy.
Marilyn says Helen Bishop's
trying to stop them
from putting parking meters
at Depot Plaza.
Apparently, she got chummy
with some administrator at the high school.
Big, fat fellow.
Carlton's put on a few.
I think it's nice he's filled out.
It shows he's happy.
I wouldn't say that.
Why not?
Did he say something?
What did he say?
He didn't say anything.
Well, he should be happy.
Okay, maybe he is.
He should be happy and grateful
and showering Francine with love
after what he put her through.
Look, Bets, I'm not going to fight.
I'll say whatever
you think I should say,
but I'm not going to fight with you.
What, sweetheart?
You laughed. What's funny?
I just...
I was just thinking that the last
conversation I had with him,
we were arguing about
whether Barney Kellogg
bred Boston terriers
or French bulldogs.
I'm sorry you were arguing.
Those ugly little pushed-in faces.
The labored breathing.
He said they were French bulldogs.
I said they were Boston terriers.
He was angry about it.
Oh, Peter, neither of you
knew it was the last time.
Fighting about facts, my mother calls it.
We do it all the time.
Argue over something
that's actually one thing or another.
What do Barney's dogs look like?
Just beige.
Kind of like pugs, but with big ears.
Those are French bulldogs.
Really?
When I woke up, I felt fine for a minute.
Then I remembered.
You should be thinking
about the good times.
Right.
So they go out a third time,
and now the restaurant's
even worse... Indian food.
But she really likes him.
I told you he worked
for City Hall, for the Mayor.
- So what happened?
- I need three copies.
One goes to Mr. Robinson,
one to Mr. Fairbanks,
and one to Mr. Smith.
The strange one.
That doesn't narrow it down.
Thank you.
Mr. Kinsey.
Is something wrong?
I'm avoiding you.
Or haven't you noticed that
after three days?
Are you worried
about the typewriter?
I'm not going to tell anyone.
Although you were so brazen,
you don't deserve clemency.
What did you say to Sheila?
- Who?
- Sheila.
My girlfriend.
Describe her to me.
Very funny.
I know what's first on the list.
Oh, my God, I knew
you were a lot of things...
I'm not a phony.
You're so proud.
It's so obvious why you're seeing her.
A supermarket checkout girl?
Conversation must be stimulating.
Lettuce costs a nickel.
What a relief. You're just jealous.
Because you're the one who got away?
You, out there in your
poor-little-rich-boy apartment
in Newark or wherever.
Walking around with your pipe
and your beard,
falling in love with that girl
just to show how interesting you are.
Go ahead. What part is wrong?
Pete?
Duck. Come in.
Where's the girl?
She's supposed to tell me
if she goes anywhere.
When my old man died,
I went on a hell of a bender.
You heard about that.
I had to read about it
in the Times.
I wish you felt that you
could talk to me about it.
You should be able to.
We're practically family here.
I don't know, Duck.
There's not a lot to say.
No. Of course not.
Your old man was in advertising, right?
Boston.
Used to talk about the '20s
like we're idiots.
My father wasn't.
Of course, it turns out
I really didn't know
anything about him
except that he did not
like advertising.
Ah, that's his style.
I'm sure he was proud of you.
Some people have trouble saying it.
Yes. That was a problem for him.
What's not to be proud of?
You pay attention. You're hungry.
Most of the time you know
what you're doing.
I've noticed that.
I appreciate that.
Now, I don't want you to think
I'm being insensitive,
but we're going after American Airlines.
Well, it's...
I don't want to make you
feel uncomfortable.
Okay.
I'm meeting at the University Club
with Shel Keneally.
Tonight, actually.
Get everything rolling.
If anything, I'd like you on board.
I want you leading
the way on this thing.
I think I am uncomfortable.
I don't think I should do that.
It just happened.
I haven't even cried yet.
Of course.
It was inappropriate.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Can you come in here
with the papers I asked for?
Sweetheart.
You mind?
I need you to set a meeting.
A quiet place, but public.
Have a heart-to-heart
with Henry Lamont.
Why would I do that?
Because we're cutting him loose.
Duck's having a meeting
with Shel Keneally
from American Airlines tonight.
He's letting them know
that Mohawk is over.
And that gets us a pitch?
It sends a signal that we're serious.
And that we're willing
to do whatever it takes.
He has nothing.
And this is more of it.
- It's desperate.
- Come on.
You should be salivating to
rip these guys away from DDB.
And even if we don't
win this account,
we're going to be on a list
in the New York Times
of big boys pitching for this business.
We have an airline.
What kind of company
are we going to be?
The kind where everyone
has a summer house?
I can't believe I look like an idiot
for wanting to be loyal
to these people.
Take off your dress.
You get a chance
at American Airlines, you take it.
End of discussion.
Hildy, can you get my wife on the phone?
Of course.
Forget it.
Mr. Campbell.
Don. Do you have a minute?
What do you want, Campbell?
I just was... I don't know.
It's not a good time.
If you want, you can
leave him a note.
People do that.
No.
Thank you.
Good night, Joan.
Did you see who did this?
No.
I never would have guessed
you were in your 30s.
People should not bring
their personal problems
into the office.
I agree.
Is it so hard to just leave
everything at the door
and just do your job?
I look forward to it.
They can't stand it.
They'll drag you into
the garbage out there.
They just want you to be
as miserable as they are.
I say let them have it.
Thanks.
How are you, Don?
Henry.
Sit down.
Can I get you anything?
You know, I'm glad you picked this place.
It reminds me of Pearl Harbor.
For many reasons.
Do you think you're not
going to have to say it?
Sterling Cooper has decided
to end its relationship
with Mohawk Airlines.
Sterling Cooper.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't my decision.
You know, when we came in there,
they all said Sterling Cooper
is Don Draper.
That's what you get.
That talk you gave me
about us growing together.
You said Sterling Cooper
didn't need a big airline.
You were going
to make us a big airline.
I wish things hadn't
worked out this way.
I'm almost embarrassed to say this.
You fooled me.
Stockholders weren't remotely impressed
with firing our head of ops.
So this agency change,
well, that's going to be a process.
And to be part of that process?
- Listen, we're here talking, right?
- Of course.
But it's hard for me
to leave here comfortable
unless I know what
your objections are.
Well, we're a few steps
away from objections.
We're just sticking a toe in the water.
Well, we're not. We jumped in.
Pete.
It's good to see you.
Shel, this is Pete Campbell.
I don't think he's our best.
I think he's the best.
Pleased to meet you.
You as well.
I was just telling my buddy Shel here
how we've really cleared
the way to be in this.
I was telling Duck here
we don't know where we are yet.
I don't think you're aware
of the level of commitment
and enthusiasm
for this project at Sterling Cooper.
It's true.
We've got writers bucking the gate.
I've already got a stack
of ideas on my desk
that I think you'd love to see.
We understand how delicate
the process of rebuilding
the public's confidence will be.
Not just the public. Our stockholders.
Well, I want you to know that,
should you decide
to bring us your business,
there will be someone
on your account
who knows exactly
what you're going through.
My father was on that plane.
My goodness.
Sorry to hear that.
Yes. Well...
it's a horrible thing.
Hopefully, something good
will come of it.
That is something I will pass on.
Shall we grab a bite?
I put our name in.
I'm not your waitress,
but are you all set here?
Excuse me?
You've been sitting alone a long time.
Can I get you a menu?
I don't think so.
I have to drop this off,
but I can swing back
around on my way out.
Not tonight.
Would you hold him for me?
Thanks.
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA