Previously on Mad Men.
You have any idea how unhappy
I was before I met you.
I was thinking of leaving my wife.
They call a girl like her a lobster,
all the meat's in the tail.
If it is kennedy, nixon will lower
himself to the occasion.
It's going to be kennedy.
My mother used to say,
"you're going to get stout."
Tell me more about that.
I miss her.
I'm living like there's no tomorrow,
because there isn't one.
Season 1 Episode 10
Long Weekend
Running in the house.
Grandpa's here, and his aunt Gloria.
If I leave, can you keep
your mouth shut?
Elizabeth, are you hiding
your sugar bowl from me?
Gene, I think I have some packets
from the Howard Johnson.
Daddy, have a saccharin or nothing.
Where is your sugar bowl?
Do you want to wake up with
a cold leg like grandpa herman?
Diabetics don't live long, and
sometimes they lose their legs.
Hey grandpa.
Good morning.
- Good to see you, Gene.
- Don.
This is my friend Gloria.
I heard you might be joining us.
It's good to have another
woman around.
Give betty a break.
I live to serve.
Hey, you heard that, right?
I have a witness.
She's a hell of a sport.
Don, will you help me
with the suitcase?
We're only going for the weekend.
I can't get it out of the closet.
Honestly, it's unseemly.
I can imagine everyone at the club.
Was she waiting at the funeral,
unbuttoning her top button like
at some sadie hawkins dance?
She seems like a perfectly nice lady.
What am I supposed to do with this?
Fill it with hay?
How far do you want to go with this?
Oh, I'll say you talked me out of it.
She's a vulture.
Her husband was a failure.
When he died they found out
he cheated on his income taxes.
And her kids, louise never married.
Two more years and she'll be hanging
out at funerals too.
Huntley, he was my brother's age.
- He was always funny.
- Birdy,
your father was married
what, 40 years?
The man can hardly fix himself
a cup of tea, let alone do laundry.
All he needs is a housekeeper.
A housekeeper goes home at night.
Let him have it.
And that fake smile.
You've been looking forward
to the beach.
Let her cook.
Let your father put some stones
by that wall
so we stop getting water
underneath the deck.
I guess I won't have to worry about
talking to her. She never stops.
Just get through today.
I'll be there tomorrow afternoon.
We'll go to that place
with the lobster rolls.
Just come now.
You hate the way I drive.
Well, my father taught me.
Half the office has cleared out.
kennedy, kennedy, kennedy, kennedy,
Do you like a man who
answers straight?
A man who's always fair?
we'll measure him against the others
and when you compare.
Looks like a maple ad.
It's incredible.
Happy days are here again.
I'm just wild about Harry.
It's light. It's fun.
Doesn't cloud the mind with,
I don't know, issues.
It's catchy.
Catchy like it gets in your head
and makes you want to blow
your brains out.
The president is a product.
Don't forget that.
I would like to talk to you for
a moment about dollars and cents.
Your dollars and cents.
Now, my opponents want to
increase federal expenditures
as much as $18 billion a year.
How will they pay for it?
There are only two ways.
One is to raise your taxes.
Turn it off.
The other--
An ad made by a public
relations team.
Message received and forgotten.
We should give this
to Franz for some music.
Nixon's campaign song
in the key of E.
Ethal, go get the ice pick
that nixon guy is on tv again.
Should've never been this close.
I'd say we could run them again, but
I don't think you want to see them.
I've seen them, which reminds me,
you people aren't watching
enough television.
It is your job.
The shows and the ads.
I was just wondering, there must
be any number of people
harvesting mud on
Johnny kennedy right now.
Have we heard anything?
We hear things. Nothing useful. He's a
womanizer. That's not gonna hurt him.
Women find out about that
it'll push him up to the top.
Nixon is still ahead in the polls.
Should've never been this close.
Why do we need to attack
when there's a story to tell?
Kennedy, nouveau riche.
Recent immigrant who bought
his way into harvard,
and now he's well bred?
Great.
Nixon is from nothing.
Self-made man.
The abe lincoln of California
who was vice President
of the United States
six years after getting out
of the Navy.
Kennedy, I see a silver spoon.
Nixon,
I see myself.
If we were to run a critical ad,
there are obvious benefits.
When you run an ad that's positive
you're only convincing the people
who are already voting for you,
but when you run an ad that's critical
you get a shot at the people
on the fence.
There are a lot of people
Gentlemen, whether the nixon
campaign wants it or not,
we have to produce a spot that aims
a howitzer at kennedy's balls.
I want to hear ideas...
after the long weekend.
I agree. Let's go down swinging.
If we can switch to a conversation
about paying clients,
Mencken's is coming in today to sign off
on the roll out, father and daughter.
I get the feeling old Abe Schminken
can kill this whole thing.
Of course, the checks have
cleared already but-
Don, I want you to go in and
ride bareback over Paul here.
Done.
And, Don, I want you
on your best behavior.
- Excuse me?
- I know she bothers you.
Miss Holloway, may I?
I really need to get to
the bottom of that.
Yes, I would like to get
a look at those.
Margaret and Mona are off
to block island for labor day.
Gone for the weekend along
with every other wife in town.
We can go anywhere tonight.
We can see a Broadway show
and sit at any table at the colony
with our clothes off if we want to.
How about a movie?
Have you seen The Apartment*?
I went last week with
Mona and Margaret.
I hear Shirley MacLaine is good.
Please.
A white elevator operator,
and a girl at that?
I want to work at that place.
I bet you do.
The way those men treated
that poor girl,
handing her around like
a tray of canapes.
She tried to commit suicide.
So you saw it, huh?
Red, that's not how it is.
Look, it was crude. That's
the way pictures are now.
Did you see that ridiculous Psycho*?
Hollywood isn't happy unless
things are extreme.
It didn't seem that extreme to me.
Are we actually gonna get
in a fight over a movie?
You know, Mona had a dream once
where I hit the dog with a car.
She was mad at me all day,
and I never hit the dog.
We don't even have a dog.
Why don't I call you later?
Call me soon because
we can go anywhere.
The new atrium will make the store
brighter and more vibrant.
The aisles will be wider, spotlighting
these new chrome display cases.
Over here will be a new restaurant.
Elegant tea room.
Modern classic signs and
champagne linens.
A tea room, nice,
but 30% of my ground floor
is devoted to the restaurant business?
Lunch and shopping,
a day of indulgence.
That's what ladies like.
Yes, I saw that in the chapter here.
It's much longer than
the little schedule.
It says we have to close our doors
while it's getting nailed together.
Three months of construction
during which time we build
enormous anticipation.
It's like a movie premiere.
The new Mencken's.
You will have a line the first day.
Even if you have to pay
people to stand in it.
We'll do whatever it takes.
Mr. Draper,
my daughter's presence here
should let you know
that I am not against change,
and let us assume that this is
the most amazing idea in retail
since "Buy one, get one free."
I still don't understand
why we have to throw out
the baby with the water.
Can't I keep what I have
and just build on it?
Honestly, the unpleasant truth...
Is you don't have anything.
Your customers cannot
be depended on anymore.
Their lives have changed.
They're prosperous.
Over the years they've
developed new tastes.
They're like your daughter.
Educated, sophisticated.
They know full well
what they deserve
and they're willing to pay for it.
Why would I want to own a store
that I wouldn't want to shop in?
Mr. Mencken, I don't know
if that's true.
You had no problem
abandoning that second
floor hosiery store on 7th avenue
for your present location,
and that's a story you'll be proud
to tell your grandchildren.
The only problem is they won't care.
As much as grandpa likes
that marble palace,
I can promise you they won't.
They'll look at it and they'll say,
"Grandpa, it must've been hard
back in the olden days."
And it was.
Everybody's jumping to forget it.
Excuse me.
This is not some phony
story you people print
in your fourth of july circulars.
My father actually started
with nothing
and he made it into everything
we're talking about.
Who here can say that?
I meant no disrespect, sir.
None taken.
This is the plan, daddy.
As you can see, it wasn't
just thrown together.
It does seem very well thought out.
It is.
Pleasure to finally meet you.
I hope you two know
what you're doing.
Looks like we both get to keep
our jobs a little while longer.
Don't screw this up.
I think he likes me.
I guarantee you there is nothing
about you he likes.
What about you?
Daddy, can we?
This place reminds of
a czarist ministry.
No matter what the decision,
you don't feel it was yours.
Fortunately, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
He's very good. persuasive.
Yes.
A little dashing for my taste.
Carol,
it's 10:30. Did we have lunch?
'Cause even I can't leave this early.
No- I need to talk to you.
Why aren't you at work?
Don't tell me you're late again.
Do you need to see Dr. Emerson?
- Good grief, Joan.
- Then what?
You walked 12 blocks in a heat wave,
and I see you didn't take my advice
about the dress heels.
You know how mr. Aldridge has
had me reading the slush pile?
Yes, writing the rejection letters.
You told me. It's depressing.
I'm so stupid!
This morning in
the submissions meeting,
the editorial director asked
why we haven't responded
to this poet from Yale, Marlin Rice.
Mr. Aldridge tells him
we never saw it.
Then the director asks me,
and I cover for mr. Aldridge.
I said that I had read it
and rejected it.
Then they made mr. Aldridge fire me.
Honey, that's awful.
He was really sorry about it.
- Of course, that S.O.B. .
- I know.
I'm going to have to ask
my dad for money again.
It's humiliating.
Stop it.
You shouldn't be embarrassed.
There's never enough money.
You always seem to manage.
These men...
Constantly building them up,
and for what?
Dinner. Jewelry. Who cares?
We need to go out and shake
all this loneliness.
All I want to do is sit
in the movies and cry.
No movies.
Let's look for some
actual bachelors.
Empty their wallets.
- I hate Manhattan sometimes.
- Don't say that.
This city's everything.
Where's howdy dowdy at?
What can I do for ya?
I just got off the phone with
Brett Rowley at Dr. Scholl's.
Don't tell me they're coming in again
about the exercise sandals.
Did you tell 'em summer's over?
They're not coming in... ever.
- They're going to the Leo Burnett.
- What?
Why didn't he call me?
Probably because they were
disappointed with the creative.
Rowley called it dull and humorless.
- And what did you say?
- What could I say?
I've never lost an account before,
especially one that was here
before I got here.
So you really put up a fight?
He had very strong feelings.
He said some unpleasant things.
Which you don't remember
or I'm sure you'd tell me.
The day you sign a client is
the day you start losing them.
Are you going to tell Sterling,
or should I?
Unless you think it can wait
until after the weekend?
I'll take care of it.
Were you buzzing me? My intercom
was making a funny sound.
Leave it.
You wear Dr. Scholl's inserts?
I thought we all had to.
Take them out.
Get rid of this, please.
We lost Dr. Scholl's.
Where?
Leo Burnett.
Campbell enjoyed telling me it was
something to do with creative.
Thought I should tell you. Make
sure the ink is dry on that raise.
That fat piece of shit.
He's a cigarette ash.
Chicago, what a joke.
Small time.
Sorry, maybe you're from there.
I know I didn't drop
the ball on this.
Sales are steady.
Probably didn't help that
our billings crept up
for no apparent reason.
Eventually, an accountant
is gonna read the mail.
If you're trying to cheer me up,
it's working.
The day you sign a client is
the day you start losing 'em.
You don't really believe that.
You know what my father used to say?
Being with a client is like
being in a marriage.
Sometimes you get into it
for the wrong reasons
and eventually they hit you
in the face.
Damn it.
Are we supposed to cry about this?
So we lost an account.
That means we'll just
have to cut back.
Let's go fire somebody.
Labor day weekend.
Between now and monday
we have to fall in love
a dozen times.
Betty's at the shore.
I'm headed down tomorrow.
What do we work so hard for?
To have enough money
to buy fabulous vacations
for our family so
we can live it up here.
Give me tonight. You owe me that.
I can use you as bait.
There's a casting call at 4:00.
Double-sided aluminum.
If Freddy Rumson's brain works
the way I think it works,
slow and obvious,
I think we should go down to casting
and see who's on the couch.
Remember, Don, when
God closes the door
he opens a dress.
What do you have there?
Precious cargo?
Mr. Rumson has me trafficking
the Belle Jolie patch.
Aren't you a busy beaver?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
If you want to see the proofs, you'll
have to check with mr. Cosgrove.
It's his account.
Look at you. Minister of protocol.
So, has Draper talked to
Sterling yet?
You'll have to ask him.
I'm asking you.
You should talk to him.
What's wrong with you?
Excuse me?
I'm just trying to do my job and
you're making it very difficult.
Peggy dear, I think I understand
what this is about,
but you're not being
professional right now.
I cannot believe
I am in this conversation.
Think this is easy for me?
I don't know.
I don't know if you like me
or if you don't like me.
I'm just trying to get along here,
and every time I walk by I wonder
are you going to be nice to me
- or cruel.
- Cruel?
What am I supposed to say?
I'm married.
Yes, I know, and I heard all about how
confusing that can be.
Maybe you need me to lay
on your couch
to clear that up for you again.
That's some imagination you've got.
Good thing you're a writer now.
What do you need me for?
It's incredible.
I mean, we're just hanging out
in the art department
and you two wander in.
- We thought it was casting.
- I wish it was.
I'd definitely pick you two.
You have such an exquisite look,
the bones of your face.
And your sister, my goodness.
You two look very different
when you pay attention.
I have an older brother.
My neighbors growing up had a dairy
and one of the cows gave
birth to two calves
that were attached at the back,
then they cut them apart
but they always
wanted to be together.
Is that what happened to you two?
Do you like ukrainian food?
Let me ask you something, Draper.
Do any of these men have
anything else to do?
I just wanted to make sure
the girls were, you know.
Matching?
Exactly.
Well, there you have it.
Double-sided aluminum as
envisioned by Sterling-Cooper.
Look at you.
- Roger Sterling.
- Eleanor Ames.
What a great God that
made two of you.
What a sweet thing to say.
Mirabelle.
This is Donald Draper.
He's our creative director here.
What a pleasure to meet you.
Well, honestly,
I think we're going to send
everyone else home
and use our authority to say
that you two are
the new faces of Cartwright
double-sided aluminum!
My god. thank you.
I think this calls for a celebration.
Come on upstairs with us.
One drink could be fun.
One last question.
How many birthdays have you had?
Twenty.
How about her?
You're coming, aren't you, Don?
Aren't you two a pair of bookends.
What do you say, Draper?
Shall we cast 'em in bronze and
mount them on the credenza?
Oh, my. Everything he says means
something else too.
Did get warm in here.
They shut the air off at five.
Rochester,
get her an extra ice cube
or something.
Mirabelle, what's
your special talent?
Singing? Dancing?
Baton twirling?
I ride, mostly just dressage.
She has a wall full of blue ribbons
back home in Winchester.
I have a few awards myself.
Look at your skin. It's translucent.
It's see through.
Can I touch it?
I don't see why not.
After all, I do work here now.
That tickles.
Soft as a lamb's ear.
You gotta feel this.
I'm talking to you, Eleanor.
Do you love your sister?
Of course.
Why don't you show her how much?
Give her a kiss.
Right now.
Why do people always ask us that?
My God, because it's a beautiful thing.
I should be heading home.
Wonder boy, have a great night.
You know what?
I think we should go, too.
Come on.
Nobody's going anywhere.
Do you want to dance?
That's nice.
Dance for us.
I don't dance.
Sure you do. look at that.
I feel like I'm stuck somewhere
between Doris Day
in Pillow Talk* and Midnight Lace*,
and what I need to be is Kim Novak
in just about anything.
You're prettier than Kim Novak.
What a rut.
1960, I'm so over you.
Zip.
Shalimar?
Too much?
You never say die, do you?
What's the point?
Carol, sweetie, it's not that bad.
Tomorrow's another day.
I know.
- I'm okay actually.
- Good.
No water works. Mascara.
I'm just so happy right now.
Okay, are you on the Gilbey's already?
No. I just love this, you know,
being with you.
We do know how
to have fun, don't we?
Joan...
I love you.
I really do.
You.
That first week in college I saw you
walking on the commons
and I thought,
"Who is she?"
Then college was over
and you came here,
and I followed you.
You need a roommate,
I moved in...
Just to be near you.
I did everything I could
to be near you,
all with the hope
that one day
you would notice me.
Joanie.
Think of me as a boy.
You've had a hard day.
Let's go out and try
to forget about it, okay?
Of course.
Good, because I'm starving.
They seem to be having a lot of fun.
Down the road.
Do you got any gum?
No.
No, I don't.
Listen, I should get going.
Over to the left there.
There you go. Don't make me use
my spurs on ya.
Easy.
Right over there by the trough.
I really should go.
Eleanor?
I'll be right outside.
Let her go.
Listen,
- let me call you a car.
- I should wait for my sister.
I mean, I've been around
the block a few times,
but her...
I bet all you're thinking about
is going around the block, huh?
I don't even think I can get out
of the driveway.
Please, just wait with me?
I like your office.
It's really fancy.
Mirabelle, love that name.
Listen to that.
I haven't heard Margaret laugh
since she was seven.
- Who's Margaret?
- My daughter.
I think I like Mirabelle
better than Margaret.
I wanted to name
her Margo like the wine.
I lost that battle.
I'm sure she would've hated Margo
almost as much as
she hates Margaret.
Why is she so angry?
You're only a little older than her.
You're not angry.
Don't be sad.
I just wish I could talk to
her without her rolling her eyes.
Of course, she's right.
I have nothing to say to her.
I'm sure that's not so.
Girls love their fathers.
You have such beautiful skin.
My God. I just want to eat it.
I want to suck your blood
like Dracula.
Aren't you two the sweetest
for walking us up.
You should be roommates.
He seems to be a delightful
young man.
You don't teach at Fort Hermosa?
No. We were just sitting next
to each other at the bar
and it seemed to be working.
Kelly, you know what we need? Ice.
Now where is that Gin hiding?
Just so we're clear about what's
what, the redhead is mine.
So, Franklin, you're into language?
Yes, well, it's kind of
hobby of mine.
I do carpentry.
I'm building a dry sink.
I love language.
Words and their ways.
Well, this is just bad speech.
I collect it.
There's this polish janitor
in our building.
His name is Stash. Stanislov.
He's locked me out of my office
on more than one occasion.
One time, he described his bride
as not speaking real good english.
I cherish that gift.
Put that in a book and sell it.
Well, this is a party, isn't it?
I was wondering
if I could impose on the professor
for one more teeny favor.
I never say no to a beautiful girl.
The light fixture in my room is out.
Could you change it for me?
I'm up to that task.
We don't have a lot of men
around here.
It's not that dark.
What are we gonna do?
Whatever you want.
You're married, aren't you?
Yes. Yes, I am.
You kiss like a married man.
Your own way.
No talking you out of it.
- Is that good or bad?
- It's good.
Tell me what to do and I'll do it.
Maybe it's this office,
but you are selling too hard.
Eleanor! Hello, Ellie!
Where are you?
Something's wrong!
Your friend, something's wrong.
I knew I shouldn't have asked him
to do it a second time.
Oh, jesus.
I feel like there's a tank
on my chest.
Call an ambulance and then leave.
Is he okay?
Leave. Right there.
Mirabelle.
Mona.
Your wife's name is Mona.
How ya doin'?
All these years I thought
it would be the ulcer.
Did everything they told me.
Drank the cream.
Ate the butter.
I get hit with a coronary.
Son-of-a-bitch it hurts.
Well, you're talking, that's good.
That's not what the doctors think.
Do you believe in energy?
What do you mean?
Like the thing that
gives you get up and go?
No.
Like human, energy.
I don't know a...
A soul.
What do you want to hear?
Jesus...
I've been living the last 20 years
like I'm on shore leave.
What the hell is that about?
It's living, just like you said.
God...
I wish...
I was going somewhere.
He's doing great. Mona.
Mona.
I love you so much, Mona.
- God, I love you so much.
- I know.
Sweetheart, I know.
Listen to me, darling.
Margaret is outside
and she needs to see you.
No. I can't let her
see me like this.
Roger...
I'm getting her.
My goodness! All this from
selling toilet paper.
Mr. Cooper, where is everyone?
My roommate just gave me
the message.
Out.
It's the middle of the night.
I'm not leaving you here.
You should go.
Thank you.
Suit yourself.
Miss holloway, Roger Sterling
has suffered a heart attack.
What?
He survived it and
he's currently being hospitalized.
Now we need to immediately
send a telegram
to every one of our clients
assuring them that business
will not be interrupted.
- Of course.
- This is
the master client list,
names, addresses, and
I'll read them out and you
compose the telegram, huh?
"Kyle McElroy.
"President, Alpine Real Estate."
it's me, Bets.
Were you sleeping?
Not really.
The kids are in bed with me.
Gloria and my father made such
a big deal about having
separate bedrooms.
Listen,
Roger had a heart attack.
What?
Don, that's terrible.
Is he going to be okay?
The doctors basically
say they don't know.
Mona's with him.
She must be a wreck.
It's good that you're there.
About tomorrow...
No, I understand.
Well, what happened?
He was at work.
He just keeled over.
It was awful, actually.
Well, if the kids wouldn't be so
heartbroken I'd come home now.
I don't want to be here.
You should've seen the two
of them in the kitchen tonight.
She was making
some pot roast with a ketchup.
My father started
hovering behind her, watching,
like he used to do with my mother.
How can he pretend
that she never existed?
I still pick up the phone
sometimes to call her.
I don't know, Bets.
I know people say life goes on...
And it does.
But no one tells you
that's not a good thing.
Why is that?
I don't know.
Stop thinking about that.
I can't.
I try.
Do you want me to come up there?
No, there's nothing you can do.
Give mona my love.
And, don,
make sure you eat something.
How's he doing?
- Not great.
- What happened?
I don't know.
Public and politician
wants you to believe
that richard nixon is quote,
experienced.
They even want you to believe
that he has actually been making
decisions in the white house.
But listen to the man
who should know best,
the President of the United States.
I just wondered if you could
give us an example
of a major idea of his
that you had adopted
in that role as the decider?
If you give me a week, I might think
of one. I don't remember.
At the same press conference,
President Eisenhower said...
No one can make
a decision except me.
I know it's late-- I'm sorry.
I got the telegram.
Let me in.
Are you okay?
No.
You look terrible.
- Can I get a drink?
- Of course.
Are you happy with the doctors?
I can have my father make a call.
I don't know-- he's rich.
They seem to be taking care of him.
Is he okay?
You can tell me,
I'm not moving the account.
He's gray and weak.
His skin looks like paper.
I'm sorry.
He's your friend, isn't he?
What's the difference?
You don't want to lose him.
Don, don't!
What good is that gonna do?
Is this like some solar eclipse?
It's the end of the world,
just do whatever you want?
- I don't know.
- You do.
You're exhausted.
You need sleep, that's all.
I just need to sit down.
Sit with me.
Why?
Because I feel like you're looking
right through me over there.
I'm not.
I don't like feeling like this.
No one does.
I remember the first time
I was a pallbearer.
I'd seen dead bodies before.
I must've been 15-- my aunt.
I remember thinking
"They're letting me carry the box."
"They're letting me be
this close to it."
"No one is hiding anything
from me now."
and then I looked over and
I saw all the old people
waiting together by the grave,
and I remember thinking I...
"I just moved up a notch."
Never heard you talk
that much before.
- Rachel--
- What do you want from me?
You know. I know you do.
You know everything about me.
I don't!
You don't want to do this.
You have a wife.
You should go to her.
Jesus, Rachel.
This is it.
This is all there is,
and I feel like it's slipping
through my fingers
like a handful of sand.
This is it.
This is all there is.
That's just an excuse
for bad behavior.
You don't really believe that.
No.
Not unless you tell me
you want this.
Yes, please.
Miss Holloway, I know
it's none of my business,
but you could do a lot better.
He's just a friend.
That's not what
I'm talking about, my dear.
Don't waste your youth on age.
Could you-- lobby.
Do you want one?
No.
You told me your mother
died in childbirth.
Mine did too.
She was a prostitute.
I don't know what my father paid her,
but when she died they...
Brought me to him and his wife.
And when I was ten-years-old...
He died.
He was a drunk who got...
kicked in the face by a horse.
She buried him and took up
with some other man
and I was raised by
those two sorry people.