Previously on Mad Men.
What do you do, just kiss women all the
time? Women you aren't married to?
Of course not.
I know, I'm grown up,
but Dick, it's me.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
it's Adam...
Your little brother.
Go home, get undressed and
look at yourself in the mirror.
Really evaluate where your
strengths and weaknesses are,
and be honest.
I always try to be honest.
Where'd you get the tv?
Someone gave it to me.
And you took it?
- All better?
- Yes.
Season 1 Episode 6
Babylon
Dick Whitman, you watch
where you're going,
you're gonna break your neck.
You gonna cry or get up?
I'm getting up, uncle Mac.
Good, there's someone
who wants to meet you.
What are you afraid of?
There was lots of screaming.
Always is.
The lord has given us a blessing,
you have a new brother.
He ain't my brother.
Of course he is, you got
the same daddy.
Isn't he beautiful?
I named him Adam,
after the first man.
Daddy!
Are you all right?
Happy mother's day.
This is fascinating.
It's better than
the hollywood version.
Certainly dirtier.
Well Joan Crawford is not
what she was.
And honestly, I found her eyebrows
completely unnerving,
like a couple of Caterpillars
just pasted there.
Her standing next to Susie Parker
as if they were the same species.
Well, some men like eyebrows,
and all men like Joan Crawford.
Salvatore couldn't stop
talking about her.
To think one of the great beauties,
and there she is, so old.
I'd just like to disappear
at that point.
It makes perfect sense.
I promise you, bets,
The first sign of crow's feet
and I'll put you on an ice flow.
Would you, will you be
my gal in the iron mask?
Did you have a nice mother's day?
It was lovely.
And my mother was at
least two years older
than whatever Joan Crawford
says she is, and
she was still very fetching.
I'd like to think that
she'd stand up very well
as a prediction of
my eventual appearance.
Bets, don't...
No melancholy.
I'm allowed to be sentimental
on mother's day.
But it's your mother's day, not hers.
I'm just saying, my mother
looked handsome...
Actually vivacious and positively
cheerful right up to her end.
It's good remembrance.
Doctor Wayne suggested a book which
says it's part of the mourning process.
Doctor Wayne?
I do think it's helping.
So you're cured?
I don't know how they tell that.
When their vacation house
is paid for.
Don't deride him.
Mourning is just extended self pity.
In New Guinea, Pygmies
grind up their ancestors and
drink the powder in a beer.
And a model culture at that, Pygmies.
Did you know Michel Angelo
was painting the Sistine ceiling
when those people were
still living in caves,
discovering fire?
I didn't know that.
Well, it's true.
Introduction to basic anthropology.
What about
advanced reproduction?
How are your studies
progressing in that?
Completed.
I got an "A" actually.
- You did?
- Yep, I did.
I flunked the whole thing.
Well that's because
you got caught cheating.
Get the light.
And I want you so much.
I thought about it all day.
Me too.
No, I mean it.
It's all I think about...
everyday...
your car coming down the driveway.
I put the kids to bed early.
I make a grocery list,
I cook butterscotch pudding.
I never my let hands idle...
Brushing my hair.
Drinking my milk.
It's all in a kind of fog
because I can't stop
thinking about this.
I want you- so badly.
You have me...
You do.
Don, you remember Nick Grodis
from Olympic Cruise Lines.
Nick, did you ever add that
second deck of portholes?
Yes, but those rooms get pretty wet.
This is Urin Bensul Hi
from the Israeli administery
of tourism.
It is pronounced Uraum.
- Of course.
- And this young lady is Lily Meyer.
Pleasure to meet you.
And you.
caviar blinis, mal tal's...
We're thinking of a land
of exotic luxury.
We'd like to think that if Beirut is
the Paris of the middle east,
Heifa can be the Rome.
It's an exciting idea.
Of course, we should keep in mind
that Paris has the Eiffel tower
and Rome has the Coliseum.
Grandtel avenue
is about to have a Hilton.
Olympic is charting a most
luxurious liner,
all along the wonderous ports
of the Israeli riviera.
We are going to
visit mr. Van Berg down the street,
but some of us
find his humor to be kitsch,
we thought we would try
a traditional way as well.
Sterling Cooper doesn't like
to think of itself as tradition.
Maybe that is the wrong word.
My english is not so good.
Glamour, like glamorous,
that's the word.
We saw your awards.
We were impressed with
your work on Rio de Janeiro.
You're not thinking of,
putting a 150 foot statue of
Jesus in Tel Aviv are you?
Cause that's how we sold Rio.
This book
has been on the best seller list
for two years in the states,
and is soon to be
a major motion picture
starring Paul Newman.
America has a love affair with Israel,
and we would like to bring
the two parties together.
Well, you certainly saved me
some leg work.
All I have is the Bible.
Let's stay away from that.
So, your ideal tourist,
what's his yearly salary?
Whatever you make.
They always say that.
Well, look who's here...
A couple of angels.
Do we have lunch today?
No, darling, we're going to
get Margaret a haircut.
A haircut?
I like your ponytails. Of course,
it makes you look young.
I like your hair, daddy,
it makes you look old.
We just have to find the right place.
Ginger?
I cut my own hair.
You picked her.
Don't you two make
a handsome couple.
Honestly, I don't go for handsome.
Mona. Margaret.
What brings you below 59th street?
Margaret, say hello.
Hello, mr. Draper.
Mona, aren't you lucky, mother
and daughter on the town.
Where are the girls getting
their hair done these days?
By girls you mean Bridget Bardot,
cause that's what I'm seeing.
As long as she can pit
a hat on it for church.
You are going to love this man.
I will make you an appointment,
come on.
Bye, Don.
Roger, sweetheart.
She used to love being in my office.
A haircut is the least
of Margaret's problems.
She's dated what, two boys?
One of them joined the service,
the other one committed suicide.
She doesn't want to go to college.
Doesn't want to work.
Not interested in charity.
I don't know what we did wrong.
We gave her everything she wanted
and she's still useless.
You're being too hard on her,
she's a young girl.
When I was her age,
I rode a tramp steamer
from bar Harbor to Hilton head.
I bet it was a yacht.
Someone still has to sail those things.
I think Margaret reminds you of you,
you're both spoiled... zip.
Come back to bed.
I can stay here all afternoon.
You don't have to go
back to work, I do... zip.
Do you like the pearl
necklace I gave you?
It's gorgeous.
Aren't you even gonna
have any of this?
Look, we've got Oysters Rockefeller,
beef Wellington, Napoleon.
We leave this lunch alone,
it will take over Europe.
I don't like eating in here.
Food that close to the bed
reminds me of a hospital.
If you had your own apartment,
we could go to your place.
You could cook for me.
Don't you like things
the way they are?
Are you kidding?
This has been the best year
of my life.
Do you have any idea how unhappy
I was before I met you?
I was thinking of leaving my wife.
I am just getting tired of all...
The sneaking around,
aren't you?
Roger, I know
as much about men as you
know about advertising,
and I know that this sneaking
around is your favorite part.
You know, I have
a lot of favorite parts.
I'd like to get you
a little fourth floor
walkup somewhere,
with no doors, no windows,
and lock you up for a week.
That's tempting...
But I like hotels,
and you leave with
what you came in with,
and the little soaps, I love those.
I wish I knew what
you wanted, Joanie.
I love this Roger,
but a week is a considerable
length of time,
and I have my own world.
I go out and I have parties,
and I have friends over.
Male friends.
Yes.
I don't want to hear this.
Carol and I have
this nice little rotation.
Carol... the disaster.
I've known carol since college,
and she's been a good friend,
and she's bright, and she's neat.
So you think you'd be lonely?
I think it would be half
as much fun alone.
You could get a bird.
They're fairly neat for animals.
If you had your way,
I would be stranded
in some paperweight
with my legs stuck in the air.
Wait, wait-wait,
you're just gonna paint that
picture and go, huh?
Can't we...
Just enjoy this?
I mean,
we both know
I'll eventually find a more
permanent situation, and you'll find
a new model,
the 61's are coming out soon.
I hear the fins are bigger next year.
Whatever you want, red.
I see why they want the guns.
It's tough to compete with
Bermuda only three hours away.
Helps if they stop blowing up hotels.
Kill me, you busty Jewist.
Maybe we should try and
exploit the danger,
instead of fighting it...
travel as adventure.
Or how bout this?
Average American family of three
standing on the shore,
suitcases in hand,
the red sea parts before them.
On the other side waits
a gleaming four star resort,
"shouldn't you see the promise land?"
Take religion out.
They've got plenty of stations
of the cross traffic.
I've skimmed this research,
and the whole thing's pretty red.
These communes, kibitzes,
it's positively soviet.
Except the daughters of
the American revolution
are shuttling this book up
and down fifth avenue.
It's a good story. They start in
these prison camps...
Real prisoners, then
the next thing you know,
they're in the desert,
armed to the teeth,
cutting their way through
the enemy, dying for the cause,
and then they have a government.
A commie government.
Made my mother cry.
So, we have a quasi communist state
where women have guns,
and it's filled with Jews.
Well not completely filled,
let's not forget that
there are also Arabs.
They've got oranges.
As far as I can see,
the biggest thing this place
has going for it,
the people are good looking.
The Jews there don't look
like the Jews here.
Have you been to
the diamond district?
All right, I have to make
a couple phone calls.
Let's pick this up later.
Peggy, will you get me
a private line please?
Right away, mr. Draper.
Donald Draper, line two.
I debated not taking the call.
I'm glad you did, I need to see you.
I don't think that's a good idea.
It's business.
Meet me for a drink.
I'm busy this evening.
I wouldn't of called
if it wasn't important.
I should still be able
to talk to you.
Give me credit for that.
Lunch, tomorrow.
Lunch.
The tea room at The Pierre... 12:15.
Message received.
It's so muggy tonight.
Did you just get a library card?
I rarely see you read anything
that doesn't have
a manila folder wrapped around it.
You should clean the gutters.
This weekend.
Is that good?
Well, there's less action
than I thought.
I thought it was a romance.
You know, the first boy
I ever kissed was Jewish.
How did that happen?
My friend, Deirdre Shaw was
friends with a Jewish girl,
Beth Goldsilver or something.
Beth invited us to a mixer at
her Synagogue in lower mareine.
Surprised your mother let you go.
Well, it was a fundraiser
for charity.
Those poor skinny people
in the boats.
This boy danced with me all evening,
David Rosenberg.
He was very good looking,
but there was something
about him that was gloomy.
Was he a good kisser?
Let's just say he had
more practice than I did.
Yeah, I'm sure he was
very disappointed.
Please, the only reason he picked me
is because I wasn't part
of the Synagogue.
In fact, the next day
on the school bus,
Beth told everyone I was necking
with David Rosenberg.
The looks they gave me.
They were all blondes
by the next summer.
Honey, it's hot,
and I have to read this book
about the desert.
Of course,
go ahead.
We should get an
air conditioner up here.
Yeah, we'll see.
Hi, Fellas, come on in.
Did you see this?
Someone broke into
the Yankees equipment locker
in Cleveland yesterday, swiped
Mickey Mantle's pet glove.
They should of taken his bat.
Should I wait for you
to have your breakfast?
A day without orange juice
is a hell of a long day.
Hey look man, no hands.
"Belle Jolie."
I've been looking at the work
of our esteemed predecessors,
I'm not heartened.
They make more colors of lipstick than
Howard Johnson has ice cream flavors,
but their sales are in the crapper.
These names...
Passion flower peach,
tropical bourdois red,
look ethel roserburg pink.
Wear it to the chair.
Did you know that lipstick
was invented
to simulate the flush in
a woman's face,
after you treated her right?
If you're gonna quote
the research report,
don't start with "did you know."
Research, I'm stumped.
I'll be honest, I don't speak moron.
Do either of you speak moron?
Let's throw it to the chickens.
Okay girls, come on in.
Come on in ladies, gather around.
Settle down.
What no lunch?
No dear,
this is better. Belle Jolie wants us
to tell them what we think
about their new line of lipsticks.
One way glass.
Doesn't it seem weird to you?
It should be two way glass, right?
I don't care what they call it.
Beats the hell out of x-ray specs.
It's called brainstorming.
That sounds intimidating,
is it like a test?
There are no wrong answers. You just
be your pretty little selves.
Grab a lipstick,
grab a mirror, and sit down.
And remember, the mirror could be
your best friend, or your worst enemy.
Has no taste.
Ugly dress.
Horrible wig.
They're brainstorming.
I wouldn't expect more
than a few sprinkles.
I love it when they do that.
My little blowfish.
Anybody mind if I take off my pants?
Red one's for me.
How many lipsticks do you own?
Gee, I don't know.
I'd have to go home and count.
Do you match your lipcolor
to your clothing
or to your accessories?
I know, that seems like
a loaded question.
It is unloaded
and I insist you curb your
editorial comments.
Sometimes I match it
to my nail polish?
Good answer.
Go ahead.
Do you change your lipcolor
with the seasons?
You, stand over there.
At what point do we start running
electricity through the chairs?
We should of put a man in there,
so they'd take it seriously.
Good,
I was afraid I'd missed it.
I want to stand and salute that.
what's with the mouse ears
over there?
Thanks for coming.
- Can I get you anything?
- No.
- How have you been?
- Fine.
Fine, tired.
Doesn't show.
I'm in the middle
of spring inventory.
I hope you're not gonna tell me
that the grand plan  for remaking
our store has a hitch in it.
You look beautiful.
I thought you had
urgent business to discuss.
Anything for the lady?
Nothing for me, coffee.
- Irish coffee?
- Coffee.
Business?
Turns out Israel tourism
is considering becoming a client,
and I'm having a hard time
getting a handle on it.
And I'm the only jew you know
in New York city?
You're my favorite.
Jesus, Don, crack
a book once in a while.
I have,
it's all sentimental.
World War II trivia, oranges...
Kids in blue and white hats.
They're doing the movie of
"Exodus" with Paul Newman.
Paul Newman, that's nice.
Now I have two reasons to see it.
Damn it.
You're usually so put together.
I'll say one thing about Israelis,
don't cross them.
Well those people at the meeting
were definitely zionists.
Zion just means Israel,
it's a very old name.
I'm sorry, I'm not an expert on this,
and something feels strange
about being treated like one.
I just want to know
something about it
that doesn't come from some
administrative propaganda.
Well here's some more
World War II trivia,
they just arrested Adolf Eichmann*
in Argentina last week,
have you seen his resume?
Okay, I deserved that,
but I'm talking about
tourists going to Israel.
I don't know what I can say.
I'm american, I'm really
not very Jewish.
If my mother hadn't died having me,
I could have been Marilyn
instead of Rachel,
and no one would know the difference.
What is the difference?
Look, Jews have lived in exile
for a long time.
First in Babylon, then
all over the world...
Shanghal, Brooklyn, and
we've managed to make a go of it.
Maybe it has something
to do with the fact
that we thrive at doing business
with people who hate us.
I don't hate you.
No, individuals are wonderful.
That's not what I meant.
I don't know...
A country for those people,
as you call us, well
seems very important.
Why aren't you there?
My life is here.
My grandfather came from Russia,
now I have a store on fifth avenue.
I'll visit, but I don't have
to live there.
Just...
Has to be.
For me, it's more of
an idea than a place.
Utopia.
Maybe.
They taught us at barnard
about that word...
Utopia.
The greeks had two meanings for it,
utopos- meaning the good place,
and utopos-
meaning the place that cannot be.
I have to get back to the office.
I better not see this on my bill.
Okay, girls, playtime's over,
time to put down your lipsticks,
and head back to your desks.
Thank you for your cooperation
and your lips.
These go in the closet.
Well now we have to count
he shades they tried,
can you bring me those tissues, dear?
Here's your basket of kisses.
Basket of kisses... that's cute.
Who told you that?
What do you mean?
Where'd you hear that?
I just thought of it.
Isn't that what it is?
It is, sweetheart.
Which color did you like?
I didn't get the one I liked,
someone took my color.
Why didn't you choose another one?
I'm very particular.
As opposed to the other girls?
I don't know...
I don't think anyone wants to be
one of a hundred colors in a box.
I think that's enough complaining.
Why don't you head back to
your desk, Peggy?
Bet you wish you could
put that in a glass and drink it.
Peggy, clear the rest of
my afternoon, would you please?
You have the sliders Ketchup
people at 3 o'clock.
Have a box of cigars sent over
to Jim King with my apologies.
I'll find out what he smokes.
Good girl.
- You got a minute, chief?
- Just.
You don't mind, do you?
Use a glass, freddy.
Your girl full of surprises.
Pretty Peggy Sue.
Peggy?
If you say so.
I try to avoid eye contact to avoid
being blinded by the earnestness.
Actually, she really stood out,
brainstorming wise.
Brainstorming?
Sorry I missed that.
What was the line?
"A bucket of kisses."
"basket of kisses."
bucket sounds better.
If you like them wet and sloppy.
Point is, while the rest of
the hens were busy
pulling out each other feathers,
that one saw the benefit,
not the feature.
- Really?
- Yeah,
she said she didn't want to be
one of a hundred colors in a box.
That's interesting, isn't it?
It is.
It was like watching
a dog play the piano.
It's me, Barbara can you talk?
She's still sleeping, thank God,
what's on your mind?
I think I might of met somebody.
You're not sure?
That's good.
He has some serious limitations.
Does he work in the store?
No, he doesn't work at the store.
Well, he has a job, doesn't he?
Yes.
Then what's the problem?
Would daddy like him?
Daddy would hate him.
So, he's not Jewish.
Who cares what daddy thinks.
He's not your boyfriend anymore.
You're 28-years-old.
You work 60 hours a week,
the last thing you want is
to end up like aunt Rosie,
lying to your nieces about
how many engagements you had.
Aunt Rosie wasn't lying.
Please, there was
no max the communist.
Does he have all his hair?
More than he'll ever need.
Is he funny?
Sometimes, after a couple.
So he's a schecker,
daddy will hate him.
I do feel this attraction.
I want him, and I want to ignore
everything else about him.
It's 1960, we don't live in a shadow,
we can marry for love.
I'm not sure people do that anymore.
Why do you always
have to be so cynical?
Because sometimes...
Things come...
good things, but there's
no future in them.
You're a modern woman, Rach,
forget the wedding.
Believe me, I'd do anything
for some romance right now.
Peggy.
Hi, Joan.
Mr. Rumsen would like you
to put your industrious little mind
towards coming up with copy
for Belle Jolie lipsticks.
I don't understand, they want me
to write something?
Whatever you said in that
brainstorming session, apparently
knocked their socks off.
My gosh!
I don't know what to say.
You will of course continue
to cover mr. Draper's desk.
Any writing you do will be
on your own time.
Do I get a raise?
No... Congratulations.
More work and more responsibility.
I guess you'll be entitled
to some dinner money.
That's swell.
Maybe I should go and thank them.
I'm not really dressed...
tomorrow maybe.
No need. They wanted me to tell you.
They were very specific about it.
You know what they say,
the medium is the message.
And here I was just wishing for
a man to help me with my yard work.
Sorry.
That's what I get for being domestic.
Let's get this off.
God, hold that...
The thought.
Hi, Roy.
Hi beautiful,
what's shaking?
Busy dance card, huh?
This is my friend, Don Draper.
Don, this is Roy Hazlett.
Pleasure.
Ian's playing down at the Gas Light.
We're gonna go support him,
pass the basket, you in?
That is if dad will let you out.
Well, that sounds like fun, Don,
- We should go down for a while.
- Come on, it will be a kick.
What do you say, afraid
you'll miss 531?
I think I'm gonna stay here.
I'll wear a skirt and nothing else.
What took you so long?
One of the media buyers ambushed
me in the elevator
with tickets to the ballet
of all things.
I told him I had plans
but he insisted
we share a cab across town anyways.
And I couldn't shake him.
Which one was it? George Asbury...
he's a hound.
It doesn't matter,
they're all just boys.
The poor bastard probably
couldn't help himself.
The way you glide around that
office like some magnificent ship.
Well, I don't want to be a distraction.
Shall I...
order horse blinders for
the rest of the office?
You didn't?
I sure did.
What am I supposed to do with it?
The store lady said you can do anything
but put the cage on the radiator.
You're terrible.
Well, you can't blame
a man for trying.
I just hate the thought
of having to share you.
You don't have to share me now.
Joanie, you smell so good.
I've been thinking
about this all day.
Mona is looking at a weekend
in old saybrook with the in-laws.
There's not enough
liquor in the world.
Roger...
Sorry.
"Mary Catherine Cahill,"
"a daughter of Harriet M. Barr"
"and Archibold W. Barr of
Stoneyton, Connecticut,"
"and Kevin Mark Duncan the III,"
"a son of Beatrice Hoslinger"
"and Kevin Mark Duncan jr.
of Manhattan,"
"were married last evening at the
episcopal church of the heavenly rest."
He travels around the country, and
collects miniature replicas
of monuments...
Washington memorial*,
Bunker Hill*, Mount Rushmore*,
and then,
he sticks them up his ass.
Symbolism intended.
Place to put your coats.
Switch seats with me.
No way.
Can we get a round over here?
Jack Daniels, scotches.
Sounds like a great idea.
Anyway, turns out, spanish cat
and I were mucho sympatico
with the direction that
we talked about going.
- With the theater of the people thing?
- Conscious drama.
Not the soloist bullshit
kept alive by the middle class,
with season tickets to
Dick Van Dyke* and Mary Martin*.
I bet Don here can tell you first hand,
Broadway's the birthplace of mediocrity.
Maybe it's born there,
but I think it may be
conceived right here.
"And take up residence
in Rye, New York."
Thank you.
So what do you do, Don?
I blow up bridges.
Don's in advertising.
No way.
Madison avenue? What a gas!
We all have to serve somebody.
Perpetuating a lie, how do
you sleep at night?
On a bed made of money.
Isn't this an education?
You hucksters and your tower created
religion of mass consumption.
People want to be told
what to do so badly,
that they'll listen to anyone.
When you say people, I have
a feeling you're talking about thou.
And I have a feeling that
you spent more time
on your hair this morning
than she did.
You two want to head to the urinals
and poke it out?
So, Roy, if you had a job,
what would you do?
I'm starting a theater,
right here in the village...
it's a cooperative.
Midge is gonna get in there
and paint some flags.
I said I'd think about it.
Last night,
I dreamed of making love
to Fidel Castro,
in a king size bed at
the Waldorf Astoria.
Viva la revolution, he roared
as he vanquished my dress.
Outside the window,
Nikita Kruschev watched us,
plucking a chicken.
Take off your shirt!
Take your shirt off!
I should go,
too much art for me.
Stay,
this is Ian.
We'll go right afterwards.