Previously on Mad Men...
Those of you who meet the
qualifications will receive an interview.
- Je voudrais mas Harry.
- Good morning.
Beans, they have to be cool.
Don, you know what
I'm talking about.
Things aren't perfect.
Mohawk is coming in,
I brought them in.
What do you know about that?
This does not involve you, Roger.
I know what you see in her...
and you could have
gotten it without marrying.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Betty, are you ready?
It's stuck.
What about now?
Betty!
I'll get it.
Just go.
Betty.
The car is here!
What's going on?
We've got to go.
Darling, I just don't think
I can go tonight.
What's the matter?
It's... a woman's thing.
Is there any way
you could play with pain?
It's the junior league
of New York.
I don't want to
do it without you.
Your mother will be there.
It'll be very endearing.
Forgive me on the way?
Thank you.
Say "au revoir."
Bon jour, Marie.
Marie, I can't understand you.
- Moustiques?
- Mosquitoes.
Okay, mama.
We can't let Heinz
beat us there.
He has a name, you know.
And do you know what that is?
Are you kidding me?
He's the only man I want
to please more than you.
And your father.
I'm the baby.
They miss me.
So, Megan, you're French.
I suppose I should ask you what looks good.
I'm Canadian.
Although for all
we know, they are, too.
You know, back in Pittsburgh,
everybody's pretty much
who you expect them to be.
Or you know them forever.
Raymond and I
met in high school.
Well, then we've been
married longer than you.
- I told you he was smooth.
- How did you two meet?
- Well...
- At work.
Don was divorced.
Well, that's none
of my business.
You have a teenage
daughter, Emily.
- How's her summer?
- It's tough.
She's around the house
all the time.
Too old for camp,
too young for a job.
- I say let her enjoy it.
- I agree.
You don't sound so happy
about it when I get home.
Well, the music is so loud.
Do you know
the Rolling Stones, Don?
- Sure.
- The Stones.
She can't get enough of them.
The other night, she's playing this
song "Time, Time Is On Your Side."
- "Time Is On My Side."
- Yes, it is, dear.
Well, it's catchy.
And I was thinking,
what if they were
to sing, you know,
"Heinz, Heinz, Heinz
is on my side"?
Or something like that.
I don't know.
They're gonna be in New York.
Emily almost jumped in our bags with
us when she heard we were coming.
Maybe you could, you know,
get them to record
it while they're here.
Well, that's not exactly
the way it works,
but we can certainly
approach them.
This is boring.
Am I right, Megan?
Yes?
Clara, where is Roger?
Caroline says the meeting
is in his office.
You wanted to see me?
I was waiting in my office
to give you some good news.
Drinking good news?
Mohawk called.
You're welcome.
They haven't informed
their agency,
but I'm told it's
a matter of hours.
Welcome back, suckers.
I think you should
handle the account.
- So, they asked for me?
- They enjoy your company.
And since you were here
when they were here,
they think you know
their business.
I know Hank from the war.
He likes vodka.
Jack likes Jack.
Anything else?
So you're aware they've taken
on $54 million in debt
to replace their planes?
And there's a mechanic strike looming.
- Although they'll likely be spared.
- So far, so good.
Don and I have been
trying to explain to Lane
this is a daily business and we'll
need a dedicated copywriter.
I don't understand why Miss
Olson can't handle it.
Because these guys are gonna
ask her to make drinks.
We're still paying Don,
aren't we?
Don's not going to rewrite local
fare ads three times a week.
That's all it is?
Just get a guy with basic retail
experience and run with it.
Congratulations!
Lane, smile.
We've got an airline.
Morning.
I'm here to see Don.
Yes, just a minute.
Mr. Draper.
Mr. Crane to see you.
Just a minute, Dawn.
Is Don in a meeting?
He's with Mrs. Draper.
Thank you, Dawn.
You're welcome.
It's so confusing.
People keep saying that.
But we haven't had
any problems.
You haven't.
But out in the office,
it's really hard
to tell who's who.
- Hello, Harry.
- Good morning.
Backstage Forest Hills tennis
stadium Saturday night,
put your hands together
for the Rolling Stones.
And how would you
gauge their interest?
The manager sounded greedy.
I thought we'd take one car.
- I'll drive.
- It starts at 8:00.
But apparently they're always late.
I thought we could grab a bite.
There's a dynamite Italian restaurant
with a first-rate veal parm.
- Nope.
- Good.
Then I will be ready
at 7:30 having eaten.
Have Dawn pencil it in.
- Hello, Pauline.
- Hello, dear.
I just wanted to see
how you were feeling.
Aren't you sweet to come
all the way over here
when a phone call
would've sufficed?
Are the children home?
They're at day camp.
You know that.
Betty, you were sorely
missed last night.
Well, that's good
to hear, I guess.
You've missed a bunch
of these, Betty.
Pauline...
And I'm sure he never shows it,
but it upsets Henry
when you're not there.
I want him to be happy.
And you being with him
is part of that.
I wasn't feeling well.
Honey, I know how it happens.
You get comfortable
and you give up a little bit.
And then it just
gets out of control.
There are things
you can do about this.
There are pills you can take.
Why haven't you taken them?
Believe me, I would if I could.
I have a heart condition.
And honestly, at my age,
I don't have to
please men anymore.
But you...
Don't you want to get back
into that incredible
closet of yours again?
It'll be easy for you.
You're just one of those girls.
Thank you, Dawn.
- What's so funny?
- She was the most qualified.
We've got great news,
but assume this is for
your ample ears only.
Is it about Heinz
and the Rolling Stones?
- What?
- No.
Harry's such a liar.
Baked beans
and the Rolling Stones.
A client's idea
if I ever heard one.
Mohawk airlines is returning.
That's great.
That's a big fish.
It's a minnow,
but it's our minnow.
Well, I obviously
have experience.
- I mean, at a low level, but I saw how it worked.
- Your plate is full.
And, frankly, Mohawk is going to
insist on a regular copywriter.
- Someone with a penis.
- I'll work on that.
Call in books.
You're the search committee.
- Okay, when?
- Immediately.
Now, this is gonna
be my account.
So I don't want just some
hack with retail experience.
He should be brilliant
and have awards.
I want you to bring me
a good-looking version of Don.
Oh, that'll be easy.
- Mrs. Francis.
- Hello.
So nice of you
to see me so quickly.
Well, slow day.
What seems to be the
well, it's just that
I've been wondering--
I've put on a few pounds
and I haven't had much luck
reducing on my own for some reason.
Well, with middle-aged women, it gets easier
to put it on and harder to take it off.
Well, a friend told me
it'd be easier
if you gave me diet pills.
Just to give me
a little jump-start.
Is your friend a doctor?
No.
Well, I'm not going to
give you a prescription
without giving you an exam.
For diet pills?
If you think it's necessary.
Mrs. Francis, when a housewife
has a rapid weight gain,
the cause is usually
psychological--
Unhappiness, anxiety,
boredom--
Things that cause us
to lose our self-control.
But first, we have to rule out
diabetes, hyperthyroidism.
Well, I don't need
to take the pills forever.
I don't like that.
- What?
- Shh.
Could you swallow?
Henry!
Mrs. Francis is on line one.
- Betts, you there?
- Don.
- I don't know what to do.
- About what?
I went to the doctor this morning
and he found this thing.
It's a--
a node or a nodule
or something
and it's on my thyroid.
They don't know what it is,
but it's a lump, Don.
And he's sending me to the city
to some specialist for tests.
Okay, okay, calm down.
I can't, Don.
I can't.
Betts, what exactly did he say?
Well, nothing.
You know how they are.
Do you want me
to take the kids?
The kids.
Oh, the kids.
Oh, God.
Birdy.
Say what you always say.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
If I see one more volkswagen ad
with something else in it...
You can do an ad
on anything you want.
Don't pick toilet paper,
shit bird.
Too fat.
Too thin.
Shelly Parker-- Might be
a woman, God forbid.
"Judge not,
lest ye be judged."
Irony.
That's promising.
Have I lost my sense
of smell or is this good?
That's bitchin'.
What's this guy's name?
Michael Ginsberg.
Nice knowing you, Mike.
What are you doing?
That's the best one I've seen.
This is why girls
don't play sports.
You've been working on
Heinz for four months.
Somebody else is gonna carry
the ball across the goal line?
Bringing him in for Mohawk.
I hope you like him.
He's gonna be your boss someday.
I like working with talented people.
It inspires me.
I'm not talking about me.
I'm talking about another writer.
Are you suddenly not
competitive?
The chick who races
people to the toilet?
I'm going to bring him in.
Stick to mediocre.
You'll sleep better.
Can I come in?
Of course.
I just got off
the phone with Jim.
He said tomorrow at 11:00.
Tomorrow?
My boss made a call.
You told Mayor Lindsay?
He's got bigger secrets
than this, Betty.
I don't know if tomorrow--
You want to wait on this?
Well, if it is something--
If, if, if.
Betty, let's not play
that game, okay?
Come to bed.
You want some Brandy?
I see you all the time.
You're beautiful.
You're sweet.
I'm gonna have a Brandy.
Betty.
Betty Draper.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Joyce. Hello.
How are you?
Not good.
I'm here.
Mrs. Francis,
the doctor's waiting.
It's Francis now.
My husband's name
is Henry, too, actually.
Look, you know what?
I'm gonna be in
radiology forever.
Mrs. Darling, they're
waiting for you, too.
Why are you here?
You want to get
some lunch after?
Oh, I don't know.
My husband's picking me up.
You think you don't want to
have lunch, but you do.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
I'm going.
Hello.
I'm Peggy Olson.
Michael Ginsberg.
Lead the way.
No, we're meeting here.
So what's he like?
Is he like a firm
handshake kind of guy?
- Excuse me?
- Don.
I want to make a good impression.
You could help me out.
No, I'm interviewing you.
I'm a copywriter.
Have a seat.
So is Don stopping by?
Nope, it's just me.
Can you hire me?
Well, no,
but I'm the first round.
Wouldn't you want to talk to
the person who could hire you?
I spent three weeks dancing
at that crappy New York
satellite of Leo Burnett.
Never met him at all.
Turns out Leo's not a real person.
- Yes, he is.
- Is Don a real person?
'Cause I'd really like
to meet him.
I'm the person you need
to impress right now.
You looked at my book.
What more can I say?
Okay.
- I liked your work.
- And I like your work.
You thought I was a secretary.
Do you have a current resume?
- Allen Ginsberg?
- He's the most famous Ginsberg there is.
I figured we got
to be related somehow.
And what's he gonna say?
Okay, well, it was
nice meeting you.
Oh, nuts.
Listen, my stuff is good.
You can see advertising
ain't my day job.
Look, you're a fair woman.
I insulted you because
I'm honest.
And I apologized
because I'm brave.
I didn't pick this profession.
It picked me.
I didn't have
any control over it.
Turns out, it's the only
thing I can do.
Your work's
very impressive, but...
Here's some other
advantages--
I have no hobbies,
no interests, no friends.
I'm one of those people who
talks back to the radio.
No girlfriend, no family.
I will live here.
Then you're like everyone else.
I've never been accused of
that, but I really am trying.
I don't know.
You can't act
like this with Don.
Like what?
- We'll call you.
- Okay.
You know, your book
really does have a voice.
That's what they said
about "mein kampf."
"The kid really has
a voice."
You're sure you're
okay just with tea?
- Yes.
- Everything tastes like sawdust to me.
Everything still tastes
good to me.
Turns out I have the only
kind that makes you fatter.
Look, I'm sure you're fine.
When do you find out
the results?
I don't remember.
It wasn't until the third
visit that I knew.
Because Hank was waiting there.
Have you told your children?
They know I'm going
to the doctor a lot.
And they know I'm sick,
but I've always been
in a bad mood, so...
I joke with Hank.
He should just tell them
I got hit by a car.
It'd be easier to deal
with than saying good-bye.
Ugh, the scene.
I'm leaving behind such a mess.
You're not going anywhere.
He's my second husband.
His mother's domineering.
And Don's girlfriend--
Well, they're married.
She's 20 years old.
They'll never hear
a nice word about me again.
I'm sorry,
but I have to ask you.
What is it like?
Well,
it's like you're
way out in the ocean
alone and you're paddling,
and you see people
on the shore,
but they're getting
farther and farther away.
And you struggle
because it's natural.
Then your mind wanders
back to everything normal.
What am I gonna fix for dinner?
Did I lock the back door?
And then you just get so tired,
you just give in
and hope you go straight down.
That's horrible.
No one's ever asked.
Hello, ladies.
I am Cecilia,
and I have the gift of sight.
Could I offer you a reading?
You're gonna
predict our future?
- Go ahead.
- Really?
It's always good.
- Oh, my.
- What?
You're a great soul.
You mean so much
to the people around you.
You're a rock.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We're done.
Thank you.
You need some more tea.
- Are you okay?
- I had drinks with Mohawk.
I sat down with two of them and I
swear by the end there were three.
Did you hire him?
No, he was crazy.
I'm calling in more books.
Define crazy for a copywriter.
Sleeps all day,
disrespectful of authority,
drunk half the time.
Did he smell like pee?
- Who smells like pee?
- Writers. Just hire him.
I can't. Don will hate him.
He's certifiable.
I order you to bring him in.
You have to.
I already told Mohawk.
Why would you do that?
I wanted to smooth the ground
about working with a Jew.
Turns out, everybody's
got one now.
Tell you the truth, it makes
the agency more modern.
Between that and "it's always darkest
before the dawn" over there.
At least this one
we're hiring on purpose.
I can find another Jew if
that's what you care about.
Look, I know
what you're afraid of.
Sweetheart, no one's
gonna replace you.
Oh, I'm not threatened by his talent.
He's not that good.
I just think Don will hate
him and then he'll hate me.
Oh. I'll be there.
I'll handle Don.
- How can you hear anything?
- I'm following your advice.
I'm being bathed
in commercials.
My God, you're so square,
you've got corners.
I have to make sure
I look like the man.
If Betty calls
or, you know, the kids,
tell them I'll call
them in the morning.
What did she want anyway?
Who knows?
Well, have fun.
I don't mean that.
This is backstage.
That's the real backstage.
Nice to see yo.
- We're here to see the Rolling Stones.
- They're not here.
Well, actually, we're here to
see their manager, Allen Klein.
- He's not here, either.
- I'm Harry Crane.
- I'm on the list.
- There's no list.
Will you let us know
when they get here?
Sir, I promise you'll know.
I should have talked him out
of this at the dinner table.
Well, we either wait
for them to show up
or wait for them
to come out of there.
Hey, mister, tell your friend I'll
trade him a joint for a cigarette.
You can have one for free.
No, I just wanted to make
sure you guys weren't cops.
Can you light this for me?
There's a cop right over there.
He's cool.
- What are you doing?
- They're cool.
They don't look cool.
- What are you two doing here?
- We're here on business.
- What kind of business.
- Advertising.
Like "Bewitched"?
You're Durwood
and he's Mr. Kravitz.
Are you sure you want to?
It's been too long.
I thought that's what
you wanted.
You know who has
the best stuff?
- Charlton Heston.
- Who's that?
We went to his house,
he came out naked.
He's a very
good-looking man.
I guess if I looked like that,
I would be naked a lot, too.
In fairness, I don't think
he knew we were there.
It was kind of
an impromptu meeting.
We wanted him to be
the voice of Vaporub.
Right?
Wouldn't that be perfect?
She just said she doesn't
know who he is.
Come on, they're letting us in.
I told them how important you are.
- Thank you.
- No, just Harold.
- Who'd you tell 'em I was?
- Just go!
Hey, he's getting
me in, not you.
I'll send for you.
She knows what she's doing.
You really think you're gonna get
the Rolling Stones to do a TV ad?
They did one
for cereal in England.
It must have been
a long time ago.
It was three years ago.
When you were probably,
what, 11?
You see someone
do that in a movie?
You need to relax.
So what do you like so much
about the Rolling Stones?
Why don't you get me
backstage and you'll see.
What do you feel
when you hear them?
Brian Jones.
He's a troubadour.
So you feel romantic.
God, you're like
a psychiatrist.
What do you know
about psychiatrists?
Do you have a business card
or something I could
try on the doorman?
I'll make breakfast.
If, if, if.
You know what?
I am hungry.
I'm so sorry, sweetheart.
So what do you think?
They gonna show?
Stop looking at your watch.
They're gonna come
when they come.
right down that hallway
and I'm gonna jump on
Brian like Jack Ruby.
And what do you
expect to happen?
I'll get into
that dressing room
and I'm gonna stare at him
while he tunes his guitar.
He'll see me from across
the room.
I'm lady Jane.
He'll know that.
Then what are you gonna do?
Me I don't know.
Whatever he wants.
And what do you think he wants?
None of you want any of us
to have a good time
just 'cause you never did.
No, we're worried about you.
Got it!
I got it!
They want to do it.
I have never seen people more excited.
- Wait, you met them?
- They're here. They're here.
The Stones are here!
Who were you talking to?
They even sounded just like
them when they were singing.
They played for me.
I'm sorry I failed, Don.
We can try again tomorrow.
Asbury Park?
Forget it.
Manager looked right through us.
You want the last one?
There were 20.
I thought you were getting
it for your family.
You know what?
Let them get their own.
You bring home a bag
of food and they go at it,
and there's nothing
left for you. Eat first.
That's my recommendation
to people who say
they're getting married
and having kids-- Eat first.
- Sure you don't want it?
- Harry, you have to go.
Just let me sit here
for a second.
I have to get home.
Those girls, Don.
Those young girls.
They are so much fun.
Everybody's having fun.
They're all on drugs.
You're on drugs.
You signed the trade winds.
Who the hell are they?
Just go inside.
What are we gonna tell Raymond?
That the Rolling Stones
aren't good for Heinz.
Yeah.
His daughter just probably
wanted to meet them.
I don't think they're good
for her, either.
I'm gonna leave the bag.
Jennifer has me on a diet.
- We should do this again.
- Bye, Harry.
I waited as long as I could,
but we've got to go.
Really?
Drink too much with the Stones?
No, we didn't get to meet them.
Well, you'll have plenty
of time to tell me.
It takes forever
to get to Fire Island.
Did Betty call?
No.
Let's go.
Megan.
What?
I have to tell you something.
What happened?
It's Betty.
She might be sick.
Really sick.
What?
They found a tumor.
That's terrible.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't know how you'd react.
What, did you think
I'd be happy?
I don't know what I thought.
I just knew she wouldn't want you to know.
Well, it affects me.
There's a possibility
that it's nothing.
And if it's something,
we'll deal with it.
You know I love Sally.
No, no, no. I don't want
to have that conversation.
Great.
Then let's go.
Your trunk's on the dresser.
No.
I just can't.
Megan, you are 26 years old.
So I don't understand death?
I understand you went to
that concert last night,
but now it's suddenly too overwhelming
when we're supposed to go see my friends.
Come on.
There's nothing you can do.
It's okay.
This is very provocative.
Oh, that one.
I was at the movies.
Well, not the movies.
I was in Times Square at a peep show.
- Shouldn't we wait for Roger?
- For what?
He doesn't even come to the
meetings that are important.
- Go on.
- There's a resume in there.
Okay.
So you were at Needham
for a long time
and a lot of other places
for a short time.
I checked his references thoroughly
or I wouldn't have brought him in.
Would you let him talk?
Ahem.
I'm opinionated, but I
know if you were my boss,
I would have no problem
saying, "Okay, Don."
Unless you want me
to call you "Mr. Draper."
I worked for someone like that.
Kirk Whitby?
I'm not gonna say.
You wouldn't want me running all
over town telling your secrets.
Well, I wouldn't want you
grumbling behind my back, either.
You're right.
I shouldn't have said that.
I just wanted
to make you smile.
I'll be honest.
I've admired you
since the letter.
I thought it was the funniest
thing I ever read.
And the fact that I can
say the letter
and everyone knows
what I'm talking about.
I just want to be
a part of this place.
I think it's on the way up.
Between you and Margaret...
She's very interesting.
And I think I made
it clear, so are you.
Pleasure to meet you, Michael.
Good work.
Thanks.
Promise me you didn't just
hire the handsomest one.
Anything else?
Get him set up and let
him haggle with Lane.
Roger, I see you've met
Mr. Ginsberg.
Yeah, turns out we both have a dream of
throwing something through this window.
- How'd it go?
- Good.
See?
I'm proud of you.
Mr. Ginsberg,
follow me.
Ahem, I'm sorry.
My stomach grumbles sometimes and
it can sound like the F word.
You kn, I thought you were crazy when
I met you, and you have confirmed it
by not acting the way
that you acted with me.
You told me
not to act that way.
And the fact that you can
control it really scares me.
So I'm not getting the job?
No, you start tomorrow.
I would like to pick you up and
spin you around right now,
but I don't want people to think
that's how I got the job.
I'm glad you're excited.
Come on, be proud of me.
I need it.
Nobody in the world cares
I got the job but you.
Then I'm happy.
I can't believe this.
You should have
just gone in to work.
Come on.
Do you want me to
turn down the TV?
It's fine.
Henry Francis.
Well, tell Jim His Honor's
not going to Michigan.
Because Romey's a clown
and I don't want him
standing next to him.
Because he got a city to run.
Can we talk later?
Francis residence.
This is Betty.
Okay.
Yes.
Thank you for getting
back to me so quickly.
Okay.
Good-bye.
It's benign.
I knew it.
I'm so happy.
You're okay, you know.
I feel like I just
got off a boat from China.
Hey, everything's okay.
No, it's good.
It's good.
It's nice to be put
through the wringer
and find out I'm just fat.
Betty, come on.
You're exhausted.
That's what it is, isn't it?
I don't know
how many ways to tell you,
but I don't see it.
I know.
Your mother's obese.
Hey.
Listen to me.
I feel like I've been
given a gift.
Like scrooge seeing
his tombstone.
Oh, my God, this is what it could be.
But it's not gonna be.
Saturday night was fun.
Okay.
I'd like to say that
I've gathered you all here
so you may remember how small
this agency once was.
Mohawk Airlines
has chosen to return
to Sterling Cooper
Draper Pryce.
Now, now.
I'm just pleased
that after a long effort
I was able to sign them.
I've also hired a new copywriter
and look forward to great
success with your help.
Oh, and, of course,
Mr. Sterling will be
handling the day to day.
But rest assured,
everything he knows I'll know.
You gonna break that
over its nose?
Forget everything
I said before.
- Excuse me?
- That's the last guy I hired.
Hey! Ooh!
- Roger.
- What?
Little prick dangled it in
front of me and took it away.
It was disrespectful.
You know, I used to
love that kid.
I would hold his hand and
help him up on the swing set.
He grew up.
What did you expect?
I'm tired of it, Don.
I'm tired of trying to prove I
still have any value around here.
I'm exhausted from
hanging onto the ledge
and having some kid's
foot on my fingertips.
Bombs away.
Betty has cancer.
Really?
I don't know.
They're waiting on tests.
Well, that would
solve everything.
You want me to make a call?
She probably knows already.
I'm the one that has to call.
She's a fighter.
Come on.
I just imagine them
growing up without a mother.
I never had one.
Megan will try,
but what are they gonna do?
How does that end up?
Actual life and death.
I've given up on that.
I can't do that.
When is everything
gonna get back to normal?
- Henry Francis.
- Hi, Henry. It's Don.
Hello, Don.
I, uh...
Wanted to know if there was
any news about Betty.
I didn't realize she--
She's fine.
She's out of the woods.
Well, that's great news.
It is. You know, we're about
to put supper on the table.
I'll let you go.
Who was it?
Nobody.
Betty's fine.
I'm glad to hear it.
You're such an optimist.
She just needs to have
something to call you about.
Take you to dinner?
Sure.
Pete Fox died.
57 years old
for crying out loud.
I don't know who that is, pop.
Red Sox.
Right field he played.
I got the job.
You don't say.
What do you want to eat?
What do I want to eat?
You should get girls.
An old one and a young one.
I got rye bread
and some farmer cheese.
Look at me.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Te don't you like it?
It's good.
Aren't you going to finish?
I'm full.
Can I watch TV?
Go ahead.
♪ you wait, little girl,
on an empty stage ♪
♪ for fate to turn
the light on ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ that men will want
to write on ♪
♪ to write on ♪
♪ you are 16 going on 17 ♪
♪ baby, it's time to think ♪
♪ better beware,
be canny and careful ♪