Previously on Mad Men...
I get everything right and
I'm still getting it from you!
We were in the running,
I mean, actually this time...
for Jaguar.
Since I was a little girl it's
all I've ever dreamed about.
I don't wanna keep
you from your dream.
I have a spectacular
new site in the city.
Aren't you worried
you're going to get caught?
I've got an apartment.
When we land Jaguar the world
will know we've arrived.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Jaguar, the mistress who'll
do things your wife won't.
What did I say before?
The client doesn't want
to hear the word mistress.
Salesmen can use it,
but the campaign can't.
Jaguar, you'll love it
when you're in it.
Are we just spitting up
lines now?
You know what?
Let's take a break.
Where are you going?
What was unclear about the fact that
he's taking a break and we're not?
I need you to sign off
on Secor laxative.
I told you you were in charge of all
ongoing business till Jaguar's done.
- Just handle it.
- Done.
- How's the prospect doing?
- Is it lunchtime?
Jesus, is it?
Mr. Sterling bought
lobster from The Palm.
Doesn't that sound good?
So I don't know what the
Jaguar executives will say.
But I got dealerships
in Montclair,
Englewood, Morristown,
Paramus and Rutherford.
And I carry three other
foreign cars.
So, frankly, creative has
to be pretty spectacular,
or Jaguar is just another
word on the sign.
Well, then we have
nothing to worry about.
The dealership on the ground
floor of the corporate offices
on Madison has done very well just
having that XK-E in the entrance.
You have to be excited
about this car.
Oh, it's a red-hot number.
I'm excited about that.
But I'm a hard man to please.
I always feel like someone
should go the extra mile.
We're open to anything
your heart desires.
Well, the other day
when we were all touring
your offices,
our guide was
a dynamite redhead.
- Joan Harris.
- Built like a B-52.
Yeah, we know who
you're talking about.
Well, I sure would like the opportunity
to get to know her better.
Well, a lot of guys would.
But, you know, she's--
She's a very interesting girl.
She's one of these free spirits?
You know, open to ideas?
So you like redheads?
I think I know some.
I like that redhead.
And I think she and I
would both
welcome the opportunity
to spend a night together.
Well, you could ask her out.
It wouldn't be a conflict.
No, I'm kind of shy.
All I'm saying is, if it happens,
it would make me happy.
If it doesn't, well, no
guarantees in life, right?
Get another round.
I'll get it.
Absolutely not.
Was that what I think it was?
Yes, it was.
Why didn't you just let me
tell him she was married?
Because so is he.
And he already knows that.
Well, we wanted to be
in the car business.
- You waited up.
- No.
I mean, yes.
I'm going in to read tomorrow
for a really good part.
An audition?
Why didn't you call?
Honestly, because I had to go to
10th Avenue to get the script
and then I went
and talked to Fanny,
you know, who teaches
my auditioning class.
You're very good at auditions.
Not as good as the girls
who get parts.
You know what?
Let's talk about your day.
Well, I was gonna watch Carson
and cry myself to sleep.
It'll come to you.
- It always does.
- Unless it comes to you.
Do you really want help
or do want to yell at me?
I don't know yet.
What's the strategy?
A Jaguar is beautiful,
but unreliable.
It comes with a tool kit
the size of a typewriter.
You basically have to own
another car to go places.
So we're saying it's
your gorgeous mistress.
So a wife is like a
Buick in the garage.
We're trying to make
a weakness into a strength.
- We're selling to men.
- No, I got it.
Doesn't being a mistress
make the car immoral?
The word mistress
won't be in the ad.
I don't know,
but it sounds great.
I need to learn some of this.
You're here early.
What can I do for you?
Nothing.
Nothing, it's just I got
some bad news last night
and I was hoping
you'd help me deliver it.
What happened?
Well, we were having dinner
with Herb Rennet.
I think you met him
the other day, from Jaguar.
- Handsome guy.
- I don't remember any of them.
Well, I don't know what to do.
He basically pledged
he wasn't going to back us.
Why not?
Turns out he wanted something
we're not prepared to give.
Something very unorthodox.
- Good morning.
- Yes?
I'm here.
I'm going to get Danish.
What does he want?
Uh...
I feel like I shouldn't
even bring this up.
In fact, I don't know
how to bring this up.
But we're going to lose Jaguar
unless an arrangement
is made, and
it involves you and,
well, Herb.
How did that come up?
He said he was crazy about
you and then he just asked.
And then I thought
we were past it,
but right before
we put him in a cab,
he said it again and it
was quite conditional--
A night with you or no vote.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
Anyway, if you can think
of some way to break the news
to the company that we're out of
this, I'd really appreciate it.
You're unbelievable.
I'm married.
How would you feel
if someone asked Trudy?
I didn't bring this up.
He did.
If you're not interested
in the idea at all,
I appreciate--
It's just--
It seems to me that there's something
that could be worth the sacrifice.
We're talking about
a night in your life.
We've all had nights in our lives
where we've made mistakes for free.
You're talking about
prostitution.
I'm talking about
business at a very high level.
Do you consider Cleopatra
a prostitute?
Where do you get this stuff?
She was a queen.
What would it take
to make you a queen?
I don't think
you could afford it.
This was an act of desperation.
I hope I haven't insulted you.
That's all that matters to me.
I understand.
Scarlett, we're ready.
Now, we can't get Ginsberg
out for the call,
we want you to pretend
you're his junior.
- Partner?
- Supervisor.
I have Mr. Rick Swanson from
Chevalier Blanc Cologne on speaker.
Hi, Rick.
It's Kenny.
I'm here on a speaker with
Harry Crane and Peggy Olson,
Mr. Ginsberg's
supervisor,
and we want to know
why you want to pull the ad.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hi, Rick.
- Hello.
- We're very happy with the work,
but sales have leveled
off since the holidays.
It's Harry. And you know
Valentine's day is coming up.
A girl can't get a guy flowers.
Why would a woman buy a man
anything for Valentine's day?
Rick, it's Peggy.
I think you're right.
The target of "A Hard Day's Night" was men,
but we can easily change that.
How do you do that?
Hello?
What if it's our
leather jacket hero
running down the street
being chased by screaming girls
and, instead of jumping
into a bar,
he comes upon Lady Godiva
on a horse
as naked as we are
allowed to make her?
And he stops short,
but she leans down
and picks him up
and puts him on the horse
and rides away with him.
What's the tagline?
It's something about
how, you know,
the right woman
loves Chevalier Blanc.
So it's exactly the same
except for the ending?
And maybe Paris
instead of London.
Ooh-la-la.
A French song.
Close the door, please.
Herb Rennet has demanded
to spend a night with Joan.
And I don't mean
dinner and dancing.
He just came right out
and said that?
Who is he?
He's the head of
the dealers association.
And I hope you told him
to take a long walk.
There's three votes.
We only need two.
I thought about that.
But all he has to do is say he
can't sell cars with our campaign
and neither marketing
nor the factory will fight him.
- So?
- So I brought up the subject with Joan.
- You what?
- Now, relax.
She seemed more amused than
shocked.
And it's my opinion, if we
brought her the right amount...
So you thought you'd have us in here
for coffee and talk about this?
What's the problem
if she's amenable?
She said she'd do it?
She said we couldn't afford it.
She has a husband in Vietnam
and a baby at home.
And the work will be good
enough to win on its own.
- Plus, it's not a guarantee.
- No, it's not.
It's a guarantee
we won't get it if we don't.
You have some nerve
to even ask her.
That's right.
And you should be thanking me
because we've come too far
and are too close
to turning this place
into what it should be.
Now we're going to walk away?
Over what?
He's one guy and we can win it without him.
End of discussion.
Speaking of one guy,
how does everyone else feel?
I'd love to approach
her with, say,
a 10% finders fee on
the first year's commission.
That's $50,000.
A flattering amount
which begs no negotiation.
I'm not going to stand in the way,
but I am not paying for it.
Not even with
our Christmas bonuses?
Maybe Jaguar
wasn't meant to be, hmm?
I say we take our
bonuses and move on.
This is a car.
You cannot put a dollar figure
on its significance.
Extend our credit line.
Say it's for Jaguar.
Well, why don't I...
Look into it to see
what we can afford
so you may approach her
in the morning
with something definitive?
So, we're 75% of this company.
There's no need to create a conspiracy
by having a vote, is there?
Don't fool yourself. This is
some very dirty business.
Let her know
she can still say no.
You know what?
We're not doing this mistress thing.
It's vulgar.
We're going back to racing heritage.
- Why?
- People that writers horse around
because they're coming up
with ideas.
But, actually, it's because
they're horsing around.
Now knock off the grab-ass
and give me some lines.
And don't try to reuse these.
They do not apply.
Hey, skipper.
You got five seconds?
Five seconds is not
enough time to sit down.
Good news. Chevalier Blanc
wants to do a pool-out.
- Great.
- Peggy was incredible.
She came up with this
Lady Godiva bit on the spot.
But in the end, we're doing the
same ad as before, but in Paris.
The guy has a Beret.
Bid it out.
Ginsberg should be free by then.
Be nice to get him here.
Ginsberg?
I thought of this.
- It's his account. - So I guess
I'm not in charge of everything.
Jesus, Peggy, you know what?
You want to go to Paris?
Here.
Go to Paris.
- I'm not crying.
- I didn't think that.
What, we're all suddenly
interested in each other's lives?
I know for a fact that
Jaguar's not going to happen.
And he probably does, too.
- I don't care.
- I'll get you to Paris.
And if I don't,
we'll both get out of here.
You and your stupid pact.
Save the fiction
for your stories.
What can I do for you?
May I?
Signing Jaguar
would be disastrous
for the financial health
of this company.
You have to stop being afraid.
It would be a defining
moment for our business.
We don't want it that badly.
- All right, get out.
- It bears discussion.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Now get out.
Well, I'm sorry that
there was a discussion.
But when a company is
planning on spending $50,000,
there needs to be a discussion.
You were all in there
talking about it?
Why does it matter if you
have no intention of action?
I don't want them
to know I was asked.
Roger Sterling participated
in this discussion?
Yes.
He's a partner.
If you're against it, why did
you tell me that number?
Sounds like a joke.
Because that may be enough
money to turn your head,
and I wanted a chance
to discourage you.
It is a lot of money, Lane.
It's four times
what I make in a year.
I suppose you wouldn't
even be tempted.
Well, if I were,
I would try to avoid
the mistake
that I've made my entire life.
Every time someone's
asked me what I wanted,
- I've never told them the truth.
- And what would you want?
Three years ago
when I was essential
to the future of this firm,
I settled for much less
than I needed.
The cash would only
cripple the company
and would do very little
to change your future.
But a partnership
yielding a 5% stake
in the company itself...
Could take care
of a woman and a child
for a lifetime.
Here I thought
you were trying to stop this
because you have
feelings for me.
That's why I'm looking
out for your interests
over the company's.
"Good night, nobody.
Good night, Mush.
And good night to the old lady
whispering 'hush.'"
Hey.
How's it going?
You want to help us out?
Throw some taglines at the wall?
How about, "Jaguar,
it's your problem,
not mine."
May I speak with you?
So that's Megan.
Be careful what you say.
We're best friends.
So you're wearing
your audition dress.
What are you hoping
I can do for you?
You noticed.
I've only bad associations with
letting you leave the house in that.
There's probably 20 girls.
And Julia's coming with me.
Plus, he's a fairy.
So whatever this is,
it's not for me.
I want to walk in
there with confidence.
I could be in a bikini and you
could paint my body with spots.
Jaguar, try to tame it.
- Don't try and tame it.
- Here, kitty, kitty.
So she just comes and goes
as she pleases, huh?
Ginsberg.
What?
Yeah, I got it.
You can unplug that
if you want.
Aren't I interrupting
your routine without me?
Don't be cranky.
I was in a great mood when I left work.
Now I'm just exhausted.
So let's go to bed.
If and when we get Jaguar,
I'm going to need
an apartment in the city.
Absolutely not.
It's an epic poem
for me to get home.
And you're dressed
for bed at dinner.
Peter.
Let's stop playing games.
What are you talking about?
I'm tired of competing.
Your love affair
with Manhattan is over.
Well, how can you stand living
out here in this cemetery?
There's nothing to do.
There's no good night noises anywhere.
Because I want to raise
my child in the fresh air.
And we should
have another on the way.
I mean, it was a miracle the first
time and we're not even trying.
I'm using all my energy
putting my foot down.
It's 8:00.
Where were you?
What's that smell?
The refrigerator
is on the fritz.
- I had to take everything out.
- Did you call someone?
His wife won't let him
come here anymore.
I don't want to talk
about that.
We can afford to have someone else fix
the refrigerator, for God's sake.
Why won't anyone believe me?
Apolo and I are just friends.
- Ahem.
- You know what?
Just hire someone.
Get a colored girl in here.
They're used to
being bossed around.
Do whatever you want.
And what are you doing?
Drying up inside?
Because of what?
Greg? I hate him.
I don't want you talking
that way around Kevin.
He's a baby. He doesn't know that
we all wish his father was dead.
Please, stop.
Have you been drinking?
Yes.
Sit down.
"Little Murders" called.
Four of us got callbacks.
I'm supposed to go meet
the playwright tomorrow.
That's fantastic.
- That's a big deal.
- I know.
You have to promise you'll
come visit every weekend.
You're going to
Broadway, not jail.
No, rehearsal starts
in Boston in 10 days.
- Oh, forget it. I'm getting
ahead of myself. - Boston?
Yeah, I think there's eight weeks
of rehearsals plus previews.
So you're just gonna leave
for three months?
- If they want me.
- Well, forget it.
What do you think this is?
You think I'm gonna be
a singing waitress.
Maybe put on a show
in the laundry room?
I have to go to work.
You never thought about it because
you didn't expect me to make it.
This is the way it works.
Now you know.
Just keep doing whatever
the hell you want.
Please, come in.
You didn't have to make
an appointment, you know.
Yes, I did.
Tell them I want a partnership,
not silent,
comprising 5% of the business.
- Well...
- There's no negotiation.
Okay.
I want documents
by the end of the day.
I don't know
if that's possible.
Well, I'm not
guaranteeing results.
I don't think he'll have trouble performing.
He's quite ardent.
I meant winning the business.
Yes, of course.
So, I have instructions, but
I don't know how this works
in a practical sense.
The presentation's
tomorrow, isn't it?
So I just call him
and have him call you?
Probably not.
Well, how do I--
Figure something out.
Do I have to do all of it?
Which one is he?
He's not bad.
He's doing this.
Come in.
I know I'm not a manager,
but it's very hard
to get things done
with you in another room.
Well, I obviously have
the opposite feeling.
Permission to speak freely?
What?
I know you forbid us from
thinking about the mistress,
but I kept imagining the asshole
who's gonna want this car.
Now he's probably already
got a lot beautiful things.
Or maybe he thinks the car
will help him get them.
So I can go on?
And one way or another,
what he has isn't enough.
So no matter what,
the first idea has got to be
finally, like, you're
getting what you wanted.
The copy is still describing
the car as another woman.
But a woman you can't have,
because they have all
the qualities of a Jaguar--
Good-looking,
expensive, fast,
and, frankly, not practical.
I've always been fine
with all that.
But what's the line?
"Jaguar, at last,
something beautiful
you can truly own."
So he threw the money
in your face?
I don't even want
to talk about it.
I've never had
more responsibility.
I'm on everything but Jaguar.
I worked on Plymouth
at NW Ayer.
Car guys are a bunch of creeps.
They're all a bunch of creeps.
Could I get some more coffee?
I can never tell, ballerina,
if you're ambitious
or you just like to complain.
Why can't it be both?
Well, if this was about
work and not feelings,
you'd make a move.
You're right.
I could take a couple of meetings and get
an offer and throw that at Don's face.
Or you can do
what everybody else does--
Have a bunch of meetings,
pick a place and leave.
Don't think I haven't
thought about it.
Well, you'd get to find out
if you could shine elsewhere.
And I know you can.
And you'd let him know that
you're not some secretary
from Brooklyn who's
dying to help out.
I don't know if I can do that.
Sure you could.
You could hire a headhunter
or you could buy
a friend a piece of pie.
Of course, if you do move,
you can't complain
if I gave Draper a call
on my own behalf.
What if Don finds out
you helped me?
Don's a big boy.
If he was having this
conversation with you
and he wasn't
the subject of it,
he'd tell you
to leave in a second.
I've seen the campaign and it's
something I couldn't have imagined,
yet exactly what I expected.
Thank you.
And I want you to present
in the fullest confidence.
I think it's a winner.
Well, all I wanted to say
was we've removed
all other impediments.
But you do know
no matter what else goes on,
it's the creative
that's going to win this.
Close the door.
It was four to zero.
You abstained in absentia.
The conversation doesn't end
just because you leave the room.
What did you promise her?
A 5% stake as a voting partner.
Dawn, can you
buzz Mrs. Harris?
She's not here.
Actually, Dawn,
could you get my things?
Yes, you should be well rested.
I don't want it like this.
It was her idea.
Hello.
I'm Don Draper.
I work with Joan.
Is she in?
Yes, of course.
Please come in.
What?
She'll be right with you.
- I should take your coat.
- I won't be long.
Well, I will leave
you two alone.
I'm really sorry to bother
you if this is a bad time.
Well, I was just stepping
into the shower,
but how can I help you?
I wanted to tell you
it's not worth it.
And if we don't get
Jaguar, so what?
Who wants to be in business
with people like that?
I was told
everyone was on board.
I said no and they voted
when I left the room.
You're a good one, aren't you?
So you understand
what I'm saying?
Yes, I do.
I'm all right.
And thank you.
So you have a nice night.
And I'm gonna go prepare.
- Say good night to your friend.
- Good luck tomorrow.
You must get tired of hearing
what a beautiful thing this car is.
But I've met a lot
of beautiful women in my life.
And despite
their protestations,
they never tire of hearing it.
But when deep beauty
is encountered,
it arouses deep emotions
because it creates a desire,
because it is, by nature,
unattainable.
You look radiant, Joan.
May I call you Joan?
I'm Herb, by the way.
Well, I should hope so.
We're taught to think that
function is all that matters.
But we have a natural longing
for this other thing.
Oh, I got you
a little something.
I thought a woman
with your complexion
would look good in emerald.
When I was driving
the e-type,
I passed a 10-year-old boy in the
back window of a station wagon
and I watched his eyes follow.
He'd just seen something
he would want
for the rest of his life.
I feel like a sultan of Araby
and my tent is graced
with Helen of Troy.
Those are two
different stories.
He'd just seen that
unattainable object
speed by just out of reach.
Because they do that,
don't they?
Beautiful things.
You know, I don't know how much
longer I can restrain myself.
Let me see 'em.
Then I thought about a man of some
means reading "Playboy" or "Esquire"
and flipping past the flesh
to the shiny painted curves
of this car.
There was no effort
to stop his eye.
The difference is
he can have a Jaguar.
Well, thank you
for a wonderful time.
You're a hell of a gal.
Oh, this car,
this thing, gentlemen,
what price would we pay?
What behavior would we forgive?
If they weren't pretty,
if they weren't temperamental,
if they weren't
beyond our reach
and a little
out of our control,
would we love them like we do?
"Jaguar,
at last something beautiful
you can truly own."
What?
Mr. Draper is here
to see you.
Why'd you tell him I was here?
He's your boss.
You should see him.
Well, I will leave
you two alone.
I'm really sorry to bother
you if this is a bad time.
Well, I was just stepping
into the shower,
but how can I help you?
I wanted to tell you
it's not worth it.
And if we don't get
Jaguar, so what?
Who wants to be in business
with people like that?
How'd it go?
We'll see.
It was one of his good ones.
- Come have a drink?
- Maybe later.
- Where are you from?
- New York.
Turn around, please.
Could you step forward, sweetheart,
and turn around, please?
You know, I would have
taken you anywhere.
Well, no one comes in here.
The food's too bad.
We're not actually gonna
eat here, are we?
I'm not hungry.
Freddy Rums says you are.
And so does Tom Vogel.
You know we have Clearasil.
In fact, he sung your praises
while he was yelling at me that
the work wasn't as good anymore.
That was my first account.
Everybody else is gonna
wanna know if you're married
or planning on having a baby.
And then they're gonna want to
know how much you want to be paid.
But all I want to know is,
you must have heard
some pretty terrible things
about me
from Don Draper's mouth.
But why would you want
to play for the other team?
It's not a game.
It's my career.
Look, I need a writer.
They don't have
to be like me, but...
Do you know anything
about Ralph Waldo Emerson?
Uh....
From school.
He said that you have to be
a transparent eyeball.
What he meant was,
you have to take in the world
and pass it through you.
I am tired of people
who treat this like math.
I looked at your book
and I saw somebody
who was writing like
every product was for them.
No cliches, no homilies,
no formula.
Well, I had a lot of help.
Everybody does.
So I lied to you.
What do you want to get paid?
Freddy told you to do this?
You already know
you want to go.
You know how much
you'll do it for.
And you didn't make me wait.
I'm going do you
the same favor.
- Oh.
- If this is your last meeting.
I think I
need a chocolate shake.
First day of work ends with
you and me at La Caravelle.
- You're here.
- I'm here.
How'd it go?
How did yours go?
We're waiting to hear.
I bet you were great.
I bet you were, too.
The difference is
I want you to get it.
Stop it.
Well, you get to disappear
for work whenever you want.
And if I have to choose
between you and that,
I'll choose you.
But I'll hate you for it.
You know I don't want
you to fail.
Good.
Because I'm not going to.
- Don't run away like that.
- Shh.
Good morning, Mr. Draper.
Miss Olson wants to see you.
Peggy, come on in.
- D'arcy's out.
- Says who?
Arthur's girl told me
on the QT.
She said he was in
his office crying.
Jaguar is calling the
president of every agency.
- Dancer just got a big "no, thanks."
- D'arcy is out, too.
Get the partners in my office and
wait for further instructions.
Roger Sterling's office.
I want all the partners here.
You can't leave him on hold.
Where's Pete?
Just answer it.
Hello?
Hugh, how are you this morning?
I'm glad to hear that.
We like him, too.
- Well, that is terrific news.
- Bravo.
- Spectacular.
- Great.
We'll be over this afternoon
to kiss the bride.
He said it wasn't even close.
- Well, congratulations to everyone.
- We got to get champagne.
I promise you they're
opening it right now.
Before everybody's too drunk,
I need a list of names.
I promised them we'd staff up immediately
and we're going over there today.
Can't we wait to see what the
scope of the campaign will be?
Is this about
the bonuses again?
There are no bonuses this year.
Now, next year
Joan, shall we address the men?
- Congratulations.
- You wanted to talk to me?
You're not busy?
I'm not in the mood.
You really have no idea
when things are good, do you?
I swear, I don't really
need to talk right now.
Drink with me.
I have to talk about
something kind of serious.
I can't put a girl on Jaguar.
These car guys...
I just can't.
- But, you know--
- It's not that.
Is this about Joan
being made partner?
What?
The circumstances...
She's been with us 13 years.
I want you to know that
the day you saw
something in me...
My whole life changed.
And since then,
it's been my privilege
to not only be at your side,
but to be treated
like a protegee
and for you to be my mentor
and my champion.
But?
But... I think
I've reached a point
where it's time for me
to have a new experience.
Really?
I'm giving my notice.
I've accepted another offer.
- Are you done?
- I'm giving the customary two weeks.
My last day will be the third.
- And don't think--
- Hold on.
It's been crazy around here and I know
I've been taking you for granted.
And, frankly, I'm impressed.
You finally picked the right
moment to ask for a raise.
It's time for me to move on.
Come on.
I'm serious.
You're serious?
It wasn't easy.
Oh, I'm sure it wasn't.
Well, good for you.
Where are you going?
Cutler Gleason and Chaough.
Perfect.
Okay.
Well, let's pretend
I'm not responsible
for every single good thing
that's ever happened to you,
and you tell me
the number or make one up
and I'll beat it.
- There's no number.
- There's no number?
How long do you
to play this out?
I'm sorry,
but you know this
is what you would do.
You don't need to wait
until the third.
I've got a room full
of freelances out there.
I'll get by.
I understand.
Don't be a stranger.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ girl, you really
got me going ♪
♪ you got me so I don't know
what I'm doing now ♪
♪ yeah, you really got me now ♪
♪ you got me so I can't
sleep at night ♪
♪ yeah, you got me now ♪
♪ you got me so I don't
know what I'm doing now ♪
♪ oh, yeah, you really
got me now ♪
♪ you got me so I can't
sleep at night ♪
On the next episode of
AMC's Mad Men...
I don't like what we are doing.
So you're drinking
with a purpose.
I'm sure the others
are more deserving.
Were you celebrating with Don?
Should we be having this
conversation on the phone?
You know, you can't
keep being the good
little boy while the
elders run this business.
We're going to celebrate.
You can't tell anyone.
Only two episodes left
this season.
For more Mad Men video
go to amctv.com