Previously on
AMC's Mad Men...
Jesus. What a mess.
Part of it it's good, right?
You told me you
told her everything.
You had to know she'd be hurt.
After I told her
I felt relieved.
I know that your
name is not Don Draper.
Get out!
Mr. Pryce will be taking off
the last two weeks of August
for his son's visit.
So depressing...
I'm this close to
North American Aviation.
Good work.
I'm not sorry, but
I'm married. So are you.
I feel something...
And I know you do.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I need to speak with you.
Away from the neighbors, eh?
Roger.
So... Here we are.
Weeks later, man out of town.
Well, I know you, red.
This is the tenderloin
of your distress.
I'm late.
- What?
- I'm very late.
- Congratulations.
- I thought you should know.
- Me?
- He's been gone
for seven weeks.
It can't be his.
- Are you sure?
- There hasn't been
anyone else.
No no, are you sure you're...
You know, are you sure
that's what's going on?
Have you had a rabbit test?
I can't go to my doctor.
Hey, look at me.
You're overreacting.
One step at a time.
Let me take care of this.
I'm really sorry.
These things happen, right?
Will you stop being so upset?
Very well then.
I'll wait on your word.
Buck up.
It's gonna be fine.
Get me an
outside line.
- Francis residence.
- It's me. Has Sally
left for camp yet?
- No.
- Can I speak with her?
You can try.
Sally, come in here.
Your father is on the phone.
Talk to him.
- Hello.
- I missed you
this weekend.
And I have
a big surprise for you.
Can you keep a secret?
Do you think your friends
are going to be jealous
When they find out
that you're going
to see the Beatles
On Sunday at Shea stadium?
- What?
- You heard me.
Hello? Sally?
What's going on?
I'm gonna need her Sunday.
We're going to see
the Beatles.
Oh. My goodness.
- Sally, say thank you.
- Thank you, daddy.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
You can't be mad at me
if I wear earplugs.
I won't.
I promise.
Okay. See you Sunday.
You have a guest
in reception.
I'm on my way.
Oh. Hello.
Lane, you're looking well.
This is... Unexpected.
Um, have you brought Nigel?
No, I haven't.
Good morning, lane.
That's quite a reception.
John gibbons,
George Casey, this is
Robert Pryce my father.
- Hello.
- Sir.
- Laura will
show you inside.
- Pleasure to meet you.
I'm here to bring you home.
This was not the arrangement.
Rebecca doesn't
want to see you
unless you're in London.
- But Nigel does.
- I'm here to bring you home.
I'll be at
the Warwick until Friday.
That should be ample time.
Well, there's no reason
to stay then.
I suppose we should
at least dine together.
Have you plans
for this evening?
I do now.
I guess we're just
a little confused about
what it is we're selling.
Senator Murphy
would be appreciative
If voters were
very aware of the hundreds
of millions of dollars
He's brought
to California.
North American aviation
is a friend of Anaheim.
Pork is only half of it.
The guidance
and control systems
In the minuteman ii
Have significant
civilian potential.
United, t.W.A., American...
they're gonna want this.
So you never have to say
the word "bomb," right?
That's good.
Gentlemen.
Don't get up.
How would you feel
about avoiding the idea
of defense altogether?
If you think that's best.
We'd prefer something
more comprehensive though...
Defense,
cutting-edge technology
And of course the moon.
We've got a 60% bump
in our advertising budget
- To $4 million.
- I assume this means
television.
We're taking this
very seriously.
And so are we.
We see this
as the beginning
of a new era
In the relationship between
north American aviation
- And sterling Cooper
draper Pryce.
- Uh-huh.
There'll be fewer black bars
as the process moves forward.
Gibby.
- Don.
- George.
- Good to see
you both again.
- Likewise.
I should get on a plane
to the coast immediately.
Why? I thought
we were talking about
"meet the press."
I don't see minuteman missiles
breaking up the "hillbillies."
- I have to go anyway.
- Give me those tickets
before you go anywhere.
- Don't worry.
They're coming.
- I'm not worried.
Not in the slightest.
My father has come to visit.
I wonder if you might
join us for dinner
this evening.
I may have plans.
I'd consider it
a personal favor.
- So how long is
your visit?
- Too short.
So, father,
how have you found
your accommodations?
Adequate...
sixth floor.
Father likes a view.
I was quite impressed
with your office.
I think the view's better here.
Hello, gentlemen.
I'm your bunny... Judy.
May I see your key please?
Lane Pryce.
Are you the keyholder
or is this a borrowed key?
I am the keyholder.
May I take your
cocktail order,
Mr. Pryce?
Three whiskey sours would do.
She's asking what you want,
not how many you've had.
I'll have a nice bourbon.
Whiskey sour sounds good.
And, um, Judy,
Could you see
If that lovely creature
could drop by?
Of course.
So what's your line, Robert?
Carrington surgical,
but I retired.
Father was a salesman.
And therefore no stranger
To places such as these.
Oh, hello. How are
you gentlemen this evening?
Oh, very good, thank you.
Toni, I'd like
to introduce you to some
special guests of mine...
My father Robert
and my colleague don.
I tried to get us booked
in your section,
But it seems
you're very popular.
Mr. Pryce.
I hope you gentlemen enjoy
your evening with us
And let me know if there's
anything I can do.
We will.
She's the finest waitress.
I'd be partial to anyone
who brings us our drinks.
Hello, may I help you?
Is this the Francis home?
- It is.
- I'm special Agent Norris
And this is
special Agent Landingham
From the department of defense.
- May we come in?
- What is this regarding?
I promise there's
no reason to be alarmed.
I... well, I don't know
what this is regarding,
But I'm sure you'd rather
speak with my husband
And he's not home, obviously.
We need to speak with you.
Your ex-husband
Donald draper has requested
Security clearance
regarding business with
the United States government,
And it's our job
to confirm his application.
- Oh.
- It's a routine
background check
So, you see,
there's no reason
to be nervous.
No. Of course.
Do you mind
if I get my cigarettes?
Of course not.
So, Mrs. Francis,
You were married
to Donald draper
for how long?
- 11 years.
- And in general
Would you describe him
as a man of integrity?
We divorced.
We obviously had
differences.
No, of course.
Do you recall
Any of the magazines
or newspapers
Mr. Draper read
when you were married?
Anything that
struck you as radical
or subversive in nature?
No. He read,
but mostly for work.
Did he belong
to any clubs
or organizations?
N-n-new York
athletic club.
Would you
describe him as loyal?
Excuse me?
By that we mean
anything that might have
Given you doubts about
Mr. Draper's allegiance
to the United States,
Any possible
ties or sympathies
to the communist party,
- Or the soviet union.
- No, nothing like that.
So do you have
any reason to believe
Mr. Draper isn't
who he says he is?
What was that?
I'm sorry.
It's a standard question.
I know it sounds funny.
No.
It's Mrs. Francis.
Are you in?
I'll take it.
And, Megan,
can you check
on those tickets?
Of course.
- Hello.
- I just spent 40 minutes
- With two men
from the government.
- What?
Couldn't you have at least
given me some warning?
Betts, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, you applied
for some security clearance.
They need to know
all about you and I've
been through hell, don.
- I'm sick to my stomach.
- Whoa. Hold on.
What exactly happened?
- What?
- Who were they?
Two men from
the defense department,
And they asked me all kinds
of questions about you.
- About what?
- I don't remember everything.
Your military service,
your politics,
Your loyalty, your name.
And what did you say?
What do you think
I said? Nothing.
Hello?
Are you there?
I'm sorry. I, uh...
Jesus.
I didn't know
anything about this.
I don't even know
if I should be talking
on the phone.
Of course you should.
There's no problem
with any of that.
You know,
my husband works
for the governor.
You should've told me
they were coming.
You're right.
I'm sorry
for inconveniencing you.
Okay.
Well, goodbye then.
- Betty.
- Yes?
Thank you.
Megan, have I been contacted
By the department of defense?
Yes, of course.
There was a form...
I filled it out,
you signed it.
- What?
- Two weeks ago.
I have it. Did you want
to change something?
- I never looked at it.
- But you signed it.
- Why didn't you
tell me what it was?
- It's standard information.
It's in your
employment records...
just your name,
Social security number,
marital status.
This is very serious, Megan.
I should have been consulted.
We have a contact number.
I'm sure you can change
anything you need to.
Oh God, I'm so embarrassed.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
If you want to fire me,
I'd understand completely.
Is Mr. Campbell
still at lunch?
- Yes.
- Let me know
the minute he returns.
Bye.
- How did you get in here?
- I paid someone.
Nigel didn't come.
He's not coming.
I'm sorry, baby,
But you can't do
what you're doing
And you can't do
what you did last night.
- You're gonna
cost me my job.
- No, I know.
I apologize.
You know that I love you,
My chocolate bunny.
Stop it.
I love you too.
I just wanted
father to meet you.
Well, that was
a silly way to do it.
And I don't know why
you're asking for trouble.
No. You're in my life.
I want him to know
why I'm staying.
Why do you have to be
so damn dashing?
I'll ring you.
What kind of man are you?
You've used this woman
And you've ruined her.
Hold on a second.
A man of your age...
only slightly younger
than myself...
That you could behave
with such selfishness,
Such irresponsibility.
We came here
for your discretion,
not your judgment.
I know why you came here.
There's a good man...
He's not in the city.
He has a practice
in Morristown.
It's $400.
Here.
I don't want it
in my handwriting.
Shut the door.
Were you aware
that we applied
for a security clearance
To the department of defense?
Did that go through already?
Pete.
They interviewed Betty...
G-men.
- Why did you
fill out the form?
- Megan did.
And I signed it
without looking,
because that's what I do.
What did Betty say?
You've been fine this long.
There're three lies
in eight questions here.
If they talk to his family...
he was an engineer.
My age is wrong.
Jesus. I didn't
even think about it.
I remember
you mentioned once...
Don't you have a friend there?
And what's he supposed to do?
Stop it. Kill it.
At least find out
how far it's gone.
Calm down.
Let me think.
Look, this isn't your problem.
I just want some warning.
Why? What are
you gonna do?
Whatever I have to.
You can run
the agency without me.
Are you kidding me?
I'll look into it...
Immediately, okay?
I hate this.
Not that I would
change anything,
But I hate that it happened.
You know,
not the first part
but this.
I understand.
Don't you feel the same way?
I mean, what if this is a sign?
I haven't stopped
thinking about you.
Maybe I'm in love with you.
So you want to keep it?
No, of course not,
but it's just...
I mean, if there's going
to be something between us,
I don't want it
to start this way...
Do you?
... With a scandal?
I see.
But I guess you could keep it.
I mean, when he comes home,
who's gonna know
the difference?
Lots of g.I.S came home
to a little surprise.
No one did the math.
It wouldn't be my child.
Let's make that clear.
I mean if he comes home.
Jesus.
- Greg dying is not
a solution to this.
- Okay okay.
I'm desperate.
I'm just trying to think
of what's best for you.
I'm going to take care of it.
Oh. Well...
Whatever you want.
I'll take care
of it, obviously.
- When?
- Immediately.
And I don't want you to come.
You sure?
At least let me drive you.
We shouldn't be seen together.
I don't need you to come.
Look, I'm sorry
I missed dinner.
It's fine, Henry.
I know that you're working.
Don't say it like that.
I'm just tired.
It's late.
I have to tell you something.
Two men came
from the f.B.I. Today.
What?
They interviewed me
for 45 minutes about don.
Why?
Some kind of
security clearance.
Really?
Well, that's what they do.
Is that what
you're upset about?
Please don't
make me feel silly.
I didn't know if I was
allowed to say anything.
You can always tell me.
And if everything goes
as I hope,
One day you may
be talking to those
people on my behalf.
I just wanted you
to know they were here,
Because I don't...
Well, I don't want any secrets.
Okay.
- I've got it.
Take the next one.
- He's looking into it.
- How many people does
he have to talk to?
If you're asking if he knows
how to keep a secret,
He works for
the department of defense.
- But he talks to you?
- It's going to be okay.
I was thinking
about this and I know
it'll be uncomfortable,
But if we have to,
we can ride it out.
- Are you crazy?
- This many years later?
It must be past
the statute of limitations.
It's desertion.
There's no statute
of limitations.
I thought nobody cared
about these things.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't know.
You've been doing it for years.
I don't have to live
with your shit over my head.
You know, I signed
this account after you
disappeared in California.
It's taken three years,
but I've grown it
From cocktails to $4 million.
Get rid of it.
Good morning.
Mr. Keller is here.
- Would you like some coffee?
- No, thank you.
I appreciate you seeing me
on such short notice.
Well, you said you couldn't
discuss it over the phone,
So I assume it's serious.
Well...
I'm interested in setting up
Some kind of trust for my kids.
Oh. Well,
starting from when?
18 years old?
- 21 years old?
- Now.
And I want it to be
the kind of account
their mother can access.
Don, why would
she need anything?
Look...
If circumstances conspire,
She'll know why.
I don't like this.
I don't like this at all.
An emergency meeting and...
I'll be honest...
You seem very edgy.
What's going on?
Nothing. It just ran
through my mind
That maybe I'm not prepared.
I know this
has been hard on you...
The divorce...
but don't go spinning.
Everybody has bad dreams
every once in a while.
The wound is still fresh.
It'll heal in time.
Just... Tell me
that you'll do that
and I'll sleep better.
Okay, but I'll tell you...
I don't like hearing
that tone in your voice.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Now please tell me
You're shut upping
that girl out there.
Hillary.
Are you sure
you don't want me
to come in?
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm sure I will be in a minute.
She's 17 years old.
What do I say to her?
I had her when I was 15
and I don't regret it,
But she seems so much younger.
She's very beautiful.
Thank you.
She is.
I'm sorry.
There's no one to talk to.
I understand.
Thank you for being so sweet.
How old is your daughter?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't pry.
15.
Dr. Miller is
here to see you.
Send her in.
I owe you
a phone call, don't I?
Yes you do.
Are you all right?
What happened?
I've been snowed under.
I should've called...
I should've called today.
I have to cancel.
You look sick.
- You have a fever.
- Yeah, I haven't been
feeling well.
- Let me take you home.
- I'll be fine.
Come on, get your coat.
This pretty young thing,
She didn't know
which way to turn
With my father
on one end of the hall
And my Uncle on the other.
Should've tried
that move at Gettysburg.
My grandpa fought
in the civil war.
Mmm, really?
Where did he surrender?
He never surrendered.
That man could turn
going to the shitter
Into a parade.
- What are you doing?
- I'm getting this.
- Why would you do that?
- Sometimes a fella's gotta
pick up the check.
Since when?
You know that
I like you, Roger.
Hell, you a genuine character.
I'm sorry.
That's the long
and the short of it.
What the hell is
that supposed to mean?
It's over.
I'm sorry.
Are you kidding me?
Are you trying to kill me?
Is that your plan?
If you want to put us
through our paces,
We will shake heaven
and earth for you.
You know that.
Just tell me
it's for show beforehand
Because I swear
you're going to kill me.
Roger, it wasn't my decision.
Since daddy's...
Incapacitation
The board has been
more aggressive,
And that's never
been my bailiwick.
You know that.
But they want
to consolidate everything...
One agency, one rate,
All the ad work,
all the brands.
So fine, let's...
you know what?
Get draper
in a room with them
where do they want to go?
Where do you think?
B.B.D.O.
Do you think you'll
get the kind of attention
you get at sterling Cooper?
Well, you're not
sterling Cooper anymore.
That's right. We're better
and we're devoted to you.
Oh, hell.
I don't want you to think
this is for cause.
There's no reason.
There's nothing you can do,
Nothing you could do.
It's just the way it is.
Wait. This is
not happening.
You just don't end
business with people
After 25 yea...
30 years.
We're family.
I... I invited you
to my daughter's wedding.
I don't know
why you didn't get
the invitation.
You should fire your secretary
Is what you should do,
not fire your agency.
We're dead.
You know that.
- The question is when?
- We're gonna call for
the files on Monday.
No, you can't do that.
I'm begging you...
you can't do that.
You've gotta give me some time.
I told you, Roger.
It's done.
You're not gonna win
these fellas over.
- Give me 30 days.
- What's that gonna do?
After all the lies
I've told for you,
you owe me that!
I don't owe you squat.
You inherited this account.
30 days.
Keep it under your hat.
Give me a chance to get
our affairs in order.
I'm begging you.
Okay. I can do that.
Thank you.
No hard feelings.
- Excuse me.
Yes?
I'm really sorry.
We're looking for the Vernons.
I don't know them.
Is this 110 Waverly?
- No.
- What I tell you?
Sorry about that.
- Are you all right?
- Don't.
I'm gonna
get you a glass
of water. Sit down.
Are you all right?
I think I'm having
a heart attack.
Are you in pain?
Is it in your chest?
No, but I can't breathe.
Stop it.
Please, don't touch me.
If there's no pain,
you're not having
a heart attack.
You're not a real doctor.
My father has
a heart condition.
I've been through this, okay?
You should go.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm not leaving
you like this.
- Good evening.
- Good evening, father.
Do come in.
Father, come with me.
I'd like you to meet someone...
Properly this time.
Toni Charles, this is
my father Robert Pryce.
- How do you do?
- A pleasure to meet
you again.
How are you finding the city?
Are you enjoying yourself?
- I am.
- Very well then.
What do you say
we all head to dinner
and get acquainted?
As delightful as that sounds,
I'm afraid
I'm traveling tomorrow.
I'm terribly sorry.
Oh. Well,
that's too bad.
But please, go on ahead.
I don't want
to ruin your evening.
Uh, well, of course...
Toni, why don't you
run along ahead
And I'll join you
in a bit? Don't want
to lose our reservation.
Well, it was
a pleasure to meet you.
Lane said so many
nice things about you.
Yes.
I'll be right along, darling.
Come along.
Out with it.
I see your face.
Are you more distraught
that I found someone I love
- Or that she's a Negro?
- You're coming home, lane.
I'm afraid I've moved on.
- Ah!
- Put your home in order
Either there or here.
You will not live in between.
Yes sir.
What was that?
Darling, what's wrong?
I can't tell you.
Peter, look at me.
Is there something
I should know?
Trudy, no.
It's nothing to do
with you. Come here.
You should talk to me.
You'll feel better.
How is it that
some people just
walk through life,
Dragging their lies
with them, destroying
everything they touch?
- Who are
you talking about?
- I loathe it.
No one ever knows...
Except the honest people
Who have to pick up the pieces.
I don't know what
you're talking about
And I want to.
No, you don't.
And I don't want you to.
You can tell me anything.
- Ooh.
- What was that?
Huh. Just a kick.
He's turning over.
Feel.
Just remember
everything's good here.
No, we don't go
to East Hampton anymore.
We go to Southampton.
It's a rental,
but it's a beaut.
So listen, it's been
wonderful catching up,
But I have
to admit I'm calling
for Larry, actually.
What?
No.
God, I'm so sorry to hear that.
When did that happen?
I mean, when did he go?
I mean, what happened?
Oh, Louise,
I'm... I'm so sorry.
I obviously didn't know.
I must've been out of town.
Do you want something
to help you sleep?
I might have a Valium.
Why didn't you
tell me that two hours ago?
I don't know.
I just thought of it.
I never take them.
Thank you for staying.
I don't know what happened.
I think you do.
Those men...
Who did you think they were?
I'm so tired.
Please tell me what's wrong.
It's me.
I'm tired of running.
Running from what?
In Korea I was wounded,
But this other man was killed
and they mixed us up.
And I wanted them to.
And I...
Just kept living...
As him.
Oh my goodness.
Yup.
But now I think that's over.
What happened?
North American aviation
told the government
They need to know who I am.
What are you gonna do?
There's nothing to do.
Well, can't you get a lawyer?
You were a kid.
Turn yourself in,
have someone plead
for clemency.
It's not that simple.
There are things you can do.
I shouldn't have told you,
But I'm just
so damn tired
of all of it.
Hey.
I'm glad you told me.
I don't want to talk at
the office and I don't want
to talk over the phone.
Come in.
I spoke to Russ
And you haven't been flagged.
And if we end things
with n.A.A.,
The investigation
will stop where it is.
Thank God.
So I walk away from $4 million
And I just keep this
to myself because why?
Because you can't
live in the open?
You don't know any other way.
I come here unannounced
and there's another thing
I don't want to know.
Tell n.A.A. We want
Martin Marietta or Hughes.
And what do I tell
the partners?
I called your house
100 times last night.
I'm fine.
Everything went fine.
Should you even be here?
Should you be on your feet?
Roger.
Oh God.
I wish I could
hold you right now.
It's okay.
I feel good.
Ah.
I feel awful.
We avoided a tragedy.
What?
Oh. Yeah.
We have a partners meeting.
Oh Christ.
Really?
Come on.
Life goes on.
You're so beautiful.
- Gentlemen.
- Morning.
Let me call to order
a meeting of the partners.
- In attendance...
- get on with it.
I don't know
how to explain it,
but I have some serious news.
North American aviation
is moving on.
What happened?
There was a misunderstanding.
Some names were left
off of a document.
A general was insulted.
I apologized,
but the damage was done.
Well, that's just great.
- What general?
- Unfortunately
this is irreparable
How can that be?
Because I didn't
pay enough attention.
That's your only damn job.
I swear, when I think
what we're trying to do here,
When all you had to do
is hold their hands
and jerk 'em off...
Is that so hard to do,
Campbell?
We have to come in here
and have this catastrophe
Dropped into our lap
because you don't know
what the hell you're doing,
- Because you fucking up!
- Hey!
- Roger.
- That's the business
we're in...
Accounts come in,
accounts go out.
Roger, I think
you should apologize.
I'm sorry.
I have an announcement.
I'm going to be taking
a leave of absence...
Two weeks, perhaps a month,
To return to London
and tend to my family.
I shall be reachable
by telex and telephone.
I can say with full confidence
That the company
is in a state of stability
Even with this morning's news.
All matters financial
May be referred
to Mrs. Harris.
Very well then.
I'm sorry.
Is there more business?
Shall we go down
the current status
of accounts?
Lucky strike?
Vick chemical?
Send her in.
- How are you?
- I didn't expect you
to stop by.
Stop it.
I've been worried.
I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
Let's get something to eat.
I think I'd better be
on my own tonight.
Why don't we see
each other tomorrow?
Okay.
We'll figure out
what to do.
I promise.
We'll see.
- Mr. Draper?
- Saturday night?
- Yes.
Very good then.
You can call me
with the details.
Good night.
I know I messed
so many things up
And I... well,
I got Mr. Crane
to get these sent over.
It's the Beatles tickets.
- I thought you'd
want them right away.
- Yes.
Thank you.
You see?
Everything worked out.
Yes.
- Thank you.
- I hope it's okay,
But it's almost 8:00.
Do you need me?
No.
You can go.
Thank you.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com