Previously on Mad Men...
You're going to Vietnam!
I think I'd like eventually
to do what you do.
Every chip I make we become
less dependent on you!
- Why you...
- Roger...
- I have made the best of this.
- This is not my home.
Feel him.
The Mohawk Airlines is over.
Don't stop.
I'm late.
Me?
He's been gone for seven weeks,
it can't be his.
When can I start looking?
I'm so in love with Greenwich.
Will you marry me?
Yes!
Things aren't perfect.
( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
( Chanting )
O-wee-o, o-wee-o.
We got the poverty,
where is the dough?
O-wee-o, o-wee-o.
We got the poverty,
where is the dough?
Shut up!
- Get a job!
- Somebody call the cops.
That's all there is--
cops and negroes and priests.
( Chanting continues )
You're walking in a circle.
Must be hot out there.
What are you doing?
- ( Horns honking )
- ( Chanting continues )
You hit one.
Hey, watch the work.
- ( Laughing )
- To the men's room.
Crowd:
Less promises, more money!
Do you know somebody's throwing
water bombs out your windows?
What are you talking about?
Everybody saw it was
coming from this floor.
We all saw it.
This is the executive floor.
That's utterly ridiculous.
Don't you call us ridiculous.
Is this what Madison
Avenue represents?
( Laughing )
And they call us savages.
( Music playing )
What are you doing up?
I thought this
was the bathroom.
It's down there.
Okay.
You want breakfast?
( Bacon sizzling )
Happy Birthday.
Oh, thank you.
We should wait for his cake.
We're not gonna be here
on his actual birthday.
Thank you.
It's from all of us.
We'll go to the deli for dinner
tonight and have cherry cheesecake.
- Open it now.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Can I turn the bacon?
- No.
I love it.
Good morning, everybody.
- Good morning.
- Hi, Megan.
- Hi.
That's so nice.
He needs one of those.
It's a badger--
from its tail.
- What are we doing today?
- We're going to the Statue of Liberty.
You always say that,
but we never do.
( Sighs ) You hungry?
Just black coffee for me.
Okay, everybody.
Have a Happy Birthday.
Thank you, Sals.
How old are you gonna be?
40.
So when you're 40,
how old will I be?
You'll be dead.
We're not gonna see
you next weekend,
but we'll see you the weekend after.
That's the 11th.
- If you say so.
- You'll be 70.
That's right.
You're not gonna come in?
No. But give Morticia
and Lurch my love.
Flick the porch light
when you get there, all right?
- All right.
- Good night, animals.
Say good night, honey.
Good night, daddy.
Get your brother's hand.
Bye.
You're losing your head there.
Dandruff.
It's spit-up.
I saw your wife
dropping you off.
Such a sweet scene.
Yes.
She has quite a smile.
She's getting back to herself.
How old's the kid?
I thought it would be
a little faster.
Does she cry all the time?
No.
She just...
There was a time when she wouldn't
leave the house in a robe.
Listen, there's a point
when you go from going home
on the 5:25 to the 7:05.
If you finally
learn how to drive,
you can push it to 9:30.
You're getting
the wrong impression.
Or not come home at all.
Beth and I got into it
so bad the other night,
I just jumped in the car
and drove.
Made it all the way to
some motel in Rocky Hill.
Put my fist through a wall.
Howard, don't get
emotional again.
Maybe she's right.
Maybe I am a little selfish.
I said I needed time
with my thoughts.
She asked me what
I do at work all day.
They don't understand.
Conductor:
Greenwich.
Next stop, Greenwich,
Port Chester, Rye...
Who am I kidding?
It's nothing a little peace wouldn't fix.
There you go.
Morning.
Of course.
I'll let him know.
- Was that for me?
- No.
- Who was it?
- Really?
Fine.
What's Don up to today?
I see a lot of napping
and pillow talk.
That's your schedule.
You all had the status
meeting 20 minutes ago.
Can't you sit over there
once in a while?
What if I have someone
important coming in?
When you have somebody come
in, I will sit over there.
Here, why don't you
buy yourself
a fancy hat or a mask
or something?
No, thank you.
All I'm asking for
is a few hours a day
where the world might mistake
you for my secretary.
Joan said you were
supposed to share.
- And his phone rings more.
- Joan's not here.
And you just took $50 from me.
( Phone ringing )
Let your conscience
be your guide.
( Coos )
That feels good.
That feels so much better.
Yeah.
I was right.
Somebody was very wet.
When you were that size, I
used to change you every hour
whether you needed it or not.
I don't know how many times
I have to say this.
Those go in the cabinet
in the hallway.
I'm sorry.
I thought it'd be easier if
they were near your bathroom.
I didn't mean it that way.
I haven't slept.
And I just feel
cooped up in here.
I think it's bad for
Kevin to be out there
until I'm done cleaning
the oven-- the fumes.
I don't know why you had to
do that on a hot summer day.
Anyway, I think we're about
to run out of formula.
Hello.
Hello, you.
You're gonna take a nap.
Would you like that?
You want to lay in the bed with mommy?
A 10?
You buying his
formula or yours?
I'll take him for a walk.
Oh, God, would you?
You're gonna go
with Grandma Gail.
That's where you're gonna go.
( Fussing )
Close the door.
How was everybody's weekend?
Great. We all went
water-skiing together.
- Made a human pyramid.
- I was here.
Splendid. So I trust you're adequately
prepared for the Heinz presentation.
Yes, boss.
We have almost everything.
Mm-hmm. Just short
Mrs. Draper's work.
- She's writing the coupons.
- Has Don signed off?
He's late.
And so is she, coincidentally.
Clara.
Clara!
She should have just
rolled over and said,
"Don, what do you
think of this?"
I bet she says that
every morning.
( Laughing )
Come on, it's 11:00.
- ( Laughing )
- No sunbathing?
No.
Look, we had
a three-day weekend
and you didn't do anything?
That's not my calendar.
Pete:
Clara.
- How was your weekend?
- Clara, is Mr. Draper in yet?
- No.
- You're late for the status meeting.
You should probably go prepare
instead of molesting my secretary.
Well, sweetheart,
the torture's over.
Let the fun begin.
My office is 30 yards away.
So when I hit that buzzer,
I'm trying to save myself
a trip through the miracle
of telephonics.
Mr. and Mrs. Draper
are here.
- Good morning.
- Megan: So sorry. I overslept.
That's not true.
I did.
How was Memorial Day?
It was nice.
We had my kids.
You had the status
meeting at 10:00.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
( Chuckles ) Did you read about
Y&R's paper bag drop?
I did.
- I don't see the humor.
- It's funny.
I mean, if nothing else, it serves
them right for stealing Pond's.
What does one thing
have to do with the other?
They stole the Pond's account
and now they're a laughingstock.
- Makes me feel better.
- Gentlemen.
Shall we mosey on over
to the conference room?
- We did have a meeting at 10:00.
- Morning, Lane, clipboard.
We should run a want ad
saying something like,
"Sterling Cooper, an equal
opportunity employer."
- Our windows don't open.
- ( Laughs )
As tempting as it sounds,
I don't know if we need to be
spending money to further
their embarrassment.
Look, if there's no line item
for humiliating the competition,
Don will write it
and I'll pay for it.
But you're not
allowed to read it.
Forget the want ads.
The advertising column.
- I want them to see it.
- ( Laughs )
So, Heinz is coming in.
Don?
Yes. Caroline, can you get Megan
and the Heinz boards, please?
- Do you want the team?
- No.
- What else?
- Status is status quo on my end.
I'm supposed to have drinks with
Bruce Lewis from oldsmobile.
He wants to know if there's
a way around nader.
There isn't.
Anything else?
Lane?
I have a lunch at the 4A's,
so I should be back in time but
not necessarily conscious.
And according to the memo,
Kenny finally has signatures
from Chevalier, Galone
and Butler Shoes.
Footwear.
All good news.
I suppose that brings
this meeting to a close.
Don, may I speak
with you privately?
Uh, I should take a look
at these right away.
Mr. Campbell.
I have a call of nature.
Do not begin this meeting
without me.
When is he free next?
You obviously haven't seen
my coupons yet.
- Let's get out of here.
- No.
Then lock the door.
As soon as I'm in here
longer than five minutes,
people will start to...
What?
Who?
I have to get these to Peggy.
You have a presentation,
you know.
I could make you go home right now,
you know. I have that power.
( Intercom buzzes )
Caroline: Mr. Campbell
is here to see you.
- I just saw him.
- I have to get back to work.
Open your blouse.
You're a dirty old man.
- Anything else?
- No, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
Am I interrupting?
I asked for your first
available meeting,
and it turns out you have
nothing to do today.
If you could have any client in
the world, who would you want?
- American Airlines.
- Why?
- Because they stood us up.
- Right.
So I started thinking, who has
those feelings about us?
Mohawk Airlines.
You were very close.
The company's in
a lot of trouble.
It's very nice that things have not
gone well since we cut them loose.
They want to come back?
After the way
we treated them...
So that American Airlines
thing isn't happening?
- I, for one, am very excited.
- Oh, me, too.
I just don't understand
the secrecy or the urgency.
I'm meeting with them today, and
I think you should drop by.
Hank Lammott hit me pretty
hard on his way out the door.
I may not help.
Don, you're the big draw.
They're not going to ask
for someone else.
Look, get through this,
get them back for more,
and I'll make time
in my busy schedule.
Got it. I'll let you know
when I need you to...
It's a good idea.
Can I get some coffee?
Peggy: Oh, Megan,
you're here.
I took a risk on one of them.
Two for 22¢.
Nice.
Of course, we're really
locked into the 5¢ off,
but good thinking.
Stan, can you do
something to these?
Like what?
I don't know.
Do that thing with the border
around the edge so it kind
of looks like legal tender
with the can of beans
where Washington goes.
You want me to put
a little wig on him?
Play with it.
Drop dead.
They keep asking me to be
more and more specific
until you're
drawing it yourself.
- Do you want me to move?
- Oh, no, no.
- I'm just looking for gum.
- Oh, I have some.
So I have to ask your
opinion about something.
You did a great job,
but I can't really go
overboard on coupons.
I did that kind
of baloney for two years.
You should take comfort
in the fact that
it's very important to
the client-- too important.
No, it's something else.
Tomorrow's Don's birthday.
Oh, shit.
It's June 1st?
Ugh, I forgot.
Got to get him something.
I still haven't gotten
you a wedding present.
Sorry. You know
how busy I've been.
No, it's just, um...
I'm throwing a party
for him on Saturday.
It's a surprise.
Oh, okay.
For Don?
Yes.
Men hate surprises.
Didn't you have
"Lucy" in Canada?
Look, nobody likes it
in theory,
but people are always glad.
And you've never
seen me throw a party.
Everyone's gonna home from this
and they're gonna have sex.
Okay.
Sounds like fun
for us at least.
I mean, if I'm invited.
I don't want to assume.
You're invited.
I'm not sure who else is.
I went through his rolodex.
I crossed out all the clients
and everyone he's fired.
That doesn't leave
a lot of people.
Freddy Rumsen doesn't
come to parties.
- You have to invite Harry.
- I know,
but he really doesn't like him.
Really?
I didn't say anything.
( Laughs )
- Frank Keller, his accountant?
- He likes him.
There are six phone numbers
for Herman Phillips.
- Is he important?
- That's Duck.
What birthday is it?
( Mouths ) 40.
( Keys jingling )
( Door opens )
( Quietly ) How'd he do?
He was fussy the whole time.
But the elevator
always knocks him out.
Must be the vibration.
Who would have thought
you'd be so good at this?
You'll be good at it,
too, sweetheart.
What am I going to do
when you go home?
Are you really going
back to that office?
You worked.
I had to.
Your husband's a doctor.
It doesn't matter.
I promised and they need me.
I'm not saying you're
not important to them,
but they also know
that priorities change.
- They should, anyway.
- Why are you doing this?
You don't know how sick you're going to
feel inside or what you're going to miss.
What he's doing now,
that's nothing.
- Just wait.
- I know, I know.
I just--
I don't want
to break my promise.
And Greg will be stationed at
Fort Dix for a second year.
- I can commute from New Jersey.
- And then?
And then when he's done,
we'll see.
Joan, he's not going to
allow you to work.
Allow me?
Whither thou goest, I will go.
And how did that
work out for you?
( People chatting )
Ah, Pete Campbell.
Late as usual.
He obviously didn't
come in on a Mohawk plane.
- Hank. Jack.
- You're not late.
- Roger told us to come early.
- Hmm.
Have a seat. You're only one
behind, but they're nuclear.
Roger, they're looking
for you back in the office.
- It'll keep.
- We were just laughing about Y&R.
It couldn't have happened
to a better bunch of bigots.
( Laughs )
Roger, it's an emergency.
Really?
Oh, come on.
We just got started.
All right, all right.
Sorry, fellas.
Heavy is the head
that wears the crown.
You don't want me to fly
copilot or be your wingman?
Check your valises?
Hold your airsickness bag?
Do you want me to throw one
into the bag you're in?
You enjoy yourself, then.
Garcon, assume that
these are gone.
I should warn you
about these two--
- They're a thirsty lot.
- Always a pleasure.
When you're done with him, just fold
him up and slide him under the door.
( Laughs )
I love that guy.
And so we take advantage of
this new microphotography
and high-speed camera
to show...
A bean ballet.
( Humming )
Spinning in air with their
delicious perfection,
the beans pirouette
in slow motion,
they somersault in slow motion.
Some of them spin clockwise,
some counter-clockwise
so they'll appear to be
moving towards each other.
Until...
They drop into a full can
first seen from the top.
There's a splash of
mouth-watering sauce
as each one lands.
Then we cut to the front,
the iconic label.
( Stops humming )
"The art of supper."
Have you done this before,
this special photography?
It's been done before, but
you'll be the first on TV.
How do they get the beans to do that?
They can't just get lucky.
This camera can show
a bullet spinning in midair.
Where's the bite and smile?
Ken, you said there'd be
a bite and smile on the phone.
I think I said there was gonna
be a bean ballet, Raymond.
But I'm sure we can add that.
And what do they
take away from it?
It puts beans on their mind.
It's an unforgettable image.
And believe it or not,
it makes them exciting.
And it'll show you have
a sense of humor,
because, really,
they're being portrayed
as far more important
than they are.
You ever see beans up close
they're slimy. They look like
a bunch of bloody organs.
And it's not just for fellas like
me that saw things in Korea.
Kidney beans are
called kidney beans
because they're
shaped that way.
But you could call
all beans that.
They look better
in a group, in a bowl.
Hell, what's wrong
with a spoon?
Don.
- Well, hello, Don.
- Hello, Raymond.
Good to see you.
Are you as excited about this as we are?
I don't know.
You said to be bold.
Nothing on TV is going
to look like this.
And just imagine seeing
one of these dancing beans
on the subway wall.
People will hear the music
in their heads.
Look, it's very artistic.
And I want to be bold,
but this isn't what I had in mind
when I was talking about a
new generation of consumers.
The ketchup kids,
are they even going to notice this?
I mean, that waltz alone
reminds me of old people.
Maybe I wasn't clear.
This is temporary music.
We can change it.
It's got no message.
I can see your point.
Beans is the war,
the depression,
bomb shelters.
We have to erase that.
They have to be cool.
Don, you know what I'm talking about.
I want the kids in college.
It's convenient.
They have the hot plate.
They're sitting in.
Okay.
We'll work on that.
Maybe it's someone with
a picket sign saying,
- "We want beans."
- You know what, Raymond?
This is our job from here on out.
We'll make you happy.
Raymond: I'm really sorry
about that.
Please, this is a process.
Let me walk you out.
What else you got?
That was the best thing so far.
Unless you like
this beans protest.
Please, you can't be
surprised that that man
- doesn't have a taste for ballet.
- It's a joke on ballet.
And you can't be surprised he
doesn't have a sense of humor.
I'm not.
But I guess I thought
you'd come in here
and tell them how good it was.
Do I really want to waste an hour
and a half shoving it down his throat
only to have him pull
the plug at the last minute?
This is business that
came in over the transom.
We didn't pitch it.
He has every right to make us work for it.
I wish I would have known that.
I would have saved this
for round two.
We'll get him next time.
( Phone ringing )
Caroline.
Is he in?
He's gone for the day.
Ha!
Ah! Oh!
Damn it.
Clara.
Clara!
Oh, my goodness.
What happened?
- You want me to get some tissue?
- No.
I want you to tell me why
Roger Sterling was at my meeting.
- I don't know.
- I know.
Because he hovers over
your desk like a damn U-2.
- What?
- You think he's looking at your breasts?
He's looking at my calendar.
Did she hit you?
Thank you, Clara.
You've done enough damage for today.
You need to lower your voice.
Have a drink.
No, no more drinks.
- Heinz looked miserable.
- They're making us work for it.
Don didn't seem worried.
Did you crash with Mohawk?
No, it was perfect.
Except for my deep nausea
and pending headache.
Oh, and Roger made
an appearance.
( Chuckles ) Well, that shows
it's a good lead.
It's my lead.
Wasn't Roger in the service
with Henry Lammott?
Did you do any rowing?
- You rowed?
- I was a coxswain.
The boat moved because everyone
pulls in the same direction.
I'm not supposed to worry
about Roger.
I'm supposed to worry
about other agencies.
You shouldn't be worried at all.
Business is stable.
Stable is that step backwards
between successful and failing.
Fine, Pete.
Just don't be impatient.
You know how this works
from here on out.
We start with a bunch
of piddly shit.
Your topaz,
your white knight cologne.
We add your mid-sized stuff.
Maybe Mohawk.
We still got Vicks.
That's big.
Next, we worm our way
into a few niche companies,
get something sexy in a good
neighborhood, a pharmaceutical.
Maybe if God
is gracious, a car.
And then we go public,
open an office in Buenos Aires,
and Elvis plays
at Tammy's Sweet 16.
Kenny Cosgrove writes another
great American novel.
You know it didn't hurt
to have Roger warm them up.
There's no one better
at turning a meeting into a bender.
And they love his pickled guts.
Am I going to see you
at Chez Draper on Saturday?
I wish I could get
overtime for it.
( Chuckles )
You ready?
- We're almost done, actually.
- Do you need her?
No, it's okay.
It'll be here in the morning.
- Great.
- Big weekend plans?
It's Tuesday.
I don't know.
I was talking about me.
My cousin's coming in.
Stan, assume that
you're working.
Good night.
You're amazing.
It could have been worse.
I almost said, "I'm sorry
I can't make it."
- You're not going?
- No, my cousin's on shore leave.
He's only got two days.
A little notice would have been nice.
I would have loved
to have seen the look on Don's face.
You almost just saw it.
Like we have nothing
else to do.
Did you believe him in there?
The guy didn't like it.
What was he supposed to say?
What he usually says.
"Hey, buddy, you got such great
ideas, open your own agency."
The clients are right
all of a sudden?
I don't recognize that man.
He's kind and patient.
And it galls you.
No, it concerns me.
( Groans )
Where are you going?
I've got tickets
to the bean ballet
and the curtain's
about to go up.
Never gets old.
( Laughs )
You're home late.
I thought I was going to have
to walk home from the station,
but luckily there was
a cab driver leaving a bar.
How was your day?
I didn't want to disturb you.
Oh.
This becomes a home the minute
you walk through that door.
( Sighs )
There's no fruit
to my labor, tweety.
Well, I suppose
none of this counts--
An acre of land,
a wife, a child.
That has nothing
to do with work.
I'm ungrateful.
I'm sorry.
Dissatisfaction
is a symptom of ambition.
It's the coal that fuels the fire.
You know that.
( Sighs )
Do you really want a dog?
Maybe just a beagle
to scare off gophers.
We'll see.
Oh, luckily my parents
can baby-sit Saturday.
Now tell me the truth.
Did Megan really just invite you today?
She did.
I don't know about everyone else.
Well, she's very impulsive.
We know that.
I have to go to bed.
Tammy will be up in a hour.
Go ahead.
( Chatting, laughing )
Attention, party guests.
- Hello.
- ( Chatter stops )
We're T-minus
five minutes or so.
So if we can bring things
down to a sotto voce,
that would help.
I'm gonna turn off the lights.
- No!
- ( Guests laugh )
Well, fine.
Just keep it down.
My God, is he queer.
He reminds me
of Lane's brother.
( Laughs )
( Elevator opens )
Ah!
Finally.
We're gonna go
inside in a second.
You're the one that dragged
me out to the restaurant.
Come on.
- ( Whistles )
- ( Sighs )
Jane:
You have to knock.
- You have to knock to get in.
- What if it's started already?
It doesn't matter if it's started,
you still have to knock.
No.
We were just in
the neighborhood.
And my mother always said
never show up empty-handed.
Oh, damn it.
- No.
- ( Sighs )
Calice.
All:
Surprise!
( Applause ) Sorry, I blew it in the hall.
All:
Aw!
But I am very surprised.
( Applause )
( Band playing )
I have to say that I am honored
and touched to be included
in this group of intimates.
And I predicted this,
did I not?
This.
( Laughs )
( Grunts )
Who is this?
Oh, that's my wife.
- Nice to meet you.
- Charmed.
The domino theory
is not a joke.
The Vietnamese
are fighting a civil war.
There is no monolithic
communism.
- It's an excuse.
- Really?
Come on, Bert.
It's for profit.
Bombs are the perfect product.
They cost a fortune
and you only use them once.
So I suppose this young man here is
coming home in a bag for nothing.
If he's lucky.
You ever read "Johnny got his gun"?
No eyes, no ears, no nose,
tapping out his last
wishes in morse code
with his deformed head.
I thought there we
going to be girls here.
For purely selfish reasons, I want
to thank you for excluding Joan.
I would have had to buy
earplugs for the ride home.
It wasn't up to me.
Can't you tell?
( Laughing )
Hell of a party.
Jennifer couldn't make it.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- No, she couldn't get a date.
( Laughs )
Anyway, I know
she said no gifts,
but I got you this.
Open it.
You don't have to
if you don't want to.
It's a silver-handled
walking stick.
Oh, look, he got you a cane.
Don Ameche has one.
It's a steinway walking stick.
You could stick it up
your ass and have a concert.
Thank you very much.
( Megan laughing )
Oh, my God, really?
Harry:
Oh, a negro homosexual,
a Canadian sexpot
and unaccompanied redhead.
I think this may be
my key demographic.
Hello.
Don't.
Just leave it alone.
I know. You're wondering
what they're laughing about.
It's not you.
Well, I for one think
you're very brave, Megan.
My mother always said
a woman should surprise
her husband every day.
That's why they had
no lock on the WC.
It's true.
Look at you delivering drinks.
We should get you
a pair of roller skates.
Roger, I didn't know
you were invited.
Or did you just hear
I was coming and show up?
- Is he going bald?
- ( Chuckles )
( Laughs )
It just goes on and on.
It's beautiful,
but it's very loud.
Listen, you can hear the
traffic even over this party.
I know.
Who cares?
I just want to take my pants off
and slide my ass
on the carpeting.
How's the summer treating you?
Well, it's been good
because it's been bad.
- What do you do exactly?
- He's a journalist.
Underground papers mostly.
You may not have seen it.
And what exactly has been bad?
Well, I don't know.
Four riots in three cities in two months.
It is terrible.
And lord knows the police
aren't much help.
I was raised sex, politics, and
religion aren't party talk.
Well, what does that leave?
I don't know.
Alcohol and work?
Mmm.
Hello again.
Trudes, which one
is Jane Sterling again?
Mm, the glamour puss
with the tan.
Marry early and often.
We're thinking about smoking some
tea with Megan's friends out there.
Will you keep
an eye out for Don?
As long as you're
just thinking about it.
You should join us.
Kenny gets brave
and recites poems.
And she thinks they're good.
Oh, absolutely.
Megan was the best
waitress they ever had.
No, but I did get
the best tips.
- How did you manage that?
- She laid on that accent.
You know, she's
a really good actress.
Not good enough, obviously.
- Man: Julia, come here for a second.
- Hello there.
Hello.
- Glad you could come.
- Great party.
You got a great spread here.
I just wanted to
make sure we said hi.
I can't stay that long.
I have to go back and redo the Heinz pitch.
But I guess you know that.
Come on, Don.
What are you doing?
Was that bad?
Hell, look who you're talking to.
How do I know?
Okay, everyone.
- My friends.
- ( Band stops playing )
First of all, I wanted to
thank you all for coming.
And second of all,
I think I've had
just enough to drink
that I'm ready to give my own
present to the birthday boy.
All:
Oooh!
Thank you.
Thank you all for coming.
I think we should
call it a night.
Absolutely not, Don.
You stay there.
- Did you buy him a pony?
- ( Laughing )
Un, deux, trois, quatre.
( Band playing )
( Singing in French )
Oui, oui!
Oui!
( Guests cheer )
( Song ends )
Happy Birthday, baby.
( Cheering, whistling )
Why don't you sing like that?
Why don't you look like him?
( Clinking )
- Je m'appelle Roger.
- ( Guests laugh )
- If I may raise a glass.
- Happy Birthday, Don!
( Chuckles )
As I was saying--
to Megan
for letting us see
the Don Draper smile
usually reserved for clients.
Hear, hear!
And to Don,
you lucky so and so.
As a wise man once said,
the only thing worse
than not getting what you want
is someone else getting it.
Okay, now, no one has
called and complained,
so there's no reason
everyone shouldn't dance.
( Band playing )
I should probably clean up.
Leave it for the girl.
She doesn't come till Monday.
Call her and have
her come tomorrow.
And Monday.
Problem solved.
Did you have fun?
Move over.
No, I just want to sleep.
Oh, come on.
I know you had a good time.
I can see it.
I don't want to talk.
I just want to go to sleep.
Hey.
( Sighs )
Don't waste money
on things like that.
It was my money
and you don't get to
decide what I do with it.
Well, cod you please not
use it to embarrass me again?
What?
I know why you're upset.
You're 40.
I've been 40 for half a year.
This is your birthday now.
Fine, I don't like my birthday.
I told you, I never had it
when I was growing up
and I've never wanted it since.
You never had a birthday?
Didn't Betty ever
throw you a party?
No, because I forbid it.
( Laughs ) Why?
I don't need to be
the center of attention.
You love attention.
You twitched every time
I talked to another person.
( Sighs )
More people feel the way
I do than the way you do.
Where's your research?
Fine, I'm 40.
It's too late.
Aw.
Nobody loves Dick Whitman.
I love you.
That's why I threw you a party.
I'm going to sleep.