I've prepared all of your correspondence,
and the summaries are here
for you to go over.
You can put them down.
Well, it's just... It's 5:00.
Sorry about that.
You probably want to be leaving.
What are you up to?
Well, some of the girls from here
and the traveler's insurance
got a place in Saltaire.
- Mosquitoes.
- They don't bother me.
Some people they bother,
some people they don't.
- I'm just one of those people.
- A thing like that.
Is he making you work
because he's got no place to go?
- No.
- Have a wonderful weekend, dear.
Why is it that a man on his own
is an object of pity
when she's really the one
you should feel sorry for?
I don't feel sorry for her.
Those girls do whatever they want.
Still working, Campbell?
There's no reason to show off.
Cooper's in Montana, Sterling's in Jane
- and Draper's on vacation.
- He's not on vacation.
He's been in Dallas or Denver or something.
Hilton sent him to every armpit he has.
I'd like to get out of town in August once,
even for work.
I love this time of year.
It's quiet. It used to be like this
when I was a kid all the time.
I'd lie in bed at night, hear horses going by.
New York in August?
It's like a great, big, melting wax museum.
Nothing but those fat girls
with the hairy armpits
putting their feet in the fountain.
You know what?
My weekend doesn't look so bad now.
I'll take anybody for a drink who wants one.
I poured you a beer.
If you were wondering,
there's a Hathaway in there.
- The hotel gave me someone else's shirt.
- Then you should complain to Mr. Hilton.
- They should be paying you for this.
- There's a hearing,
and I'm paid well enough already.
- What are they doing out there?
- Catching lightning bugs.
You should join them.
Yes, this is Elizabeth Draper
from the Junior League of Tarrytown
calling for Mrs. Howard Englewood.
We're trying to save
the Pleasantville Road Reservoir.
When do you expect them back?
Well, that's no good.
Yes, have a good evening.
Draper residence.
Just a minute. Don. Come on, Don.
It's for you.
It's Mr. Hilton's office.
This is Don.
Okay. When?
Tuesday night.
Pan Am? Sure, send it to my office.
You as well.
- Where are you going now?
- He wants me to fly out Tuesday night
- and join him in Rome.
- Rome?
- Well, that's a lot better than Dallas.
- Not for two days it isn't.
I'll see the Colosseum from a taxicab.
We should've gone to the beach
for the summer.
You've been gone the whole time, anyway.
First of all, that's not true.
Second, there's nothing stopping you
from coming with me.
- You have a passport.
- I guess our two-month-old isn't an issue.
We can stay at the Waldorf
anytime we want.
- Because that's just like Rome.
- Sorry, Birdie.
I gotta catch up on my sleep.
- Okay, you're all set. Stand up.
- I am.
Are you okay?
- Are you trying to get that in or out?
- It's stuck.
- You work for the Lawrences, right?
- I'm very sorry.
- You're their au pair, aren't you?
- Yes, but they will send me home.
First of all, let's take care of this.
- What happened?
- I can't tell you.
- Yes, you can.
- I can't.
What's your name?
- Gudrun.
- My name is Peter.
I'm in 14G.
And I'm not going to get you in trouble.
I have this party and I borrowed her dress
and this happened.
- No one can clean and she's coming home.
- So you thought you would throw it away?
They're just going to think you stole it.
Whoa, whoa, wait. Hold on.
I don't think you're thinking clearly.
You could put it back in the closet,
and when she takes it out,
blame it on the little kids.
They have a girl, right?
I would never do this.
- When are they coming home?
- Thursday.
- Give it to me.
- For what?
Just give it to me.
- Let me see what I can do.
- Are you sure?
- And people say New York's not friendly.
- Thank you.
Now, I'm not promising anything.
I'll do my best.
Good night.
We've read your statement, Mrs. Gumport,
and we appreciate your concern.
- So where is he? We're next.
- I don't know.
- Did he say he was coming?
- I didn't speak to him exactly.
Maybe he sent a letter,
a proclamation or something.
I believe that completes our old business.
Move onto the new business on the agenda.
We will begin with addressing the gas
station signs on South Water Street.
Excuse me. I believe there's been
a request for discussion
of the Pleasantville Road Reservoir.
It's on the agenda.
Somehow that got shifted
into new business.
That's definitely old business.
- Who are you exactly?
- She's with me. I'm Mrs. Jack Farrelly,
and we're representing
the Junior League of Tarrytown.
- Would the trustees please locate the...
- There should be two petitions there.
- Am I late?
- No, you're just in time.
We have someone
who'd like to speak on our behalf.
Yes.
Yes. Mayor, trustees.
I'm Henry Francis, Governor Rockefeller's
director of public relations and research,
and I've been sent here to deliver this
request on behalf of the governor's office.
- Really?
- It's a request that further study is needed,
because, as you know,
this project was initiated
based on an assumption that
the water quality of the reservoir is lacking.
I don't think that was an assumption.
There was a study.
With all due respect,
the governor's office believes
that was not conclusive.
- May I see that letter?
- I've brought copies for everyone.
Very well, Mr. Francis.
We appreciate the governor's interest
in our hamlet,
and do hereby order the development
of the Pleasantville Road Reservoir
be suspended until further notice.
Calm down, ladies.
I believe that completes our old business.
Move onto the new business on the agenda.
I am so impressed.
- So how long will that report take?
- I have no idea,
but there's a saying in politics,
"When you have no power, delay. "
- Betty says you're from around here.
- Yeah, about 3 miles that way.
I have to get out of here
before Florence Esterhazi comes out
- and reiterates the financial report.
- I should be getting back as well.
- Are you driving to Albany?
- No.
Well, I'm this way.
- They say you can't fight city hall.
- Good night, Francine.
Well, this is me.
No station wagon for you, I guess.
I have one. It's just, this was my father's.
I thought it would be good luck.
So.
So what?
Nothing.
I'd love to buy you some coffee,
but I don't think there's any place open.
I appreciate the offer,
but I should be getting home.
I just want to say thank you.
You really...
You really did everything we wanted,
and I know how busy you must be.
Well, I think you'll find
that I put my heart into things
when something's important to me.
Or someone.
That is a beautiful car.
He loved it.
I saw how happy you were in there.
- I was. I am.
- And I thought, "Dear God.
"Did I have anything to do with that?"
Because that would make me happy.
You did.
- Good night.
- Drive safely now.
Do you know what happened
to the Hilton cufflinks?
They're little Stetsons, sterling silver.
They're in my top drawer.
Bobby was playing with them. They're fine.
- Look at that. How'd it go?
- It went very well. We won.
We won, we won, we won!
- What time are you leaving?
- Car comes at 5:45.
- You're leaving from work?
- Yes.
- So they just killed the whole development?
- Not exactly.
We had completely forgotten this,
but there's a man
from the governor's office,
and he pointed out
something we'd forgotten,
which was that the whole project
was based on the idea
that the water's no good up there anymore,
which is a lie.
It's not true at all, not even a little.
They just made it up.
So he ordered another study, you know,
like a chemical analysis of the water,
and that could take years,
so I think they'll move on.
They should just do it up in Newburgh.
It's already disgusting.
That's real politics.
Well, you know, when you don't
have any power, you have to delay things.
Don.
- I'm up. I'm up.
- No, it's not time to wake up.
I want to come with you. Is it too late?
What? No.
- I can buy you a ticket at the airport.
- Carla can watch them for a few days.
Sure, why not?
I know you'll be working the whole time,
but I just want to get on a plane.
Pardon me. Do you work here?
The men's room is exactly here,
one floor down.
No, I don't need the men's room. I...
I can't return this. It has this stain here.
I spilled wine on it
and my wife hasn't forgiven me,
and I'd really appreciate
if you could get me out of the doghouse.
I'm sorry, but anyone
could've sewn a tag in this and...
Do I look like someone
who wants to steal a dress?
- I'll pay for it.
- And I was going to say if we did carry it,
it would be from last season,
and I don't know that we still have it.
- Let me speak to the manager.
- Of the entire store?
Of the republic of dresses.
Whoever can help me with this,
because you're falling short.
Just a minute.
- May I help you?
- Yes, I...
Joan! Is that you?
Yes. Yes, it is. How are you?
I'm well. Thank you.
I was asking for the manager. I had no idea.
Well, I'm just filling in.
They needed some extra help.
- I get my pick before they get put out.
- Isn't that smart?
- So how can I help you?
- Well, I don't mean to be a bother,
I was just hoping someone could.
It's this dress.
Trudy spilled wine on it.
She's beside herself.
I may have spilled the wine,
and I was hoping to exchange it
or replace it,
whichever will get me out
of the ladies dresses department.
May I?
It is our merchandise.
- This one's small. I don't see Trudy in a 10.
- It doesn't fit great, but she loves it.
- It's very...
- It's very summery.
Give me a moment.
Take this down to customer service.
They'll send someone to the stockroom.
- It'll be boxed up, but I'm sure we have it.
- I'm willing to pay for it, of course.
- It's all taken care of.
- Well, that's very generous.
Thank you. So how are you?
Never been better.
How are things at the office?
Moneypenny hasn't self-destructed,
but it's just a matter of time.
And how are you?
I think I told you already. I'm very well.
Greg is just finishing up his residency.
He's actually thinking about
a new specialty.
You know doctors.
Whatever's the latest thing.
And what would that be?
Psychiatry.
I'll take the dress and you take that.
Thank you so much
for getting me out of a scrape.
And I'd appreciate it
if you should happen to run into Trudy
that you be discreet.
The whole incident was fraught with drama.
Of course. This never happened.
Nice to see you again.
Wow.
It's beautiful.
- What is that smell?
- Which one?
It's like rubber or diesel.
I can barely stand up.
Let me see what's going on.
Sorry. I haven't changed my money yet.
No, signore. Thank you.
American dollar is very good.
Thank you.
$2, Don? That's what he makes in a week.
Don, look.
- I'm sorry. Is this the Drapers' room?
- Yes, this is Mrs. Draper.
Is it? Well, it's high time I got to meet you.
This must be Mr. Hilton.
Connie. Please.
- Welcome to Rome.
- Thank you. I'm happy to be here.
I want you to put my staff
through its traces.
No complaint's too small.
I'd kick you up to a suite,
but I want Don to see the way this works
for most people.
- It's lovely.
- When I see you tonight,
I want to hear all about it.
I so, so appreciate this.
It's an hour or two at the most.
The board is trying to jap us
with a sudden meeting.
Ernie, I'm leaving!
You're drinking alone.
This is, in Rome, not in the law.
Whiskey, neat.
- May I join you?
- Yankee. Hey, go home.
It's an American millionaire.
- Are they making fun of me?
- A little bit.
I'm only in Rome for one night.
I won't have my heart broken.
- Room 763.
- That's right near my room.
Good night, signorina.
- To whatever they were saying.
- They said you were ugly.
Does that bother you?
You think because of the way I'm dressed
that I'm shallow?
I was just hoping you were easy.
- They said that, too.
- What brings you to Rome?
Seen anything interesting?
- I could take it or leave it.
- Well, look at the lovebirds, will you?
Connie, this is my wife, Betty.
By golly, you are an indecently lucky man.
By golly, he's nutty.
He's something.
He adores you.
You're tiny.
He does.
Now I can see
what all the fuss has been about.
He sees great things in you.
- Where are we going?
- We're going for ice cream.
That's a grand idea.
Close your window.
My hair is getting mussed.
- How was your day?
- Okay.
- Do I look pretty?
- I guess so.
Hey, what are you doing?
Sally and Ernie sitting in a tree.
K- I-S-S-I-N-G...
Shut up! I mean it!
First comes love...
- Shut up!
- Then comes...
Stop it!
- I said shut up!
- Hey, hey, hey! That's enough!
- She hurt me.
- He hit me first.
- She was kissing Ernie.
- I was not!
All right! Both of you, separate rooms.
I'm not gonna let Ernie and Jessica
visit anymore.
Well, aren't you a lucky girl?
Go ahead, open it. Make sure it's right.
It's like new!
They just exchanged it. No questions asked.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Peter, from my heart.
- I promise I never do this again.
- It's all right. It never happened.
We should celebrate.
- I don't know.
- What do you like to drink?
You're German, right?
I can get us some beer or a Riesling.
Schnapps?
You are so nice,
but I have my boyfriend.
Thank you so much to do this for me.
Glad I could help.
Good night.
- I woke you.
- What do you want?
I went to a lot of trouble
to solve your dress problem,
and I think I at least deserve
to see it on you.
Okay, but you have to be very quiet.
- This is cozy.
- I'll go get the dress.
I'd like to kiss you.
- Hello?
- Did I wake you?
- No. No, I'm up.
- Can I interest you two in some breakfast?
Breakfast? Sure, let me just...
Stay.
You know, Connie, Betty's telling me she
already ordered breakfast up to the room.
- Can I meet you afterwards?
- Of course.
You let me know
how you like the room service.
- Did you hear the bells this morning?
- I did.
I like sleeping on this side of the bed.
I have to get up.
Order something. He wants a full report.
Well, hello.
Welcome home.
- How is everybody?
- Everyone's fine. How was your trip?
It was short but sweet.
Well, good. I'm going to get my things.
Just one more thing.
- You might want to talk to Sally.
- Why?
- She'll tell you.
- Carla, you brought it up.
I keep talking to her about that temper.
I'm gonna go check the mail.
Do you want anything?
She kissed Ernie Hanson. Bobby was
teasing her, and she really went after him.
Okay. It's okay.
- Thank you for telling me.
- I think they just missed you.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Well, I missed you. You know that?
Mr. Campbell. Ed Lawrence, 14C.
Yes, of course. How are you, Ed?
- Is your wife at home?
- No.
- Can I come in for a minute?
- Of course.
- What are you drinking, Ed?
- I have a martini waiting next door.
Let me make this quick.
You know we have this German au pair
working for us?
- No, I didn't know that.
- Yes, you do.
- I don't know what she said...
- Please, just relax.
I know it's August and all the cats are away,
but I just spent one of my precious
vacation days refilling the Kleenex boxes.
- I don't understand.
- Would you drop it?
I've had four months without any tears,
Mr. Campbell. Four quiet months.
You know how hard it is to find someone
my wife can get along with?
And now this.
Look, there are plenty of nannies
in this neighborhood.
Stay away from her.
In fact, be smart. Stay out of the building.
- I'm very sorry.
- It'll be fine.
Enjoy the rest of your summer.
- Bobby, sit down.
- Mayday! Mayday!
Daddy doesn't know,
but Carla told me you were fighting
while we were gone.
Sally.
- Carla was very upset.
- It's not fair. I didn't do anything.
That's it. You apologize to Bobby
and you learn to control your temper,
or I'm going to have
to start taking things away.
- I'm sorry I hit you.
- That's okay.
I called the office. Hilton sent a packet over
before we even left.
I'm sorry.
- Going swimming?
- Are we?
Yes.
See you tonight.
Yes, but what you really would've enjoyed
was watching my father struggle
with the sailboat.
Well, hello.
Hello.
- Is everybody having a good summer?
- Very nice. Very hot.
I see Marta came.
Or did you keep it this way yourself?
- I did my best.
- My little bachelor. Come over here.
I missed you.
I missed every part of you.
- Trudy, I have to get to work.
- I don't care.
Peter.
You always get that guilty look
on your face when we see little children.
I told you.
I don't care.
You're my husband. I want what you want.
Did you miss me? A little?
What's wrong?
Peter. Look at me. Did something happen?
- Sally, get down here.
- Coming.
I want you to know that I think
Ernie Hanson is a very nice little boy,
but I don't want you running around
just kissing boys.
- I wasn't.
- And you don't kiss boys. Boys kiss you.
The first kiss is very special.
But I already did it. It's over.
You're going to have a lot of first kisses.
You're going to want it to be special,
so you remember.
It's where you go from being a stranger
to knowing someone,
and every kiss with him after that
is a shadow of that kiss.
Do you understand?
I think so.
Go play.
- Hello.
I made some cold salads,
hearts of palm, tomatoes, olives.
Wonderful.
- Do you want a drink?
- No.
I walked down Lexington
and they opened a new fruit market,
but other than the melons,
most of it was unremarkable,
so I stopped in Butterfield Market
and they had all of the stone fruits
and beautiful cherries and I thought...
- Trudy.
... maybe I'd make a fruit salad for dessert.
What?
I don't want you to go away anymore
without me.
Good. I won't.
Tell me, what happened at work today?
Well, Kinsey invented some contraption
that can shoot a water balloon
across the office.
- We filled it with ketchup.
- Did you?
I have $5 for Carla.
She watched the kids for me.
The board called a secret meeting
about the reservoir.
- I think they reversed us.
- Really?
We'll see.
- So did you go to the catacombs?
- No.
Throw a coin in the fountain?
- You did have a good time, didn't you?
- You want some?
The kids didn't eat it at all.
I put them to bed.
Carlton and I went to Lake George
for a week after Jess was born.
No problems, no kids.
It was magical.
We have to do that again.
I'm afraid we may have to be vigilant
about the reservoir.
Although, it'd be an excuse for you
to get more help from high places.
I'm done with that. We made our stand.
Sunny Madrid. Doesn't that sound
like it would do the trick?
I've never been.
- Welcome home.
- Hello, Francine.
Well, I should be going.
From what I hear,
you two must be very tired.
Good night, Francine.
- Hey.
- Don't.
- What's wrong?
I hate this place. I hate our friends.
- I hate this town.
- Betts.
We'll go away again. You know we will.
Do me a favor. Look on your pillow.
Open it.
I saw it in the gift shop,
but we were leaving,
so I had Connie send it.
It's lovely.
I'll have it put on your bracelet.
Then I can have something to look at
when I tell the story
about the time we went to Rome.