Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
of imagination.
Next stop,
the twilight zone.
This is africa, 1943.
War spits out
its violence overhead,
and the sandy graveyard
swallows it up.
Her name isking nine:
B-25 medium bomber,
12th air force.
On a hot, still morning,
she took off from tunisia
to bomb the southern tip
of italy.
An errant piece of flak
tore a hole in a wing tank
and, like a wounded bird,
this is where she landed-
not to return on this day
or any other day.
Oh...
oh, yeah, i remember now.
At least i remember
parts of it.
Wing tank hit...
and lost fuel all the way over,
fell behind, went off course
and bellied in.
And the crew...
what about the crew?
Hey, did they bail out?
Did i order them to bail out?
No.
No, i didn't.
We all rode it in-
all of us.
Me...
i'm james embry, captain.
Yeah, yeah, that's who i am.
Uh... blake, copilot
kransky, radio operator
and wave-scanner,
and jimenez, navigator.
Connors- he was a tail gunner.
Klein- he was
the upper turret gunner.
Now, let's see. Who else?
Who else?
Blake?
Jimenez?
Connors?
Kransky?
Klein?
Jimenez?
Hey!
All right, now. All right, now.
Piece it together.
That's what i have to do.
Just piece it all together.
We bellied in...
we bellied in,
and i must have been thrown
clear of the plane.
Yeah. Yeah,
that's what happened.
It knocked me cold.
Yeah, i may have been out
for hours.
And then the others were...
what about the others?
Where are they?
They didn't jump.
Their chutes are still here.
And they're not dead.
They... they couldn't be dead.
And, if they left the plane
and started walking,
why didn't they take me?
Blake!
Klein! Kransky!
Connors?
Jiminez?
King ninecallingfirefly.
Mayday. Mayday.
Mayday! Mayday!
King ninecallingfirefly.
Come in, please.
Mayday! Mayday! Come in, please!
Ah, easy now, easy now.
Think about it some.
Don't go off half-cocked.
There are reasons.
There are explanations.
The crew is someplace
and... and, for some reason,
and i'm alone for some reason.
Everything looks tilt,
but there's...
there's logic behind it.
There's logic for everything.
I just have to...
i just have to keep it cool,
that's all.
Think about it rationally.
The main thing...
the main thing
i got to keep in mind is
i'm responsible for this crew.
I'm in charge.
As far as it's within my power,
i got to keep them alive.
I got to get them out of this.
I command this aircraft,
and i'm in charge,
and i'm responsible.
Blake?
Blake, is that you?
Klein?
Sergeant klein?
You incredibly stupid jerk, you.
You dropped your canteen.
You stupid bronx cowboy, you.
You're in the desert now,
you idiot.
You're going to need water.
I still have
to nursemaid you guys, huh?
Some crew i got here.
Run around the...
it's not funny, boys.
It's strictly not... not funny.
Blake! Blake!
Blake...
it's me, embry.
It's me, embry, blake.
Blake.
Blake?
Blake, where'd you go?
What's the gag?
Oh, come on, fellas.
I'm responsible for you guys.
Don't you understand?
I'm responsible.
Mayday.
King ninecallingfirefly.
King nine
callingfirefly.
Mayday. Mayday.
Pancaked in desert
one hour and 30 minutes
from last checkpoint.
Bearing 29...
hallucinations...
the whole thing
could be an hallucination.
I could be lying
out there in the sand
with a fractured skull.
I might not even
be standing here.
I might be dying out there
in the desert.
All this is what i'm just...
making up in my mind.
Or maybe i'm... i'm sleeping,
and i'm having a dream.
Hey, maybe i'll wake up,
and i'll be back at the base.
Or maybe i tied one on,
and i'm in a booth
at a bar someplace...
with a pretty girl.
Oh, this one tears it.
This one really tears it.
Wait till the medics
get ahold of me.
They'll never let loose.
They'll have
to put me on tour.
If they ever let me
out of the bin, that is.
Now, just a second.
Just a second.
I saw him sitting there.
Yeah.
And that was no hallucination.
I saw blake sitting right here.
Nobody can tell me different.
I saw him sitting
right in this seat.
Blake!
Connors! Klein!
How about it, crew?!
You hear me, anybody?!
Hey!
All right, king ninecrew!
This is your captain!
How about it, you guys?
I'm responsible for you jerks!
You're giving me
some bum action here!
You're throwing curves,
gentlemen!
How about it, team?
How about it, crew?
Look, i'm supposed
to look after you guys!
Blake!
Connors!
Klein...
i'm sorry.
I didn't know.
Rest in peace, buddy.
Rest in peace, kid.
Hey...
what kind of aircraft are those?
Wait a minute here.
What kind of pla...?
What are they?
I've never seen any planes
like that before.
I've never seen any jets.
Jets?
Jet aircraft?
How do i know
about jet aircraft?
This is 1943.
There's no such thing
as jet aircraft,
but i know about it.
I know about jet aircraft-
f-106s, f-105s, b-58s.
I know all about it.
Hey!
Hey, where you guys going?!
Hey, what's going on here?!
Hey, what are you doing here?!
Blake!
Blake! Connors?!
You ever hear a jet aircraft-
f-105s, f-106s, b-58s?
Jets! Jets!
Crew!
Hey, crew!
Now, come on,
we got to get out of here.
We've got to get out.
Now, we're not going
to be able to walk out.
We can't walk out.
That's for sure.
That's for positive.
We're going to have to fly.
Fly.
Come on, boys! Come on!
We're going to have
to prop up the ship,
get the wheels down,
try to take her off-
get her in the air.
And, boys, i'll get her back.
You can trust me.
I'll get her back.
It doesn't make
any difference...
because you're an illusion.
You don't even exist.
I'm dead...
or i'm knocked out...
or i'm off in limbo someplace.
Oh...
oh, i see.
I'm unconscious.
Or i'm cracked up
in some army base.
Some teeny-weeny little ward.
Or i don't exist...
any more than you do.
Crew, i'm all right.
Come on, crew.
Come on back.
You can break the silence now.
I got an idea.
Hey, you can yell at me.
Yell at me!
Oh, hey, why don't you just...?
Oh, this is funny.
Why don't you just...
spring up out of the sand
like a bunch of jumping jacks,
and just stand there,
and just laugh, see?
Just... la...
klein!
Klein!
Fellas, i knew
you'd come back.
Oh, no.
Fellas?
No.
Now, look, fellas. Please...
klein.
Blake?
Kransky?
Phantoms.
Everything's a phantom.
There isn't a thing...
not a single thing that's real.
Oh, god.
Oh, god, what's happening here?
What's happening?
Won't you let me in on it?
Please let me in on it, god.
Please let me in on it.
Oh, god.
Let me in on it.
Oh, please.
Please...
james embry, age 41, single.
It happened this morning.
Went by a newsstand,
looked at a paper,
then went into shock.
When the ambulance got there,
he was almost catatonic.
Is this what set it
off? This front page?
That's why i thought
we ought to have
a psychiatrist in on it.
It's very odd.
I thought so, too,
so i checked with the
pentagon in washington
on his army background.
Captain, air force, b-25,
africa and italy,
37 missions,
discharged august 1943,
recurrent fevers.
Some suggestion of
psychological disturbance,
but he was discharged
before they could find out
much about it.
And this
was his plane.
His plane and his crew.
Took off for italy
on what was supposed
to be a routine flight.
Embry never went
on that last mission.
Reported in ill,
and someone else flew
the plane for him.
Never got back.
And, for 17 years,
he's been carrying that
around in his gut.
You're all right,
mr. Embry.
You're in a hospital.
We'll look
after you.
Crazy dream.
I went back.
I went back to the desert.
That's all right,
mr. Embry...
no, no, no.
Sorry, mr. Embry.
You went back
to the desert.
Then what?
I went back to my plane.
I was looking
for the fellas.
I looked everywhere
for them.
I saw blake,
but it was... it was
a mirage, an illusion.
He wasn't there.
None of them were there.
It was an illusion,
mr. Embry
but you're out of it now.
You're going
to be all right.
I should have been on the plane.
I should have gone
on that mission.
I chickened out!
You didn't
chicken out.
You had no way
of knowing
that plane wasn't
going to come back.
Now you
realize it more
as time goes by,
and you'll feel
better for it.
It's out in the open now.
You don't have to hide it
in a pit deep inside of you.
That's what's been hurting you
all these years.
Another crazy thing...
uh... uh... an illusion
or a dream or whatever.
I was out there in the desert
and...
above me...
in the sky...
jets.
Isn't that wild?
1943.
African desert.
And jet planes overhead.
Just as if i...
just as if i...
had gone back there...
today.
Did i?
Did i go back?
Did i go back to my plane?
In your mind...
that's how you went back.
Only in your mind.
Only in my mind.
Go back to sleep now,
mr. Embry.
You're going
to be all right.
I think the worst part
of it is over.
At least the guilt
is out in the open,
and he knows
what it is.
That illusion certainly
seems real to him.
In a couple of days,
a week,
it will lose all reality.
Doctor, these are
mr. Embry's clothes.
You left them in
the examination room.
Put them on
the desk here, nurse.
I'm going back in the room.
I'll take them in.
I'd like to talk to him
in a day or so.
Fine. I'll keep
a check on him.
What's that?
It's sand.
Enigma buried in the sand-
a question mark
with broken wings
that lies in silent grace
as a marker in a desert shrine.
Odd how the real
consorts with the shadows-
how the present
fuses with the past.
How does it happen?
The question is on file
in the silent desert.
And the answer?
The answer is waiting for us
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling, the creator
oftwilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Inside this curio shop
next week,
from amidst
this old-school rococo
and some fusty,
moth-eaten antiquary,
will emerge a bottle- this one.
And from it will step a genie
to give mr. Luther adler
four wishes.
But he'll discover,
as will all of you,
that there's an economics
to magic-
a high cost of wishing.
Next week,
a most intriguing tale-
the man in the bottle.
Thank you, and good night.
Seethe new andy griffith show
each week
over most of these stations.
Consult local listings.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org