Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Suzy!
Don't take the lady's water.
It's all right,
mr. Schuster.
I've got plenty.
Nobody's got plenty.
Oh, mr. Schuster, i thought
i heard
your voice.
For the last time, mrs. Bronson,
we're leaving.
Did you get gas?
I got 12 gallons.
I figure that
ought to get us
at least
to syracuse.
Where are you going?
We're trying
to get to toronto.
Mr. Schuster
has a cousin there.
I'm not sure it's wise
you're doing this.
The highways are packed
bumper to bumper the radio says.
And what with the gas shortage
and everything...
i know that,
but we've got
to try anyway.
It's been nice
living here.
You're good
neighbors.
Let's go, honey.
Bye.
Good luck.
Safe trip.
And now we are two.
They were the last?
Building's empty now...
except for you and me.
What happens now?
I don't know.
I heard on the radio
that they're only going
to turn the water on
an hour a day from now on.
They said
they'd announce what time.
Aren't you going to leave?
No.
No, i'm not going to leave.
You know, mrs. Bronson,
i keep getting this
crazy thought...
...this crazy thought
that i'm going to wake up
and none of this
will have happened.
I'll wake up
in a cool bed, and...
it'll be night outside
and there'll be a wind...
branches rustling...
shadows on the sidewalk...
a moon...
traffic noises...
automobiles...
garbage cans...
milk bottles...
and voices.
There was a scientist
on the radio this morning.
He said that it'll get
a lot hotter, more each day,
now that we're moving
so close to the sun.
And that's why we're...
that's why we're...
the word that mrs. Bronson
is unable to put
into the hot, still, sodden air
is "doomed"
because the people
you've just seen
have been handed
a death sentence.
One month ago,
the earth suddenly changed
its elliptical orbit,
and in doing so
began to follow a path
which gradually,
moment by moment, day by day,
took it closer to the sun.
And all of man's little devices
to stir up the air
are now no longer luxuries.
They happen to be pitiful
and panicky keys to survival.
The time is five minutes to 12,
midnight.
There is no more darkness.
The place is new york city,
and this is the eve of the end
because even at midnight,
it's high noon,
the hottest day in history,
and you're about to spend it
in the twilight zone.
Norma, is that
you, honey?
Yes, mrs. Bronson.
The store was open.
Wide open.
Oh, i think
that's the first
time in my life
i was ever sorry
i was born a woman.
This is all
i was strong
enough to carry.
There weren't any
clerks around...
thank you.
Just a handful
of people
taking what
they could grab.
Well, at least we
won't starve anyway.
And there are three cans
of fruit juice in there.
Fruit juice?
Oh, norma, could we
open a can now?
Oh, of course we
can open a can now.
Oh, where's
the can opener?
Oh, in the other drawer.
Oh, i'm sorry.
I'm acting
just like an animal, aren't i?
No.
No, no, just...
just like a frightened
woman, that's all.
You should have
seen me in the store
running up and down
the aisles,
and i mean running.
Knocking things over
and grabbing things
and throwing them away
and grabbing again.
And at that,
i think i was
the calmest person
in the store.
One woman just stood in the
middle of the room and cried.
She cried like a baby,
pleading for someone
to help her.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is station wnyg
coming on the air
to bring you essential news.
First, a bulletin
from the police department.
Keep your doors locked
and prepare to protect
yourselves, if necessary,
with any weapons you may have.
A majority of the police force
has been assigned
to the crowded highways
outside this deserted city.
And citizens
remaining in new york
may have to protect themselves
from the cranks and looters
known to be roaming the streets.
From the weather bureau:
The temperature
stood at 110 degrees
at 11:00 this morning.
Humidity 91%.
Forecast for tomorrow...
forecast for tomorrow...
hot.
More of the same, only hotter.
Stop it.
I don't care.
Who are they kidding
with this weather report stuff?
Ladies and gentlemen,
tomorrow,
you can fry eggs on sidewalks,
heat up soup in the ocean,
and get help from wondering
maniacs if you choose.
What do you mean "panic"?
Who's left to panic?
Ladies and gentlemen,
i'm told that
my departing from the script
might panic you and...
let me alone.
Do you hear me?
Let me alone.
Let go of me.
There, you...
you see, mrs. Bronson?
You're not the only one
who's frightened.
There we are.
Go ahead, drink it.
It's grapefruit juice.
No, i can't. I can't
live off you like this.
You need it for yourself.
Mrs. Bronson,
we're going to have to
start living off each other
from now on.
Here's looking at you.
Current's off again.
It stays on a shorter
time each day.
Norma, what if it shuts off
and doesn't come back on again?
This place would
be like an oven.
As hot as it is,
it could be
so much worse.
Oh, norma, it could
be so much worse.
Norma...
please paint
something cool today.
Paint something...
pastoral...
with a waterfall and...
trees bending in the wind.
Please paint something cool.
Don't paint the sun anymore!
Mrs. Bronson?
You all right?
Yes, i'm all right.
It's so quiet.
I haven't
heard a sound.
What time is it?
3:00 in the afternoon.
Did you get any sleep?
I laid down awhile.
What was that?
Sounds like
something fell.
No...
it was someone.
Didn't you lock
the roof door?
Yes.
No, i...
i don't know, i...
i don't remember.
I thought i did.
Hey, somebody in there?
Come on out.
Come on out, baby.
Come on out and be friendly.
I ain't got all day.
If you don't come out,
i'm going to come in.
Did you hear that?
That was a gun.
Get out of here.
Down the stairs
and out the front door.
Leave us alone.
Okay, baby.
I never argue with
a lady with a gun.
Oh, i'm so glad he's gone.
He hasn't come out
the front door yet.
No!
Crazy dames!
It's too hot to play games.
Much too hot.
You do this?
You're good.
You paint real good.
My wife
used to paint.
Please leave
us alone.
We didn't do
you any harm.
Please.
She was so fragile,
just... just a little thing.
She couldn't take this heat.
I tried to keep her cool...
but she couldn't take the heat!
Baby didn't live
more than an hour.
Then she followed him.
I'm not a housebreaker.
I'm a decent man.
I swear to you,
i'm a decent man.
I've been
walking around
all... all day
trying to find some water.
I wouldn't hurt you.
I wouldn't do you any harm.
Honest.
Please believe me.
Please...
please forgive me,
would you?
I'm just
off my rocker.
Please forgive me.
Why doesn't it end?
Why don't we just...
just burn up?
I painted it for
you last night.
It's for you.
Oh, it's beautiful, norma.
I've seen waterfalls
just like that before.
There's one near ithaca,
new york.
Yes,
it's the highest waterfall...
the highest waterfall
in this part of the country.
And i love the sound of it.
That wonderful blue water
tumbling over the rocks.
That wonderful,
cool, clear water.
You hear it, norma?
Hear it?
You do hear it,
norma, don't you?
That wonderful
sound?
You know, we could...
we could swim
in that waterfall.
Let's do that.
Let's swim in it,
shall we?
I used to do that
when i was a little girl.
Just...
just sit there and...
and let the water
come down over me.
Mrs. Bronson?
She's coming
out of it now.
Norma?
Yes?
You were
running
a high fever,
but it's broken now.
Fever?
You gave us a
start, child.
You were so ill,
but you're going
to be all right now.
Isn't she, doctor?
Isn't she going to be all right?
Of course.
I wish i had something
left to give her
but the medicine's
pretty much
all gone now.
I won't be able
to come back.
I'm going to move my
family south tomorrow.
My friend has
a private plane.
Well, they say on the
radio, miami is warmer.
So they say.
But we're only
prolonging it.
There was a scientist
on the radio this morning.
He was trying
to explain what happened.
How the earth
had changed its orbit
and was starting
to move away from the sun,
and that within one, two,
or maybe three weeks
at the most,
there wouldn't be
any more sun-
we'd all freeze.
Oh, mrs. Bronson.
I had such a terrible dream.
It was so hot.
It was daylight
all the time.
There was...
a midnight sun.
There wasn't any night
at all.
No night at all.
Isn't it wonderful
to have darkness
and coolness?
Yes, my dear.
It's wonderful.
The poles of fear,
the extremes of how the earth
might conceivably be doomed.
Minor exercise in the care
and feeding of a nightmare,
respectfully submitted
by all the thermometer-watchers
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week
we move back into time,
back to 1863.
A distinguished actor,
mr. Gary merrill,
plays the role
of a confederate scout
who goes off on a patrol
and winds up smack-dab
in the center
of the twilight zone.
Our story is an adaptation
of a strange tale
by manly wade wellman
called "the still valley."
This one is for civil war buffs
and the students of the occult.
I hope you're around
to take a look at it.
Hello. I'm celeste holm.
Give through
the refugee aid programs
of the catholic, protestant
and jewish faiths.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org