Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is
another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Been to the
cave, jason?
Did you see
goldsmith?
Did he talk
to the old man?
Goldsmith's
still up there.
He said
to tell you
he's getting a message
from the old man.
He'll bring it down with
him in a few minutes.
Is he asking
about this food?
It's all pre-bomb,
all of it.
It's safe as anything.
Why do we have
to keep waiting
for the old man?
Why don't we just take
our chances with it?
We already
took chances.
The old man told us
not to plant on
the north acreage;
that it was
poisonous.
This is what came up.
Did these grow, evie,
or did somebody leave
them to us in a will?
They were the best.
The best?!
Hate to see the worst!
I don't think we ought
to eat those, evie.
I say we just better
bury them with honors.
That's what goldsmith
went to the cave for-
to ask the old man
what land we should
try this time.
The old man, indeed.
Who knows where he gets
his omniscient knowledge,
but evie's right.
He knows
about land.
Remember those tomatoes
that came up?
You remember he sent
a message to goldsmith,
telling usnotto plant them?
Oh... they were monstrous.
Like... rotten watermelons.
They tasted...
but, jason,
all of this stuff's pre-bomb.
I just know it.
Let's wait for goldsmith.
See what the old man has to say.
What about
the food?
Wait till goldsmith
gets back from the cave.
Wait till he has a chance
to ask the old man.
I'm surprised
at you, all of you.
Man doesn't live by bread
or canned food alone,
or freak carrots,
or mutated tomatoes.
But do me a favor,
will you?
Don't ask me what
hedoeslive by.
In this tenth illustrious
year after the bomb,
i wouldn't be able
to tell you.
Announcement!
I have an
announcement.
We've just had
communication
from the old man
in the cave.
There's an 80% possibility
of rain tomorrow.
The wind's from the northeast.
This means that
there will likely be
a very high radioactive count
in the precipitation.
Now place all rain
barrels upside down,
and keep all
water troughs
covered.
As to the canned goods there,
the old man says that
they're contaminated
and should be
destroyed.
What you're looking at
is a legacy
that man left to himself.
A decade previous,
he pushed his buttons
and a nightmarish moment later
woke up to find
that he had set the clock back
a thousand years.
His engines, his medicines,
his science
were buried in a mass tomb
covered over by the biggest
gravedigger of them all-
a bomb.
And this is the earth,
ten years later,
a fragment of
what was once a whole,
a remnant of
what was once a race.
The year is 1974,
and this is the twilight zone.
Do you have anyone in charge?
I'm in charge.
Do you have a name?
Goldsmith.
Hmm.
This place-
does it have a name?
And if it does... major?
If it does, father,
we'd like to hear it.
Uh... who are you?
Major french is my name.
Central states commander.
We're being sent around
to organize.
Organize?
Yes, that's what i said.
Now, how many people
do you have here?
We haven't counted lately.
What about food?
There's sufficient.
Hmm.
You grow your own?
Some.
We have a supply of prewar
canned goods left over.
We'll need some quarters.
Harber, have a look around.
Douglas, you stay with the jeep.
Furman...
stay with me.
Major, uh,
what do you want?
Painless things.
We'd like quarters
for the four of us,
rations for as
long as we're here
and no trouble.
That last part-
no trouble.
I don't think you
understand, major.
We don't recognize
your authority here.
We've had transients
pass through on occasion,
but they didn't stay.
Like you, they represented
themselves as authorities,
but we discovered they carried
their headquarters with them.
They represented
no one but themselves.
Well, this is a new breed,
mr. Goldsmith.
This whole area will
be organized now.
It will be set up
into military sectors,
each controlled by
a local constabulary-
yours truly.
Well, you and
your constabulary
can remain overnight
and we'll be glad
to share our
food with you,
bed you down.
Tomorrow morning, you'd better
do your organizing
somewhere else.
Mr. Goldsmith,
the following is unofficial.
Now, we'd like you
to make your transition here
as easy as possible.
Now, under certain
circumstances,
we might even
allow you to remain
in nominal control.
That's assuming that you
don't give us any trouble.
Now, that's unofficial.
The following is official.
Now, let me fill you in on the
situation here, mr. Goldsmith.
Between buffalo, new york,
and atlanta, georgia,
there are probably
around 500 people alive.
You know why.
Because there's
no authority,
there's
no discipline.
We're here to
give you both.
And if you give us any trouble-
any trouble
atall-
i'm going to hang you
from that balcony
right over there.
Well, now, what about
it, mr. Goldsmith?
You want
to cooperate
or do you want
your neck broken?
We already have
an authority.
We've had him
for better than ten years.
Whatisall this?
Poison.
It's contaminated
food.
Who says so?
The old man
in the cave.
A, uh, old man
in a cave...
have any of you looked
at yourselves
in the mirror lately?
You all look like skeletons,
you know that?
Just like skeletons.
Where is this old man
who keeps you on a diet?
When does he come out?
He never
comes out.
He stays
in the cave.
Well, i'm not surprised,
mr. Goldsmith.
I'm not surprised at all.
Off lake erie, we've got a pack
of weirdies up there
that bay at the moon
once a week.
And then around
what used to be chicago,
man, we got a real
swinging cult going there.
They've built themselves
a statue
made out of fissionable lead.
This is their deity.
What do we have here?
We have an invisible
old man in a cave.
Now, come on, mr. Goldsmith.
Now, when you take it out
and run it around the block
a couple of times,
don't you think
it sounds kind of nutty?
We've survived, major french.
The rest of the world has died
of radioactivity,
strontium 90, plague.
We survived.
Because of the old man, huh?
That's right,
because of the old man.
He cues you in, huh?
He tells you
what's poisonous,
what's radioactive,
that whole bit?
As long as he's alive,
we'll be alive.
Do you know something?
Now, i don't think any of you
are going to die
of radioactivity.
I think if you're going to kick
off, you're going to kick off
either from malnutrition
or from being conned to death.
If that's true, major, at least
it'll be a painless death.
Mr. Goldsmith,
check this.
The booking odds are as follows.
500 to one that your old man
is a soft-in-the-head hermit
who doesn't even know
what year it is.
That's not for us to say.
That's for you toask!
All of you!
Friends, romans, farm animals,
we are now going up to the cave
and check your favorite recluse.
We're going to bring him
out in the sunshine
and get a good look at him.
And then we're going to decide
if he's worthwhile
keeping alive.
Come on, you're
coming with us.
All right, goldsmith,
do you want to
tell us about this?
How do you open it?
I don't know.
To my knowledge, it's
never been opened.
But the old man
lives inside, right?
How does helive?
How does he stay alive?
I don't know.
How do you know
he'sinthere?
How do you communicate with him?
He sends out
notes... messages.
He sends out notes and messages.
Well, gentlemen,
we really have a prize here.
We get the blue ribbon for this.
An idiot leading
the idiots.
Douglas, throw me
that hand grenade.
You people better
make some tracks.
Might make
your eyes smart.
Old man, this is
just the beginning!
You hear?!
Just the beginning.
Douglas...
car.
Don't take
this food out.
You hear, it's
contaminated.
Sure, mr. Goldsmith.
Stop it! Listen
to me, all of you.
Listen to me!
There's every possibility
that all of those cans
contain enough strontium 90
to kill every man, woman
and child in this village.
Oh, come on, mr. Goldsmith,
why don't you tell us how
disappointed you are, huh?
Oh, mr. Goldsmith,
you are kooky, you know that?
You've got enough food
in that pile over there
to feed us all
for a good long time.
There's enough poison
in those cans
to kill us all
in ten days.
Most of it was canned
after the bomb.
We've no idea
where it came from;
who processed it.
All right, let's lay it on
the line there, mr. Goldsmith.
Here, now.
Come on,
who'd like
a nice square meal
for a change, huh?
Anybody else?
Dig in.
Okay, anybody else
want to continue
to play
kindergarten games
with mr. Goldsmith here,
go home
and chew on an old bone.
No, don't be fools!
Don't commit suicide!
Don't let these pack rats
invade our homes,
turn order upside down!
Stop it, stop it!
Don't eat the food.
Hey, look
at this!
We just repealed prohibition!
Just like christmas, huh?
Like thanksgiving.
Yeah, thanksgiving, too.
What's your name?
Jason.
Jason?
Jason and the golden fleece.
Yeah, i'm a literate man,
you know that?
I went to college, jason.
Yeah, i went to college.
What did
you learn?
Well, if it isn't the
illustrious mr. Goldsmith,
keeper of the legend,
protector of the fables,
and the lord, high
chamberlain of the cave.
You look hungry,
mr. Goldsmith.
And thirsty.
You've got 100 cases
of that stuff over there.
Now, you want to break
every bottle, man,
you've got a big job.
Do you have any remote idea what
you've brought to this village?
Yeah.
Yeah, i brought
into this village
the first square meal
that any of these people
have had in ten years.
And the first six protracted
hours of enjoyment
that any of them
have had since...
you started
leading them
around by
the nose.
Now, why don't you
unbend, old man?
Can you answer me that?
Why don't you unbend?
You came as intruders,
but now you're murderers.
Only god knows
how many people
will die because
of tonight.
The old man
in the cave warned us
about this food dozens of times.
He warned us.
Old man
in the cave!
The old man in a cave!
Now hear this!
There is no old man in the cave!
He's a lie!
He's a concoction.
Nobody's seen him,
nobody's heard him,
nobody knows who he is,
or where he's from.
You made him up.
You cut him
out of whole cloth!
Now, i don't know what
your graft is, goldsmith...
i don't know
how you get paid off,
but i do know
that it's time
you let these people know
what's in that cave.
Open the cave,
goldsmith.
You'll have to
kill me first.
Mister, i have killed
a hundred times you.
That's how
i've stayed alive.
Jason, gather up
your people
and we're going up
to the cave.
He'll open it for us.
Harber, follow me.
Everybody!
Everybody,
he's going up to the cave.
Get him out of there!
Please, please,
all of you, listen.
Listen to me.
There's no reason,
no reason under the sun
why this cave
must be opened;
why you must see
the old man.
All you have to know is
that he's kept us alive.
He's let us survive.
Goldsmith, we've survived
for ten years!
But we haven't lived.
Jason, he didn't drop the bomb.
He didn't kill off this earth.
We did that to ourselves.
All he's done is to let us
survive our mistake.
All he's done is to let us plant
a seed again and let it grow.
All the compassion
that's left on this earth
is in that cave.
Well, then,
make him open the cave!
Let's see the
old man now!
Open up
that door!
All right.
My god!
My dear god!
It's a machine.
It's a computer.
There's your old man,
there's your tyrant.
Kill it.
Well, you've got to kill it.
You've been hungry
long enough.
Now, kill it!
All right,
all right!
All right!
All right, you're free now.
You understand?
You're free!
When we talked about the ways
that men could die,
we forgot the chief method
of execution.
We forgot faithlessness,
major french.
Maybe you're not to blame.
Maybe if it weren't you,
it would have been someone else.
Maybe this has to be
the destiny of man.
I wonder if that's true.
I wonder.
I guess i'll never know.
Mr. Goldsmith, survivor,
an eyewitness to
man's imperfection,
an observer of
the very human trait of greed
and a chronicler
of the last chapter-
the one reading "suicide."
Not a prediction
of what is to be,
just a projection
of what could be.
This has been
the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next onthe twilight zone,
the distinguished
sir cedric hardwicke
lends us
his considerable talent,
along with the very accomplished
miss constance ford.
They appear in what can
most aptly be described
as one of the shockers
in our schedule.
The play is called
"uncle simon,"
and this we submit is a relative
you've never met before.
It's a story
with a final curtain
i doubt anyone can predict.
Next ontwilight zone,
"uncle simon."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org