Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Well, rollie, i kept it
from you long enough.
The fact is we're lost.
And you know something else?
Take a look at this.
Almost empty.
Well, you just earned yourself
a steak.
How do?
Hi, can you fill it up?
I don't see why not.
It's right there
behind the license plate.
Oh, sure.
Probably bone dry.
Doubt i could've gone
another mile.
How'd you let a thing
like that happen?
I listened
to a friend of mine.
He told me i could cut
a couple of hours
off my trip to albuquerque
by taking the back route.
Nice scenery, he said,
no traffic.
If i'd have gone
the way i know,
i'd be home by now.
You mean you're lost.
Yeah, that's what i mean.
Say, you couldn't
show me the way
to a big highway around here,
a nice, big highway
with a lot of signs?
Oh, ah, you just go
back to the fork,
take the other road to bredon.
That's about 80 miles.
And when you get there,
ask somebody for a map.
Nice little town
you got here.
What do you call
this place?
Peaceful valley.
It's peaceful,
all right.
Is there a restaurant
around here?
Up there, up
the street,
but it's closed.
You'll be better
off in bredon.
Well, i know,
but i'm hungry right now.
So is my dog.
Well, i'm sorry.
We don't get many
visitors here.
Well, i can see why.
That'll be $4.42.
Here's a tenner.
I hope i got change.
Here you go.
Rollie, shut up.
Rollie, rollie,
come back here!
Not yet. Wait a minute.
Nine...
rollie, get away
from that cat!
9.50, 9.75... ten.
Ten, right.
Rollie?
Hey, kid, what'd you do
to my dog?
Nothing.
What do you mean, nothing?
I was standing right here.
I saw you.
You leave me alone!
Listen, i'm not going
to leave you alone
till you tell me
what you did to my dog!
You've seen them.
Little towns, tucked away
far from the main roads.
You've seen them, but have
you thought about them?
What do the people
in these places do?
Why do they stay?
Philip redfield
never thought about them.
If his dog hadn't gone
after that cat,
he'd have driven
through peaceful valley
and put it
out of his mind forever.
But he can't do that now,
because, whether
he knows it or not,
his friend's shortcut
has led him
right into the capital
of the twilight zone.
You scared
my little girl.
Well, that makes us even.
Your little
girl scared me.
What do you mean
by that?
Just what i said.
Now, look, i don't
know what she did,
but she made my
dog disappear.
What?!
Look, she pointed some kind
of a machine at my dog,
and he disappeared.
Are you feeling all right?
No, i never feel all right
when i see that kind of thing.
It makes
my blood pressure rise.
Easy, now, mister.
Let's look
around the yard.
He's bound to be here
somewhere.
What's his name?
Rollie. Rollie's
his name.
Here, rollie!
Look, he was
standing right...
you look around there.
I'll go out back.
Now, don't worry.
We'll find him.
He couldn't
have disappeared.
Well, that's what i'm
trying to tell you.
He did.
Here, rollie!
Rollie?
Rollie.
Come on, fella, come on.
Where you been, huh?
You've been a bad boy,
haven't you, huh?
Rollie, rollie, rollie.
Well, where was he?
In the back.
I guess he must have found
another cat.
Uh, yeah. Yeah, sure.
Well, thanks a lot.
That's all right.
The way sissy disappears
sometimes...
well, i know
how you must've felt.
Uh, sissy's your
little girl?
Yeah.
Look, what was
that thing she
had in her hand?
What thing?
Well, it was a
brown box and
a kind of a wire
with a little deal
over here, uh...
now, wait a minute.
Don't tell me i
imagined that.
Oh, no, no. It, um...
oh, it must have been
her radio.
All right.
Well, i'm sorry
i bothered you.
Come on, boy.
Come on, rollie,
get in here, get in here.
Did you see all that?
All what?
Never mind.
Hey, bredon's the other way!
I want to talk to dorn.
He's not here.
Well, you better find him.
It's important.
We've got an outsider...
and he saw something.
Now, you just take it easy,
rollie.
I'll find you a steak somewhere.
I'm sorry, but
we don't have
any openings.
Oh?
Now, why is that?
Well...
all the rooms
are taken.
Oh.
Well, i guess
everyone's out, then.
Well, the keys...
yes. Everybody's out.
Well, i wasn't looking
for a room, anyway.
I was just looking
for a restaurant.
I'm sorry, but
it's closed.
What, you mean
you only have
one restaurant
in peaceful valley?
Yes, sir.
Well, where do you eat?
At home.
What about the guests?
Well, they do eat,
don't they?
L-i have to go now.
Look, just a minute, miss.
My name is philip redfield.
I'm a reporter.
Now, if i begin to sound
a little nosy,
i suppose it goes
with the job.
You don't mind,
do you?
No.
Well, maybe you can tell me
something.
Ever since i landed here
in peaceful valley,
people have been trying
to get rid of me.
Now, why is that?
Well, we just don't get
very many outsiders here.
So i heard.
Yet you manage
to fill up a hotel.
I'm sorry,
but i really have to go now,
and i think you should, too.
Well, you better get
your subscription
to the paper renewed.
A lot of things
have happened since '53.
Thanks for everything.
Rollie.
Are you all
right, sir?
My dog is dead.
I don't know
how this could've happened, i...
there wasn't a car around
anywhere.
Perhaps it was a rock.
Well, wouldn't it be around
somewhere?
Well, you could've
knocked it
into the woods.
Come along,
mr. Redfield.
We've got to get you
to a doctor.
We'll take care
of your car.
What about my dog?
Well, we'll
take care of
your dog, too.
You have nothing
to worry about.
Wait a minute!
Wait a minute, i don't want
to go back to your town!
Well, you have
to be examined.
I'm all right.
You don't know that.
There could be
internal injuries.
If anything
happened to you,
it would be
on our conscience forever.
Come along.
We insist.
No, w-wait...
wait, now.
There you are,
good as new.
We certainly haven't been
treating you very well,
have we, old fella, hmm?
Come on. Here. Come on.
Is this a doctor's office?
In a way.
Thank you, gentlemen.
You can leave now.
Mr. Redfield.
Please sit down.
How do you feel?
Terrible.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Perhaps it would help
to learn your dog is well.
My dog is dead.
Oh, no... no, no,
merely stunned.
He's really quite happy now.
How do you know?
Mr. Swanson-
one of the men
who helped you- called in.
He thought you'd be pleased.
Well, i am...
if it's the truth.
My, you do have
a suspicious nature, don't you?
Oh, uh...
forgive me.
Ny name is dorn.
I'm the mayor
of peaceful valley.
The gentlemen
to my left:
Mr. Connelly, mr. Evans,
my associates.
Which one is the doctor?
Doc...?
Oh, oh, oh, of course.
But you don't really need
a doctor, do you, mr. Redfield?
Because if you did,
we'd get one here
immediately.
Please... sit down.
We'll try not to
detain you long.
Then you couldn't go anywhere
in a wrecked car, now, can you?
We'd just like to ask you
a few questions,
if we may- uh, just a few.
Perhaps you'd like to begin.
Mr. Redfield, it's been reported
you saw something unusual
in the yard
next to the gasoline station.
Would you please tell us
about it?
My dog chased a cat.
The details, please.
Well, that's it.
Are you quite sure
you saw nothing more?
Yes.
Mr. Connelly, your question.
I was simply wondering,
mr. Redfield,
why you told
the girl at the hotel
that people were trying
to get rid of you.
Now, wait a minute, look.
What is this,
some kind of
a quiz hour?!
My car is out there wrecked
somewhere.
I'm already a day late for work.
Your car's being repaired.
By who, that
station attendant?
Why, he couldn't even find
the gas tank.
It is being
repaired.
Uh, just a few
more questions, please.
I understand you mentioned
you're a newspaper reporter
by occupation.
So?
Oh, noble calling...
but limited.
I suppose you have that novel
in the planning stage.
Who told you about that?
No one, but isn't it a fact
that most reporters aspire
to be novelists?
I wouldn't know.
Are you married?
No.
Engaged?
No. Now, look...
one last question,
please.
Did you indeed come
to peaceful valley by mistake?
I mean, no one knows
you're here?
No, no one knows i'm here.
But i'll tell
you this:
A lot of people
are going to
know i was here.
Oh, dear.
Now, what's the story
on this place?
My dog didn't disappear
chasing a cat,
and my car didn't crash
into any rock.
Now, what
did happen?
Come back in an hour,
mr. Redfield.
Perhaps then you'll get
the answers to your questions.
All right, i will.
Where's the phone?
There's one at the hotel.
You think it's wise
letting him go like that?
He'll be watched.
Well, gentlemen...
it's happened.
It had to, eventually.
No! It didn't have to.
And it wouldn't have
if we kept our wits about us,
but we didn't.
We were so complacent,
so infernally sure of ourselves
and complacent.
Dorn.
Mr. Evans,
would you explain
the point of keeping
the hotel open
and the restaurant closed?
Well, now, i don't think...
doesn't it seem
more likely
that there would be
more inquiries
for food than for rooms?
There hasn't been either
in over 16 years.
You see? Complacency.
And i'm as much to blame
as anyone.
If only the little johnson girl
hadn't been so careless.
If only fredericks
hadn't acted suspiciously
at the gasoline station.
If only i hadn't panicked
and raised the wall!
You had to.
There wasn't any choice by then.
So now...
an innocent young man
who hasn't done anyone any harm
must suffer for our mistakes.
How do you get long distance
on this thing?
You just pick it
up, but you...
hello, operator?
Operator, get me long distance.
But what?
Nothing.
Operator.
Operator, i want to put through
a call to albuquerque.
The number's chapel 77205,
and i want it to be
station to station, please.
Just a moment.
That's quite a mirror you got.
It makes you feel
really welcome.
Have you talked to dorn?
Yeah, i talked to him.
He's a great guy.
My dog vanishes,
my car crashes into thin air,
and he wants to know
if i'm writing a novel.
Hello?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
The circuits are busy.
All right, miss. Will you
keep trying and call me back?
My name is redfield.
Well, i see they
haven't gotten back.
Pardon me?
Your guests.
Oh, well, no.
That's because
there aren't any guests.
Isn't that right?
You really should've left,
mr. Redfield.
Well, i tried to,
but my car smashed into a rock
that wasn't there.
How do you suppose
that happened?
L-i don't know.
What is your name,
or is that a secret, too?
Ellen marshall.
Well, ellen, i want you
to contact me
as soon as my call
comes through.
Now, this is important.
Will you do that?
Yes, of course.
Where will you be?
I'm going to check
on my car now,
and i'll be
at the mayor's office
in a couple of minutes-
probably starving
to death.
Rollie!
Rollie, how are you, boy?
Huh? How are you?!
I had you counted out,
did you know that, huh?
How are you, rollie?
I fed him.
Well, thanks, but
what about my car?
It's pretty banged up.
Well, i know, but
you were supposed
to be trying
to fix it.
Didn't anybody tell me.
Well, i'm
telling you!
I can't do anything
unless it's official.
Well, look, all right,
it is official-
about $200's
worth of official
if you get it fixed
as soon as you can.
Sorry.
Well, you're going
to be sorrier.
Come in, mr. Redfield.
I thought
you told me
my car was going
to be repaired.
Please sit down.
I don't want
to sit down!
I want to know
why nothing's been
done to my car,
why it's just
sitting out there.
Primarily because
you won't be needing it anymore.
Oh, no? Well, why?
Because you are never going
to leave peaceful valley.
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
You are never going
to leave peaceful valley.
You see, the situation is rather
complicated, mr. Redfield.
Although we hold no brief
against you personally...
wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Sure.
I think i got this
thing figured out.
Oh?
Well, sure-
peaceful valley is a town
full of lunatics,
and you guys head the list!
Now, what do you mean,
i'm not ever going
to be able to leave here?
Just that.
Well, who's going
to stop me?
We are.
There's nothing you
can do, mr. Redfield.
Well, how's this?
Now... let us continue.
What did you...?
How did i get in this chair?
You were disassembled
over there...
and reassembled there...
with this.
What is that?
I'm afraid you wouldn't
understand, mr. Redfield...
even if you were a physicist,
which you are not.
Let us say it
is a device
by which we move
things about.
All things are collections
of atoms with spaces in between.
Even you, mr. Redfield.
And atoms are in a
given mathematical
arrangement.
This device breaks them up,
stores them
and puts them together again
in the same order.
That's ridiculous.
Perhaps, but...
it saves a lot of time
when you want
to move furniture around.
Dorn.
Yes, mr. Evans.
Let's get this over with.
I'm sorry.
You sensed a story in this town,
mr. Redfield,
and you were right.
You turned off onto the road
to peaceful valley.
You saw certain things
that defied logic.
People began to behave oddly,
and you became
curious, so...
so we had to stop you.
And now we must do even worse,
because, mr. Redfield,
you stumbled upon the best-kept
secret in the world.
What secret?
Our gift, mr. Redfield,
bestowed upon the people
of this village 104 years ago.
A man came to peaceful valley,
from what land or...
what planet, nobody knows.
He was a brilliant scientist
many hundreds of years
before his time, but...
he was also wise,
as you shall see.
From his brain came equations
the likes of which no one
had even seen or dreamt of...
not on this planet, at any rate.
Of course, i
cannot tell you
what they are.
Mr. Redfield, you are aware,
i trust, that the basis
of this complicated thing
we call life is energy.
It's a frightening
and mysterious force.
The scientist's equations
unlocked this force,
and from it came the greatest
power for good... or evil
the universe
has ever known.
He decided to entrust
his secrets-
his equations and the machines
that he had built-
to three men he had selected,
and he instructed them to give
the benefit of this power
to the people of peaceful valley
for their comfort.
But under no circumstances
were they to release the secret
to the outside world.
It was to remain
in peaceful valley...
until humanity learned
the ways of peace.
That is your story,
mr. Redfield.
You see why we cannot allow you
to leave us.
No, i can't say that i do.
Perhaps if we showed you.
Mr. Redfield.
This is the original
desimulator,
somewhat larger
than the one
we moved you
around with upstairs.
More or less
the same principle here,
but with a big difference.
It works in what we call
the time dimension.
It has many, many uses.
For example...
mr. Evans.
Mr. Connelly,
would you hand me
the letter opener?
Don't be frightened,
mr. Redfield.
Come with me,
On this console,
among other things,
we have a duplicating machine,
but not like others.
Ah!
Here's something.
On this card,
we have a statement
giving the
atomic structure
of a ham sandwich
on white bread
with mustard.
Of course, we have
larger machines
for the bulkier items,
but this will
give you an idea.
I believe you said
you were hungry, mr. Redfield.
Well, not anymore.
Look, what was
that thing i ran
into out there?
Oh, you mean in the car.
I'm, uh, sorry about that,
but we had to stop you.
It was an energy field:
A wall of loosely-packed atoms,
so to speak.
Purely an emergency device.
This lever operates it.
Come with me, mr. Redfield.
And these are the
sacred papers,
as we call them...
the equations from
which everything
you see came about.
Well, i think
i could use a drink.
Do you have any
idea what you
have down there?
Of course.
And you mean
you don't intend
to share it
with the rest
of the world?
Oh, good
heavens, no.
Why?
Well, i've already explained,
mr. Redfield.
The world isn't ready.
But peaceful valley is?
Well, obviously.
We have no war here, no crime,
no violence, no greed.
Unlike your world,
we live in peace.
We use the power for good,
not for evil.
Well, how can you be sure
the rest of us wouldn't?
Come, now, mr. Redfield,
the history of civilization
has been written in blood.
But that's because
people wanted things!
With that power...
with this power,
they would destroy
the universe.
They're children.
But this one machine-
it could stop sickness
and sufferings.
It could cure disease.
Well, couldn't it?
Yes.
And you just let people...
well, don't you have
any conscience about it?
Yes.
That is why we will not release
the secret.
The same power that could
be used to heal sickness
can also be used
to destroy the innocent.
You see, one
secret would lead
to understanding
the rest,
and that could
be the end
of the world.
I don't believe that.
Think, mr. Redfield!
Think!
What did you do with professor
einstein's primitive equation,
e = m c squared?
It could have been used to
bring waters to the deserts...
to feed starving millions.
Was it?
It was used to destroy countless
thousands of human beings.
So you're just going to sit
on your secrets,
use them to make ham sandwiches
and roadblocks?!
Ham sandwiches
and roadblocks
are a bit better
than total destruction,
wouldn't you say,
mr. Redfield?
Let's get on
with this.
You're a bunch
of hypocrites!
You talk about us,
but what do you do
when you want someone
out of the way?
What do you do?!
The same as we do!
You eliminate him!
Be quiet!
No.
He has a point,
mr. Evans.
It's just what
i've been pondering.
If we kill this man...
in what way do we differ
from the outsiders?
But we do it out
of necessity,
not out of choice!
Thank you, adolf hitler.
It is for the good
of the world.
We have nothing against you.
It's the law.
We cannot go against the law!
And let him who discovers
the secret be eliminated.
You can be eliminated
in one of two ways:
Through death
or through assimilation.
The choice is yours.
Will you die,
or will you join us?
You mean live here
the rest of my life?
Exactly.
Become one of us.
It really won't be so bad.
We'll provide you
with a fine house
built to your
specifications,
plenty of food,
time to write
that novel.
All your wants seen to.
Nothing or everything, eh?
Substantially, yes.
What will it be?
Everything.
Welcome to peaceful valley.
And this is
your study.
I'm sorry
about the typewriter,
but we couldn't find a card
for anything newer.
Don't worry, though.
It'll work fine.
And dorn promised
that you'd have a new one.
Look...
why are you going
to all this trouble?
Oh, because dorn
asked me to.
And-and because
i wanted to.
Yeah, but why?
Because l-i don't
want you to think
that l-i'm unfriendly.
I'm not.
In fact, i think
you and i could be
very good friends,
mr. Redfield.
Do you play chess?
Is something wrong?
No, no.
Well, don't you like
the house?
L-i tried to make
everything nice for you.
Ellen, i like it.
It's beautiful.
Are all the other houses
in town this beautiful?
On the inside.
Well, i'm afraid
you've wasted
your time on me.
Why?
Because i'm not
staying here.
Of course you are.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
Well, if you keep thinking
like this,
you'll have no choice.
Dorn won't trust you.
Well, he trusts me
now, doesn't he?
Well, doesn't he?
I'm leaving
mr. Redfield's house.
If-if you get hungry...
or if you want anything,
just call me.
I showed you
where the button is.
Ellen, wait.
You're not like
the others here.
Yes, i am.
No.
You're-you're different.
You're a human being.
Rollie, get down.
Get down. Get down.
Yes.
Mr. Redfield?
Yes?
On your call to albuquerque...
the circuits are still busy.
Come in.
Hello.
I, um...
i brought you a new
typewriter ribbon
and-and some,
uh, erasers.
Have you started
your novel yet?
No.
Why not?
I don't know.
Maybe i don't concentrate
so well in a prison.
I don't understand.
Well, you ought to;
you got the same problem.
I'm locked
in the house.
You're locked
in the town.
What's the
difference?
I can leave
any time i want to.
Then why don't you?
Well, why should i?
Why should you?
We have everything
we need.
Except freedom.
Face it- if
you were to go
even a couple of steps
outside of this town,
why, they'd nail you.
Have you ever tried?
No, but why should
i want to try?
What could
the outside world
have to offer
that we don't have?
That's not the
point, ellen.
It's what you
have to offer
the outside world.
I mean, right now,
at this very moment,
thousands and thousands
of people are starving.
Don't you know that?
Well, you could
feed them- you!
They're suffering,
and you could
make them well.
They're breaking
their backs
ten, 15 hours a day.
Don't you know that?
What do you care?
No, let them starve,
let them suffer,
let them break
their backs.
Let the children die
because their
mother can't give
them any milk!
What difference does
it make to you?!
You're happy!
Is this really happening?
All over the world.
Every minute
of the day or night,
somebody is dying... alone.
Somebody that you could help.
Don't say that.
Why not?
What difference does it make?
But...
but what would you do?
A terrible thing.
I'd take your secrets
and give it to the world.
You mean you'd steal
them and run away?
Very fast.
But you promised
dorn that...
look, ellen,
i promised myself first.
I'd-i'd try and be some kind
of a decent human being,
maybe even try
and help somebody out.
What's the use?
You don't even know
what i mean.
You never wanted anything
you couldn't whip up
in ten seconds
in one of your
little machines.
Once i did.
When i saw you leaving
peaceful valley.
And i've thought
about you
since then, philip.
Even asleep, i've
thought about you.
And it hurts.
I don't know why,
but it hurts.
Do you know why?
I think so.
Then what is it?
We have machines
for so many things,
but i can't make
this feeling stop.
And you won't, ellen.
Not on your machines.
Don't you people
ever fall in love?
I never have until now.
But-but now i want us
to be together, philip.
Don't you want that?
I could want that
very much in a real world.
But not here.
Look, i'm sorry, ellen.
As long as i'm here
in peaceful valley,
i just want
out.
I want us to be together.
All right, you wait here.
Put them back,
mr. Redfield.
No.
Do as i say.
Ellen, i want to tell you
what happened back there.
It may change your mind
about coming with me.
No.
Whatever it is,
i don't want to hear.
You have the papers.
Well, i know, but...
have you seen them?
No.
You see what would happen,
mr. Redfield,
if we gave our secret
to the outside world?
The very first
thing you'd do
is make a weapon.
You'd
kill with it.
You tricked me.
Yes.
And you...
everything a lie.
Not everything, philip.
She cooperated
because she thought
you would prove
your good intentions...
as i did.
My colleagues
were right.
You're just like
the others.
If the end is just,
so are the means,
whatever they may be.
Pity.
You have just lost paradise,
mr. Redfield,
and you don't even know why.
I did the right thing.
I'd do it again.
Of course.
Now you're going to do
the same thing to me.
Not quite.
You will be executed, yes...
but not in the same way.
I've been studying the law,
our law,
and i believe i've found a way
that will satisfy
everybody.
I... would have thought of it
long before, but...
please, try to appreciate
our position.
Try to imagine a state
that has carried
the death penalty on its books
for hundreds of years
and has never had to invoke it.
That is the case here.
You see, you were our
first prisoner, so to speak.
You forced us
to examine our law.
Good-bye, mr. Redfield.
I'm sorry to do this.
I was becoming fond of you.
$4.42 out of ten.
There's five,
and five is ten.
Sorry, i, uh, must have
dozed off there a second.
That's what happens
when you drive too long.
Yeah. You say bredon
is back this way, huh?
80 miles.
Shut up, rollie.
Anything wrong?
No, no, i, uh...
thought i saw
somebody i knew, that's all.
Wishful thinking, i guess.
It's a nice little town
you got here.
We like it.
Can i just back in here?
Yep.
You've seen them.
Little towns tucked away
far from the main roads.
You've seen them, but
have you thought about them?
Have you wondered what
the people do in such places,
why they stay?
Philip redfield
thinks about them now
and he wonders,
but only very late at night
when he's between wakefulness
and sleep...
in the twilight zone.
We move next ontwilight zone
into a shadowy area
that treads a very thin line
between flesh and fantasy.
You'll see a performance
by dennis hopper that,
even from my rather
close-in perspective,
strikes me
as an exceptional one.
Our story is called
"he's alive,"
and if this doesn't
get you where you live,
you'll find it close by
in the suburbs.
Need medical attention?
We don't need any.
Okay, jack.
Hey, jack!
You forgot your, um...
your flag.
There'll come a day
when guys like you
will crawl on your belly
just to salute this.
Who's out there?
Who is it?
A friend, mr. Vollmer.
Come down,
mr. Vollmer.
Come down, and we will talk.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org