Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Nurse?
Time for your sleeping medicine,
honey.
Is it night already?
It's 9:30.
Oh. What about the day?
Oh, what about it?
Well, was it
a beautiful day?
Was it warm?
Was the sun out?
It was kind of warm.
Yes... and clouds?
Were there clouds in the sky?
I suppose
there were.
I never was much
for staring up
at the sky.
No?
I used to like to
look at the clouds.
If you stare at them long
enough, they become things.
You know what i mean?
People, ships,
anything you want, really.
It's time to take
your temperature now.
Oh, please, one
more thing, nurse.
Well?
When will they take
the bandages off?
How long, nurse?
Until they decide
whether or not they
can fix your face.
Oh, i guess it's...
pretty bad, isn't it?
I've seen worse.
Well, yes, but... it's
pretty bad, isn't it?
Oh, i know
it's pretty bad.
Ever since
i can remember-
ever since i was a little girl-
people have turned away
when they looked at me.
Funny...
the very first thing
i can remember
is another little child
screaming when she looked at me.
I... i never really wanted
to be beautiful, you know.
I mean, i never wanted
to look like a painting.
I never even wanted
to be loved, really.
I just wanted
people not to scream
when they looked at me.
When, nurse? When? When?
When will they take
the bandages off?
Maybe tomorrow.
Maybe the next day.
Now hush.
You've been waiting so long now.
It doesn't really
make much difference
whether it's two weeks
or days now.
Does it?
Dr. Bernardi, evening
report on patient 307:
No temperature change,
resting comfortably.
Thank you, nurse.
I'll be down later.
Ever see her face- 307?
Indeed i have.
If it were mine,
i'd bury myself
in a grave someplace.
Poor thing.
Some people want to
live no matter what.
Cigarette?
Suspended in time and space
for a moment,
your introduction
to miss janet tyler,
who lives in a very private
world of darkness,
a universe whose dimensions
are the size, thickness, length
of the swath of bandages
that cover her face.
In a moment, we'll go
back into this room.
And also, in a moment,
we'll look under those bandages,
keeping in mind, of course,
that we're not to be surprised
by what we see
because this isn't
just a hospital,
and this patient 307
is not just a woman.
This happens
to be the twilight zone,
and miss janet tyler, with you,
is about to enter it.
Blood pressure and
temperature are normal, doctor.
There's
been no change.
All right. Come back
about 11:00, nurse.
Give her
the usual sedative then.
All right,
doctor.
Well, it's warm this
evening, miss tyler.
Yes, i thought it was,
but i couldn't be sure.
Well,
it's very warm.
Take my word
for that.
We'll have those bandages
off you very soon.
I expect you're pretty uncomfortable.
Well, i'm used to
bandages on my face.
I have no doubt.
It's your ninth
visit here.
It is the ninth?
The 11th.
You know, sometimes i...
i think i've lived my whole
life inside of a dark cave
with walls of gauze,
and the wind that blows
into the mouth of the cave
smells of ether
and disinfectant.
Of course there's a...
there's a kind of a comfort
living inside this cave-
wonderfully private.
Nobody can ever see you.
It's hopeless,
isn't it, doctor?
I'll never look any
different than now.
Well, that's
hard to say.
Up to now, you haven't responded
to the shots, the medications-
any of the proven techniques.
Frankly, you've stumped us, miss tyler.
Nothing we've done
so far has made
any difference
at all.
However, we're very hopeful
for what this last treatment
may have accomplished.
There's no telling, of course,
till we get the bandages off.
I'm sorry your case is not one
that we could have
handled with plastic surgery,
but your bone
structure,
flesh type...
many factors
prohibit
the surgical
approach.
Your 11th visit.
No more after this, doctor.
No more tries.
11 is the mandatory number
of experiments.
We're not permitted
to do any more after 11.
Now what, doctor?
Well, you're kind of jumping
the gun, aren't you, miss tyler?
You may very well have responded
to these last
injections.
There's no
way of telling
till we get
the bandages off.
And, if i haven't
responded, then what?
Well, there
are alternatives.
Like?
Don't you know?
Yes, i know.
You realize, of
course, miss tyler,
why these rules
are in effect.
Each of us
is afforded
as much opportunity
as possible
to fit in
with society.
In your case,
think of the time
and the money
and the effort
expended to
make you look...
look like what, doctor?
Normal. The way
you'd like to look.
Doctor...
doctor...
may i walk outside?
Please, may i?
May i just go and...
and sit in the garden?
Just... just
for a little while.
Just...
just to feel the air.
Just... just
to smell the flowers.
to make believe i am normal?
If... if i sit out there
in the darkness,
then the whole world is dark,
and i'm more a part of it
like that, not just...
one grotesque, ugly woman
with a bandage on her face
with a special darkness
all around.
I want to belong.
I want to be like everybody.
Please, doctor.
Please help me.
There are
many others
who share
your misfortune-
people who look
much as you do.
Now, one of the
alternatives...
just in the event
that this
last treatment
is not
successful,
is simply
to allow you
to move into
a special area
in which people
of your kind
have been
congregated.
People of my kind?
Congregated.
Oh, you mean segregated!
You mean imprisoned,
don't you, doctor?
You're talking about
a ghetto, aren't you?
A ghetto designed for freaks!
Miss tyler!
Now, the state is
not unsympathetic.
Your presence here
in this hospital
is proof of that.
It's doing all
it can for you.
But you're not being rational, miss tyler.
Now, you know
you can't expect
to live any kind
of a life among...
normal people.
I could try.
I...
i could wear a mask
or this bandage or...
i wouldn't bother anybody.
I'd just go my own way.
I'd get a job. Any job!
I...
who are you people anyway?
What is this state?
Who makes all these rules
and conditions and statutes:
The people who are different
have to stay away
from the people who are normal.
The state isn't god, doctor.
Miss tyler,
please, please.
The state is not god!
It hasn't the right
to penalize somebody
for an accident of birth!
It hasn't the right to make
ugliness a crime!
Miss tyler! Miss tyler,
stop this immediately.
I feel the night
out there.
I feel the air.
I can smell the flowers.
Oh...
oh, please.
Please, take this
off me, please.
Please, take this off me.
Oh, please, take this off me!
Take it off me!
Help! Somebody, help me!
Help!
No, no, no.
Let me go.
Please, let me go.
Let me go, please.
Oh, please.
Please, let me go.
Please, please, let me...
all right, then.
I will take
the bandages off.
Get the anesthetist.
Yes, doctor.
You look tired,
doctor.
Do i? Well, i hadn't
thought about it.
I suppose i am.
You've been under a great deal of tension.
I know how much
it means to you-
this case in 307.
Well, you try to be
impersonal about these things.
You do everything
medically possible,
everything
humanly possible
and then, in the end,
you cross your fingers
and you hope
for a miracle.
You know, once in a while,
a miracle does happen
just often enough
to let you know
that you're not wrong
or foolish
to hope for one.
But you're destroying
yourself this way.
Forgive me, but you mustn't
let yourself get
personally involved here.
I know. You think
i haven't told myself that?
But you see, nurse,
i've... i've looked
underneath those bandages.
So have i.
It's horrible.
No, i mean deeper
than that.
Deeper than that pitiful,
twisted lump of flesh-
deeper even than that
misshapen skeletal mask.
I've seen that woman's
real face, nurse-
the face of her real self.
It's a good face.
It's a human face.
I understand,
but i must confess,
it's easier for me to
think of her as human
when her face
is covered up.
But why?
Why must we feel
that way, nurse?
What is the dimensional
difference
between beauty and
something repellant?
Is it skin deep?
Oh, less than that.
Why, nurse?
Why shouldn't people be
allowed to be different?
Why?
Doctor, careful.
What you're talking is...
treason.
Oh, this case has
upset your balance-
your sense of values.
Well, i suppose.
Don't be concerned,
nurse.
I'll be all right once
the bandages are off.
Once iknowone way
or the other.
Leader's
speaking tonight.
He goes on in
just a few minutes.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
our leader.
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Tonight, i shall talk to you
about glorious conformity.
About the delight
and the ultimate pleasure
of our unified society.
Now, i have to ask you
once again, miss tyler.
And i must insist
that you promise
you'll
remain rational,
no tantrums, no
temperament, and no violence.
You understand?
Now, i'll tell
you precisely
what i'm going to do.
I'm going to
cut the bandages
a section at a time,
then i'm going to unwrap
the bandages very gradually.
The process
has to be slow,
so that your eyes can become
accustomed to the light.
As you know,
these injections
may have had some
effect on your vision.
I understand.
So now, as i unwrap, i want
you to keep your eyes open,
and i want you to
describe to me
the various shadings of
light as you perceive it.
All right.
Now, if you make
any movement,
or if you start getting
emotional on us, miss tyler,
i'm going to have to have
the nurses hold you down,
and have the
anesthetist
put you under sedation,
you understand.
I promise i won't.
All right, then.
Do you see any light
now, miss tyler?
Oh, just a little.
It looks gray.
All right, now.
Just be very quiet.
Now,
miss tyler?
Oh, it... it's much brighter.
Good, good.
Look- look up
toward the light.
How about now,
miss tyler?
Oh, yes, it...
it's very bright.
Good, good.
Now...
i'm at the last layer
of bandages, miss tyler.
Oh...
i, i can just see you.
I can just distinguish
your outline vaguely,
but i can just see you.
Good.
All right,
miss tyler,
i'm going
to remove
the last of the
bandages now.
Would you
like a mirror?
No.
No, thank you.
No mirror.
All right, then.
I want you
to remember
this, please.
Miss tyler, are
you listening?
Yes, i'm listening.
Now, we have done
all we could do.
If we've been
successful,
well and good.
There are
no problems.
But if,
on the other hand,
this final treatment
has not achieved
the desired result,
please remember,
miss tyler,
that you can still live
a long and fruitful life
among people of...
your own kind.
Now, as soon as we
discover the results,
we'll either
release you or...
doctor?
Yes?
If i'm still terribly ugly...
well, is there
any other alternative?
Could i please be put away?
Well, under certain
circumstances, miss tyler,
the state does
provide for
the extermination
of undesirables.
However, there
are many factors
to be considered
in the decision.
Under the present
circumstances, i...
i doubt very much whether
we would be permitted
to do anything
but... transfer you
to a communal
group of people
with your disability.
They'll make me go, then?
That would probably
be the case.
Now, remain
very quiet.
Keep your
eyes open.
All right,
miss tyler...
here comes
the last of it.
I wish you
every good luck.
No change.
No change at all.
I was afraid
of this.
Turn on the light.
Needle, please.
Life at the...
stop that patient!
Stop her!
We know now that there must be
a single purpose,
a single norm,
a single approach,
a single entity of people,
a single virtue,
a single morality,
a single frame of reference,
a single philosophy
of government.
We must cut out
all that is different
like a cancerous filth!
It is essential,
in this society,
that we not only have a norm
but that we conform
to that norm!
Differences weaken us!
Variations destroy us!
...this norm is what
has ended nations
and brought them
to their knees!
Conformity, we must worship
in all interests!
Conformity is
the key to survival!
Miss tyler.
Miss tyler,
don't be afraid.
He's... he's only
a representative
from the group you're
going to live with.
Oddly enough, you've
come right to him.
Now, come on now.
Don't be afraid.
He's not going
to hurt you.
He won't hurt you.
Don't be afraid.
It's all right.
It's all right, miss tyler.
Now, this is mr. Smith.
Mr. Walter smith.
Mr. Smith is in charge
of the village group
in the north.
He'll take you
there tonight.
It's the only way now.
Miss tyler, we have
a lovely village
and wonderful people.
I think you're
going to like it
where i'm
going to take you.
You'll, uh... you'll
be with your own kind,
and in a little while-
oh, you'll be amazed
how little a while-
you'll feel a sense
of great belonging.
You'll feel a sense
of being loved...
and you will be loved,
miss tyler.
Miss tyler...
...would you get
your things now?
We can leave
anytime.
Mr. Smith?
Yes?
Why do we have
to look like this?
I don't know, miss tyler;
i really don't know.
But you know something?
It doesn't matter.
There's an old saying...
a very, very old saying:
"Beauty is in the eye
of the beholder."
When we leave here,
when we go to the village,
try to think of that,
miss tyler.
Say it over and over
to yourself.
Beauty is in the eye
of the beholder.
Come on now.
We'll get your things
and we'll leave.
Good-bye, miss tyler.
Now the questions
that come to mind:
Where is this place
and when is it?
What kind of world
where ugliness is the norm
and beauty the deviation
from that norm?
You want an answer?
It doesn't make any difference
because the old saying
happens to be true-
beautyis
in the eye of the beholder,
in this year
or a hundred years hence,
on this planet or wherever
there is human life,
perhaps out amongst the stars.
Beauty is
in the eye of the beholder.
Lesson to be learned
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling, the creator
oftwlight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
You've probably run across
these penny machines
that tell your fortune.
You put a penny in...
and out comes a card.
Only this particular machine,
which you'll see next week,
is a little bit unique,
in that the fortunes
that it tells
happen to come true.
A most intriguing tale,
called "the nick of time,"
by mr. Richard matheson.
And you're invited
to partake of it.
Thank you and good night.
See the new
andy griffith show
each week,
over most of these stations.
Consult local listings.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org