Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
of imagination.
Next stop, the twilight zone.
Yeah?
Oh, hello, george.
I been expecting your call.
Yeah, i been sitting here
waiting for you.
Yeah, it's kind of
a hot night out, ain't it?
Yeah, well, that's what i want
to talk to you about, george.
I was wondering
what you had in mind tonight.
Now... now,
wait a minute, george.
Now, i been sitting here
three, four hours now.
I been roasting to death
out there and...
well, i like to go
out of my mind, george...
george?
George, look, will you...
george, will...
george, will you let me...
will you listen to me, george?
Will you listen to me?
Now, look, i'm not trying
to cop out, george.
I am not trying to cop out.
I'd just like to know what
you had in mind, that's all.
You know i got a tendency
toward nerves, george,
and, well, you can sit in
a hotel room only so long and...
well, it's such a hot night
outside, george.
George, look,
i'm not complaining, george.
You know i'm not complaining,
george.
I'm going to do the job,
whatever it is. You know that.
You got a number one boy
here, george.
I'm going to do the job, but...
george?
Hey, george?
George?
This is mr. Jackie rhoades,
age 34,
and, where some men leave
a mark of their lives
as a record of their
fragmentary existence on earth,
this man leaves a blot-
a dirty, discolored blemish
to document a cheap
and undistinguished sojourn
amongst his betters.
What you're about
to watch in this room
is a strange mortal combat
between a man and himself.
For, in just a moment,
mr. Jackie rhoades,
whose life has been given over
to fighting adversaries,
will find his most formidable
opponent in a cheap hotel room
that is, in reality,
the outskirts
of the twilight zone.
Yeah?
Yeah? Who is it?
George.
How are you, george?
I'm in the pink.
How are you, jackie?
Oh, i'm all right, george.
I'm all right.
I'm just a little nervous
about the action tonight.
I was...
it's a gorgeous place
you got here, jackie.
Well, four bucks a night,
you can't go wrong, you know.
Four bucks a night.
No, you can't go wrong,
but you could get
roasted to death,
or poisoned by
small creatures.
What about tonight,
george? What's the job?
Does it make
any difference?
Difference?
No, no, no. It don't
make no difference.
I was just wondering.
I just wondered what you
had in mind. That was all.
What would you like to do,
jackie?
What's your heart's desire?
Oh, you're kidding me, george.
You're pulling my leg.
I know you.
Well, if it was up to me,
i'd... i'd, uh...
well...
if it was up
to me, george,
i'd like some decent
odds for a change.
I don't mind a little
shakedown- a little bunco-
but it's just that i'm
getting all the hard stuff.
You know i almost got
picked up the last two times.
Remember the heist?
That kind of stuff
ain't for me, george.
Except they pick me up
one more time, george,
it's three strikes
and out.
I'm long gone,
and for good.
Boy, it's so hot in
here, ain't it, george?
Ain't it hot?
Anybody ever tell you
what you look like?
You look like a man trying
to catch a subway at 5:00.
You always look like
somebody's squeezing you
through a door.
What do you do to sleep
at night, jackie,
hide in the locked closet?
Now, look, george,
i'm not knocking you,
and i don't see why
you all the time
gotta knock me.
All i'm asking
from you is...
george, what's the job
i've got to do tonight?
All right, i'll
tell you, jackie.
Tonight, i'm going
to let you be a man.
I'm going to let you
show some muscle
for a change.
No shakedowns, no
deliveries to a fence-
nothing little, jackie.
Not tonight.
Tonight, jackie, you're
getting up in the world.
Now, there's an old man
runs a little bar
on 38th street
between lexington
and sixth.
He's a feisty old bum.
He's always giving us trouble.
He don't want to pay
off for the jukeboxes,
he don't want to
pay for protection.
We lecture him
all the time,
but he spits
in our eye.
So, tomorrow morning,
they find the old gleep
sprawled across his bar.
And then all the rest
swing in line.
Now, that's
simple, jackie.
Even you
can understand.
Kill him?
You want me to kill him?
You're the one, jackie.
But, george, i can get sent up
for just carrying that thing.
George,
this one ain't for me.
Listen, you're in hock to
me for your collar buttons,
so don't tell me what's
for you and what isn't.
But i never done anything
like this before, george.
I'm strictly
breaking and entering.
I'm nickels and dimes.
You put me in an alley,
i do a mug job,
but i got to do it
from behind.
I got no guts, george.
You know that, george.
I got no guts.
Why don't you get
a couple other guys, huh?
Get a couple
of torpedoes?
'Cause every torpedo i got in
the line is gonna get picked up
the minute they find
that old gleep.
Because you're not
going to get picked up
because you're nickel-and-dime
and everybody knows it.
You never did
a job like this
because you never could
do a job like this,
and that's why you're
gonna do this one, jackie.
And that's how you're
going to get away with it.
But, george,
i got no guts.
Get guts, jackie! I
don't care where from.
You get them under the bed,
you buy them from a vendor,
you grow them in a pot.
I don't care,
but you get them,
and you do the job.
Now, he closes
that bar at 2:00.
You be there when
he's about to lock up,
and you do it.
And i'll be back
here at 2:30, jackie.
And if i find out
that you welshed
on me, jackie-
that you chickened out-
you're dead.
Hey... george.
Hey, george!
George!
George! Please, george!
Look at you.
Look at you. What's the beef?
Go out and get rid
of an old man.
Some dopey old man.
He's going to be 90 years old,
maybe 100 years.
That's what he is-
some dopey old man- a gleep.
Hey, that's what george
called him- a gleep.
That's what
george called him- a gleep.
Boy, i wish i could trade you,
and i could use another model.
Aw, it's not your fault.
It's not my fault.
It's just the breaks,
that's all.
Why am i scared?
Why am i, all the time, scared?
I'm all the time scared.
Oh, man, i've had a long haul.
How many nights in a tank?
How many nights in stir?
How many nights in a cheap,
lousy little room like this?
Four bucks a night
to roast to death.
Nail biter.
Scared, nervous
little nail biter.
Hey, george! You ain't no judge
of people, george!
You ought to peel cantaloupes!
You ought to stick
with apples and oranges, george,
because you ain't no judge
of people!
Jackie rhoades the killer!
Hey, jackie rhoades, killer!
I know you, jackie rhoades.
You ain't no killer.
But you got to kill tonight.
Kill or be killed.
So you do the job
and you're dead anyway,
because you know you never
got away with anything.
You live till tomorrow,
and that's how it ends.
Boy, i wish
i could trade you in.
No matches.
Cigarettes and no matches,
that's me all over.
That's jackie rhoades,
the halfway boy.
That's the story of my life.
Hello, jackie.
Come back here!
You're not running out
on me this time!
You talking to me?
Who you...?
Yeah, sure you are.
Now me and the mirror,
we're having a talk.
I've had it, huh?
All my marbles are gone.
This is how it happens.
This...
yeah, this is
how it happens,
but you ain't lost
your marbles yet,
and i mean to see
that you keep them.
Who are you?
I'm you, jackie,
and you're me.
How's that?
You're me
and i'm you?
Oh, this is crazy.
This is really crazy.
This is crazy! Crazy!
Jackie, i'm part
of you, jackie.
Another part of you.
Don't you even
remember me?
You used to know me
a long time ago, jackie.
A very long time ago,
you were up for grabs.
You could have gone
one way or the other.
my way or your way.
You went your way.
You know what
that means, jackie?
No, i don't.
A cheap, weak, scared
half vulture,
all mouse.
That's what
you are, jackie.
All right,
so knock me.
So i'm this and i'm that,
and i'm this and i'm that.
Look, here, buddy,
whatever i am,
i got flesh and bones
and i breathe.
And. In just a couple
of hours from now,
i'm going to put
the finger on somebody!
So, ha-ha!
What do you do
for a living, huh?
Haunt people in mirrors, huh?
Listen to me, boy. Listen to me.
I'm having an argument
with a big piece of glass.
Listen, glass, i'm leaving.
See, i'm pulling out.
I'm pulling out.
I've had it with you.
I'm a mouse, huh?
Well, you're nothing!
Jackie...
jackie.
Now, jackie...
jackie, don't pass out
on me now.
Jackie, we've got
a big night ahead of us.
Where you going?
What's it to you?
Everything.
Everything you do
is everything to me.
Can't you get that?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
now i get it.
I'm talking to myself.
That's just who
you are talking to-
part of yourself- the part
you never let come out.
Now, listen, buddy.
You got no invitation
to come out now,
so you can go right back
where you came from.
Who needs you?
You do.
You've always needed me.
Wait a minute.
Now i get it.
Yeah, now i get it.
You're chicken, too.
You're scared
i'll get caught
same as me.
You're scared
this is the last job,
so you make a big noise
like a conscience
so the big man don't say
you been goofing off
all my life.
It means more than
that to me, jackie.
You think i can
keep quiet now
while you go out and
get us both killed?
Killed?
That's right.
You said so yourself-
you never got away
with nothing,
and you know you won't
get away with this.
And i got
a right to live.
You had the same chances
as me- no chance.
So, if i'm wrong
and you're right,
then how come every move
i made turned out wrong?
How about that, huh?
Because, every time
i tried to talk to you,
you listened
to somebody else.
That was your mistake.
Okay, wise guy,
you know so much,
then how come you don't
know the big thing?
Big thing?
Don't you ever
look in a mirror?
I was a runt.
I was a skinny little runt.
When you want to join
a street gang,
you got to go
along with them.
You back down,
they give you business.
They call you a chicken,
and yell,
"you ain't got it!"
Yeah, you went
along with them.
And you made me
go along, too.
The first time, we
were ten years old.
Remember that?
The class picnic?
The teacher had a locket,
and the catch broke,
and she laid it down,
and some of the big kids
dared you to swipe it.
Well, i didn't
want to swipe it.
I told you,
i was a runt.
They dared me.
And, a year later,
they dared you
to break into that
grocery store with them,
and you went along,
and you dragged
me along, too,
and we got caught.
And you spent
the next 11 months
in reform school,
and so did i.
What did that
prove, jackie?
Yak, yak, yak, yak.
Talk my ear off.
No wonder
i cut you down.
You're walking on your
lower lip all the time.
What do you want from me anyway?
You know what i want.
No, i don't
but i'll tell you
what i do know-
i got to go out
and do a job.
I got to knock off an
old gleep on 38th street.
And, if i don't do it
by 2:00 a.m.,
you can take
what's left of me
and scrape it off
that mirror with a spoon!
I ain't got much time.
I got to go now.
You got less time
than you think.
But you never had time.
You didn't have time
when that parole officer
tried to help you.
You could have
listened to him,
but you joined another gang.
Six months later,
you were in jail again,
and that parole officer
couldn't help you
any more than janey reardon could.
Janey reardon.
She was a nice kid.
She was a
beautiful woman.
She tried to
set you straight.
I loved her, jackie.
I loved janey reardon.
You loved her?
You got a nerve.
How could you love anybody?
You're just a piece of glass.
I could love, jackie.
I could love.
I needed her, jackie.
So did you.
I tried to tell you
how much we needed her,
but you graduated
from the gang
into the shakedown rackets.
Big shot, huh?
Two years we
spent in the pen
on that one.
And, when
we got out,
janey reardon
had gotten married
and moved away.
She walked out of
your life, jackie.
Out ofourlife!
You cheated me out of her.
Don't tell me your troubles.
It's nothing to me.
Dames i can take or leave alone.
Dames you can take
or leave, huh?
That's a statement
for the press.
You wouldn't want to have
a girl, would you, jackie?
Somebody sweet and pretty.
Somebody who would love you.
Somebody who'd be kind
and gentle with you.
You don't need that,
do you, jackie?
Why don't you cut it out?
Will you do that?
Will you knock it off?
What do you want from me anyway?
I'm asking you,
what do you want from me?
I'm still waiting to hear.
What do you want?
I want to take over,
jackie.
I want to call the shots.
I want you to let me out.
I want a chance to live.
I want to live
with all the guts
and goodness
you left behind.
I want to live
the dreams you dreamed
and never had
the guts to live.
Fat chance, buster.
Big fat chance.
I'm me and
you're you!
And that's no statement
for the press.
That's the goods.
I'm going out
and knock me off an old man now,
and i'm going to cut me
a nice slice of cabbage
for my troubles.
I'm calling the shots!
And neither you or anybody else
is telling jackie rhoades
what to do!
Neither you or anybody else!
Yeah?
Oh... yeah, george.
Uh... george, i'm doing
what you told me, george.
I'm just on my way out now.
Yeah, george. I'm just leaving.
Yeah. Honest, george. Honest.
I'm... i'm... i'm on my way now.
Yeah. Yeah, i'm... i'm...
i'm going to leave right now,
george.
I'll meet you back here
at 2:30, okay?
Yeah. I'll meet you
right back here, george.
Okay.
Hey!
Hey, there.
Hey, where are you?
Hey, glass, come on out here.
Come on. Do your job now.
Hey, come on, i want to see
how i look, glass. Come on.
It don't make any
difference, jackie,
because you're
not going anywhere.
You go out that door,
you're finished.
We're both finished.
That's the door
to nowhere.
Jackie, jackie,
let me out!
I want to take over.
I got to take over!
I want a decent job,
some friends.
I got a job.
I got friends.
I got everything i want.
You got nothing. You got
nothing but a pain inside.
You got no friends. You got
nothing! You are nothing!
It's time to be something.
Jackie, let me out.
Let me take over, jackie.
This is your last chance.
All right, i'll let you
out of there.
Come on out of there, wise guy.
Come on out!
What a phony.
You're a liar!
Get up, little man.
I'm going to take your
skin off foot by foot.
Nobody went to the old
man's bar tonight, jackie.
Nobody at all.
At last reports, he was
in excellent health...
thanks to you.
Thanks to you, you
raunchy little welsher.
Well, what do you got to say
for yourself, crumb, huh?
What have you got
to say for yourself?
What have i got to say
for myself, george?
Not much.
I resign.
That's it,
george.
I resign.
You what?
You can have
your gun back,
plus the following.
Move out, george.
And don't ever come back...
for anything.
Room clerk, this is jackie...
this is john rhoades, room 14.
I'm checking out.
No, i'm not coming back.
No, as a matter of fact,
nothing's all right.
The room's too hot,
too small and too dirty.
It's just the place for bums,
but not for me.
Hey, hey,
what's to do now?
What's to do now?
Now we go look
for a job.
Now maybe
we get married.
Now maybe we stop
biting our nails.
Exit mr. John rhoades, formerly
a reflection in a mirror,
a fragment
of someone else's conscience,
a wishful thinker
made out of glass,
but now made out of flesh,
and on his way
to join the company of men.
Mr. John rhoades,
with one foot through the door
and one foot out
of the twilight zone.
Rod serling
the creator oftwilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
These are familiar items,
i'm sure-
television set, electric razor,
clock, typewriter-
the normal,
everyday accoutrements
that are part and parcel
of 20th century progress.
But, next week, you'll see them
under different circumstances,
and in a totally
dissimilar guise.
They'll be machines,
but they'll also be monsters.
Our story is called
a thing about machines,
and it will be here
waiting for you
in the twilight zone.
Seethe new andy griffith show
each week
over most of these stations.
Consult local listings.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org