Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Strike two!
Strike three!
You're out.
Howie gottlieb, you're never
going to get to heaven.
That was a ball,
and you know it.
Was not.
Was too.
How about that,
ben, you saw it?
Jenny, howie's the umpire.
Who's up?
You are.
Well, it's about time.
Look out.
Yippee!
Home run.
No fair. No fair.
You said you wouldn't
use magic anymore.
Four to four.
Dirty deal,
that's cheating.
Come on,
let's play ball.
What with?
All right, never mind.
Let's do something else.
How about spaceman?
All those who wish
to play spaceman
raise their hands.
All right, and this time,
jenny, you're the martian.
Naw.
It's your turn.
I know, but i can't turn
into things the way you can.
Aw, come on, ben,
don't be a dirty guy.
Jenny moves too slow.
All right, all right.
This is the last time.
Now, let me see,
what should i do?
Jenny, you get to
write the script.
Well...
that's the rocket ship
over there.
And i'm the captain.
What are you
talking about?
Who ever heard of
a dame with a brace
being captain?
All right, you bunch of babies.
Yoube the captain.
The rest of you
are lieutenants and stuff.
Who are you?
I'm the beautiful stowaway.
Okay, now, ben,
you go on over to the ship.
Now we just landed, see.
This is mars.
We've been exploring around
trying to find out
if anyone's alive.
Got that?
When we come over to the ship,
you come out.
And make it real horrible.
I mean, you know,
real horrible.
Not too horrible.
You suppose
any martians
snuck inside
the ship, captain?
Not a chance, this ship
is heretically sealed.
You go ahead.
You go, you're
the captain.
Go on, howie.
Okay, i'll lead,
but i want my men behind me.
Sneak formation.
It's a martian.
Somebody shoot!
Boing, boing, boing...
boing, boing,
boing...
i think you got him.
It's been said
that science fiction and fantasy
are two different things-
science fiction,
the improbable made possible;
fantasy,
the impossible made probable.
What would you have
if you put these two
different things together?
Well, you'd have
an old man named ben
who knows tricks
most people don't know
and a little girl
named jenny who loves him...
and a journey into the heart
of the twilight zone.
Ooh-wee!
Now, everybody off.
Now, that'll be ten cents,
please.
Pay you tomorrow.
How do i know
i can trust you?
You can't.
Well, in that case,
it's a deal.
Ahh...
"say i'm weary, say i'm sad
"say that health and wealth
have missed me
"say that i am growing old
but add, jenny kissed me."
What's that?
Earth poetry.
You made it up,
but i like it.
So do i.
All right, up we go.
With your skates on?
I forgot.
Scat!
Nothing to it.
Here we go.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Ben, tell me something.
What is it,
little monkey?
You can do
so many things,
how come you don't
make my leg well?
Well, because then i wouldn't
have the fun of carrying you.
And you'd get yourself
a young boyfriend.
I'm serious.
You could do it,
couldn't you?
Perhaps, but...
no, jenny, i mustn't do it.
Why?
I told you to be back
before the stores closed.
It's my fault,
mrs. Gann.
It's always your
fault, ain't it?
Come on, aunt agnes.
Shut up, you ungrateful
little guttersnipe.
After all
i done for you.
After i fed you
and took care of you
and give you
a place to sleep.
Where'd you be
if it wasn't for me?
In an orphanage!
If you don't mind,
that's where you're going.
Now you get inside.
Don't you ever
lift your hand to jenny again.
Look, you just
listen to me.
I've got my
stomachful of you
hanging around that girl,
turning her against me,
filling her head up
with crazy stuff.
You hear me?
You think i'm deaf?!
I ain't
putting up with it.
You even talk to her,
and i'll call the cops!
Oh...
you bother us again,
that's what's going to happen.
You hear me?!
Now you get into bed.
No supper for you tonight, miss.
Well?
Excuse us, madam,
we're gathering
information about a tenant.
A man they call old ben-
you know him?
You cops?
In a way.
I knew it.
May we come in?
Sure.
What'd he do?
We'll ask the questions.
All right, got to
come in the kitchen.
I'm fixing supper.
How long has he
lived here?
This building?
A year and a half.
Do you know
his previous address?
Mister, we don't
know nothing
about him-
where he comes from,
what his name is... nothing!
Ever seen him
do anything unusual?
Like what?
Like magic.
Nah, kids say he's
good at tricks,
but i never seen any.
Ben?
Jenny?
Oh, ben.
What's the matter,
what's wrong?
Two policemen
downstairs.
They're after you.
I didn't think she'd do it.
Aunt agnes didn't call.
They came right
after you left.
What'd they look like?
I just saw a bit of
them in the kitchen.
Tall...
one had blond hair
and the other
was dark-haired.
That's them.
They've caught up with me.
Who has?
What are you scared of?
I can't tell you.
I thought we
were friends.
We are.
Friends don't
keep secrets.
I don't even know
where you come from
or why you're
running away.
Jenny!
Jenny, where are you?
I'm sorry,
little monkey,
but, well,
it doesn't matter.
Anyway, it's too late now.
No, it isn't.
You can hide someplace-
under the bed,
or in the closet.
They'll never find you.
All right,
where is he?
I don't know.
You're lying.
She knows
where he is.
Do you, miss?
No, i came up to see him
but he was gone.
I think he's in the park.
If you see him,
say nothing.
I know to keep
my mouth shut.
Come on.
Well, thank you,
mrs. Gann.
Any time,
gentlemen.
I ought to beat you
till you can't sit down
but i won't
'cause i'm too tired.
Now get in there
and go to bed,
and i don't want
to hear a peep out of you.
And don't try sneaking out again
if you know what's good for you.
That fooled them,
whoever they are.
Sure did.
Did i tickle you there?
What i can't
understand is
how you can change
the clothes, too.
It's all matter-
one molecular structure
is much like another.
Speaking of changing clothes,
young lady,
you'd better
start wearing a dress
or your aunt
will have a fit.
Let her.
Now, that isn't respectful,
jenny.
Remember that mrs. Gann
is a nervous person
and isn't wholly responsible
for her behavior.
Then who is?
Well, i'm not too sure.
In any case,
you try to forgive her.
All right.
But what about you?
What are you going to do?
Ah, i wish i knew,
little monkey.
Ben?
Yes?
How come those men
are after you?
Are you a criminal?
In a way, yes.
What'd you do,
rob a bank?
No.
Kill somebody?
You must be a communist.
No, little monkey,
i'm not a communist.
Then, what?!
Shh!
Ben, listen, why
don't you fool 'em?
Turn into a spider
or a cockroach.
They'd never
find you then.
I'm afraid they would.
Those boys are pretty clever.
You see, jenny,
my real shape, i mean,
the way i really look...
isn't this the way
you really look?
No.
Have i ever seen you
the way you really look?
No.
Gee, i bet you're icky.
Some found me
quite attractive.
I want to see.
No.
Listen, jenny.
You've been very good
letting me keep my secrets.
Now, i'm going to tell you
one of them.
You see, i am not actually
a resident of this world.
Huh?
I'm from another planet.
I knew it, i knew it.
Which one, mars?
No, you've never heard of it.
Anyway, jenny, those two
men are trying to catch me
so they can take me back.
'Cause of what you did?
Uh-huh, and i don't
want to go back.
But they've located me,
so the only thing i can do
is find another world
that i can hide in.
You mean you're just
going to go away?
I don't want to,
little monkey,
but i have no choice.
Before i go, though,
there's one thing i want to do.
I'd have done it before,
but it would've shown them
where i was.
That doesn't matter anymore.
What do you mean?
Let's take
this brace off.
My brace?
Mm-hmm.
Will it hurt?
Be careful.
Now, close your eyes.
Who're you talking to?
M... myself.
Cut it out,
you'll go crazy that way.
Ben!
Ben, my leg-
ben, don't leave me!
Ben!
Jenny, how can you
walk without your brace?
You get out
of my way.
Where's ben?
I don't know-
i won't tell.
You made him leave
me- i hate you!
No, don't.
It's the only way.
She's all right,
isn't she, doc?
I'm afraid not.
Well, what'd she want to go do
a stupid thing like that?
Like what?
Going downstairs without
her leg brace, that's what.
Whatever's wrong
with your niece
hasn't anything to
do with her legs.
Her legs seem to be
perfectly all right.
Well, i don't know
what you're talking about.
The fact is your niece
is in serious condition.
You mean... she...
you mean she's going to die?
If her pulse
gets any weaker.
Well, what's
the matter with her?
Whatever it is, it's
beyond my knowledge.
All we can do
now is wait.
Well...
hello, little monkey.
I thought you went away.
I did.
But i couldn't
stay away
from my best friend
for long.
What seems to
be the matter?
I don't know.
I saw those two policemen,
and then i fell down.
Am i going to die, ben?
Yes, eventually,
but not right now.
Close your eyes.
Feel better now?
I feel wonderful.
Thank you, ben.
Ben.
I know; they're here.
Your your
majesty. Majesty.
All right,
all right.
It was a terrible
thing to do-
hurting a little girl.
We didn't want
to hurt her,
your majesty.
We knew you'd come back
to make her well again.
I understand,
but i still don't like it.
What's going on?
What's this
"your majesty" stuff?
Well, little monkey,
i have a
confession to make.
You see, i'm a fraud.
Huh?
I'm not really
a criminal.
And these men really
aren't policemen.
They're my subjects.
And, i regret to say
i am what you would
call their king.
Aw, come on.
Cross my heart
and hope to die.
Then what were you
running away for?
Well, that is a little
hard to explain.
You see, i really wasn't
cut out to be a king.
All that fuss
and responsibility.
Oh, i don't know.
After the first
thousand years,
it sort of got me down.
And i knew i'd have at
least 4,000 years more
before i'd be able to turn
the job over to someone else.
So... whoosh!
I took off.
Jenny, i skeedaddled.
Well, all i can say is
you must have been
a pretty good king
to cause all this trouble.
That's true, miss.
He was the best of kings.
That's why
we want him back.
We're as fond of him
as you are.
But you can't have him back.
Ben-
i mean, your majesty-
you're not going away
with them, are you?
Oh, i guess i'll have to.
Then take me with you.
It's impossible, sir.
You know the rules.
The council
would never permit it.
Please, ben,
don't leave me.
I love you, ben.
I know.
Oh, if there were
only some way.
Ben?
Yes?
Gentlemen...
i would like
one minute alone with jenny.
Sir...
i solemnly swear
by our fathers
i won't run away.
Very well.
One minute, your majesty.
Thank you.
Er, your...
your majesty?
Yes?
Oh, now this isn't fair
at all.
You can't do this to us,
your majesty...
your majesty?
Looks like you'll have to
take both of us.
The council
wouldn't like it
if you brought back
the wrong one.
Shall we go?
Mrs. Gann will be in
for a big surprise
when she finds this
under jenny's pillow.
Because mrs. Gann has
more temper than imagination.
She'll never dream that
this is a picture of old ben
as he really looks.
And it will never occur to her
that eventually her niece
will grow up to be
an honest-to-goodness queen
somewhere in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, an excursion
into a strange
and totally different dimension.
We'll bring you a story
by richard matheson
called "little girl lost."
And this one, we guarantee,
is not the kind
found in a police docket
or in a missing persons bureau.
When this little girl is lost,
we're talking about
out of this world.
I hope you can join us next week
and find out
precisely where she's gone.
For our youngsters to be able
to design tomorrow's world,
we'll need more and better
college facilities.
Help the college
of your choice.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org