Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Picture of the spaceship e-89,
cruising above the 13th planet
of star system 51.
The year, 1997.
In a little while, supposedly,
the ship will be landed
and specimens taken-
vegetable, mineral,
and, if any, animal.
These will be brought back
to overpopulated earth
where technicians
will evaluate them,
and if everything
is satisfactory,
stamp their findings
with the word "inhabitable"
and open up yet another planet
for colonization.
These are the things
that aresupposedto happen.
Captain.
Something glittered
down there.
It was at, uh,
255-417.
I don't see anything.
Something glittered.
We've passed it now.
Well, we went over
a lake, you know.
I know, sir,
it wasn't that.
Okay, we'll have a look.
But it was
probably the lake.
Probably
wasting our time.
What are we turning for?
What is it?
Is something down there?
Mason thinks so.
There was something.
What?
I don't know yet.
We're almost there.
I know what
you're thinking.
Don't.
It's got to happen sometime,
doesn't it?
You're alien-contact
happy.
About time.
Do you really think
man's the only intelligent
life in the universe?
All right,
not again.
We're meeting
another race. Great.
It would
be great.
Man, wouldn't
that be something!
It's got
to happen...
why not to us?
There it is.
Looks like it might be a ship.
Hardly.
You mean
you're still not going to land?
Will you
take it easy?
Will you?!
We should take
specimens.
I don't like it.
Well, it's up
to you, captain.
Okay.
Ted, we're going down!
We're-we're
going down!
I can't even talk
to him anymore.
Yeah, what's
the matter with him?
He's acting
strange lately.
I don't know.
Air spring.
Places!
Picture of the crew
of the spaceship e-89:
Captain ross,
lieutenant mason,
lieutenant carter.
Three men who have
just reached a place
which is as far from home
as they will ever be.
Three men
who in a matter of minutes
will be plunged into
the darkest nightmare reaches
of the twilight zone.
I'll, uh... check
the atmosphere.
We won't need helmets.
Mike.
Mike!
Oh, thanks.
Your jumper, captain.
Mason!
You can't wait to get out there,
can you?
What's that supposed to mean?
It means i don't like impetuous
crewmen; they make mistakes.
Have i made any mistakes,
captain?
You're on the verge.
Let me know when i make them.
We stay together.
No one takes any risks.
That's an order, mason.
Yes, sir.
Looks like one of our ships,
doesn't it?
Don't jump
to conclusions.
Well, doesn't it?
From what i
can see of the
rockets, it does.
Rocket construction
could be standard everywhere.
Even on another planet,
captain?
That's enough!
Itisone
of our ships.
How could it get
this far off course?
I don't like it.
Well, aren't we
going to go in
and find out
who they are?
All right...
but stay together.
It's from earth.
There's no
doubt about it.
We don't know that.
But look at the
structuring,
captain.
We don't know that,
carter.
Nope.
Well, maybe
it's pressurized.
No, it's not
very likely.
The door frame
is probably twisted.
Try it
together, eh?
Yeah.
If it doesn't open,
we'll have to
forget about it.
Forget about it?
There isn't time!
It's moving!
All right.
Here.
Dear god.
Try the auxiliary
light system.
The auxiliary
light system!
Move!
I don't
understand.
Oh, it's not
what it seems.
I don't
understand.
Will you hang on?
Put it back.
Put it back!
What is this?
All right,
don't let it get to you.
It's me.
Come away.
I said come away.
Carter!
It's not what it seems.
That was us
in there.
We're dead.
Can you imagine
what it was like
when this thing hit?
We're dead.
Can you imagine?
No, our ship
is where we left it,
just as we left it.
That isn't our ship!
Those aren't our bodies!
Can you imagine?
But they are!
No. I don't
know what it is,
but there's a logical
explanation for this.
Everything has a
logical explanation!
This is me...
imagine...
this is you...
use your head.
It's not what it seems!
Well, then, what is it?
What is it?
I don't know,
but think.
Mason!
Yes, sir?
We're leaving.
We're going back to the ship.
Radio the station.
They'll tell us what to do.
Yes, sir.
Shouldn't we bury...
our...
they're not ours.
Will you go ahead?
We're alive.
Alive.
Try it again.
Captain,
i've been trying...
just try it again.
Earth station 1217,
earth station 1217,
this is spaceship e-89,
e-89.
Do you read me?
Come in,
earth station 1217. over.
What is this?
It was working before.
Maybe it's
this planet.
What are
you talking about?
Maybe there's an
interfering field...
don't be ridiculous.
Try the radionic signal.
Captain, it's not
going to work...
will you do
what i tell you once?!
Yes, sir.
Again.
Captain, if it didn't work
the first time...
they didn't hear us.
This return signal works
on automatic.
Do i have to tell you that?
All right.
But let's go over this
again and again,
because there's got to be
an answer somewhere.
Somewhere!
First, those are not
our bodies over there.
That i'm sure of.
Now, use your heads.
These are our bodies.
These are our bodies!
Listen.
Wait a minute.
Do you both
remember
what they told us
once in training
about the theory of
circumnavigating time?
They said it might be possible
for us to leave the earth
during one year;
then, when we got back,
though we thought
it was the same year,
it might be the year before
or the year after.
Remember that?
That was just a theory, captain.
No, no, it's
not a theory,
because that's what's
happened to us!
We've gone into some
kind of time warp
right into the future.
And that ship standing out there
is in the future?
Is that what you're saying?
No, no, only
the probable future.
What does that mean?
That means we're not dead.
And it also means
we're going to be dead.
Not if we don't go up.
If we don't go up,
we can't crash.
Now, it's the only answer.
We're alive
now, mason.
The only way
to make certain
that we stay alive-
you, carter, me-
is not to go up.
Then we can't crash.
We avoid it,
we prevent it.
We stay.
That's easy enough
for you to decide, captain.
Now, what does that mean?
You've got no one waiting
for you back on earth.
I've made my decision.
I say we vote on it.
You do?
You're not the only one,
captain.
I'm the only one
that gives the orders.
Even where our lives
are concerned?
Especially where your lives
are concerned!
I said we stay!
For how long,
captain?
I'm not setting
any limit, carter.
One month? Two months?
A year?
I said i'm
not setting...
we don't have
enough food to stay
that long.
I've no doubt there's
edible food outside.
How will we know what's edible
and what isn't?
We have no testing equipment.
We'll watch the animals.
I saw no animals, captain,
did you?
There will be.
If there are, it'll be
a different form of life
from what we know.
What could edible to them
might be deadly poisonous
for us!
We'll worry about
that when the
time comes.
The only important thing now
is the preservation
of our lives!
Now, it may not be necessary
to stay here permanently.
We may figure something out.
But for now,
the decision is to stay.
Not our decision.
Have you a better solution?
Working at minimum capacity,
the ship's electrical system
can hold out for months.
We won't be working
at minimum
capacity, captain.
Why?
'Cause we're going
to need heat- lots of it.
It's only twilight,
and already
the outside temperature is...
minus 13 degrees.
Would you rather go up,
take a risk of duplicating
that ship out there?
I don't know.
How could we
duplicate it,
captain?
How can there...
how can there be
two crashed ships
two of me dead,
two of you,
two of mason?
We'll go over it again.
Eventually,
we'll find an answer.
Hey, mike!
Hi, boy.
When'd you get home?
You're on leave, huh?
Huh?
I...
well, you're looking fit.
I'll bet mary's glad
to have you back, huh?
Mary?
Uh, you mind if i walk
with you, mike?
When'd you get home?
L-i just got here.
You... well, i must say,
you rocket boys
are traveling
informally these days.
Uh, does, uh...
mary know you're coming?
I don't think so.
Oh, you're going
to surprise her, huh?
Yeah.
How long you got?
I don't know.
You all right, mike?
Hello, mike.
Home on furlough?
I don't know.
Old mrs. Nolan.
Still makes that long walk
to town every day.
She'll go on forever.
Hey, mike, now you're back,
how about some hunting, huh?
Not that i ever hit anything
with this thing, but...
hey! Hey, mike!
Mary!
Mary! Honey, i'm home!
Mary?
Mary, honey...
honey?
Mary?
Carter?
Carter.
Carter, i'm talking
to you!
What's the matter
with you?
I was home.
What?
You were here.
Youarehere.
No...
no.
I swear i was home!
There was a telegram...
it said i'd been killed.
Oh, no.
No, you're alive.
No.
Those people-
kramer, mrs. Nolan...
they're dead!
I just remembered that!
Now, stop it, carter.
No, no, kramer,
kramer...
he got killed in
a hunting accident.
Mrs. Nolan...
now, you stop it!
Now, you were here
all the time.
It never happened.
There's an explanation
somewhere, and i'll find it.
I swear to you,
we'll find it.
You and mason and me,
we'll fi...
mason!
Mason!
Mason.
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
Mason.
Where is he?
Where did he go?
I don't know.
Oh, daddy,
i thought i'd never find you.
Jeannie.
I've looked and looked.
I found him, i found him!
Lunch is ready, daddy.
And am i hungry
after all that
searching.
What's the matter, daddy?
Come here.
What, daddy?
Oh!
Jeannie, jeannie.
What is it, daddy?
Oh, baby, is it you?
What's wrong, daddy?
Nothing, honey,
nothing.
I'm just happy
to see you, that's all.
Oh.
Was that your mother
you were calling to
just now?
Was it, honey?
Yes, daddy.
You know.
Where is she?
Over by the
table, daddy.
You stay right here.
Don't go away.
Okay.
Ted!
Well, you startled me,
bursting out of the bushes
like that.
Ted? What is it?
Oh, ruth.
Ruth.
Sweetheart,
what's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing now.
Are you sure?
Yes, i'm sure.
Ah! Oh, all this,
just for lunch?
My goodness.
So emotional over
a little fried chicken.
Where's jeannie?
Back there.
Were you asleep?
Are you still asleep?
Oh, if i am, i hope
i never wake up.
I just want to
keep on dreaming.
Let's go, mason.
Ted, why is he here?
Get out of here.
I said let's go.
Keep away from here.
You're coming back
with me.
Back?
Where you belong, on the ship.
No, ted.
You're having
a hallucination, lieutenant.
No. No, it's real.
It isn't.
You're coming with me.
No. Now, keep away.
Keep away from me!
No!
You're coming back!
No, i'm staying.
Let me go.
Let go of me!
I don't want to be here.
I don't want
to be here.
Ruth...
ruth.
Ruth?
Ruth.
Ruth...
ruth!
There was no ruth,
no jeannie.
What does that say?
Read it.
"The wife and daughter
of space pilot ted mason died
"early this morning
when the car that..."
don't you see, ted?
You weren't there.
They're dead.
You're alive.
I was there, paul.
I was, i was.
No, no, it just...
you took me away.
No, it isn't true.
Isn't it?
You took me away
from my wife and my home.
Well, you were both
here all the time.
He was gone!
No. We just couldn't
see him, that's all.
What are
you talking about?
I know what
it is now.
That's what i'm
talking about.
I was wrong.
It has nothing to do
with circumnavigating time.
Nothing at all.
Remember what
you thought
before you saw that
ship over there?
Alien contact-
that's what you thought.
Well, that's exactly
what's happened to us.
I thought you didn't
believe in alien contact.
Listen to me.
Neither of you were home.
That is not our ship.
Those are not our bodies.
We've been tricked.
By whom?
By whoever it
is that lives
on this planet
and doesn't want
anyone else
to live here.
Well, don't you understand?
We haven't been able
to see them,
but there are aliens here...
but aliens who aren't
strong enough to kill us
or drive us away by force.
So what can they do?
How can they keep
their planet
from being colonized?
By mind control.
By picking
our brains
and finding
the death fear
and making use of it
by-by showing our crashed ship
and us dead inside it.
Scaring us so much
that we didn't dare
take off again.
Therefore, we weren't
able to make a report
about this planet.
They even know that we can't
make a radio report
back to earth because there's
too much interference here.
A short while ago,
you didn't believe
there was any
interference.
I believe it now.
Everything that has happened
on this planet since we landed
has been a delusion.
Oh, no...
no, no, this happened.
It happened.
It was a delusion.
Even mason's
disappearance?
Why not?
If they could make us believe
that we saw a crashed ship
and our bodies inside that ship,
they could make us believe
anything.
It isn't out there, then?
Oh, maybe you can see it.
You may still be able
to touch it again,
but that doesn't prove
it's really there.
What's going to prove
it isn't there, paul?
that you're right now?
What's going to prove that?
Us... going up...
all the way back to earth.
Proving there's
nothing
keeping us here
but deluded fear.
Wait a minute!
Wait, wait a minute.
Now, what if
you're wrong?
I'm right.
You thought you
were right before.
You were ready to keep
us here indefinitely,
you were so sure.
Are you positive
enough now
to risk all our
lives, paul?
Yes, i am.
I'm not.
Put it away, carter.
Now, you're not going
to take us up.
Remember what you said?
If we stayed here,
we'd freeze to death
or starve to death...
you'd never see
earth again.
He's right, mike.
That's no answer.
Put it away.
We've got to go up.
Oh, god...
have mercy on our souls.
All right.
Here we go.
Twenty.
Forty...
we're out!
Well...
you were right.
He was right.
Boy, if ever i see
anything glitter
on that viewer again,
i'll just keep
my big mouth shut!
Yeah... i was right.
Hey, what are you...
what are you doing?
What?
Preparing
for a landing.
What?
Well, now that we know
what it is,
there's no reason
we shouldn't go back.
No reason?!
What, are you out
of your mind?!
We have orders, carter-
pick up specimens
of foreign life.
We're going to pick them up.
No, we're not!
Carter, get
your hands off!
You idiot!
Let go of that thing!
You did it!
What'd i tell you?!
We're going
to crash!
No!
We're going
to die!
No!
No, we're not going
to die.
Carter, auxiliary engines!
It's no use.
Carter!
Carter, you fool!
Auxiliaries on!
I don't understand.
Shut up!
You haven't even got the guts
to fight for your own life.
Are we still
going down?
You bet
we're going down.
And when we get there,
you'll see that ship
is no longer there-
gone, vanished!
Because it was never there
in the first place.
Air springs.
Yes, sir.
Get set for touchdown.
It's gone.
How do we know
we're facing
the right direction,
captain?
Gone, captain?
All right, it's
still there.
That doesn't
mean anything.
I'll tell you
what it means.
It means you're wrong.
There's an explanation
for this somewhere.
I don't know what
it is, but i'm
going to find it.
Well, you'll
never know.
You know why,
captain?
Because we've got
to go back up again.
And this time,
we're really going to crash!
No, we're not.
We're not going
to crash...
because we already
have crashed.
What are you talking about?
Stop fighting
it, captain.
You're all out
of explanations.
There's only
one left, and
you know it.
I know nothing of the kind.
Oh, yes, you do.
Carter was home.
That telegram
was really there.
I was with my wife
and my daughter
because i'm
just like them now.
No, no.
Accept it, captain.
Stop trying to prove
that we're alive.
We are alive.
There's something
happening here-
i don't know what it is, but
there's an explanation for it.
I've given you
the explanation.
I don't accept it!
We're going to go over it again
until i find the answer!
Can't you see?
That's what we've
been doing-
going over itagain.
Let us go, paul.
No.
We're dead, paul.
Let us die.
We're going to
go over it again,
do you hear?
We're going to
go over it again!
We're going to go
over itagain!
Captain.
Something glittered
down there.
It was at, uh,
255-417.
I don't see anything.
Picture of a man
who will not see anything
he does not choose to see,
including his own death.
A man of such indomitable will
that even the two men
beneath his command
are not allowed
to see the truth:
Which truth is that they are
no longer among the living...
that the movements they make
and the words they speak
have all been made and spoken
countless times before
and will be made and spoken
countless times again,
perhaps even unto eternity.
Picture of a latter-day
flying dutchman
sailing into the twilight zone.
Next, we delve into the realm
of american folklore,
and through the offices
of a fine writer
named earl hamner jr.,
we peruse a little witchcraft
and bring you a story called,
"jess-belle."
This exercise in terror
and talismans
stars anne francis
and james best.
? form a ring, circle right
with a pretty little thing?
? now break that ring
with a corner swing?
? go back home, do-sl-do...?
Elly!
Elly! Elly! Elly!
I ain't never seen no cat
with spots like that.
A witch.
That cat was a witch.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org