Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Viva clemente!
Viva clemente! Viva clemente!
Viva! Viva!
You hear that?
Do you hear that
"viva clemente, viva clemente
viva, viva, viva, viva,
viva, viva, viva, viva"?
Viva
clemente!
Viva!
To the revolution.
Ah, do you know...
do you know why i laugh?
I laugh
because
there is
so much... so much stuff
bubbling inside of me,
and i didn't know
in the beginning...
i didn't know when
this moment would happen,
how i would react to it,
what i would do-
if i would drink or laugh
or get drunk or...
i didn't know.
What makes a man drunk- wine,
or that mob screaming his name?
I'm going to make
a toast to you.
I'm going
to toast
my friends.
To cristo,
the bold one...
to d'alessandro,
the dedicated one...
to tabal,
the quiet one...
to garcia,
the strong one.
To the four
lieutenants of
the revolution.
To the new heads
of the government.
All right,
bring him in.
We'll start
with that.
This is the face
of ramos clemente,
a year ago, a beardless,
nameless worker of the dirt
who plodded behind a mule,
furrowing someone else's land.
And he looked up
at a hot central american sun
and he pledged the impossible:
He made a vow that
he would lead an avenging army
against the tyranny
that put the ache in his back
and the anguish in his eyes.
And now, one year later,
the dream of the impossible
has become a fact.
In just a moment, we will
look deep into this mirror
and see the aftermath
of a rebellion...
in the twilight zone.
You
disappoint me.
You recognize
that man?
That one- the
one in the picture.
Arrogance
in full braid.
What is he now?
Hey.
Hey...
what is he know?
He's an old man
in a dirty uniform.
What is it you want
with me, clemente?
Not what i want...
not what i want.
Not whatiwant!
Whattheywant!
Notwhat i want,
whattheywant!
Whattheywant!
But i'm not going
to place you
against the wall.
No, no, that's a cheap
death for underlings.
The firing squad
is for followers!
Not for leaders!
No, no, general. You're
too good. Too good.
For you, i'm going
to strip you naked
and cover you
with honey.
Then i'm going to tie
you to the ground
under a hot sun,
and then i'm going
to let the ants at you.
And, every time
that you scream,
i'm going
to drink wine.
And every time that
you pray for mercy,
i'm going to
laugh out loud.
Because i want you to take
a long time to die, de cruz.
One part death for every
acre of land you stole,
then one part death
for every morsel you took
out of a peasant's mouth,
and one part death
for every voice that
you stifled by decree.
I will not oblige
you, clemente,
with a cry or a plea.
You can strip off my flesh
because it is there for you,
and easily done.
But my manhood...
my manhood,
you greasy little peon,
this... this is as far
from you as the moon.
Greasy peon, eh?
Greasy...
he's to be judged,
not tormented.
Heis the animal.
And you
are not, eh?
You are the
purists, hmm?
The saviors, the
avenging angels, eh?
Gentlemen... you will
soon be disillusioned.
You are me.
You are de cruz.
You are battista, you are
castro, you are trujillo.
You are the keepers
of the grab bags.
Oh, you can
wave your flags
and put up
your statues
and embrace
all the people,
the oldest and
the youngest, but...
we are all
the same breed.
We are the spoilers.
We care
for no one...
no one
but ourselves.
He presents
his case,
and we are his
best witnesses.
We corroborate
everything he says.
You cannot help
but do it.
You think this room...
the people out there...
you think these are
the fruits of victory?
The spoils.
They are simply
a legacy, clemente-
what i pass on to you.
Power you shall have,
general clemente.
Certainly power,
enough to make you giddy.
But there are other things
in the inheritance,
and you'll find them
soon enough:
Fear...
fear.
The chief legacy.
Fear of
assassination...
fear of disloyalty,
fear of rebellion,
fear of a...
another clemente
hiding in the hills.
God help you.
God pity you.
Take him out,
now!
I see you have
found my mirror, too.
An old woman
brought it to me
ten years ago, when
i'd first taken over.
She said it was magic.
She said,
by looking into it,
i could see the faces
of my assassins.
Maybe she's right.
Look deep,
general clemente.
Find out who
your assassins are.
You will see them
in that mirror.
You will see them in the mirror.
In the dark corners.
You will see them
in the crowd.
You will see them everywhere.
Cristo, how many
prisoners are there?
Here in the capital?
Well, a thousand.
Have them shot
immediately.
But... the trials.
We don't have
time for trials.
But for murder
there is plenty of time,
hmm?
What are you,
some kind of a chameleon?
What is this ease with
which you strip off one color
and put on
another?
You turn
my stomach.
Murderers can never be murdered.
Murderers can only be executed!
Cristo...
take tabal
and garcia.
Carry out
that order.
Gladly.
A mirror that reflects
the faces of my assassins.
Isn't that intriguing?
Isn't that
intriguing,
d'alessandro?
You know, i had no idea
that some...
you!
It was you!
It was you.
Ramos...
i saw you.
Ramos, what's
the matter?
I saw you in the
mirror, with a gun.
What gun?
You sound like
some demented man.
I would have to be you.
I should have known
that it would be you,
you moralist,
you dedicated one.
It would have
to be you.
I knew!
Why are they so quiet?
They scream for justice
and, when you
give it to them,
they're suddenly bored,
like an audience
at a cheap burlesque.
The entertainment
must be varied.
Every five minutes,
must be a costume change.
But i know them very well.
You fill their stomachs,
and you empty their brains.
They have cheap tastes
and short memories.
What's the matter, tabal?
Is there something
that's sitting heavy on you?
That.
That sits heavy on me.
That is what sits heavy on me!
And the death of a man
who was my friend.
That puts a hook
into my heart.
D'alessandro...
an assassin.
And that is
the worst lie of all!
That was a lie, ramos.
He was no assassin.
What's the matter?
What's going on?
Oh. Still at it, huh?
Leave it be, ramos.
You can talk yourself
into an illusion.
You can make yourself
believe anything.
What is it, ramos?
Well...
what is it?
The mirror
again?
No, no.
You think you
saw something
in the mirror?
No, no. No, i'm concerned
about de cruz.
I'm worried
Tabal,
take garcia.
Go over to
the prison.
Take a look
at de cruz
and report
back to me.
Report back to you what?
About his health?
I'm concerned whether
he's being properly guarded.
Yes, sir.
Do you have a message
for de cruz?
Should we tell him
that he was right
about the fears?
That there are
assassins under the bed,
in the shadows,
and all around
the room?
Tabal...
you have your freedom
and you have your life,
but you have them both
on my sufferance.
Don't throw them away.
Yes, general.
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
What are you doing,
sleeping?
This is general clemente.
That's correct.
This is urgent.
I want the prison.
No, i want the front gate,
not the office.
That's right.
This is general clemente.
In a few moments, two men
are going to arrive there-
spies- and they are
to be shot on sight.
Their names are
tabal and garcia.
I know who they are!
And i knowwhatthey are!
And they are to be shot!
That's right.
You let me know
when it's done.
Cristo...
sir?
Any complaints?
None.
None, eh?
Why should there be?
A pie cut into
two pieces
is better than
a pie cut in five.
Pie... pie...
this is no pie.
These are the
lives of friends.
They were... they
were very close.
We were very close.
You know that.
We were like brothers.
See, that's what
i don't understand-
i don't understand
how it is
that i could
crush them out,
and i don't
think about it,
i don't feel it.
I just crush them.
Men cannot be brothers
in these settings.
You must expect this
from now on.
When a man
has power,
he has enemies,
and now you
have enemies.
Enemies, yes,
i understand that,
but must my friends
be my enemies?
From now on, ramos,
you have no friends.
You have followers
and you have competitors.
That is the breakdown
of the world now.
You must live
with it.
How do you classify
yourself, cristo?
Myself?
I am a follower,
general.
A follower...
for how long?
How long?
How long will you be a follower?
Until some quiet moment
when my back is turned?
No...
only until that moment
when you prove to me
that you cannot lead.
Only until that moment
when i think perhaps...
perhaps what?
Perhaps i am stronger than you.
You'll be eaten by worms
before that moment comes.
What is it?
Take a drink of wine.
It will make you
feel better.
That's right.
Have a glass of wine.
I'll feel better.
Well, go ahead.
Have a glass of wine.
It will make you
sleep better.
Yes, it would make me
sleep better, wouldn't it?
For how long?
For how long will
it make me sleep?
Maybe for all
eternity, eh?
You are demented.
You've gone crazy.
Why did
you do that?
Because i'm crazy.
And because
i'm allergic to poison.
I also have
a yen to live.
Yes?
Yes, he's here.
When?
All right.
I will tell him.
That was the gatehouse
of the prison.
The guards have shot
tabal and garcia.
They are both dead.
And what shall we do now,
cristo?
Shall we mourn for them?
They were our friends,
weren't they?
But, then again,
they can't be our friends
because they can't be friends
andassassins.
They cannot be both.
That was your point,
wasn't it, eh?
Ramos!
There was no poison
in that wine.
I had nothing
like that in mind.
Nothing
of the sort.
You are imagining things.
Look! I'll show you.
It's an illusion, you see?
It's just a mirror.
An ordinary
mirror.
But it's glass, you see?
Just glass!
Now you will be all alone.
Now i'm afraid...
you'll be
very lonely.
But you have just killed
a better man,
ramos.
General clemente.
I am father tomas.
Yes?
You will forgive
me, general,
but this must
be said now.
What must be said?
The executions- they have
been going on now for a week.
The people are appalled.
Is this what we are to expect
from the new regime?
I have enemies, father.
I have enemies.
And, as long as i have enemies,
the executions will continue.
They'll continue 24 hours
a day, seven days a week.
And, if that disturbs
the people,
well, then, if that's...
then what?
Then let them do
something about it.
Let them go in the caves.
Let them starve for a year!
Let them raise
an army like i did!
I don't care what they do!
General clemente,
the victory is not
so sweet, is it?
Instead of the flavor of wine,
it's the taste
of ashes.
Father...
i can't stand it.
I can't live like this.
I'm frightened.
From morning till night,
from night till morning,
i hold my breath
and i keep looking in back of me
to see if there is something.
I want to know, why do
i have so many enemies?
It is the story
of all tyrants, general.
They have but one real enemy,
and this is the one
they never recognize...
until too late.
God help you.
The last assassin.
And they never learn.
They never seem to learn.
Ramos clemente,
a would-be god in dungarees
strangled by an illusion-
that will-o'-the-wisp mirage
that dangles from the sky
in front of the eyes of
all ambitious men, all tyrants.
And any resemblance
to tyrants living or dead
is hardly coincidental,
whether it be here
or in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
It's traditional
in the great american western
the climax of any given story
is the gun down
on the main street.
Next week, montgomery pittman
has written a story
in which we have our gun down,
and then go on from there.
It's a haunting little item
about a top gun as he was alive,
and his operation after death.
This is one for rainy nights
and power failures.
But, wherever you watch it,
i think
it will leave its imprint.
There's an economic
upswing coming.
How will it affect you?
To find out,
write for your free booklet:
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org