Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
I'm jordan herrick.
I have an appointment
with miss morris.
Come in, please.
Thank you.
This way,
please.
Thank you.
I'll tell
miss morris you're here.
1940.
I thought i told you
to stay in your room.
I'm not going to stand by
and watch it happen this time.
You will because i say you will.
Jordan herrick,
syndicated columnist
whose work appears
in more
than a hundred newspapers.
By nature a cynic,
a disbeliever
caught for the moment
by a lovely vision.
He knows the vision he's seen
is no dream.
She is pamela morris,
renowned movie star,
whose name is a household word
and whose face is
known to millions.
What mr. Herrick does not know
is that he has also just looked
into the face
of the twilight zone.
Mr. Herrick?
Miss morris... hello.
I've kept
you waiting.
Oh, no, it really
doesn't matter.
It does matter,
and i am sorry.
Oh, but i do
so love the pool.
Am i forgiven?
Of course, i...
i should be asking your
forgiveness for this intrusion.
Please relax.
Thank you.
I think
you're very nice.
Miss morris,
how old are you?
I must say, mr. Herrick,
you are a very direct man.
You're not offended?
Why should i be?
I have producers, directors;
you have editors-
all very
demanding people.
Besides, a woman in my position
can't afford to have secrets.
I'm certainly relieved
to hear that.
I was afraid you'd be offended.
You have nothing
to be afraid of here.
There, that's better.
Now, why don't
you tell me
how old
you think i am?
Oh, now, that's
hardly fair.
Oh, do,
come on, now.
Well?
You're very beautiful.
That wasn't the question.
You don't look any older now
than you did in that painting.
I was only a child
when i posed for bersonne.
I was so frightened of him.
The world was so bright
and new to me,
and he was
so wild and creative.
I've never met
anyone like him.
His genius enabled him
to project
the "flowering
of a fragile blossom,"
as he put it.
Would you like
some coffee?
Yes, coffee, thank you.
Would you like
something in it?
Cognac? Whiskey?
No, thanks,
i'll take it black.
I thought
newspaper people
were heavy drinkers.
That's a myth.
My mother,
mrs. Draper.
Jordan herrick.
How do you do?
He's a newspaper
man, mother.
How do you do?
Sit down and
have some tea.
With my mother
it is tea
this precise time
every afternoon.
Me, it's coffee.
Mrs. Draper, you must feel
very proud to have a daughter
as famous
as pamela morris.
Mother never did wholly approve
of my career.
Believe me, mr. Herrick,
i had little choice
in the matter.
She thinks
i'm too headstrong.
Dedicated
is the word.
You still are, pamela.
Was she always as beautiful
as she is now?
Always.
A mother's loyalty.
As a matter of
fact, mr. Herrick,
it is the truth.
Perhaps from the mother,
i'll learn the real age
of the daughter.
Isn't age relative?
Besides, didn't i promise to
reveal all to you, mr. Herrick?
Mr. Herrick!
Mother, would you mind seeing
if charlotte has things
under control in the kitchen?
Pleased to have met you,
mrs. Draper.
Good-bye,
mr. Herrick.
Forgive her, but...
she's getting old.
I was hoping she'd give me
some ideas for my article.
No, her mind wanders.
Her memory becomes
increasingly distorted.
Shall we finish
our coffee
on the terrace?
I'm sure there's a breeze
out there.
Isn't it lovely
out here?
I often sit here
by the hour,
watching the clouds
and the birds.
At night,
i watch the stars.
Yes, it
is lovely.
Oh, but that isn't
what interests you, is it-
my nocturnal habits,
how i dream out here?
I could work it
into my story...
the question of age
is the big thing, isn't it?
I'm 38, jordan.
May i call you jordan?
Yes, of course, please.
Is 38 terribly old?
The years have never
been kinder to anyone.
What a nice thing
to say.
I mean it.
What have you got there?
Some notes-
dates, mostly.
Do they concern me?
Yes.
According to this...
i know, you read a column
by one of those
stupid, jealous women.
If you are 38,
how could you
have starred
in a movie
made in 1935?
I can't believe it-
jordan herrick taken in
by the printed word.
Tell me, do you believe
everything you read?
The movie wastrails west.
Darling, it couldn't
have been me.
I would've been ten years old.
Don't you see?
It's an old mistake
i've run across before.
According to our files,
your costar was john bradley.
You were in
love with him.
I never even met him.
Your files are in error,
and it does happen, you know.
In 1935,
you know, i don't think
i'd even seen a movie yet.
We were poor,
living in iowa.
My father's business
was failing.
It wasn't until 1940
that i set out for hollywood...
a starstruck girl in my teens
following the trail blazed
by so many other hopefuls.
But i was lucky.
You must have been.
You madequeen of the nile
with charles danforth in 1940.
You were 15.
Darling, juliet was 12.
But 15?
Now, is that
so much harder to believe
than my being 38 today?
No one knew
i was 15.
I matured very early.
I suppose that picture
inspired the decor?
I call it
early egyptian,
though i suppose
it is rather silly, but...
it was my first big break.
Well, i'm just glad
that it wasn't a horror picture,
or i just might have the place
full of caskets.
Do you know...
the fact is that i...
i still do feel
just about 15.
I really do.
No?
With you sitting
there, i feel new
and breathless
and just 21.
Oh, i want to savor
all there is
in this life, jordan.
Is it wrong
to feel that way?
No, no, it's not wrong.
I'm being foolish,
saying these things.
And you're not
being foolish.
I so seldom get
a chance to...
speak my mind
or air my dreams.
And yours...
what must
you think of me?
I wanted to do that.
And you wanted me
to do it, too.
You're sweet...
and very real.
But you must go now.
Why?
Because i say so.
We'll see each other again
if you'd like.
What about tonight?
Dinner, hmm?
All right.
Why don't we say... 8:00?
Why don't
we say 8:00?
Mr. Herrick!
Hello, mrs. Draper.
Mr. Herrick...
yes?
You are a fine
young man.
Well, thank you,
mrs. Draper.
It is not an
idle compliment.
Are you going to
see her again?
Yes, tonight.
We're having dinner.
No, you must
not do that.
You must never
see her again.
Why not?
She's older
than you think.
Yes, she told me
how old she was.
Yes, i know.
Thirty-eight.
Well, isn't that true?
Mr. Herrick, you
wouldn't believe me
if i told you how
old ithinkshe is.
You think? Don't you know?
No... not really.
But you're her mother.
No.
I'm not her mother.
I am her daughter!
I don't know when
i've had such a wonderful time.
You've been so quiet
all evening.
What is it?
Oh, it's... something
your mother said.
Now, i don't believe
it, but just...
just sticks in my mind.
Well, tell me.
She said that you
are her mother.
Her mother?
Her mother.
Jordan, darling,
you must believe me.
My mother is disturbed.
I'm sure it's because
she feels responsible
for my father's death.
You see, they were returning
home from a party ten years ago.
She was driving the car,
and it went off the road,
and my father was killed.
I'm sorry.
Ever since then,
she's been furtive, suspicious,
imagining all kinds
of terrible things.
I've tried to help her-
really, i have-
but the doctors say
it's hopeless.
She really should be put away,
but i haven't had...
i never should've
brought it up.
Now, let's
forget about it.
All right.
We'll talk
about something else.
After all, we've been talking
about me, and...
now you know about my mother.
What about your life?
Very dull...
up until now.
All right, then tell me
where you're from.
Chicago. I still
live there.
I've played chicago.
The wells theater.
Have you really?
I've loved
every moment of it.
I really have.
Shall i see you tomorrow?
Tomorrow.
Krueger.
Jordan herrick in hollywood?
Yeah, put him on.
Hi, jordy, glad you called.
Got another job for you
if you're through playing
with that little femme fatale.
Not yet. Not for a while, krueg.
I want you to do something.
Get out the file on a picture
calledqueen of the nile.
Which one?
What do you mean, which one?
You're a little young for this.
They made two of them.
The first one, a silent,
i think.
Around 1920,
maybe a little later.
All right, get them both.
I'll hang on.
Right.
Hey, you there?
Yeah.
What was the name of the girl
who starred in the original?
Constance taylor.
Anyway, she starred
in most of it.
There was an accident
during the last day of shooting.
Cave-in in a tomb in egypt.
They never found her.
Never found her?
No, it was the end
of a very promising career.
As a matter of fact,
i met constance taylor
when i was about your age.
Extraordinary woman.
How do you mean,
"extraordinary"?
Well, she was ageless.
She'd been a reigning beauty
in the days
of the flora dora girls.
That was before your time.
She was arealfemme fatale.
She'd been married
half a dozen times
before the accident in egypt.
Sounds like pamela morris,
the same history.
Very much the same,
as a matter of fact.
You got a picture
of this taylor girl?
Yeah.
Compare it to a picture
of pamela morris.
Yeah, jordy?
Well?
They look alike,
but then, they played
the same kind of parts.
Same makeup, same type costume.
Krueger, the wells theater,
the old wells theater-
what year
did they tear that down?
Oh, sometime back in the '20s.
Why, jordy?
Oh, never mind.
Not until i'm real sure.
In the meantime, get me a list
of all the men who were ever
involved with pamela morris.
Get me every press release,
every clipping you have on her,
got it?
Sounds interesting.
May sound fantastic.
Well?
It's all true,
mr. Herrick.
It'salltrue.
But don't show
it to her.
Leave here at once.
Is this pamela?
Yes, yes.
Please, mr. Herrick,
you don't know
how it is.
She had many
different names.
But she hasn't changed
in 40 years.
40 years?
At least70years-
the total sum of my life.
Can you imagine
what it was like
to see her always so fresh
and beautiful
while my mirrored image grew
seared and yellowed with age?
How old is she, really?
She's ageless.
Perhaps she's eternal.
What is the secret?
What woman would not
sell her soul to know?
It has something
to do
with this beetle...
with egypt.
The scarabael beetle.
Egyptian symbol
of everlasting life.
Tell me, if you hate her
so much...
why do i stay?
What else
could i do?
After pamela
and my husb...
go on, tell me
the rest.
No, i cannot.
You must go now!
What about the other men,
john bradley, charles danforth?
Don't ask
about them!
Mrs. Draper,
listen to me...
mr. Herrick!
How nice you
dropped in.
Has my mother
entertained you?
What wild tales
did you spin?
I don't think they're
wild tales at all.
For example, the
wells theater,
where you played...
was torn down
in the '20s.
You may leave us, mother.
Charlotte will prepare
your tea in your room.
Pamela, please!
I wish to speak
to mr. Herrick alone.
Your coffee.
You were saying...
don't you think
it's time we had
anhonesttalk?
What do you want?
Money?
No.
Just the truth.
And you shall have it.
What?
What is that?
The rare egyptian scarab.
The secret of eternity.
Where did you...
get it?
From the pharaohs
who understood its power.
Pharaohs? Hmm?
I told you, mr. Herrick,
i was once queen of the nile.
You, uh...
i told you never
to come in
until i called
you, viola...
ifyou want to
live another day.
Get rid of
it, quickly.
You must be
mr. Jackson.
Yes, i called
the other day.
And i told you
to come out when you could.
Did you think i'd forget?
We'll have coffee
in the living room.
Everybody knows pamela morris,
the beautiful
and eternally young movie star.
Or does she have another name
even more famous,
an egyptian name
from centuries past?
It's best
not to be too curious,
lest you wind up
like jordan herrick-
a pile of dust and old clothing
discarded
in the endless eternity
of the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next time out, we do a little
biting of the hand that feeds
and we tell you
a delightful yarn
that has to do with television.
Not normal television, mind you,
but a wacky tale
about a tv set
that predicts the future.
It's written my martin goldsmith
and stars three
eminently talented people
who make their first visit
to the zone:
Joan blondell, william demarest
and sterling holloway.
On thetwilight zonenext time,
"what's in the box."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org