Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
All right, lance, move away
from the bar.
I've had all i can take of you.
Whatever you say, father.
When you were a boy,
you hated your brother...
your move, professor.
How's that?
It's your move.
Oh, yes, of course.
You are filled
with hatred, lance...
that's my piece,
you're black.
Rebellion of youth...
oh, yes, yes.
You're a man.
You're going to have
to face up to...
very good, very good job.
Green, green cool grass.
The touch, the smell
of green, cool grass.
Now, brought to you
for the first time
in green,
the new chlorophyll cigarette.
The smoke that doesn't smell
like tobacco
but smells good-
green, cool
like grass.
Yes, green is brought
to you...
what's the matter
with you, professor?
What's the matter
with all you people?
Are you hypnotized
or something?
Going out of your
blessed minds?
If you don't care
for our program, mr. Lindsay
you can request
a different channel.
What difference does that make,
what channel you got?
The new chlorophyll cigarette
can make that statement.
And it's 54, termite jones...
termite jones,
my hero...
termite jones.
He makes it, you...
the prettiest song
in the world.
Isn't that wonderful?
Just ruining it, completely
ruining a beautiful song...
? ho, ho, ho, you and me?
? little brown jug,
how i love thee?
? ho, ho, ho, you and me...?
If you act now, you can get
your acreage in splendor flats
for the fantastically
unbelievable price
of 25 cents an acre a week.
Just look
at this land, folks.
It's flat, it's gray,
it's undeveloped, but...
it will be
a veritable oasis...
a verit...
an oasis, yes.
Only green, the new green...
oh, yes, let's all roll
in the grass
the green, cool hills of grass.
25 operators just waiting
to take your call, folks.
Hey, mr. Lindsay,
what's that?
That's a radio, boy.
Yeah, what's it do?
Don't you know
what a radio is, boy?
Well, sure, but i've never seen
one like that before.
No one ever saw one quite
like that.
Because that's a very special
sort of radio.
In its day, circa 1935
its type was one of the most
elegant consoles on the market.
Now, with
its fabric-covered speakers
its peculiar yellow dial,
its serrated knobs
it looks
quaint and a little strange.
Mr. Ed lindsay is going to
find out how strange very soon
when he tunes in
to the twilight zone.
Careful of that door.
That's it.
We're going to take it up
these steps here, boy.
Well, what do you
got there, ed?
What's it look like?
A radio.
Now let's put it down here.
Put it down, boy.
I remember that.
I thought you'd thrown it out
years ago.
I never throw anything away
that's worth keeping.
Need any help, ed?
Oh, no, no, no.
I wouldn't, i wouldn't want
to disturb you, professor.
Pick it up by
the legs, boy.
That's it.
Now, careful.
Take it right. That's
it. That's it, boy.
Right up here.
That's it, boy.
Got to plug it in here.
Think it
still works?
Sure. Course it works.
They made things
to last in those days.
That's pretty wonderful,
all right.
Go buy yourself a switchblade.
And so, ladies and gentlemen
with the strains of
"getting sentimental over you"
tommy dorsey and his orchestra
bid you all
a very pleasant good night
direct from the princeton campus
in a broadcast
of the summer swing festival
and listen to that applause.
But before we sign off,
we invite you to stay tuned
for major bowes
and his famous amateur hour.
This is station wpda
in cedarburg, new jersey
returning you to...
good evening, friends.
Once again, the wheel of chance
or faith, as you please,
is about to revolve.
And as the barker standing
at the wheel of fortune
says, "around, around she goes
"and where she stops,
nobody knows."
Now, does anybody know
what will happen
when these young people...
well, what do you want?
I just thought you'd like
to know that dinner's ready.
I ain't hungry.
You know how mrs. Nielson feels about...
oh, all right,
all right, all right.
Ever since i can remember,
women have been running my life.
Now do this, do that,
come to dinner,
don't come to dinner...
frankly, mr. Lindsay, i don't
care whether you starve to death.
I just want to make sure
that it's on purpose
and not because you'd forgotten
that food is available.
I'm not that old yet.
Mr. Lindsay.
What?
You're humming
at table.
What was that, anyway?
What?
That melody, it went, um...
it's called "i'm getting
sentimental over you."
I heard it on the radio
this afternoon.
That's an old tune,
isn't it?
Yeah, tommy dorsey,
they-
playing it
direct from the...
direct?
Tommy dorsey's dead.
You don't say.
Yeah, he died
a few years ago.
What about major bowes?
Who?
Major bowes.
Never heard of him.
No, you wouldn't.
Well, he's dead, too.
I heard both major bowes
and tommy dorsey this afternoon
on the radio.
Couldn't be.
Couldn't be?
How is it a man
with such a tiny brain
could have such a big mouth?
Now, wait just a minute...
now, please,
mr. Bragg
i think what
mr. Lindsay means
or what he's
trying to say
is that a local radio station
was broadcasting recordings
of some of the old programs.
They didn't have tape back
in those days.
No, but they did have wire,
and before that, disks.
I'll tell you
what else they had-
good music,
hmm, professor?
Plays that meant something,
magic, real magic...
i doubt it.
You doubt it.
Mr. Bragg doubts it.
Mr. Bragg,
who watches television
until his brain
turns into oatmeal
and his eyes roll down his face
into his beer-
mr. Bragg, the modern man,
doubts it.
Well, i'll show you,
i'll show you.
Where's that portable radio?
Really, mr. Lindsay...
where is that portable
radio? In the kitchen.
Now, that guy's nuts,
that's all. He's nuts.
Oh, miss brown,
you can thank your lucky stars
you never married that man.
Now, mr. Bragg,
we'll show you.
We'll just prove it, right here,
right in here.
Well, it was right in here.
I'm sorry,
i can't wait.
Gunfireis on
in exactly four minutes.
Gunfire,
we can't miss that.
Ed, remember
what station it was?
The station?
No, i, i...
yes, yes, you know,
the announcer said something
about... station wpda,
that it...
what can you expect on a dinky
little radio like this, hmm?
Why don't you come up
to my room?
Listen to it on a real radio.
Come on.
Come on, professor.
Let's go up,
vinnie.
I'd like to hear
that program.
Well, it certainly
is a handsome thing.
Can't seem to get it.
Maybe they're having
transmitting trouble.
Why don't we phone
the station?
That's
a good idea.
That's an excellent idea.
Let's get hold of
information and find out...
here, ed.
Thank you, professor.
Information, would you please
give me the number of wpda?
That's a radio station.
Wpda, yes, yes.
Heard major bowes.
You remember major bowes, hmm?
"Round and round
she goes, and...
and where she stops..."
uh, uh, yes... yes.
Oh?
Oh.
Well, what'd
she say?
Oh, the operator said
according to her supervisor
that wpda had been out
of business for 13 years.
Well, maybe you had
some other state
or even another country.
This thing has shortwave,
doesn't it?
Uh, but the announcer said,
uh, cedarburg, cedarburg...
maybe it's...
it isn't listed
in the radio section.
I heard it.
I heard it, i know i did.
Professor, is it so impossible?
Impossible?
Well, that's
a dangerous sort of a word
to use nowadays, vinnie.
We take things for granted today
that we called impossible
just a few years ago.
Let's call it highly unlikely.
Then what did i hear?
I don't know, ed.
Ed...
professor...
do you really think
he heard those programs?
Well, vinnie
i believe
he thinks he did.
Now, we take you directly
to the white house
in washington, dc, for an
address by the president
of the united states,
franklin delano roosevelt.
Since my annual message to
the congress on january 4 last
i have not addressed the general
public over the air.
In the many weeks
since that time,
the congress has devoted its...
professor!
Professor!
Vinnie! Vinnie!
I've got it.
I've really got it.
Come quick. Quick.
Why bother? You won't hear
nothing but static.
Oh, professor, don't encourage
that poor man.
Yeah, but...
oh, he's gone completely
psychological.
Oh, my.
Well, i'm sorry, i've lost it.
It was tommy dorsey.
He was playing "i'm getting
sentimental over you."
It was soft and slow,
real pretty.
But i've lost it.
Why do i lose it every time
somebody else comes around?
Why, professor?
Well, you just
keep on trying, ed.
We're bound
to hear it eventually.
Sure, sure...
we're, we're bound to...
bound to hear it.
What do you want?
Oh, nothing, ed.
I just thought
we might talk.
Do you mind?
No, talk away,
just don't come too close.
I might start
climbing the walls
barking like a dog.
That's what you all think.
"Poor old ed,
he's gone ding-dong."
No, that's not
what i think.
If you'll sit down
and be quiet
i'll tell you
what i think.
Sure, i'll... i'll sit.
Right now,
ed lindsay
you're just about
the meanest, sourest
most cantankerous old man
on the face of the earth.
Thanks.
And i'm not
much better.
We've been living
like two hermits
under the same roof
for the last 20 years.
Staring at each other
every morning
day in, day out
20 long years,
wondering what went wrong.
I don't know what
you're talking about...
oh, yes, you do.
You know exactly
what i'm talking about
but you won't admit it.
We were going
to be married...
oh, for heaven's sake...
don't get
your back up.
I'm not trying
to change anything.
I'm just talking.
We met
in this boarding house in 1940.
And it was here
that you proposed.
I wanted
to set the date
but your mother was ill,
you remember
and so you
decided to wait.
And that's just
what we did.
We waited and waited
until, by the time
your mother died...
it was too late.
Vinnie, i'm not
going to listen to...
don't interrupt me.
I've got to get this thing said.
Oh, i know you don't care
anything about me now.
I'm just a silly woman
who watches television
dyes her hair, grows old.
You don't even...
like me anymore.
And i don't
blame you.
You're a bachelor
set in your ways.
You can't change what you are
and neither can i.
We had our chance
and missed it, ed.
But i'll tell you
one thing that's true
and i know it's true.
You did love me
as much as a man
ever loved a woman.
Didn't you?
Yes, vinnie.
That's true. I did, yes.
And now you love what we were
what we might
have become together.
So just about this time
every year-
it would have been
our anniversary-
you start getting unhappy.
You want to go
back to 1940
and start
all over again.
Why do you think
you keep hearing
"getting sentimental over you"
on the radio?
That was our song, ed.
And those programs-
we used to listen
to them together...
in the dark.
I'd forgotten.
When you hear
those programs
you're like
a young man again
with all of your life
ahead of you
but it isn't so, ed.
It's all over between us.
We missed our chance.
We can't go back.
You think it's all
in my mind, don't you?
You think i'm just imagining...
ed.
...that i hear the radio.
That's not true at all.
Get out of here, vinnie.
Get out of here.
And let me alone.
Just let me alone.
Well, portland, here we are
back in allen's alley.
Say, the senator's home tonight.
His hound dog is curled up
there under the porch, see it?
Somebody, i say,
somebody knocked.
Drag-on's the name,
senator drag-on...
i know, you're from dixie.
When eat i crackers in bed,
i only eat georgia crackers.
When i leave new york harbor,
i take the south ferry.
Now, wait a minute...
? way down upon
the swanee river.?
I'm singing swanee song!
Well, i know
what you're singing.
Delivery boy.
How about a game
of checkers, ed?
Oh, no, no, no.
"Let's pretend" is on in
five minutes, then there's...
would you like some lemonade?
Lemonade? Nope.
No, no, no.
Say, what's that funny
looking thing, huh?
You know, when i first started
listening to radio again
i kept wondering whatever
happened to the picture tube.
The picture tube is right here.
Radio. I tell you,
radio is a world
that has to be believed
to be seen, hmm?
Where's my radio?
What happened
to my radio?
Ed, be reasonable.
Do you know
anything about it?
Ed, calm down!
Ed, i'll tell you.
Oh, you'll tell me?
I might have known.
Take away the one thing that...
well, where is it?
At the junk dealer's.
The junk dealer?
You gave my radio
to the junk dealer?!
Hey, wait a second.
What do you think
you're doing?
This is
private property.
Well, this belongs to me.
Oh, no, it don't.
We picked this
up this morning.
Now, if you want
to buy it...
well, how much, how much?
Oh, uh,
take a look at it.
That's a beautiful
piece of furniture.
How much?
Ten dollars.
It better still work,
i can tell you that.
Because if it don't,
it's going to cost you.
It's going to cost
a lot of people
if this don't still work.
Now, direct from
the aragon ballroom in chicago
tommy dorsey and his band.
Thank god.
Thank god it works.
Oh, vinnie, vinnie,
come up here, quick.
Ed, what's...?
Vinnie, tommy dorsey
from the aragon ballroom.
I know, dear, it's on
this time every thursday.
And then there's ed wynn,
and fred allen, and...
ed, what is the matter
with you?
Oh, vinnie...
vinnie, vinnie, vinnie.
Dear, dear, vinnie.
Around and around she goes
and where she stops,
nobody knows.
All ed lindsay knows
is that he desperately wanted
a second chance
and he finally got it
through a strange and wonderful
time machine called a radio
in the twilight zone.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
be sure and see the colgate-
palmolive company's
new comedy show
my sister eileen
wednesday night on many
of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org