Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
And here we have
the famous temptress
from ancient egypt-
cleopatra.
Her captivating beauty
almost brought about
the destruction of
caesar and mark anthony.
If you will follow me...
and now our next group.
Ourpiece de resistance,
if i may say so.
Here you will find
the most infamous, black-hearted
killers of all time.
It is not for the faint-hearted.
So... if there are any
who would prefer
to remain behind...
no?
Very well, then.
Oh.
Did i startle you?
This is martin senescu-
curator of
murderers' row.
You all
right, honey?
Sure, it's just
they're so real.
And i, i thought...
there's nothing
to be afraid of.
They're just
a lot of wax.
Perhaps not,
young man.
Who knows
what evil lurks
in the heart
of the man
standing next to you?
This is albert w. Hicks,
a mate on the oyster smack
v. A. Johnson.
A gentle man.
Yet one day in 1860
off the atlantic coast,
he murdered his entire crew.
Killed them with an ax
exactly like this one.
Why did he go mad?
What made him change?
And here... here we have
burke and hare,
the monsters
of their time.
But do they look
like monsters?
This is how they suffocated
their victims.
It was called... burking.
Think of the agonies
they endured.
Which one's he
talking about?
Oh, sir,
all of them.
All of them.
Surely, it is horrible
to be murdered,
as our victim here
could tell you
if-if she could talk.
But to murder!
To take a life with your hands
again and again...
and not be able to stop oneself.
Can you begin
to imagine the horror of that?
No.
Tell us
about it.
Well,
i cannot.
But somewhere
in the world
now, at this
very moment...
there is
someone who can.
Yeah?
Who?
Well, no one
knows yet,
but if his torment is
great enough
and he kills
as these poor creatures did,
then future generations
will know.
For he'll be here...
immortalized in wax.
Remembered...
as you and i will never be.
This... is henri
desire landru.
One can see
the agony
that he, too,
must have felt
as he was driven
to strangle the life
from disappointed spinsters
and lonely widows.
Landru was a master
of the garrote.
And he used a waxed cord
identical to the one
he holds there.
Get away from there!
Those figures are not
to be touched.
They're too rare
and valuable.
Besides...
the museum can't be
held responsible
for what might
happen to you.
Now, here we have
another soul in torment.
Jack the ripper.
Who was he?
And which- of
all the faces
that moved about london's
whitechapel district-
which one was his?
And why did he
feel driven
to kill those
pathetic drabs
with one sweep
of the knife
you see here?
I'm afraid we shall never know.
And as we look at hicks,
burke and hare,
landru
and jack the ripper
we see men,
as you and me.
And we can only guess
what devils pushed them
to their bloody fate.
Thank you.
Boy, let's blow
this creepy joint.
Martin lombard senescu,
a gentle man,
the dedicated curator
of murderers' row
in ferguson's wax museum.
He ponders the reasons
why ordinary men are driven
to commit mass murder.
What mr. Senescu does not know
is that the groundwork
has already been laid
for his own special kind
of madness and torment-
found only in the twilight zone.
Martin?
Yes.
I'd like to talk with you.
Oh, well,
i'll be through
in a moment.
That
can wait.
What i have to say
is rather important.
All right.
You know,
mr. Ferguson,
landru needs
a new suit.
This one is
ten years old,
and it shows it.
Is something wrong?
Well, yes and no.
I think we'd better discuss it
in the office.
Is it something
i've done?
Or haven't done?
No, nothing
like that.
Uh, sit down,
martin.
Martin,
i'm abandoning
the museum.
Hmm?
Abandoning?
I'm afraid so.
Oh.
Is this a joke, sir?
No.
Oh, mr. Ferguson.
You can't do that.
You mustn't.
Uh, i know
how you feel,
martin,
believe me, i do.
But... i'm afraid
there isn't
any choice.
I don't understand.
I've been offered
a large sum
for this property.
Some people want to build
a supermarket
here.
A supermarket?
Here, let me get you a drink.
It'll help settle you.
No, no, no. No.
Please, i don't...
when i first opened the
museum 30 years ago,
i never dreamed
i'd see this day.
But the day is
here, martin.
And we will just
have to face it.
30 years.
We've been together
a long time.
I know.
You're the best employee
a man could ever have.
The way you've run the
murderers' row exhibit-
why, i don't think you
ever missed a tour.
No, no.
Oh!
I never did, never.
How many more days?
None.
This was the last.
They begin wrecking
the building next week.
No more tours?
None at all?
I had to agree to it.
What about the figures?
I haven't
decided yet.
Mr. Ferguson,
we can open
another museum.
We can move everything
somewhere else.
We don't have
to give it up.
No, no,
i'm not as young
as i once was.
Uh, i need a rest.
Fanny and i talked...
don't, don't...
i'll do the work,
i mean it.
You won't have
to do a thing.
Not a thing!
I appreciate that, martin,
and i know you'd be
a great help, but...
it would be foolish.
But why?
Why would it
be foolish?
Let me show you something.
We are passe,
martin.
People aren't interested
in wax museums anymore.
Here. Look through it-
it's all in there.
Our attendance figures.
Our gains,
but mostly our losses.
This last year has been
the poorest of all.
You'll also find
a news story about the closing
of the grand guignol.
A sign of the times-
the handwriting on the wall.
Grand guignol.
Uh, sure you
won't have a drink?
No, thank you.
You, you see, martin,
the outside world
offers them fears
we could never match.
The ovens
at belsen and dachau
have ruined our
chamber of horrors.
People are blase,
sophisticated.
They think they've outgrown
the need to be frightened.
They live in fear
day in, day out.
It, it's
the world, martin.
No, no, martin...
it would be foolish
to open another museum.
Mr. Ferguson,
maybe...
maybe the location
is wrong.
Or maybe... maybe
it's the way
we have the
figures exhibited.
You remember
how the people came
when we worked out
the ripper's arm?
Yes.
Oh, but that was
years ago.
Mr. Ferguson...
you're not...
thinking of destroying them,
are you?
They're meant to live forever.
Martin, i tell you, i don't know
what i'm going to do!
You're forgetting something.
Forgetting something? What?
Come with me.
Please.
Martin!
Martin.
Mr. Ferguson.
Please.
Look at him.
Just look at him.
Look at his eyes.
Can't you see
the shy, frightened
little choir boy
that he once was?
Can't you see the bookkeeper
who so longed for freedom?
Why, even the flesh
feels real.
Why, it's
like flesh.
And look at the mouth.
Just look at the mouth.
Isn't it about to say something?
Why, landru was
an eloquent man.
He was full
of tenderness.
And it's there!
It's there-
it's caught right in the mouth.
Martin, what are you trying
to say?
Mr. Ferguson,
you seem to have forgotten
that these figures are the work
of the great henri guilmont-
the only ones he created
outside
of europe.
No, i haven't forgotten that.
Mr. Ferguson?
I want to buy them.
That's
ridiculous.
I don't think i could bear it
if these figures
were destroyed.
It would... it would be like
losing five close friends.
I won't destroy
them, martin, i
give you my word.
But-but where
would i store them?
I could put them
in my basement.
Yes, it's a perfect place.
Oh, for heaven's
sake, martin.
What would emma say
to having the figures
of five famous murderers
in her basement?
Emma wouldn't mind,
she would understand.
And i would put
an air conditioner
in there, i tell you that.
And a heater,
for the colder days.
I would take
care of them.
Just as i
always have.
They should be here by now.
You haven't eaten
your breakfast.
And they'll get here
when they get here.
I'm not hungry.
How long are we
going to keep them?
I have plans
to open my own museum.
But i'll have to buy them
from mr. Ferguson first.
Supposing something
happened to them.
You know, it's not like
moving furniture.
They should have
let me ride with them.
What if they drop one?
Is everything all right?
Uh... you, uh, martin senescu?
Yes.
Everything's okay.
Ah...
no bumps?
Huh?
Any bumps?
No. No bumps.
Oh, it's getting warm.
Huh?
I said it's getting warm.
You see, they're delicate.
They can't take more
than 80 degrees.
Oh. Huh-huh.
All right... wait.
Easy, please. Easy.
Easy!
Easy, easy,
oh, please.
Please, don't jiggle it.
That's it, easy.
That's-that's it.
There, there.
Fine.
Here, sign here.
All right.
One, two, three...
there.
Hmm.
Well, emma...
here they are.
Landru...
is in here.
Jack the ripper
Ooh, emma, emma,
it's going to be like
opening christmas presents.
I didn't think they were
going to be so big.
Oh, well, no, that's
just the boxes.
The figures themselves
are as big as we are.
Well, i'll have to be very
careful with the uncrating.
Mr. Senescu?
Yes.
The movers said
you were down here.
Where do you want
the air conditioner?
Ah... there. Put it
in that window,
over there. You see it?
Oh, okay.
All right.
Martin-
you bought an
air conditioner?
Yes, the figures
can't stand heat.
We had to have it.
Well, how much
did it cost?
Well...
don't worry
about it.
Well, i am
worried about it.
And i'm also worried
about how i'm going
to do the laundry
with all this lying around...
oh, emma, you can't... you
can't do the laundry here.
The... the humidity!
I mean, you don't have
a decent shirt to wear,
and it's been a week since i...
look, go to
the laundromat.
Just take it anywhere,
but leave me to
my friends, please.
You cleaned
that cape last week.
Brushed it, you mean.
It's going to need cleaning
and pressing pretty soon.
In fact,
all the clothes
are going to need it.
It's almost been a year.
Martin...
the truth of the matter is,
they all need new clothes.
The ripper comes
off worst, do
you know that?
Why, his coat is torn
right over there.
Martin!
What is it?
We're not buying them
any clothes.
Oh, but emma,
it's not just buying.
It's tailoring.
You see, they have
bodies that have...
i don't care
about their bodies!
You don't mean
that, do you?
Yes, i do.
Honestly, martin, you've been
paying more attention
to thesemurderers
than you ever did tome.
Oh, emma,
that's not true.
Then why do you spend
every minute of the day
and night down here?
Don't you see? This is
the work of guilmont.
It's a trust.
Why, they're
masterpieces.
All right,
so they're masterpieces.
You told me
they'd only be here
for a few days.
But they've been here
for weeks.
Don't you
realize that?
I've been nice
about it, martin.
You can't say
that i haven't.
But how long am i going to be
locked out of my own basement?
Oh, emma!
I'm sorry,
dear, i am.
But i didn't lie.
I thought that they'd just
be here for a short while.
I really did.
But i can't seem
to find anybody
who's-who's willing to
finance the museum.
But how can you
find anybody,
if you spend
all of your time down here?
But i've phoned,
and these people...
do you know these
people never even
heard of guilmont?
Can you imagine?
What, what's that?
It's the
electric bill.
You'll see how much
it's costing us to keep
the air conditioner
running day and night.
But you know it has
been hot down here.
Oh.
That is high,
isn't it?
I just wish i could figure out
how we're going
to keep on paying it.
Martin, there's no more money
in the bank.
I know, but
don't worry.
Please,
i'll find a way.
There must be
somebody, somewhere.
Mr. Ferguson.
Hmm... no.
Martin, why not?
You told me yourself
that he loves these things
as much as you do.
And isn't it really up to him
to take care of them?
Emma, i don't know
anyone in the world
i have more respect
for than mr. Ferguson.
But i wouldn't trust him
with those figures.
I don't think he could
take care of them right,
and i wouldn't be
able to sleep if i...
so, we're stuck
with them!
Stuck?
What do you
mean stuck, emma?
Oh, please,
it's an honor.
It's a privilege.
For you, maybe.
But what about me?
How do you think i feel?
Every time i come down here
and look at them,
i just about have
a heart attack.
The way they stand there
and stare at me,
they're frightening!
But emma...
they're supposed
to be frightening.
Let me tell you this.
When you live with them
as long as i have,
you come to love them.
Love them?
Yes.
And... then they cease
to be strangers,
and you want to say...
good morning!
How'd you spend
the night, jack?
And then it seem...
emma?
Emma!
Emma?
Oh... if only one of those
people he's been talking to
would lend him enough money
to open the museum,
that would make
everything all right.
Now, emma, listen
to your brother.
Nobody's going
to put money
into a crazy scheme
like that.
Old ferguson knew
what he was doing,
all right, when he sold out.
He got martin to take care of
all those crazy dummies,
and he's not even paying him
for it.
Pretty shrewd.
What we've got to do...
we've got to get martin
away from those things.
Does he have them all?
Only a few.
Well, how come?
I mean, ferguson had
two or 200,
didn't he?
Well, these are special.
Some man
in europe
made them.
I don't know how
they could be so special,
if they didn't
cost anything.
They are to him.
This is the first time anything
has come between us.
Ihatethose murderers!
You come on.
We're going to go talk
to him right now.
No, no, dave,
it wouldn't do
any good.
Okay. Then you talk to him.
But here's what you do.
Don't talk to him
the way you have been.
I mean, lay it
right on the line.
You tell him it's either
those stupid dummies oryou!
Of course, if that
doesn't work, there...
there is something else.
What?
Well, um...
air conditioners
do break down, you know.
Oh.
Oh, i couldn't do that.
Couldn't you?
Emma.
Emma, where have you been?
You walked out on me
while i was talking to you.
Oh, emma, emma, i
know you're angry
with me, but i...
what can i do?
I have to keep
the figures in
perfect condition.
I can't let
them go or...
i thought you said
we didn't have
any money left.
I bought them
with some money
davegave me.
Dave!
Oh, my...
my, my...
oh, martin!
We can't go on this way.
Yes, i know. Well...
i'll borrow some money
from mr. Ferguson.
Borrowing isn't
going to help.
Well, then, i'll-i'll-i'll...
i'll mortgage the house.
That isn't going to answer
our problem.
Martin, nobody knows
better than i
how much those figures
mean to you.
But...
but what, emma?
Emma?
But i simply willnothave them
in this house
one minute longer!
Why shouldn't mr. Ferguson
take care of them?
They're his.
Well, why shouldn't he?
That's what
you really think, isn't it?
Is that all they mean to you?
Yes.
And i want you to call
and tell him tomorrow morning.
Martin,
once they're away
from here
you'll be a different
man, you'll see.
You've been around those
wax dummies for so long,
you've forgotten how
to be a human being.
No!
What kind of a friend
do you think i am?
I can't desert them now,
after all these years.
They need me!
They'd be lost without me.
Martin!
They're not alive.
They don't need anybody!
Martin...
i want you
to see a doctor.
A doc...?
Yes, just once.
Well, there's
nothing whatever
the matter with me.
I, i didn't
say there was.
Then, what do i need
a doctor for?
Because, martin
thereissomething
the matter with you.
Well, what?
But you haven't been
yourself lately.
Well...
who have i been?
I don't know.
Somebody i've
never known.
But martin, staying down
in that basement all day
and talking to thosethings
as if they were alive,
it's not natural.
Emma...
that's my job.
I'm not the only husband
in the world
who brings his work home.
Don't you see?
I don't want to talk
about it anymore.
And...
you go back and you tell
that brother of yours
to mind his
own business.
You hear me?
Emma?
Emma.
Emma, you down there?
Emma?
Emma, you down here?
Emma.
Emma?
Emma!
Emma, what happened?
Emma...
twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
Ah, i hate
to put you here, emma, but...
what can i do?
I know i should report it
to the police,
and i want to, but...
but who would believe me
if i told them that you were
killed by jack the ripper?
You can see that, can't you?
Besides...
if i went to prison-
as i probably would-
who would take care
of the figures?
No.
It's better this way.
Poor emma.
Too late to tell her
anything now.
There.
That's the best i can do, emma.
Gas man!
Well, hi, there,
mr. Senescu.
Doing a little
patching i see.
Yes, uh...
floor must have been
pretty bad, huh?
It was starting
to crack a little.
Well, i had to do
the same thing in my basement.
That's the way it is with
these old houses, you know.
Oh, yes.
Holy mackerel.
Be careful of
the cement, please.
For a minute there i...
where'd you ever get
anything like this?
Well, they belong
to mr. Ferguson.
But i'm taking
care of them.
They used to be in a museum,
but it closed.
Boy, they're the most realistic
things i ever saw.
You sure
they ain't alive?
Not all together.
Well, they
could fool me.
Sure be a fine thing
to have come halloween.
Something like this
in the basement,
you'd really throw
a scare into people.
Man, oh man.
Even up close they, uh...
well, what's this?
What?
Whoever made these up,
they thought of everything.
Even put blood
on the knife.
Pretty good.
Well, i got to go.
But i want to tell
you, you've got
quite a layout here.
Hey, tell me something.
Don't they give you
the creeps?
I mean, being down here
in the basement and all?
Oh, no.
Uh, not when you know
them as well as i do.
Oh, you're a card,
mr. Senescu.
Wait till i tell the wife
about this.
Hey, do you think
it'd be all right
if i brought her over
for a look at those things?
Oh, i don't think so.
We'll be gone
for a while.
Tomorrow?
No, for days,
and, uh, we don't
know when we'll be back.
Oh.
Well, uh, i'll see you.
So long.
Bye.
Jack!
I'm surprised at you.
I amreallysurprised.
How did you manage
all those murders
without being caught
by scotland yard?
Why, any killer knows
that you can't leave blood
on a murder weapon!
It's...
well, it's not
a joke, jack,
but it's a dead
giveaway, now...
there.
It's good as new.
Now will youplease,
pleasebehave yourself?
I don't want to have to
go through this again.
Emma?
Martin.
Anybody down there?
Martin, if you're
down there, open up.
Martin.
All right, i'm, i'm here.
Open the door.
I can't, dave.
Why not?
Dave, i have a lot of, uh...
things piled up
against the door.
I'm going upstairs.
You come around the back door
to the kitchen.
You there, martin?
Yes, uh...
coming, dave.
You got
this place locked up
like fort knox
or something.
What's the big idea?
Oh, we, uh...
we always keep
the doors locked.
Where's emma?
Uh, she's, uh,
she's not here.
Oh.
It's probably
just as well.
Why?
Dave, what do you want?
Uh, have you got an
ashtray somewhere?
Yeah. Oh, here.
How's this?
Uh, sit down,
sit down, martin.
Dave, to tell the truth,
i'm kind of busy.
I'll bet.
If you just tell me
what you want, i...
come on, come on, sit down.
Sit down.
What is it?
Emma came to see me yesterday.
Oh, yes, i, uh...
i know, she told me.
She did?
All right,
that'll make things easier.
Where did she
go, by the way?
She took a trip.
A trip? Where?
To see my sister.
Oh.
You two have an argument?
Well...
everything's settled now.
Well, i'm certainly glad
to hear that.
She was sure
upset when she
talked to me.
Yes, i know.
You've got
to admit
you didn't treat
her square.
You brought
those dummies here
and kept her out
of her own basement.
Well... it's all been changed.
Well, i guess
i had you pegged
all wrong, marty.
You got rid of 'em?
Yes.
Must've been a pretty hot
night last night, huh?
What do you mean, hot?
Pretty hot for a bunch
of wax dummies, huh?
What's that humming noise?
Well, i...
i don't hear anything.
It... sounds like it's coming
from down there.
That's the air conditioner.
What are you
trying to hand me?
The door's locked.
Yes, i, uh...
i told you, you know
i like to keep the doors locked.
Why is the air conditioner going
if you got rid of
the wax figures?
Well, i was cleaning up, dave,
and i just wanted to keep
the place cool, that's all.
Look, you just came
up the stairway,
and you locked the
door behind you.
Now, why?
It's a habit.
I don't
think so.
I think you locked it to keep me
from going down there.
Now, you
better
open up.
Are you threatening me
in my own house?
You never got rid
of them things at all.
And how about this
sister of yours?
How come emma never
mentioned her before?
Where does she live?
Look, dave, i've...
had a very busy day.
I'm tired
of answering questions.
Now, will you please leave?
Okay.
All right.
Fine, i can take a hint.
I'll just be
on my way.
You, uh...
you have emma call me
if she comes back,
you hear?
Dave!
Oh!
Hicks, how could you?
Martin.
Martin!
Martin, are
you there?
Martin...
martin?
Yes.
Oh, mr. Ferguson.
Come in, come in.
Martin, how nice
to see you!
Nice to see you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't hear you.
The air conditioner's on.
Yes, it's nice
and cool down here.
Yes.
There they are.
And in perfect
condition.
Martin, i can't keep it
from you any longer.
What, sir?
The best news
in the world.
Martin, old friend,
when i told you
that nobody wanted
to buy these figures,
i was being
too pessimistic.
The fact is,
somebody does want to.
But not just somebody.
The marchand museum.
Oh.
Didn't you
hear me?
Yes.
Marchand's.
In brussels.
I can't imagine
why, but...
aren't you pleased?
Yes.
Mr. Ferguson,
look at the ripper.
I must say, martin,
you have kept them up well.
Yes, now, you see, this
needs fixing in here.
The threads are
starting to fall out.
As a matter of fact, i think
they all need new clothes.
Maybe it is too humid
in here, after all.
We won't have to worry
about that anymore.
Oh, and i asked emma
to sew this rip up,
but there's been
so many things to do.
Oh, by the way,
how is emma?
Oh, she's fine.
You have a
remarkable wife, martin.
There aren't many women
who would put up
with an exhibit like this
in their basement.
She never complains.
Oh, have you been
sleeping down here?
Yes.
Oh!
Mr. Ferguson...
i came across this little item
in this book that
i was reading just
before i fell asleep.
Martin...
mr. Ferguson,
do you remember
how excited we used to get
when we found out some new
things about the figures?
Martin, are you
all right?
Yes.
No, mr. Ferguson.
It isn't so.
I'm not all right.
No?
No.
Some strange things
have been happening.
Strange things?
Yes.
They haven't exactly
been behaving themselves.
Who?
Oh, come now.
Oh, it's true,
i swear it.
You've no idea what
they've been up to.
Oh, martin.
You've been so close...
sh!
You've been so close
to these figures
for the past three months.
You're beginning
toimaginethings about them.
No, no, it's
not imagination.
Not at all.
Well, that's neither
here nor there.
The point is...
you won't have to take care
of them any longer.
But mr. Ferguson, i want
to take care of them.
I know you do.
And as i've said,
i appreciate
what you've done,
but it's all settled.
Of course, there'll be
a substantial reward to you
for all the years
you've cared for them.
Now, why don't you prepare us
a cup of tea or something
while i take some measurements.
The marchand people want
some specifications
i wasn't able to provide.
All right.
I'll make some tea.
53 inches.
Hmm.
37.
I didn't think
you were that wide.
Well, no matter.
Mr. Ferguson,
i brought you
both the cream and the sugar.
I didn't know
which one you want...
mr. Ferguson.
Mr. Ferguson!
Landru.
It was you.
And hicks.
Hicks.
And burke.
And hare.
I know you didn't have
any part in this,
but you didn't stop it.
And you, landru,
especially you.
And you, jack.
This time you went too far.
I gave you
all the best years i had.
You wanted for nothing!
I washed you.
I cleaned your clothes.
I bought you new ones.
It was always
the right temperature for you,
becauseimade it so for you.
And who defended you...
and who defended your deeds
against the thousands
who saw you?
And when mr. Ferguson
sold the museum
who spoke up for you?
Who wanted you?
Me!
I was the best friend
you ever had.
Now...
now, what have you done for me?
You've murdered mr. Ferguson.
He was the only,
only man who was my friend.
He was my best friend.
And the books are right.
The books areright.
You are monsters,
all of you...
you're heartless
heartless monsters.
All of you,
through and through.
I'm going to punish
you all for this.
I'll break you
into little pieces.
I'll turn up the heat
so that you'll melt down
into little pools of wax.
That's what i'm going to do.
It'll be no less
than you deserve.
All right.
Now.
Which one of you is first?
You!
Landru.
Because you murdered
mr. Ferguson.
No!
No, it was not i
who garroted
your friend,
martin senescu.
No.
It was you!
No, you killed him
while i was upstairs
making tea. No!
No, martin senescu,
it was you-
you murdered
your wife.
You killed her...
while i was asleep.
It was you who used my ax
to kill your wife's brother.
No.
Not so,
martin senescu.
No, you're-you're
the murderers.
No, no!
You are the murderer,
you killed them all.
No, you killed...
it was
always you.
You're the murderers!
No! Martin
senescu.
You're
the murderers.
It was you...
and here, ladies
and gentlemen,
we have jack
the ripper-
the one murderer
who was never caught.
And now we come to a man
who only recently
became one
of the most famous of all.
Martin lombard senescu...
a remarkable and certainly
most versatile murderer.
Who knows what thoughts
went through his mind
as he dug the graves
for his wife, emma,
whom he killed with a knife...
his wife's brother, david,
whose skull was split
with an ax...
or his friend and employer
for 30 years,
ernest ferguson.
The new exhibit became
very popular at marchand's.
But of all the figures,
none was ever regarded
with more dread
than that
of martin lombard senescu.
It was something
about the eyes, people said.
It's the look
that one often gets
after taking a quick walk
through the twilight zone.
Next ontwilight zone
a trip back into time
with albert salmi,
john anderson
and guest star julie newmar.
But this trip is very offbeat,
very adventuresome
and totally unexpected
itinerary.
It's called "of late i think
of cliffordville."
You send me back in time.
Send back to cliffordville.
But i want to look exactly as
i did then. That's number one.
Agreed.
Number two,
i want to have a memory
of everything
that's occurred in the last
50 years.
I don't want that memory
impaired on bit.
Check again, mr. Feathersmith.
I want it to happen right away.
Cliffordville.
This stop
is cliffordville.
Cliffordville?
The devil you say.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org