Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Oh, jeffrey,
put those in the study.
All right.
Crowded downtown?
The greatest
mardi gras ever.
Least that's what
they're saying.
How is he?
Not good, not
good at all.
Doctor's with him now,
but he wants to be advised
when the relatives arrive.
Those relatives of his.
I'm quite sure
they'll make themselves known.
Well, sawbones?
Well, it's too fast,
it's too weak,
and it's too uneven.
Where were you
when they taught bedside manner
at medical school?
Trying out for soccer?
Jason, i have been
your physician for 25 years,
and the first time
i treated you for a head cold
and i allowed myself
one compassionate cluck,
you threw a lamp at me.
That established the pattern
then and there.
I have put up with your
inept ministrations
all these years
because your candor is
a refreshing departure
from the modern
medical norm.
I ask you a straight,
simple question,
i get a straight,
simple response.
Sam...
yes, jason, what is it?
The oft-asked question
how long?
Oh, jason,
you can't exactly say...
tell me, sam,
do i have a week?
Do i have a day and a half?
Or is there no need
to wind my watch to cover
the possibilities of
the next four hours?
Jason... my guess is
you can measure your life
in moments.
It can come
at any time now.
But that fact
you're still here
is a tribute to...
to inner strength
most of us
don't even possess.
Nonsense. It's attributable
to a cross-grained orneriness.
And the fact that there are one
or two things left to do
before i leave this earth.
That's why i must stay alive
at least until midnight.
All right, jason,
all right.
Doctor?
Yes?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes, jason,
i believe you will...
god willing.
Mr. Jason foster,
a tired ancient
who on this particular
mardi gras evening
will leave the earth.
But before departing,
he has some things to do,
some services to perform,
some debts to pay
and some justice to mete out.
This is new orleans,
mardi gras time.
It is also the twilight zone.
Oh, what a ghastly trip.
I'm absolutely
exhausted!
Here, take this,
jeffrey.
And these, too.
Yes, sir.
Jeffrey, are
our rooms ready?
Yes, ma'am,
all prepared.
Oh, fine.
Thank you.
Good afternoon.
Dr. Thorn!
How nice to see you!
Well, emily,
how are you?
Oh... i'm bearing up,
doctor,
under the circumstances.
You remember
my husband, wilfred?
Oh, yes.
Hello, doctor.
We met some time ago.
And this is my son,
wilfred jr.
Hi.
And my daughter,
paula.
Hello.
Your father has been
expecting you, emily.
I'm awfully glad
you can be here.
Oh, that silly mardi gras.
Oh, really, the traffic
was just unspeakable.
All the shouting,
screaming, rude people.
It's a wonder
father's chauffeur
was ever able
to get us...
emily...
your father is extremely ill.
In my opinion,
it is only a matter
of days, even hours.
Oh, how perfectly awful.
But, of course,
we've been expecting it.
Haven't we?
Oh, incidentally,
doctor,
i've been getting
these absolutely horrible
muscle spasms in my arm.
Sometimes they're
just unbearable.
Perhaps you might
prescribe something...
emily...
i'm sorry,
but i have
other patients
to visit today.
Oh, yes, of course.
If you'll all excuse me.
Oh, doctor?
Yes?
I'll see you
to the door.
You two take
your mother upstairs.
Tell me, uh...
the old boy's
in bad shape, huh?
"The old boy" is dying.
Good afternoon.
Well, father.
Father.
Oh! Father, you're awake.
How are you, emily?
Oh...
i'm bearing up.
Bearing up?
You sound like job
itemizing his calamities.
What's your illness
this month, emily?
It doesn't matter, father.
I'll muddle through.
You are the four most changeless
people on this earth.
I don't like being ill, father,
if that's what you mean.
Don't you?
Well, i find that
hard to believe...
considering
in the past 25 years,
you've been at death's door
so often,
it's a wonder you haven't worn
a hole in the mat.
Well!
Father!
And wilfred...
how's business?
Oh, making a little,
losing a little, father,
but i manage
to keep my head above water.
You know, wilfred,
i think the only book
you ever read was a ledger.
I think if someone cut you open,
they would find a cash register.
Oh, really, father?
Really.
And you, paula.
Delighted to see
you, grandfather.
Now, that's friendly of you
to tell me that...
considering
that you haven't seen me yet.
All you've seen
is your mirror image.
Oh, grandfather,
you're very naughty,
really, you are.
We've had the most miserable,
long trip,
and mother hasn't stopped
complaining one instant.
Well!
Do you hear that, father?
The younger
generation.
"He jests at scars
that never felt a wound."
Oh, emily, my dear.
I believe that my trouble
is hardening of the arteries
in a very sick heart.
But if you don't stop playing
sarah bernhardt,
i think i
shall succumb
to an intestinal
disorder.
And... there's wilfred jr.,
looking as
aware as ever.
Wilfred, dear,
tell grandfather
how nice it is to see him.
It's nice to see you
again, grandfather.
It was very nice and gracious
of you all to come see me.
Why, father dear, wild horses
couldn't have kept us away,
even my own agony.
Oh, i hope you
survive, emily.
Now, i've planned
that you all have
an excellent dinner
this evening,
and then we're going
to have a surprise.
Oh, grandfather,
it's mardi gras,
and i was rather hoping
you'd know of some...
nice young man.
But we're going to have
a partyhere, paula.
We're going to have
a marvelous time.
And i've arranged
for all of us to...
to wear masks.
What?
Masks?
How droll, father.
Masks!
I swear, you people
don't just celebrate
the mardi gras,
you succumb to it.
Masks, indeed.
That might be fun.
Oh, it shall be,
junior, my boy.
It shall be.
Oh, perhaps not
the same degree
of excitement
that you get
from torturing
small animals
as i've seen you
do in the past.
Lay off, grandfather.
Besides, that was
a long time ago.
Wilfred's getting along
very well
in school now, father.
He made
the football team.
Chip off the old block,
right, son?
Chip off the old
block, grandfather.
Oh, i'm sure of it.
Now, why don't
you all go
and prepare for dinner?
We're going to have
a very interesting
evening.
As a matter of fact,
i'll guarantee it.
Anything you say,
father.
Come along, darlings.
Excuse me, sir.
Your milk, mr. Foster.
Oh, thank
you, jeffrey.
Anything else
i can do for you?
Yes. You may
get the masks
and put them in the
study, if you will.
Yes, sir.
Oh, really.
I think this whole thing
is too ridiculous.
It's the most exciting night
of the whole year,
and we... we sit here in this...
this mausoleum.
The whole city
of new orleans is dancing,
and what do we do?
We have a death watch
for a crazy old man.
Did you have a swinging time
in new orleans, baby?
Oh, indeed.
We wore funny masks
and all sat around
and looked at each other.
Oh, i'm so bored.
Ah, that'll be all,
jeffrey.
Thank you.
Yes, sir.
Well, tell me, my loved ones,
did you have a
satisfactory dinner?
Oh, yes, yes, yes,
we did, father.
Sumptuous, father.
Really excellent.
Do you think it wise
to be up like this?
Wise?
No, no, but
necessary, assuredly.
Tell me, have you
examined your masks?
Ourmasks?
They're-they're,
uh, unique, father.
They are very unique.
You know, they are made
by an old cajun.
"Made" is inaccurate.
They are created.
I am told that in addition
to their artistic value,
they have certain, uh...
certain properties.
They're worn
only during the mardi gras,
and there's a ritual
to the wearing.
One tries to select a mask
that is the antithesis
of what the wearer is.
Oh, sure.
Well, that's, uh,
very interesting.
Um, very interesting.
Yes, it is.
Now, shall we select
our masks?
Tell me, wilfred,
how do you fancy
yourself?
Oh, uh, i don't
understand, father.
Oh, come now,
be candid.
When you shave
in the morning,
what looks back at you
from the mirror?
Really, father,
i think we're a little
old for parlor games...
let me be the judge of that.
Now, i want an honest
self-assessment.
You're serious,
aren't you?
I was never more serious.
Well, i'm an
affable man.
I've always been
an affable man.
Oh, you're
Well, then,
you're, uh, friendly?
You're outgoing?
You're, uh, extrovertish?
I think so.
Yes, then, along
with this affability,
you have a certain rapport
with your fellow man.
Uh, yes, indeed.
Uh-huh. Now, the opposite
of all this...
amiability would be, uh...
this face here.
Look at it.
Charming.
Wear it!
Live with it
a while, wilfred.
It has great subtlety, wilfred.
There's greed,
avarice, cruelty...
all of the character traits
that you don't have.
Ah, and my dear, brave emily.
I'm really not
up to this, father.
Of course you are, my dear.
You're up to anything.
Your courage
dictates
this brief period
of sacrifice.
Now...
look at this
face, my dear.
The face of a
self-centered coward,
a gutless flab...
in contrast to your
intrepid valor.
Here, emily.
And the one who walks
in beauty like the night.
Frankly, grandfather, i think
this whole thing is a bore.
Oh, but, paula,
look at that beauty,
that insolent
hauteur,
that skin-deep
vanity.
It has none
of your heart,
none of your
selflessness.
Wear it, paula,
just for a few hours.
And the timid,
gentle wilfred jr. Over there.
Ah, come on, grandfather.
Now, this would be your mask,
wilfred, my boy.
It's a face
of a dull, stupid clown-
in contrast to your
gentle refinement, your...
courteous civility.
Here.
Uh... what about
your mask, father?
Oh, this is mine.
The face of death,
because i'm alive, understand?
I shall wear
the thing
stalking me
at this moment.
Father, you
don't mean...
we have towear
these ugly things?
Only for a few hours.
Only till the unmasking
at midnight.
Well, i won't wear mine.
Me neither.
It's stupid.
Well, father,
it seems we're
somewhat at odds here.
Notreally, wilfred.
You all came here
for one purpose:
To watch me go
and cry "bon voyage."
To put coins
on my closed eyes
and with your
free hands,
start grabbing things
from my shelves.
Father, that's cruel.
That's truth!
You came to reap
everything i've sown,
to collect everything
i've built.
Well, i shall not
disappoint you.
Everything is yours.
Everything
is prepared.
The will is made.
The four of you inherit
everything i own.
Everything.
Money, house, property holdings,
stocks, bonds- everything.
Father, you're breaking
our hearts.
That's the most touching thing
you ever dredged up
by way of conversation, wilfred.
But i must include
this addendum,
this small proviso.
You shall wear your masks
until midnight.
If any one of you
should take them off,
from my estate,
you shall each receive
train fare
back to boston,
and that's it!
Well, we won't be
spoilsports.
If this is your pleasure,
father, we'll indulge you.
And now, my dear ones,
we will wait until midnight.
Oh... oh,
this is horrible.
Oh, this is horrible,
father.
I'm suffocating.
I really am
suffocating!
I've had dull times before,
grandfather,
but this is the worst.
This takes it.
I don't know about the rest
of you, but i've had it.
I can't stand this thing
on my face another minute!
I'm taking it off!
I don't care!
Stop it!
You stop it!
I don't blame her.
I don't blame
her a bit!
This is cruel,
father.
I have to agree,
Really, this has gone
far enough.
We've been here
for hours
staring at these
grotesque masks.
I think
there is a limit.
Please, father,
please let us
take them off now.
Have you all had your say?
Paula?
Wilfred jr.?
You, emily?
And that captain
of industry
you're married to?
Is there nothing else
you have to say to me?
Only that i'm-i'm
feeling buried alive.
Me, too! I think
you're out of your mind.
Come on, let us
take them off!
Father, i appeal to you.
It's more
than just discomfort.
It's becoming unbearable.
What is it, father?
It's, uh, what
you've all been waiting for,
i believe, wilfred.
Now you can dig deep
in the treasury.
Are you feeling
weaker, father?
At last, a note of hope
in your voice, emily.
Why must you
always say
miserable, cruel
things to me?!
I quite agree, father.
Why, indeed, emily.
Because you're cruel
and miserable people.
Because none of you respond
to love.
Emily responds only to what
her petty hungers dictate.
Wilfred responds only to things
that have weight
and bulk and value.
Hefeelsbooks;
he doesn't read them.
He appraises paintings;
he doesn't seek out
their truth or their beauty.
And paula there
lives in a mirror.
The world is
nothing to her
but a reflection
of herself.
And her brother.
Humanity to him
is a small animal
caught in a trap
to be tormented.
His pleasure
is the giving of pain,
and from this,
he feels
the same sense
of fulfillment
most human
beings get
from a kiss
or an embrace!
You're caricatures!
All of you.
Without your
masks...
you're caricatures.
And now...
you're all very rich.
Now you own everything
that i have owned.
You kept your bargain.
You wore the masks.
Enjoy yourselves, dear ones.
I've lived a full life.
May god pity you.
He's dead.
At long last, he's dead.
Good.
Now, let's celebrate!
Wha... what's the matter?
What's the matter
with you all?
Oh!
Oh...
oh... oh.
I called you
just as soon as i
found out, doctor.
This must be death.
No horror, no fear.
Nothing but peace.
Mardi gras incident.
Thedramatis personae
being four people
who came to celebrate
and, in a sense,
let themselves go.
This they did with a vengeance.
They now wear the faces
of all that was inside them,
and they'll wear them
for the rest of their lives-
said lives now to be spent
in shadow.
Tonight's tale of men,
the macabre and masks
on the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next time
out in the twilight zone,
we do a probe in depth into a
current cancer known as hatred
and we tell you the story
of a little midwestern village
which wakes up
on a violent morning
to discover that there is
no morning, no light, no sun.
Only a frightening
and pervading darkness.
It stars michael constantine
and paul fix,
and it's called, "i am
the night- color me black."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org