Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
of imagination.
Next stop, the twilight zone.
Edna.
Huh?
What about gas and electric?
What?
The gas and
electric bill.
How many months is that?
Four months.
That's one you better pay.
Huh. That's one i can't pay.
Oh, i wish...
how are you,
mrs. Gumley?
Oh, just fine, mr. Castle.
How have you been?
Oh, can't complain.
Been having a lot of rain,
haven't we?
Quite a bit of rain
for this time of the year.
Really.
It's good
for the flowers.
How's that?
An heirloom today,
mr. Castle.
An heirloom, mrs. Gumley?
Oh, yes,
mr. Castle.
Been in my family
for years and years.
It's supposed to
be very valuable.
Hand-blown glass
is what it is.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Mrs. Gumley, it's just
a plain old wine bottle.
Do you know
what it's worth?
Nothing.
If you could find
the store where it came from,
that's what they would
give you for it, mrs. Gumley-
nothing.
I... i could let it go
for a dollar.
Mrs. Gumley,
if i could spare a dollar,
i'd give it to you,
believe me i would, but...
well, things have
been rough here.
I'm so in debt myself...
i wish i could make
it more, i really do.
Thank you, mr. Castle.
You're
a wonderful man.
God bless you.
Mr. Castle...
it's not an
heirloom, you know.
I found it in an ash can.
Please,
mr. Castle,
forgive me
for lying.
Aw, that's all right,
mrs. Gumley.
Who knows? Maybe it'll turn out
tobean heirloom.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Gorgeous.
She has to eat,
doesn't she?
You don't?
Arthur...
we're just
around the corner
from bankruptcy.
You promised me,
no more handouts.
Look, edna,
maybe all i've got left
is to try to find some poor clod
whoicould feel sorry for.
Maybe a man
can be a failure
for only so long,
and then... and then...
and then it catches up
with him.
Look at it, edna!
Look at it!
The legacy
of a hundred years.
My grandfather owned it,
and it broke his heart.
And then, my father-
it killed him, too.
Look at it. Look at it.
The meanness of it,
the shabbiness of it,
the hand-to-mouth of it!
It isn't just an antique shop
where you pick up
the pitiful remnants
of other people's failures.
It's a shrine to failure itself,
that's what it is!
It's a mausoleum,
a burial ground for...
for people's hopes.
Edna, what happens
to us anyway?
What happens to us?
We're not old people,
and yet this place
is making us old.
There must be years ahead of us
that come without
scrimping and counting,
and picking over
checkbooks and budgets
and final notices
and old bills.
Hey...
hey!
Mr. And mrs. Arthur castle-
gentle and
infinitely patient people
whose lives have been
a hope chest
with a rusty lock
and a lost set of keys.
But, in just a moment,
that hope chest will be opened,
and an improbable phantom
will try to bedeck the drabness
of these two people's
failure-laden lives
with the gold and
precious stones of fulfillment.
Mr. And mrs. Arthur castle,
standing on the outskirts,
and about to enter,
the twilight zone.
How do you do?
Rather than go into any lengthy
generic explanation
of my existence, suffice it
to say that i am a genie.
That's quite correct.
A genie.
I can offer you four wishes
with a guaranteed performance.
Well, mr. Castle?
Mrs. Castle?
What have you in mind?
Arthur, what's
happening to us?
He's a hypnotist
or something.
Nothing of the sort.
I grant four wishes
to the owner,
then go back
inside the bottle
for a century and a year
until a summons comes
from the next owner.
Now, i think the business at
hand is for you and mrs. Castle
to decide upon the nature
of your four wishes,
keeping in mind,
of course...
edna.
...that each wish
is irrevocable.
Once made, it is fulfilled.
And, once fulfilled,
it is a matter of record.
It can only be altered
by yet another wish.
Clear, mr. Castle?
I think we'd better
call the police.
Wish
for them.
I can bring you scotland yard,
the federal bureau
of investigation,
or every bobby in
the city of london.
Is it the police
you want?
No.
That is not what
we would wish for.
Arthur, you out
of your mind?
You believe him?
Please go on,
mr. Castle.
You were saying?
Well, if i had a wish,
just for the sake
of argument,
i'd say i wanted
that broken glass
in that case to be fixed.
Would you like to make
it official, mr. Castle?
Well, mr. Castle,
is that your wish?
Yes, that is my wish.
I want that glass
in that display case
to be repaired.
Well, mr. Castle?
You have three
wishes left.
Three wishes.
Three wishes,
three wishes.
Anything we want.
Well, think, think.
What do you want?
Nothing, arthur.
I want nothing.
A new shop-
an expensive shop
on fifth avenue.
We could have that
just for the asking.
Or money, edna, money!
$100,000!
$200,000!
A million!
Edna, edna,
we wouldn't have
to grub anymore.
We wouldn't to sit her
and waste our lives away.
Arthur, no.
There's something
unholy about this.
Clothes, edna,
expensive clothes.
Jewels,
a beautiful house!
Anything we want,
edna!
No more worries for
the rest of our lives.
Money.
Money? The simplest, mr. Castle.
How much, and in
what denominations?
How much do we want?
I don't know.
I don't know!
A million dollars,
right here on the floor,
in five and ten
dollar bills.
That's what we want!
A million dollars!
Ask and you shall
receive, mr. Castle.
Edna, edna!
Edna! A million dollars, edna!
A million dollars!
Edna, look!
A million!
Wait, wait, wait.
So he says...
wait. So he says,
"money?"
So much money for me.
I thought maybe
she's-a go outta style!
Here you are, my friend.
Here you are.
You pay off that mortgage
and have yourself...
start living again.
That's it.
Here you are, my dear.
Here. You take yourself
that vacation,
and bring back a boyfriend.
Don't forget.
Mrs. Gumley. Oh, my dear.
Here. Here. More. More!
Mrs. Gumley, god bless you.
God bless you.
Here you are, my dear.
No, no, no, no, no.
You take that
home with you.
Here you are, reverend.
Don't you worry.
This is honest money.
You take it and get
that church painted.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir, and thank you.
Yes, dolly,
here you are. Come here.
You tell angelo
to get himself a new truck
with red wheels.
Remember.
Here you are, my...
no need. My card,
mr. Castle.
Office of internal revenue.
Yes, that's correct.
There's a matter of an
income tax, mr. Castle.
Just send
us the bill
and we'll
pay it.
But send us the
bill in a hurry,
would you please?
My wife and i will
be taking off
for europe
very shortly.
Dependents?
The whole neighborhood.
Oh, no.
They don't count.
What does that
figure there mean?
A million dollars,
mr. Castle.
Taxed on the basis
of a husband and wife,
using the standard deductions,
you owe the government
approximately
$907,000.
What?
Yes, that's correct.
Then, in addition,
there's a state income tax
involved which...
using thumb rule...
the whole thing comes
to a total of...
roughly, mind you...
$942,640.
Arthur, we've already
given away a lot of money.
Well, now, if you'll
just fill out this form
and send it to us
with your check?
Oh, uh... if you want
to use the installment plan,
we'll send you a statement after
the form has been analyzed.
Uh... mr. Castle?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just send us a bill.
Well, we'll be seeing you,
mr. Castle.
Good evening,
mrs. Castle.
Well?
$910,530.
$910,535.
$910,540.
We gave away almost $60,000.
And this goes to taxes,
and this...
five dollars?
Yeah.
Quite a wish, arthur.
Quite a wish.
And we haven't even
paid those bills yet.
Mr. Castle...
it was my suggestion
that you reflect
very carefully, mr. Castle.
Very, very carefully.
Now, had you made a wish
that took into account
the taxes involved...
oh...
look, you.
Plenty of sweet talk and
promises and the whole thing,
and all the time you're nothing
but a
con artist.
This time,
i want the million dollars,
but i want itafter...
arthur,
no more money.
You got to wish
for something else.
Something else.
How about
ten more wishes?
Or 20?
Don't be in such
a hurry, arthur.
Then you think
of something!
I'm afraid wishing
for more wishes
isn't permitted, mr. Castle.
Frankly, i'd be afraid
to have you try
for fear of the consequences.
What consequences?
Why do you keep
losing your temper?
Well, you're no help
for me. That's for sure!
Here we stand
in this crummy little shop,
with the whole world
out in front of us,
with anything to wish for
that we want,
and you just
stay on my back...!
Arthur!
Edna.
What... what's
happening with us?
What's going on?
Oddly enough,
mr. Castle,
this is the normal pattern
that seems
to be generally followed-
great excitement,
great emotionalism.
Strangely enough,
hard to believe
though it may be,
only a modicum of happiness.
Well...
you got a couple
of cheap customers
here, mister.
People that haven't
known much happiness.
What? What? What
do we wish for?
I wish
i knew, arthur.
I don't know!
What about it, genie?
What can
we wish for now?
What can come to us
without tricks?
Without tricks!
I question the semantics here,
mr. Castle.
There are no tricks involved.
There are simply normal
and understandable outgrowths
and conditions
that go with any windfall.
No matter what you wish for,
you must be prepared
for the consequences.
Something without
consequences.
Something dead sure.
Something anchored,
something airtight.
Edna, i think
i got it.
I think i know
what it is.
What, arthur?
Power. Power, edna.
To be in charge
of something...
the boss...
to be a leader.
We could wish
for that.
Possible.
Very possible.
President of a corporation?
That sort
of thing?
He could go bankrupt.
Mayor of a city?
You get voted out of office,
then what?
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
I know what.
Head of a country.
Ruler of a whole country.
That's it.
What about it, genie?
I want to be the
head of a country
who can't be voted
out of office.
Do you want to be more specific
than that?
Wait a minute.
Let me give it to you this way.
I want to be the head
of a foreign country
who can't be voted
out of office,
but it must be
a contemporary country.
Contemporary?
Within this century.
No problems.
What about consequences?
Consequences, mr. Castle?
I've already told you.
You run the risk of consequences
no matter what you wish for.
All right, then.
Go ahead, arthur.
You wish for that.
I want to be the ruler
of a foreign country,
just as i've
described it.
Go ahead, genie.
Take over.
As you wish, mr. Castle.
From now on, it's
just a mass suicide.
Well, what about
it, fuhrer?
Head of a country.
Can't be voted out
of office.
I'm hitler.
I'm in a bunker.
It's the end of the war.
Mein fuhrer.
What you asked for.
Very quick...
and very painless,
mein fuhrer.
And we have
the gasoline outside
for you and miss braun
when you finish.
I wish... i wish i were back
where it all started.
I wish i were
arthur castle again!
What's the matter,
arthur?
You look so funny.
What happened?
I had a wish
fulfilled.
Number four.
All the wishes ended
the same way-
in fragments,
little pieces.
Funny thing, though.
This place... this... this
place doesn't look half bad.
You all right?
Oh, i'm fine.
Well, maybe we'll stop
wishing for a while.
And, since we obviously
can't afford
a brand-new life,
suppose we give the
old one a paint job
or something?
I think that's
a very good idea.
What are you
laughing at?
We came out of it
ahead anyway.
Shouldn't be
a total loss.
A word to the wise now
to the garbage collectors
of the world,
to the curio seekers,
to the antique buffs,
to everyone who would try
to coax out a miracle
from unlikely places.
Check that bottle you're taking
back for a two-cent deposit.
The genie you save
might be your own.
Case in point,
mr. And mrs. Arthur castle,
fresh from
the briefest of trips
into the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator of the twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, we take you
into this 8x8 hotel room,
and we watch a penny-ante crook
make a decision.
You better ask the room clerk
the number of this room,
and then come on up.
Mr. Joe mantell is the nervous
man in the four dollar room.
That'sthe twilight zone
next week,
and we'll be waiting for you.
Thank you and good night.
Be sure and see
the colgate-palmolive company's
new comedy show
my sister eileen
wednesday night
on many of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org