Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
"Sometime during the morning,
"the rear door of the antique
shop was jimmied open.
"The police surmised
that the thief,
"obviously working
with an accomplice,
"entered and began to remove
items from the shelves.
"Mr. And mrs. Jensen j. Brown,
the proprietors of the shop,
"listed the following
collector's items
"as among the goods stolen:
Two vases
of the ming dynasty..."
i don't know what
dynasty they're from,
but they ain't mings.
There are from
some rummage sale.
They're worth about
a half a shuck apiece.
Chester!
Larceny! Plain, no-good larceny.
He's padding that list
for his insurance.
How do you like
a crook like that?
"An antique silver
service for 12,
a louis xiv candelabra,
a queen anne chest..."
aphony
louis xiv candelabra,
a set of u.s. Navy
surplus tableware,
a chest worth
maybe $3.50 tops.
"Three oil paintings
by picasso..."
three posters
in frames.
The guy that painted these
thinks a picasso
is a foreign sports car.
"Two teakwood, hand-carved
cigarette
cases..."
aw, knock it off.
Knock it off.
Hey, they forgot this-
an antique camera, no less.
Big deal.
Well, fits with
the rest of the haul.
Everything else is for nothing.
Figures we get a camera
that's for nothing.
A hotel suite that,
in this instance,
serves as a den of crime.
The aftermath
of a rather minor event
to be noted
in a police blotter,
an insurance claim,
perhaps a three-inch box
on page 12
of the evening paper.
Small addenda to be added to
a camera.
A most unimposing addition
to the flotsam and jetsam
that it came with.
Hardly worth mentioning, really,
because cameras are cameras:
Some expensive, some purchasable
at five-and-dime stores.
But this camera...
this one's unusual because,
in just a moment,
we'll watch it inject itself
into the destinies
of three people.
It happens to be a fact
that the pictures that it takes
can only be developed
in the twilight zone.
Big deal.
You know, 20 years ago,
you could get one of these
in a drugstore for 39 cents.
I got to pick it up in a heist.
Look at the crummy thing.
No place to put
the film in.
No place
to even open it.
Huh! Some crazy
foreign writing.
This must
be the clicker.
Hey, baby, get over
there by the window.
Come on, take a pose.
Aha...
say cheese.
Cheese.
Nothing.
Aw, big deal.
The whole haul
is worth maybe $5.80.
A good fence
will give us a buck.
You and your curio shops.
Mycurio shops?
Who cased the place?
Who fingered it?
Who did all
the planning?
Listen to miss culture of 1960.
Patron of the arts.
"Never mind hock
shops," she says.
"Let's get up
in life," she says.
"Let's knock over
a curio shop
"on account of
curio shops are loaded
with objets d'art
worth a fortune."
Two weeks
of planning,
one whole night
on the heist,
and what have
we got for it?
400 pounds of junk.
I could have shot pool
for a whole day and made more.
Look, baby,
the next time
you get a hot idea
on a heist...
well, how
do i look?
Well, isn't that nice?
And so clear, chet.
Can you imagine that?
No flashbulbs or anything.
And look how
clear it is.
What's the matter
with you?
withme?
Get over there by the mirror. What?
Go on. Go look
at yourself in the mirror.
Are you missing
a couple of buttons?
You go ahead and look.
So, what's to see?
Now look at
the picture.
So, there i am
standing by the window
wearing a... fur coat?!
Chet, what am i doing
wearing a fur coat?
I wasn't wearing a fur coat
when you took that picture.
I don't even
own a fur coat.
I get it.
Camera's strictly
for laughs.
Strictly for laughs.
It's a gag camera.
What do you mean?
Look, look.
They've already got the
pictures developed inside.
The negatives have
got pictures on them.
All this does is take the faces. What?
You know, like in a carnival,
when you stand back of
that crazy cardboard thing.
You know, fat lady, guy driving
a car, sailor. You know.
Well, that's what this is.
Hey, that's not bad.
That's pretty clever.
We might as well clear up
the rest of this junk.
Let's get at that chest.
Key come with this?
No. You'll
have to open it
in your own
inimitable style.
Anybody ever tell you
you got
a nasty disposition?
If i have
a nasty disposition,
it's because i'm married
to a nickel-and-dime heister
who can't tell a real
diamond from a baseball.
Look, baby doll,
this suite
is 28 bucks a day
delivered and paid for
by mrs. Diedrich's
son, chester,
on profits collected
over a potful of years
when you weren't
even in the picture.
Matter of fact,
i need you
like i need a three-
time conviction.
Hey!
Oh, look.
Oh!
Well, how do
you like this?
And don't start
giving me
any of that
cheap pizzazz
about taking this
to any fence.
This belongs to
little old paula.
And don't try to
argue with me either.
Well, how do i look?
All right,
cue me.
What's the matter?
What are you doing?
Come on back to bed.
Still with that?
Shut up.
So what do you care?
Want me to let
it go by, huh?
So what do you care?
So it's a crazy camera.
So it takes dopey pictures
that really aren't there.
Yeah, it takes dopey pictures.
Dopey pictures like things
that haven't happened yet,
but they do happen.
So what's
to do, chet?
One lousy,
kooky picture
and you
get insomnia.
So it's a camera,
that's all.
Here, i'll
show you.
There. See?
Any lightning?
Drop it,
why don't you?
Let it go.
Forget it.
How can i forget it?
This thing could come
from witches or... sorcerers.
It could be loaded
with black magic.
And what are
you loaded with?
Do you see
anything?
Where's the man
with the horns
who comes in
with a bargain
for the soul?
It's a kooky camera,
that's all.
Well?
It's my brother woodward...
standing
by the door.
Yeah.
That's who it is.
That cheap, no-good
brother of yours.
It can't be.
He's in jail.
Seven years for
breaking and entering,
and that was
only a year ago.
Oh, no. No, chet.
It's throwing
us a curve.
Maybe it's somebody
who just looks
like woodward.
Nobody looks
Look.
Chester, i'm scared.
I'm palpitating.
You and your phony
palpitations, you...
a little palpitating
never hurt anybody.
What's there to
be scared about?
The thing has obviously
gone tilt or something.
Look. Now, look.
Woodward isn't here.
Woodward couldn't
possibly be here.
Woodward's not
going to be here.
He's serving time.
He's 900 miles away
in a cell block.
I don't care what
that crazy camera says.
Whoever is
in this picture,
it is not woodward.
Woodward.
Hi, paula. Hi, chet.
I didn't want to wake you,
so i jimmied the door open.
I broke out-
me and another guy-
in a laundry truck.
That's nice, huh?
I didn't think you'd mind if
i stay with you for a few days.
Well, you don't, do you?
I was thinking,
if i was around,
you two wouldn't
fight so much.
You still all the time fighting?
What's this, chet?
How do you like that?
There i am,
standing by this door,
wearing the clothes
i got on.
How about that?
I tell you,
science is wonderful.
To be able to take
a picture of a...
wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
Like, uh... how come?
I still don't know
how we can use it.
Strictly for laughs.
Imagine trying
to sell an item like that.
They'd throw you out.
They'd say
you're off your rocker.
They'd burn you at the stake.
One thing or the other.
Hey, maybe
we could sell tickets.
Take pictures like at a carny,
and then...
well, maybe we could, uh...
well, you know, like that.
Well, i'm going
to lay it on the line.
What are we?
I asked you a question.
What are we, chet?
We're people.
Yeah, but what kind of people?
We're three small-time heisters.
Well, now we've
finally got something
that might do something good
for somebody else.
Science could use
something like this.
Who?
Science.
We got something here
for humanity.
Who?
Humanity.
You got a leak in your attic?
What's humanity
ever done for us?
Sure, paula, sure.
That's what i meant.
Just what you said.
That's the way we are.
Everything
for us.
Nothing for
anybody else.
I've risen above all that now.
I say, let's give this
to the world.
Here, world.
A gift from chester diedrich
and his wife.
And me, too, chet.
Don't forget woodward.
Yeah. And you, too, woodward.
Here, world.
A gift for humanity.
A gesture.
A gesture to show
the size of the heart
of chester diedrich
and wife.
And
woodward.
Yeah, that's better.
Isn't there something
you want to watch on tv?
Oh, yeah.
You know, paula,
this could be
a very important
scientific discovery.
There's no telling what medical
science may do with this.
How can you know...?
A half-length, a full-length,
and hot foot takes it
by a length and a half.
Jerry slash second by two,
easter baby third.
The rest of the field
is strung out.
$24.90 to win, $15.80 and $6.70.
In just a few minutes,
the second race of the day,
the los tendres handicap.
Shut that thing off.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
I got it.
I've got it, i've got it.
What is it,
chester?
This thing takes pictures
of things that happen
five minutes
before they happen,
but they happen!
I'll tell you
what we're going to do.
We're going to take a picture
of the winning board
at the racetrack...
before the race.
The winning board
before the race, get it?
No, i don't get it.
Wait a minute.
We take a picture
of the winning board,
and then we
look at it.
Oh, chester!
We getting through
to you, woodward?
Look, we take a picture
of the winning board.
There's nothing on it
because the race
hasn't been run yet,
but we got
a little camera here
that takes pictures
five minutes
before they happen.
So the picture has the
winning numbers on the board.
We know what horse won.
We know how much he paid.
Now do you get it?
Yeah!
Now i get it.
Okay, everybody,
get your coats.
Grab one of mine,
and be sure to put on a tie.
Okay, chet?
Let's see now.
That was
the first race...
we can still catch
the last six.
Hey, wait a minute.
How much money
have we got?
I got a ten
and a 20.
That's $30.
I know it's $30.
I got... $180.
Woodward,
you got money?
Yeah, i got ten.
That gives us
220 bucks.
Is that enough?
We're bound to hit
one long shot,
maybe two.
We'll parlay this
into a million bucks.
We can't lose, paula!
We can't lose! Come on!
Hey, wait a minute, chet!
Wait a minute.
What about humanity?
What did humanity
ever do for us?
Come on!
We got us
an idea.
Oh, boy, chester! Oh, boy!
Look, my ribs aren't hurting
your elbow any, are they?
Keep it quiet.
Let me get the shot.
Okay.
Ah-ah-ah.
Well?
There's numbers on it.
6, 3, 11.
Look what
number six pays.
$47.60 to win.
Oh, boy,
chester!
Let me see.
Number six, number six...
tidy too.
Okay, boys and girls,
our money goes on tidy too.
Here. You take care of baby.
Going wide, can't hold the rail.
And tidy too moves into the hole
on the rail and moves fast.
Tidy too. Tidy too.
Come on, number six.
And sir rinos falls back.
Come on, come on, tidy too.
Come on, tidy too.
Come on, horsey!
Tidy too.
Come on, come on.
Come on, tidy too.
We won.
9,500 bucks... oh!
Here we go.
Chet, go get the money.
Yeah. Be right back.
Watch the camera.
Thank you.
Open the bag, honey.
I've run out of pockets.
Look at
the loot.
95 times to win,
number four.
90...
91...
92...
93...
94...
95.
How soon can
you make delivery
on something like that?
No, no, no. Not black.
It's got to be yellow
with black upholstery.
Yeah. Wire wheels,
dual exhausts,
continental kit-
the works.
Right. And how much was it?
$11,000.
11 grand.
No, i'm not backing out.
I'm thinking about whether
i want to get two or not.
Okay, you bring the papers
around in the morning.
We'll settle the whole deal.
Right, no, no, no.
I'll pay cash. Yeah.
That must
be the waiter.
Are you finished with
your snack, woodward, dear?
Yeah. That'll hold
me till dinner.
Come in.
I came for the dishes, madam.
Right here.
Could you possibly
bring us back
a couple bottles
of champagne?
Yes, ma'am, i can.
Hey, put that down.
Oh, let him
look at it.
Bet you never saw
anything like that.
Mais non.
Most unusual, sir.
Isn't it, though?
You don't knowhowunusual.
But what do you do
after your ten pictures?
Is there any other way
to get more film?
We've only had it
a little while.
What did you say?
What about ten pictures?
Well, the inscription reads,
"dix a la proprietaire."
That means, "ten to an owner."
Well, i presume
that means
you may
only take ten.
So odd.
Yes, you see,
the lettering...
yeah, okay,
pierre.
Don't forget
the champagne.
You're going to have
to get it for her.
If we want anything
else, we'll call you.
Okay, boy. Bye.
How many pictures
did we take?
There was one of you.
One of
woodward.
How many we take
at the track?
Six... six races.
We've taken
eight pictures.
There's only
two left.
Ten.
How do we know
that's what it means?
Some smart-aleck
french waiter
tells us it means ten,
so we figure we've
only got two left.
How does he know?
I bet we can take
as many as we want.
We can't take
any chances.
Yeah, she's right.
You know what i think?
I think we
ought to sell it.
Who's rattling
your cage, ape?
It doesn't
belong to you.
You're here
on charity.
We're going out to
the track tomorrow
and bet
two more races.
Are you
both crazy?
We got to hang on
to it and save it.
No, we don't,
we got to sell it.
You made me
waste a picture.
Ooh,
palpitations!
Palpitations.
Phony palpitations
and a stupid brother!
I don't have to
take that guff.
All right, all right.
Here, woodward,
take a drink.
That's better.
She's screaming.
Why do you think she's
screaming, woodward?
I'll tell you
why she's screaming.
Because somebody's trying
to do something to her husband.
Some stupid, no-good ex-con
who wants to get that camera
and doesn't care how.
Don't!
Don't do it,
chet.
Put that knife away.
Chester!
If she's screaming
in that picture,
she's because somebody's trying
to hurt her loving brother.
Boys! Woodward!
No, please.
Put it away or i'll
take off your skin.
Please, don't.
Oh, chester.
Oh, my.
My husband... woodward.
I'll die.
There's nothing left for me.
Nothing.
However, we must muddle
through these things.
We must live with tragedy.
Poor woodward. Poor chester.
One more picture left.
Ha!
For posterity, boys.
Simply for posterity.
May you both rest in peace.
What do you want?
Pardonnez-moi.
Madame, i understand
there is something
in the way of laundry
that i should take.
You've got
the wrong room.
There's no laundry
here, jack.
In fact,
i'm checking out.
So i understand,
madame.
Your two friends,
they already checked out.
What are
you doing?!
I told you i was here
to take the laundry.
I'm- how do you say? -
cleaning you out.
Cleaning me out?
What do you think
i'll be doing
while you do that?
Well, i'll cue you.
I'm going to be
calling the cops.
The cops?
Oh, you mean
the police?
Madame will forgive me
but, if you call the police,
madame will get herself
into- how you say? -
one fantastic bind.
Now this here,
this is- how you say? -
up for grabs.
Dear lady, i know
all about you now.
I have done some checking.
Your husband,
your brother and you,
you are wanted.
Now, as for the police,
i would advise you
to get out while you can.
When they discover
what is down in
the courtyard there,
they will be up here
sans invitation.
Without invitation.
Uninvited.
You- how you say? - You dig?
Now, as to the laundry,
this may be back by thursday
or maybe friday...
or maybe never.
But i'm not a hog.
This one, i will leave with you.
Sacre nom.
There is a picture
of the courtyard down below,
but there are
more than two bodies.
More than two bodies?
Yes, there are more
than two bodies down there.
Just like the picture shows-
one, two, three...
four!
Object known as a camera-
vintage uncertain,
origin unknown.
But, for the greedy, the
avaricious, the fleet of foot
who can run a four-minute mile
so long as they're chasing
a fast buck,
it makes believe that it's
an ally, but it isn't at all.
It's a beckoning come-on
for a quick walk around
the block in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
This may look to you
like any dismal,
dark and dingy alley
that lies skulking off a million
myriad shadow-places
off the main drags.
Actually, it's the private
domain of leprechauns and elves,
and supplies the locale
of next week'stwilight zone.
With us for a very special
occasion is mr. Art carney,
who plays the role of
a department store santa claus,
and he plays it with the heart,
the warmth and the vast talent
that is uniquely carney.
Onthe twilight zonenext week,
"the night of the meek."
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
be sure and see
the colgate-palmolive company's
new comedy show
my sister eileen
wednesday night
on many of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org