Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it
is another dimension-
a dimension of sound...
a dimension of sight...
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
And you?
All right, fine.
Enjoy your flight.
Well, hello.
Those all right?
Yeah. They're fine.
Give me that.
Do you want me to sit
next to the window?
No.
I'm fine.
I can f...
honey, what is it?
The emergency window?
Do you want to move?
No, no, no.
Doesn't matter.
What's the
difference
where i sit?
It's not the seat.
It's the airplane.
Honey, don't smoke that now.
Wait till the plane
takes off.
I'm not acting much
like a cured man, am i?
Honey, you are cured.
Dr. Martin wouldn't let you fly
if you weren't, would he?
I suppose not.
I mean,
if you weren't well,
dr. Martin just wouldn't let you
fly all the way back home.
It's just that simple.
Well, you make it
sound simple anyway.
It is, bob.
Yeah.
Here i am
hogging the whole state,
and you're so tired.
I've missed you...
these last six months.
It's all over now, though,
and mama's taking you home.
It must have been
awful for you-
taking care
of the kids...
bearing the full
responsibility.
Well, everything
is still intact.
Except me.
Bob, i'm not
going to let...
cabin door secured.
What?
Just a little...
abject cowardice,
that's all.
I'm going to be all right.
Had a teensy weensy breakdown,
but now i'm cured.
Understanding- it's wonderful.
It isn't the airplane at all.
Overtension and overanxiety
due to underconfidence.
Your seat belt, sir.
Portrait of a frightened man:
Mr. Robert wilson- 37,
husband, father and salesman
on sick leave.
Mr. Wilson has just been
discharged from a sanitarium
where he spent
the last six months
recovering
from a nervous breakdown,
the onset of which took place
on an evening
not dissimilar to this one
on an airliner
very much like the one
in which mr. Wilson
is about to be flown home-
the difference being that,
on that evening half a year ago,
mr. Wilson's flight
was terminated
by the onslaught
of his mental breakdown.
Tonight, he's traveling
all the way
to his appointed destination
which,
contrary to mr. Wilson's plan,
happens to be
in the darkest corner
of the twilight zone.
Fasten your seat belt, sir.
I'm sorry, darling.
Go back to sleep.
I shouldn't have taken
that sleeping pill.
I should stay awake
with you.
No, i don't
want you to.
Go back to sleep.
I'm all right.
Can't you sleep?
I will.
Don't worry about me.
Okay.
Here, quickly!
May i help you?
There's a man
out there.
What?
Look, he's crawling on...
i'm...
i'm sorry.
Must have been the...
bob? What is it?
Oh, it's nothing,
mrs. Wilson.
Can i get you
anything?
A glass of water.
Surely.
Is something wrong?
No. I thought i saw
something out there.
What?
Nothing.
I guess i need a little sleep.
Are you all right?
Yeah, fine.
Don't you think
you ought to take
a sleeping pill now?
Yeah, i'll take
one of those.
Here you are.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Can i get you
a blanket?
No. Honey?
Oh. No, thanks.
You going
to be all right now?
Yeah. Fine.
Will you wake me
if you need me?
I will.
It isn't there.
Honey? Would you
wake up, honey?
Quickly.
Yes, mr. Wilson?
Can i help you,
mr. Wilson?
Are we going
into a storm?
Just a small one.
Nothing to worry about.
Honey...
would you wake up,
please, honey?
Honey.
Julia, wake up.
What?
What are you looking at?
Bob?
Is it the storm?
Does it bother you?
No.
Honey, you remember
what i told you before
about seeing
something outside?
Yes.
Julia, there's
a man out there.
L-i don't mean a man.
I mean a...
i don't know what i mean.
I mean...
maybe a...
what did they call them
during the war-
you know, the pilots-
gremlins.
Gremlins!
You remember
the stories in the...
julia, don't look at me
like that.
Bob...
i am not imagining it.
I'm not imagining it.
He's out there.
Don't look!
He's not there now.
He...
...jumps away
whenever anyone
might see him.
Except me.
Honey, he's there.
I realize what
this sounds like.
Do i look insane?
No, darling, no.
I know i had a mental breakdown.
I know i had it in an airplane.
I know it looks as if
the same thing's happening,
but it isn't.
I'm sure it isn't.
Look, the reason
i'm telling you this...
isn't just to worry you.
You notice
i didn't tell you before.
I want you to tell me.
I didn't tell you before
because i wasn't sure
whether it was real or not,
but i am sure now.
It is real.
There's a man out there!
Or... a... a gremlin, or...
whatever it...
if i described him to you,
you'd really think i was gone.
No, darling,
it's all right, it's all right.
Julia, i know
your intentions are good.
I know you love me
and sympathize with me,
but don't patronize me.
I am not insane!
Did i say...?
It doesn't have
to be said.
It's in your face,
in your...
look, for the last time,
that creature's out there
and the reason
i'm telling you is
he's starting to tamper
with one of the engines.
Look. Look.
Look. Think
anything you want.
Think... i belong
in a straightjacket
if it pleases you.
If it pleases me?
No, l-i didn't mean that.
What i mean is...
whatever you think of me-
that i'm losing
my mind, anything-
all i'm asking
you to do
is to tell the pilots
what i've said.
Ask them to keep
an eye on the wings.
If they see nothing...
...all right.
All right, then i'll...
commit myself. I'll...
but if they do...
won't you even
allow the possibility?
I'll tell them.
I know it's...
asking a lot. I...
it's like asking you to...
advertise your marriage
to a lunatic.
No, i'll tell them.
You just sit tight,
and i'll go tell them.
Mrs. Wilson,
what's the problem?
My husband
wants to see
the flight engineer.
All right,
i'll get him.
Thank you.
It's very
important.
Hurry, please.
Hurry! Hurry!
He's out there!
What's going on?
He's pulling up
one of the cowling plates.
"He"?
Didn't my wife...?
There's a man out there!
Keep your voice down.
I'm sorry,
i'm sorry.
I don't know
what's going on here...
will you look?
Mr. Wilson,
i'm warning you.
Will you please look?
In the name of...!
Well?
No, wait a minute.
I saw him pull
that plate up.
I said i saw him
pull that plate up!
Mr. Wilson, please.
All right, you saw him,
but there are
other people aboard.
We mustn't alarm them.
You mean, you've seen him too?
Of course we have,
but we don't want to
frighten the passengers.
You can understand that.
Of course. Of...
i understand.
Now, the thing
we've got to remember...
you can stop now.
Bob...
sir...
get out of here.
Mr. Wilson...
i said you can stop.
Honey, what is it?
I won't say
another word.
I'll see us crash first.
Bob!
Mr. Wilson, try to
understand our position.
Honey,
i'll be right back.
He did pull it up.
He did.
Honey, i was going
to tell them when you...
were you?
For me?
Please, bob.
You'll sleep.
You'll sleep now,
darling.
Sure.
Oh, boy.
What did you do?
Get his wife to give
him those pills?
He'll be out for hours.
I hope so- the way
the storm is coming up.
Don't worry,
everything's fine.
I hope so.
Honey? Honey,
would you get me
a glass of
water, please?
A glass of water,
please. Hurry.
Nuttiest way
of trying to commit suicide
i ever heard of.
It's all right now,
darling.
I know,
but i'm the only one
who does know...
right now.
The flight of mr. Robert wilson
has ended now,
a flight not only
from point "a" to point "b,"
but also from the fear
of recurring mental breakdown.
Mr. Wilson
has that fear no longer.
Though, for the moment,
he is, as he has said,
alone in this assurance.
Happily, his conviction
will not remain isolated
too much longer, for happily,
tangible manifestation
is very often left
as evidence of trespass,
even from
so intangible a quarter
as the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next time onthe twilight zone,
we probe into
the element of time
and present a very oddball opus
entitled,
"a kind of a stopwatch."
We tell the story of a man,
a stopwatch,
and an incredible deviation
from the norm,
said norm being
the usual 24 hour day,
said deviation
involving what happens
when a stopwatch is pushed and
everything stop, not just time.
To titillate and intrigue-
"a kind of a stopwatch."
Next ontwilight zone.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org