Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Well, how
did you do?
It's repairable.
But i won't be able to touch
any of those gimbal bearings
until they cool off.
It's like a furnace
in there now.
And that grand moment
will come when?
Maybe tomorrow night...
the following morning.
That's a swig
from the old bottle, isn't it?
Oh, you sure picked a nice place
to set down, fletcher-
the floor of a canyon.
I took you to the first mass
of land that loomed up.
And just for the record,
mr. Craig,
i didn't pepper the nose of
that vehicle with meteor holes.
I also didn't foul up
those rocket boosters.
That's something
you can chalk up to nature.
All right, all right.
It just strikes me as kind of
a deadhead place to set down-
on the floor
of a canyon.
"Food concentrate, comma,
able-1-6-3, comma-
modified dinner plan."
Whoever invented
this stuff
must have had
stomach trouble.
A very bitter
character
with no compassion
for his fellow men
or their stomachs.
Oh, there may come
a moment in time
when i'll enjoy this.
There may come a moment
when you'll lick a rock
as if it were
a thanksgiving turkey,
but for the time
being, buddy,
you'll eat
what is prescribed to eat!
If you've got
any set of complaints,
you put them down
in a ledger;
don't spray them
all over me!
It's a waste
of effort.
It's also dull,
and it's tough to live with.
You read me, craig?
Loud and clear.
Then dwell on it!
And while
you're dwelling on it
you might count
a few blessings.
We don't have
much food or water,
but we landed in a place
where there's oxygen
and we can survive.
We walked away from it
without a single bone
out of place.
The standing order
is as follows:
You got tears to shed,
save them for night
and weep them
into your pillow.
Don't bother me
with them!
Now how do you read me?
Still loud and
clear, commander.
But there are times
when a man gets
sick to death
of being led around
by the nose.
That's a big thing with
you, isn't it, craig?
What is?
Taking orders,
being on the receiving
end of a command.
It's hard for you to
live with, isn't it?
If i had my druthers
i might stick in
a few changes.
Hmm, like what?
Say again?
I mean, beyond us
getting out of here.
Let's say this is
the end of the line.
Now, how would you
sweeten the pot?
A sirloin steak,
a blonde, what?
How about
mumblety-peg, fletcher?
Or maybe 20 questions?
Look, try me
after dinner...
i may feel up
to charades.
Point of interest
is all.
I'm just interested
in what makes you tick.
Or maybe it's what makes
you tick so loudly.
What do you hunger
for most, craig?
Try this one, fletch...
i'd like a whole lot
of people at my elbow:
The more the merrier,
the louder the better,
and i'd like yankee stadium
right alongside.
But i'd like them on my terms.
That's what i'm getting at.
What are your terms?
I'd like to be
the number one straw boss.
I'dlike to give the orders.
Uh-huh...
i'll bet you would.
What's the
matter?
matter with you?
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
That sound.
What sound?
Fletch, i heard something...
i... i heard a sound...
a sound like... like...
a sound
like what?
Voices.
People.
The time is the space age.
The place is a barren landscape
of a rock-walled canyon
that lies millions of miles
from the planet earth.
The cast of characters?
You've met them-
william fletcher,
commander of the spaceship;
his copilot, peter craig.
The other characters who inhabit
this place you may never see,
but they're there,
as these two gentlemen
will soon find out.
Because they're about to partake
in a little exploration
into that gray, shaded area
in space and time
that's known
as the twilight zone.
Well, where has
my wandering boy been
most of the day?
You take a lot
of walks, buddy.
Something better to do?
Yeah, there is.
Like, uh,
checking over a radio,
like looking over
a hydraulic system,
a propulsion system,
an ejection system,
a thrust chamber.
Yeah, there are a few things.
Where are you spending most
of your time these days?
Still hearing
your voices?
Maybe.
You know, i think it would be
an exceptionally good idea
if you'd get to work
on those charts again.
It's hot, isn't it?
Passable.
You some kind of a camel, craig?
What do you mean?
I haven't seen you
take any water.
Well, uh...
i'm a whiskey man myself,
or hadn't you noticed?
You're going to have
to do better than that.
Why, what gives,
craig?
Say again?
Your ears
don't lap.
Your water hasn't been
touched in 24 hours.
Now, you couldn't
have discovered
any mountain
stream up there
and kept it all
for your lonesome?
Why don't you
talk sense...
why don't you?!
For the last
two days
you've been taking
off on safari
every morning when
that double sun comes up.
Where do you go, craig,
and what do you find
wherever it is you do go?
I'll tell you what...
let's you and me make
that trek together, huh?
Thanks, but no thanks.
I'm tired.
Look, craig...
where'd you find this?
Uh, i... i... i told you-
i've been
looking around.
It's wet.
You found water,
didn't you?
Where?
About a
mile ahead...
it's just a crummy
little stream...
but enough for you
to drink out of!
Aw, come on, fletch,
i was going to
show it to you.
As a matter of fact,
i've been testing it.
I just found out it was
pure a little bit ago.
You know,
i underrated you, mister.
I knew you were
a grousing malcontent,
but i didn't know
you were a cheat!
It's just a variety
of lichen...
you don't mind
if i look at it
through the
magnifier, do you?
Or have you done
that already?
Trees.
Yes, that's what they are...
trees.
I might as well go
the whole route now.
They were alongside
of a stream...
it runs about 100 feet.
It's about
2½ inches wide.
If you think that's something...
look at this.
Look at it!
Then...
the voices?
You want to see
more, fletch?
Yeah... yeah,
i sure do.
Come on.
It's fantastic.
To us, that stream
is just a stream.
That clump of little green weeds
is so much moss.
But they are trees,
and that stream is a river,
and if you look closely-
i mean, really close-
you'll see a
couple of items
that aren't par
for the course.
It's incredible.
It's a whole race of people
no bigger than ants.
Yeah, a whole
race of people.
And while you were
preoccupying yourself
with gluing
together an engine
i was making contact.
In their language?
I don't know it yet,
and they don't know ours,
but they know mathematics.
That's the language i've used-
symbols, equations,
number progressions.
And they're bright,
they learn fast.
And cooperative, fletch!
You wouldn't believe
how cooperative they are!
I've told them all my wants.
They've shown me where
the edible plants are.
Last night,
i ate up one of their forests.
What else did you tell them?
Oh, basic stuff:
Where we're from,
how we got here,
what's it's like on earth,
how advanced we are.
But i've only scratched
the surface, fletcher.
I've only just begun.
Begun what?
What do you think?
All my life
i've wanted to sit
in front of the wagon
and hold the reins.
Well, what do you think
i've got here now?
A whole race
of little people
who look up to me like
a giant out of the sky.
They're scared,
fletch, petrified.
And so they do
what they're told.
Because this giant...
is like some avenging
angel to them.
I've graduated, fletcher,
from a slob with a slide rule
to... to...
to a god.
Craig, they're people.
They're flesh and blood.
They're no different than us!
Sure they are.
Because they've been created
inmyimage.
Stop it!
You're no god, craig.
That's not what
you are at all!
The only trouble
is that...
by now you've probably
gotten them
to believe in the devil.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Please forgive us.
Forgive us, please.
Craig!
Top of the morning,
commander.
Hear what i said?
Top of the morning,
commander.
Even gods have to observe
some of the amenities.
Good likeness, huh?
The little people
did that.
They did it overnight.
Ah, you should
have seen them.
A very impressive sight,
commander.
A thousand of them
working from the ground up
like the egyptian slaves
on the pyramids,
like the lilliputians
with gulliver.
A very impressive sight,
commander.
What do you give them
in return, craig?
My smiling beneficence.
I won't tramp my feet down
on their town.
They picked themselves
a corker of a deity.
It's too bad they don't know
who they're breaking
their backs for.
Meaning what?
They're worshipping
a heartless slob
whose insides are the
same as that statue's!
Yeah, it's a good
likeness, craig.
And an hour from now
they can sell it for junk!
Now, let's get
back to the ship,
we're taking off.
What do
you mean?
The ship's repaired.
We'll start
the countdown
in 15 minutes.
The orbital position
here is perfect.
You fixed the ship?
Yeah, i did, ineed.
And a hundred years from now,
when your little friends
realize how they got taken,
and that i'm the guy
that removed you
from their lives,
who knows...
...maybe they'll
build a statue to me.
Now it's a pity
they can't capture
that look, craig,
that clinical look.
Sick, scared little man,
full of delusions of grandeur.
Let's go, buddy,
we haven't a...
this one you'll have to navigate
on your own.
Put the gun away, craig.
After i see you climb
aboard that ship
and take off.
Throw your gun
over here.
Sick, sure, but just how sick
i didn't realize.
You've only got
about 12 minutes, commander.
You can waste them
psychoanalyzing me
or you can play it smart,
get aboard
that ship
and head
for home.
I'm staying behind.
Why, craig?
Reason this one out, will you?
Will you reason this one out?
You'll play make-believe
for another 48 hours,
then you're going
to crack wide open.
Yeah, you'll have
a million little microbes
honoring you
with torchlight parades,
but you're going to die
of loneliness, buddy.
Come on...
put the gun away
and come with me, huh?
Did you hear what i said?
You're down to eight minutes,
commander.
If you're still here
eight minutes from now,
i'm going to have to kill you.
This is
a monotheistic
society here-
just room for one god.
Take off!
Craig, i feel sorry
for you, buddy.
I really do.
All right, my little friends,
comes now the new age.
The age of...
the age of peter craig.
Oh, my little friends,
we've got
a lot of plans to make.
A lot of projects to work out.
Much work.
A whole lot of work.
That's a reminder,
little friends,
there must be discipline here.
Discipline above all.
There'll be periodic moments
where i must remind you
that you must not anger me.
That's important now.
You must not anger me.
Let us begin
to build the statue again.
Let us to commence to begin.
It's just a ship,
that's all it is.
Now, if you keep quiet,
they'll go away, understand?
If you just keep quiet,
it'll go away.
See, i told you
it would go away.
Go away!
You can't stay here!
Don't you understand?!
I'm the god!
I'm the god,
don't you understand?!
I'm the god!
What have you got?
A man.
A tiny little man.
Why, you've crushed
him to death.
I didn't mean to.
Say, do you suppose
there are more
of them down there?
I don't know. What's
the difference?
We're not
here exploring.
We're here
making repairs.
Come on, come on,
let's get out of here.
The case
of navigator peter craig-
a victim of a delusion.
In this case, the dream dies
a little harder than the man.
A small exercise
in space psychology
that you can try on for size
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, an exceptionally fine
actor named theodore bikel
portrays a misguided kook
who fancies himself some kind
of guardian of law and order.
He decides
that it's his mission in life
to eradicate evil
the world over.
Now this one is told
very far out,
but considering
the nature of the times,
it happens to be very close in.
Next week,
an exercise in insanity.
It's called "four o'clock."
Set your watches and come on in.
This cigarette-
chesterfield king-
gives all the advantages
of extra length and much more.
The great taste
of 21 vintage tobaccos
grown mild, aged mild
and blended mild.
No wonder they satisfy
so completely.
This is james arness.
You know, it's only a short hop
fromthe twilight zone
to dodge city ingunsmoke.
Saturday nights
over most of these stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org