Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Charley. Charley!
Recess.
Oh, uh, thank you.
I just want
to finish up here.
You trying to make us
look bad, charley?
What do you mean?
Now, just what
do you think i mean?
Forget it.
Come on, we're
going to be late.
Look at him.
Little goody two-shoes.
Oh, i'm sorry,
excuse me.
Now we're going to take a look
at one of the world's greatest
examples of primitive art.
Some of the pieces-
the shields, for example-
are hundreds
of years old,
but some were made
as recently as 1950.
Now, the reason
for this is that, uh,
some parts of africa
are still largely unexplored
and, therefore,
unspoiled land.
Some natives
in the interior
have never seen
a white man,
and they'll live and die
without realizing
the world extends
beyond the limits
of their jungle.
Oh, uh, uh,
by the way,
you know
these natives speak
over 500
different languages?
However, uh,
you ladies of the art
appreciation society
will notice that their art
has a great unity.
Each piece here has been carved
for a specific purpose.
Now, this one...
can you all see it?
Now, this was made
to frighten away
the evil spirits.
And this one
as a protection
against disease.
Now, in my hand
here...
i have a pestle,
you see.
And that is a mortar...
to the average person,
a museum is a place
of knowledge,
a place of beauty
and truth... and wonder.
Some people come to study,
others to contemplate,
others to look
for the sheer joy of looking.
Charley parkes has
his own reasons.
He comes to the museum
to get away from the world.
It isn't really
the 60-cent cafeteria meal
that has drawn him here
every day.
It's the fact that here
in these strange, cool halls,
he can be alone
for a little while-
really and truly alone.
Anyway, that's how it was
before he got lost
and wandered
into the twilight zone.
Uh, e-excuse me.
Oh, yes, sir?
I guess this
may sound silly,
but how do they
manage that?
How do they manage what?
In there, in
the glass case.
Oh, well... well,
i couldn't say exactly.
I know they use
magnifying glasses,
little tiny tools,
single-hair brushes,
things like that.
But mostly they keep
at their job
until they get
things right.
But how do they get
the girl to move?
Transistors?
How's that?
The girl playing
the piano.
Oh, it stopped now.
I don't think i...
i'll show you.
She was playing just
a few seconds ago.
It was, uh, uh,
something like this.
? dum, ta, da, dum, ta...?
Did you hear it?
Now, look, mister,
i don't like jokes-
not when i'm on duty,
anyway.
Oh, i'm not joking.
Well, then you're
hearing things.
There isn't any sound mechanism
in that piano,
and the doll was carved
out of wood,
a single block
of wood.
Now who's joking?
See for yourself.
Well, i'm, uh, sorry.
I could have sworn...
probably some kid
with one of those pocket radios.
They sneak them in
once in a while.
But i saw her move.
At least, i think i did.
You know better now, don't you?
Yes, i know better now.
Thank you. Uh, i'm sorry
to have bothered you.
No bother.
You're feeling all right now,
aren't you?
Yes, uh...
just a little embarrassed.
Well, is there anything
i can do for you?
Uh, no, i have to
be getting back...
oh, well, thanks
for your time.
Don't mention it.
Come in.
Sit down, mr. Parkes.
I'm sorry i'm
late, sir.
Well, i'm sure you have
a good excuse.
Well, no, sir, i don't.
I just let the time slip by.
I... i don't know
how it happened.
You know, parkes,
this is the first sign
of humanity you've shown
in almost four years.
I beg pardon?
Well, up until now,
you've come and gone
like some kind of wind-up toy.
You're never early.
You're never late.
You're always keeping
to yourself.
Don't you like us, parkes?
Uh, well, i never thought
about it, sir.
Well, think about it now.
Do you like
your fellow workers?
Well, i suppose so.
You suppose so?
Well... i never thought
about it, sir.
I don't dislike them.
You know, i'm afraid,
mr. Parkes,
that isn't good enough.
An office, uh,
is like a team,
a platoon.
Either it works together
or it doesn't.
Here, it doesn't,
and the reason is you.
I knew you were a square peg
when i hired you,
but you were bright,
and well, i thought
we'd wear those edges off.
We haven't.
None of them.
You're still a square peg.
You understand me?
Yes, sir, i think i do.
I was going to use the excuse
of your being late, but i can't.
The fact is
that i'm letting you go
because you just don't
fit in.
I understand, sir.
Uh, parkes.
Yes, sir?
I know this isn't
any of my business, but...
don't you think it's about time
you gave up living
with your mother?
Well, she needs me.
Why? Is she ill?
No, not actually ill.
You see, my father died
some time ago,
and my sister's married,
and, uh...
well, she needs me.
I see.
Well, you're welcome to stay on
a few weeks if...
uh, no, sir, that's very nice
of you, but i'll manage.
Thank you.
You can pick up
your check tomorrow.
Thank you.
He had no right.
He had every right,
mother.
Hiring and firing people
is his job.
But why you?
I told you;
he didn't think i fit in.
What's that mean?
It has something to do
with being on the team.
That's ridiculous.
What are
you going to do?
I'm going to
phone that man
and find out
just why
you're being
persecuted.
Mother, please don't.
It won't do any good.
Oh, charley,
what's going to
become of you?
I've worked so hard
trying to bring
you up right.
What have i
done wrong?
Have i been
too strict?
No, mother.
Or too lenient?
Maybe that's it.
Maybe if i'd let your
father punish you
the way he wanted to.
It's all right, mother.
It's just a minor setback.
Oh, you say
that every time.
Why can't you
keep a job, son?
Why do you
always end up
making everyone
feel uncomfortable
around you?
I don't know.
I suppose
they blame me.
Well, i'm not
keeping you here.
You're free to go.
I know that, mother.
Nothing in the world
would make
me happier
than to see
you settle down
with a nice girl,
raise a family
and live a
normal life.
Please, don't cry.
I can't help it.
I hate to see
you hurt, son.
I'm not hurt.
Well, you should be.
Getting fired.
It would have
killed your father.
killed him.
I'll go to the employment
bureau tomorrow.
Where are
you going?
To my room.
Charley, will you
please bring me
my heart
medicine, dear?
Charley, whywereyou late
getting back to the office?
I was, uh, detained.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Nothing. I was detained,
that's all.
Charley, do you
feel all right?
Yes, mother.
What's that
you're whistling?
Pardon?
You were whistling.
What was it?
Uh, i don't remember.
Mother!
Now, you lie
down, charley,
and take a
little nap.
All right.
Mother, please.
Why? I'm only trying to help.
I know it, mother,
and i appreciate it,
but i prefer to untie
my own shoes.
I'll bring you some cocoa.
Thank you.
Back again, huh?
Yes.
Charley, your
breakfast is
getting cold.
You see?
Late for his meals,
awake every night
tossing and turning.
I tell you, i'm half
dead from worry.
Mama...
he's sick.
I know he is.
Sounds to me like
he's got himself a girl.
Don't be silly.
What's so silly
about it?
I mean, charley's
a good-looking guy.
A little peculiar,
maybe, but, uh...
i only meant if he had a girl,
he'd tell me.
Isn't that right, myra?
Sure.
And he hasn't told me,
so it's not possible.
Okay, okay.
I'm not one of those mothers
who try
to keep their children
with them all the time.
Ask myra.
Pass the
butter, please.
Charley!
Your breakfast is
on the table getting cold.
I'm sorry.
Hey, hiya,
charley boy.
Hello, buddy,
how are you?
Couldn't be better, buddy,
couldn't be better.
Myra, you're
looking good.
Well, i wish i could say
the same for you, charley.
I haven't been
sleeping too well.
Because of what,
the job?
Yes, i suppose so.
It's been terribly hard on him
walking around every day
in the hot sun.
Boy, that can
get you down.
Charley...
yes?
We've got
a surprise for you.
Tell him, bud.
Well, it's like this,
charley.
I heard about them
giving you the roust.
I mean, you know...
and, uh, like, i know
the head dispatcher
pretty well
over where i work.
And i talked to him
about you,
and he said, uh...
well, he said he'd
give you the job!
Yeah.
Isn't that wonderful?
Charley.
That's very nice of you,
buddy, really.
Well, you've had
experience in billing,
haven't you, charley?
Yes.
Well, then what?
Well, l-i don't think i really
want to travel that far.
It's out of the city, isn't it?
Well, buddy
can pick you up
and bring you home.
Sure. Until you get
your own car, anyway.
Charley,
for heaven's sake,
don't just sit there.
Buddy's offering you a job.
I'm sorry.
I appreciate
it, really,
uh, but i'm
afraid i can't.
You got something
better?
Yes.
Charley.
Charley!
Good morning.
My mother says
that breakfast
is the most important meal
of the day.
Have i told you about my mother?
She's, uh, very nice.
Of course, she still
treats me like a child,
but you can't blame her,
because i'm all she has.
I suppose
that's not very much.
Of course, it isn't
any of my business,
but i really do think
you should eat more than that
for breakfast.
Oh, you know,
i have a sister about your age.
Her name's myra.
She's nice, too.
Her husband says
she's very pretty,
but she's not as
pretty as you are.
I guess you're
about the prettiest girl
in the whole world.
I don't mind
saying that
because i know
you can't hear me.
But i think i'd say it
even if you could,
because...
hi.
Little early today,
aren't you?
Yes.
I guess you must get a real kick
out of some of these displays.
Oh, yes, l-i...
this one here
in particular.
What do you see, mister?
Oh, nothing.
A man doesn't stand
for four or five hours
at a stretch
looking at nothing.
Well, i'm not breaking
any rules, am i?
No.
Then, uh...
leave me alone, please.
Well... all right.
Good morning.
That's a new dress,
isn't it?
I haven't seen it before.
Can i help you, miss?
Oh, no. Thank you.
Charley?
Oh, hello, myra.
What are you
doing here?
I was just passing by
and i saw you come in.
That's nice.
Buy me a cup of coffee?
Well, the
cafeteria's closed.
Well, we could go
somewhere else.
All right.
Thank you.
Charley, i want
to be honest with you.
I didn't just...
happen to... to see you.
I followed you.
Why?
Because mama
asked me to.
She's been worried about you,
charley, and so have i.
You haven't been yourself
lately.
No, i suppose i haven't.
Do you go to that place
every day?
Yes.
I thought it might be
a good idea to improve my mind.
That isn't why.
No?
No.
I'm your sister, charley.
I grew up with you,
and i know you.
And i love you.
You go there because it gives
you a chance to be alone,
and you want to be alone
because you're scared.
Myra...
charley, listen to me.
This is important.
You're over 30 years old,
and you're living exactly
the way you did
when you were 14.
Well, some of it's
mama's fault...
but some of it's yours.
And it's not natural,
charley.
It's sick.
Andyou know
it's sick,
and that's why
you're scared.
You're probably right.
Charley, stop agreeing
with me!
You agree with me all...
all the time.
I could say you were
a blue monkey,
and you'd agree.
No.
Look, charley,
i don't know anything
about psychology
or anything like that,
but i think i know
what's the matter with you.
You need a girl.
You're at that time
of life.
You know what i mean?
Well, not exactly.
Well, uh...
it's a little difficult
to explain, um...
but you've never had a girl,
have you, have you, charley?
Well, not actually.
That's what i thought.
Well... we are going to change
all of that.
How?
I am going
to introduce you
to harriet gunderson.
She's a girl
who works in my office,
and she's
a real swell kid.
You'll like her,
charley, really.
Myra...
oh, please, charley?
Just this one time.
Try. For me, huh?
And if you do,
i promise you i'll
never bother you again.
All right.
There's her address.
You don't even have
to phone.
You can just,
uh, pick her up.
About 8:00.
Charley.
Hmm?
What are you
thinking about?
Oh, nothing
in particular.
Boy, you sure
are quiet.
That means you're
thedangeroustype.
You can't trust
the quiet ones.
You can trust me.
Who says i want to?
Well, i only meant, uh...
you know, you
ought to...
relax... oh,
lean back.
Take it easy.
There.
Isn't that nicer?
Yes.
Charley?
Hmm?
Do you like me?
Very much.
Then why don't
you show it?
Well, how do you mean?
Well...
you might...
you might try
kissing me first.
Well... we hardly
even know each other.
We just met this evening.
Well, try anyway.
Ouch!
Oh, i'm sorry.
Please, let me
help you up.
Oh, forget
it, buster.
Just forget it.
And you tell your sister
you don't need a girl.
You need a doctor!
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
Then, uh, she told me
i needed a doctor
just because
i wouldn't kiss her.
I know that must be hard
for you to believe,
but that's the way
things are these days.
Of course, i realize she was
doing it as a favor to myra,
but even so...
run.
Run!
Don't you lay a hand on her.
Don't you touch her.
He was trying
to harm her.
What?
He tried to kiss her last night,
but she wouldn't let him,
so he came back.
Sure.
The maid... the maid
tried to stop him,
but he hit her over
the head with his cane.
Then he went after the girl.
She fainted, and he carried her
to the bedroom.
I had to stop him.
You can see that, can't you?
Sure, sure, i can see that.
L-i had to... i
had to stop him.
I had to.
I had to do it.
Now, mr. Parkes,
i want you to understand
that no one is saying
you didn't see these things.
There's no doubt
that you did.
But you must realize
that you saw them
only in your mind.
They were real.
To you, they were.
That's the way it is
with hallucination.
Ordinarily, the eye sees
and transmits a picture
to the brain,
but sometimes, that's reversed.
In certain cases,
the brain sees and transmits
its message to the eye.
Do you understand?
No. They were real.
In that case, others would have
seen them, too.
Isn't that so?
I don't know.
It's logical,
isn't it?
I suppose so.
But no one
did see them.
Now, how do you
explain that?
I don't know.
Think about it
for a moment.
Well, mr. Parkes?
I don't know
why nobody else saw them.
Maybe they weren't looking.
You said that there were three
figures in the display case:
A young girl, her maid
and a man.
That's right.
Now, let's look
at it logically
for just a moment.
According
to the museum officials,
there was only one figure-
the girl.
Where did the others come from?
Well, the maid always came
from the kitchen
or the dining room.
And that-that fellow...
yes... where did he come from?
Outside.
Outside the case?
No, outside the house.
Mr. Parkes, think about it.
There was nothing
outside that house but glass,
and beyond that, other displays.
Isn't that true?
Yes, but he came
in the front door.
And they went out together once,
uh, to the opera or something.
L-l-i don't know.
And... she never knew
what kind of person he was,
but i could have told her.
You only had to look at him
to see what kind
of person he was.
But she's so...
trusting and-and innocent
and helpless...
not like other women?
No, not at all.
Have you seen her?
Yes.
Well, is-is she all right?
L-i've been worried sick.
Would you like to see her?
Yes.
Be careful.
You're holding
a piece of wood
in your hand,
mr. Parkes.
A beautifully carved piece
of wood.
Do you have to take her back?
I'm afraid so.
It is museum property.
Now, i want you to
go back to your room
and think about
what i've said.
Will you do that?
And remember, whatyou saw
is not the important thing.
Our job is to find outwhy.
Once we've
accomplished that,
you'll have no more
hallucinations.
Where is charley?
Oh, he'll be here
in a few moments.
Is he really normal,
doctor?
That is a word
we try not to use, mrs. Parkes.
Why not?
Well, because
it's meaningless.
"Normal"
in the popular sense refers
only to the behavior pattern of
the majority, and that pattern
is not
necessarily good.
Well... if 99.9% of the people
in the country were to, uh...
oh, go to bed
with their socks on, let's say,
then going to bed
with one's socks on
would be the normal thing to do.
And if you didn't,
you wouldn't be normal, you see?
I go to bed with my socks on
all the time.
What i'm trying to say is,
don't judge
charley's emotional health
by the degree
to which he conforms
to other people's standards.
Don't expect him to...
well, be like
other people.
Then you don't
think he's sick?
Not now, no.
He was when he came here.
The constant pressure of trying
to be something he wasn't,
of-of trying to act
and feel and think
the way you
wanted him to
instead of the
way he wanted to-
well, these
things contributed
to a serious
breakdown.
You see, well,
charley was unable
to cope with
this world,
so his mind created
another world.
Of course, he knew it was false,
and he destroyed it.
And with that first step,
he started back
on the road to mental health.
Now, of course,
he insisted it was real
for a long time, as you know,
but that is
standard behavior
in cases of
hallucination.
Uh, that's an interesting habit
you have, that, uh...
why do you do it?
Myra.
Hello, charley.
Old buddy.
Oh, mother, how
nice of you to come.
How you feeling,
charley?
Oh, wonderful, doctor,
really, wonderful.
I can't tell you
how much you've helped me.
No more dreams?
Oh, i've been sleeping
like a baby.
Not worried about the girl
in the display case?
There was no girl, just a doll.
I know that.
And i know what it was that
made me think i saw what i saw,
thanks to you.
Thanks to you, charley.
You figured it out, remember?
I didn't tell
you anything
after the first day.
Now, mother.
Oh, charley...
i was so worried
about my baby.
I was so frightened.
I know you were,
and i'm sorry
i put you through
so much heartache,
but i'm fine now.
Isn't that
right, doctor?
I think so.
And i'll get a job,
and everything will
be the way it was,
just the way it was.
I sure missed this.
No one could make cocoa
the way you can.
Did they hurt
you, charley?
Well, they were afraid
they were going
to have to use, uh,
shock treatment,
and i hear that hurts
quite a bit,
but they decided not to
when i got well.
Everything else was fine.
They got a lot of nuts
in that place, i guess, huh?
I didn't mean him!
That's all right. I don't mind.
May i have some more cocoa?
Uh, charley, we have
a couple of
surprises for you.
Oh?
First of all,
that job
in buddy's office
is still open.
Fine.
And i talked
to harriet
and explained things.
But she's a
wonderful girl,
and she understands.
Well, fine.
And you can tell
her yourself,
because she's
coming over tonight.
Well, that's just wonderful.
Thank you, myra.
Thank you, buddy.
It took a lot of doing-
i can tell you that.
I mean, where you been
and all.
I'm sure it did,
but you won't be sorry.
I intend to work very hard.
Now, if i'm going to be fresh
for tonight,
i'd better go get
a little rest.
Would you like
to fix up my bed, mother?
Charley, are you all
right, now, really?
Yes, mother, really.
You won't go talking
crazy anymore
and smashing things?
No, mother, that-that's
all in the past.
It's good to have
you back, son.
I can't tell you.
There's harriet.
You'd better tell charley
to get ready. Hurry!
Hi. You look great.
Thanks.
New dress?
20 bucks' worth.
Hi, bud.
Hiya, harriet.
Charley, your company's here.
Charley?
What's the matter?
Can't you wake him up?
No, he must
be very tired.
Hey, it's locked.
It couldn't be.
Charley never
locks his door.
Try it yourself.
Charley, boy.
Buddy...
what on earth
is all the racket about?
Maybe he doesn't want
to be disturbed.
Nobody could sleep
through that.
Break it down.
Aw, gee,
i don't...
break it down!
Okay.
Charley!
Charley?
Charley...
oh, now, mama,
there's no need
to get excited.
But he's gone!
Harriet.
He must've crawled
out of the window.
Why would he do
a thing like that?
I don't know.
He's your son.
Myra!
What are you
going to do?
Mama, mama,
take it easy.
Myra, what...
mama...
hello, operator?
Could you give me
the number
of the county museum,
please?
Thank you.
He couldn't
have gone there.
He's well-
the doctor said so.
Mama, please!
Hello, uh, could
you tell me, please,
are you open tonight?
Oh, thank you.
Well, you're right.
He's not there.
They close at 5:00
every day except tuesday,
and this is wednesday.
They tried to tell me
you weren't real.
They tried
to make me think
that you were
only something i imagined.
Of course, i knew better,
but i pretended to believe them.
Because if i hadn't
have done that,
i'd still be in
the hospital,
and i never
would have seen you again.
That would have been terrible,
because, uh...
you see, i love you.
I don't know how
i can make you understand that.
Maybe if i
keep telling
you, you will.
I love you, alice.
I love you.
So then we knocked,
but he didn't answer,
so i had buddy
knock down the door.
I see. Now, how would
you describe his behavior
prior to his going in
for the nap?
Well, i don't know
how to put it.
It was as if he
were so healthy
that i was worried.
It was like he
didn't have a
care in the world.
So i thought,
'well, maybe he
went to the museum,'
so i phoned,
but they're
closed tonight.
So where
could he be?
Oh, he's there, all right.
But i just told
you they're closed.
I expect he went in earlier
and hid somewhere.
Now, i was
just wondering...
if you would go along
with us, mr. Russell.
Sure.
It may not be necessary,
but you never can
quite tell.
And mrs. Parkes, you might
be able to do some good,
if you're willing.
Anything for poor charley.
Good.
Doctor, are you going
to take him
back there
to the hospital?
I think it might
be wise, don't you?
Give me the police
department, please.
Dr. Wallman says it happened
because i needed a simple world
i could understand,
but your world
isn't simple, is it?
No world with people in it is.
There's always loneliness
and suffering and heartache.
Look at you,
crying because
you're alone.
Well, i've been
alone all my life.
Oh, people
have tried.
My mother and my sister-
they've tried very hard
to understand...
but they can't.
You could.
We could understand
each other...
and help each other and...
love each other.
If only...
i don't know where he'd hide.
I check things
pretty carefully
every night
before i leave.
I'm sure you do,
but you'll grant
it's possible?
Barely.
Straight ahead there.
Do you want me
to turn on the lights?
Not yet.
Mrs. Parkes,
will you come with me?
And will the rest of
you wait here, please?
Tell him you're here.
Ask him to come out.
Charley.
Louder. Command him.
Charley, it's mother.
Come out of there.
Again.
Come out of there
this second, young man!
You hear me?
All right, guard,
you can turn
them on now.
Are you sure
he's here?
I'm almost
positive.
Let's start looking.
Charley?
Charley!
They never found
charley parkes,
because the guard
didn't tell them
what he saw in the glass case.
He knew what they'd say,
and he knew
they'd be right, too,
because seeing
is not always believing-
especially if what you see
happens to be an odd corner
of the twilight zone.
Some rather special ingredients
to a bizarre brew
served up next
onthe twilight zone.
An oddball printing press,
an editor with a stringer
from the lower regions
are just a few as we bring you
robert sterling,
patricia crowley,
and special guest star
burgess meredith
in charles beaumont's
"printer's devil."
What's the matter?
Matter?
Why did you quit?
Finished.
Why would a man with your talent
want to work for a hick paper
like thecourier?
Call it a challenge.
Now, miss benson,
are you impressed?
No. I'm amazed.
It's understandable.
Well, i must confess
that this is not
my true vocation.
It isn't?
No. I am a reporter.
Oh.
Some people have a green thumb.
I have a green nose.
Wherever there is news,
this old nose smells it.
Well, i'm afraid
there isn't that much news
to smell around dansburg,
mr. Smith.
There will be.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org