Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
I told you that santa claus
should be back by 6:00.
Come on,
mom, let's go.
Hey, you told me
to tell you when it was 6:30.
It's 6:30.
That's right.
It's exactly 6:30.
So...
so what happens now?
You turn into a reindeer?
Would that i could.
I'll have
another one.
You owe me for six
drinks and a sandwich.
That's $3.80.
Why do you suppose there
isn't really a santa claus?
How's that?
Why isn't there a real santa
claus... for kids like that?
What am i supposed to be-
some kind of philosopher?
You know
what your trouble is?
You let that dopey
red suit go to your head.
Are you some kind of a nut?
Here's your change.
I'll flip you-
double or nothing.
What do you think this is,
monte carlo?
Finish and get out.
I've had enough...
to eat.
Hello, jack's place.
No, jack's not here.
This is bruce.
Wait a minute.
Santa claus, i catch
you trying that
one more time
i'm going to break
both your arms
up to the
shoulder blades.
Now, go on,
get out of here.
What's that?
No, it's just santa claus
trying to heist the joint.
Thanks a lot, bruce.
Please, santa
i want a carriage
and a dolly...
please,
i want a gun...
and a playhouse...
and a set
of soldiers
and a fort...
and oh, please,
santa claus
a job
for my daddy.
Please,
a big turkey
for our christmas dinner.
This is mr. Henry corwin,
normally unemployed
who once a year takes
the lead role
in the uniquely popular
american institution
that of
a department store santa claus
in a road company version of
the night before christmas
but in just a moment, mr. Henry
corwin, ersatz santa claus
will enter a strange kind
of north pole
which is one part
the wondrous spirit of christmas
and one part the magic
that can only be found
in the twilight zone.
You should see me
with erector sets.
Corwin, you're an hour late!
I am?
Now, you get up
on your throne
and see if you can keep from
disillusioning a lot of kids
that not only isn't
there a santa claus
but the one in this store
happens to be a wino
who'd be more at home playing
rudolph the red-nosed reindeer.
Now, get with it,
santa claus!
You go ahead.
You climb up
on his lap.
Go ahead, he
won't hurt you
will you,
santa claus?
You won't hurt
my little boy.
Go on, tell him!
What's
your name?
Percival smithers.
And what do you want
for christmas, percival?
A new front name.
Percy!
I think
we have...
look, mom!
Santa claus
is loaded.
You've got
some nerve!
You ought
to be ashamed.
Madam...
i am ashamed.
Come on,
percival.
I hope this
won't be
a traumatic
experience for you.
Sot!
Is there some
trouble here?
Yes, there's
some trouble.
I shall never trade
in this store again.
It seems you hire
your santa clauses
out of a gutter.
All right,
back to work.
Back to your
positions, please.
And now, mr. Kris kringle
of the lower depths
since it is only a few hours
to closing time
it is my distinct
pleasure to tell you
that there is no more
need for your services.
You have had it!
Now, get out here!
I'd be very glad to.
And get that crummy
red suit back
to wherever you
rented it from
before you really tie
one on and destroy it.
You drunk!
Thank you very much,
mr. Dundee.
As to my drinking,
this is indefensible
and you have
my abject apologies.
I find of late that i
have very little choice
in the matter of
expressing emotions.
I can either drink
or i can weep
and drinking is
so much more subtle.
Will you please leave?
As for my
insubordination
i was not rude
to that woman.
Someone should remind her
that christmas
is more than barging up
and down department store aisles
and pushing people
out of the way.
Now, corwin...
someone has
to tell her
that christmas is another thing,
finer than that...
richer, finer, truer
and it should come with patience
and love, charity, compassion.
That's what
i would have told her
if you'd given me the chance.
Well, how
philosophical
mr. Corwin.
Now, perhaps
as your parting word
you can tell us
how we can go about
living up to these
wondrous yule standards
which you have
so graciously
laid down for us.
I don't know
how to tell you, mr. Dundee.
I don't know at all.
All i know is
that i'm an aging,
purposeless relic
of another time
and i live in a
dirty rooming house
on a street
filled with hungry
kids and shabby people
where the only thing
that comes
down the chimney
on christmas eve
is more poverty.
Will you keep your voice down?
Do you know
another reason
why i drink,
mr. Dundee?
So that when i walk
down the tenements
i can really think
it's the north pole
and the children are elves
and that i'm really santa claus
bringing them
a bag of wondrous gifts
for all of them.
I just wish, mr. Dundee,
on one christmas-
only one...
that i could see
some of the hopeless ones...
and the dreamless ones...
just on one christmas
i'd like to see the meek
inherit the earth.
And that's why i drink,
mr. Dundee...
and that's why i weep.
George, you want
another drink?
Hey, look.
It's santa claus!
Look, there's
santa claus.
Come on in.
Nah, nah.
Go on, get lost.
Get out of here.
Merry christmas.
Santa's a lush.
Hey, everybody!
Hey, kids!
Merry christmas, everybody!
Hey, kids! Everybody!
Merry christmas!
Merry christmas, everybody!
? joy to the world?
? the lord is come?
? let earth receive her king?
? let every heart
prepare him room?
? and heaven and nature sing?
? and heaven...?
What is going on here?
What's the idea of coming
in here and disrupting
the christmas
eve service?
Sister florence, i
ain't touched a drop
since last thursday and
that's the gospel truth.
And i swear to you
on account of i've seen
it with my own eyes-
santa claus is coming down
the street heading this way
and bringing everybody
his heart's desire.
There's a real,
honest-to-goodness santa...
merry christmas,
gentlemen.
Now, what'll be
your pleasure
for christmas,
gentlemen?
How about you, burt?
I fancy a new pipe.
Let's see what
i can do for you.
Here's your
new pipe.
How about you?
I want a sweater.
A sweater-
what size?
Who cares
Oh, thank you.
Could i have
a smoking jacket?
A smoking jacket
to go with the pipe.
I'll see
what i can get.
There's your
smoking jacket.
Where did you get
all these gifts?
Sister florence
don't ask me to explain.
I'm just as much in the dark
as anybody else.
All i know is i've got
a santa claus bag here
that gives everybody
exactly what they
want for christmas
and as long
as it's putting out
i'm putting in.
Sister florence,
how about a new dress?
Give that to
sister florence
when she
comes back.
Thank you.
A bottle of wine.
Merry christmas, officer,
merry christmas.
What's your name?
Henry corwin...
or is it?
Maybe it's santa claus or
kris kringle- i don't know.
You're drunk, corwin.
Is that it?
Of course
i'm drunk.
I'm intoxicated
with the spirit of the yule.
Drunk with the spirit
of the yule.
Intoxicated with the magic and
wonder that is christmas eve.
I'm inebriated
with joy and delight.
Yes, officer, i'm drunk.
We'll settle this
in a hurry.
Have you got a receipt
for this stuff?
Receipt?
Of course you've
got a receipt.
No.
Sister florence
would you please collect
all the stolen goods
and put them
in a pile over there?
I'll send for them
when i check on
who owns them.
Come on, santa.
Be right with you,
officer.
Don't worry about
a thing, gentlemen.
There's more
where this came from.
Officer, let me tell you
how this whole thing started.
I was having a glass
down at jack's place.
It was just about 4:30 in the
afternoon when i got there.
Like i said,
officer
i arrived at jack's
place about 4:30-
between 4:30 and 5:00,
the cocktail hour.
Jack wasn't there
but bruce was.
I know bruce, yes.
Right here.
After you.
I had a sandwich
that i couldn't
finish
and i got
to talking...
uh-huh, here he is and
here we are and there that is.
And here
you are.
How nice to see you
again, mr. Dundee.
And how nice it will be
to see my wistful saint nicholas
going up the river.
Do you suppose he can get
as much ten years?
Ten years?
Well, it don't
look good, corwin.
Of course, they could
lop off a few months
if you was to tell them
where the rest of the loot was.
He's been giving out the stuff
for two and half hours.
He must have
a warehouse full of it.
I'm glad you
brought that up.
There seems
to be
a slight
discrepancy here.
Listen, you moth-eaten
robin hood
the wholesale theft of thousands
of dollars worth of goods
is not a
slight discrepancy.
Though i can tell you
right now, corwin
this whole affair comes
as no surprise to me.
I'd perceived that criminal
glint in your eyes
the first minute
i'd laid eyes on you.
It seems to me
that you've
put your finger
on the problem,
mr. Dundee.
This bag
doesn't know
whether to give out
gifts or garbage.
It was giving out gifts
when i seen it.
Whatever they was wanting
corwin was supplying.
All kinds of stuff-
toys, gifts, expensive stuff.
Admit it, corwin.
Oh, i admit it, i admit it.
But it seems to me
the essence of our problem is
that we're dealing
with a most unusual bag.
My advice to you is to clean up
this mess and get out here.
Officer flaherty, you
call yourself a policeman.
Well, i suppose it
is a demanding task-
to distinguish between
a bag full of garbage
and an inventory of
expensive stolen gifts.
Mr. Dundee, believe me.
It's like corwin says:
We're dealing with
the supernatural here.
In other words
all we have to do
is to ask mr. Corwin
to make a little
abracadabra for us
and no sooner
said, done.
Well, go ahead,
corwin.
I fancy a bottle
of cherry brandy
vintage 1903.
Oh, that's a good year.
And as for you,
officer flaherty
how dare you
drag me down here
at the busiest time
of the year
to look at a bag
full of garbage?
Mr. Dundee...
pardon me,
gentlemen.
Merry christmas
to both of you!
"To mr. Dundee,
from santa."
Here, mr, dundee.
You need one.
Here's beautiful
yellow sweater for you.
I want a toy.
I've got a beautiful
toy for you.
I want an electric
train engine.
Electric train engine?
Diesel or steam?
I don't care.
There it is.
I want
a dolly.
You want a dolly.
A blonde, brunette...
blonde!
Here she is.
I want a
toy, please.
Oh, i've got one
here for you.
Right there, sweetheart.
I've got a
baseball bat for you
and a toy dog for you.
Thanks.
And a baseball mitt.
Merry christmas to all!
Nothing for you
this christmas?
I think i've had
the nicest christmas
since the beginning
of time.
Nothing for you.
Nothing for yourself,
not a thing.
You know, i... i can't think
of anything i want.
I guess what
i've really wanted is...
to be the biggest gift giver
of all times
and in a way
i think i had that tonight.
Although, if i had my choice
of any gift- any gift at all-
i think i'd wish
i could do this every year.
That'd be
some gift
wouldn't it,
burt?
Oh, it sure would.
God bless
you, burt
and merry christmas
to you.
Merry christmas
to you, too, santa
and thanks for the smoking
jacket and the pipe.
Don't mention it.
We've been waiting
quite a while
for you, santa claus.
Oh, no.
Did you hear
what i said?
I said we've been
waiting quite a while
for you, santa claus.
We've got a year of
hard work ahead of us
to get ready
for next christmas.
Come on.
Are you ready?
Oh, yeah.
Going home,
officer flaherty?
Going home, mr.
Dundee, and you?
Going home,
officer flaherty.
This is the most
remarkable christmas eve
i've ever had.
Flaherty...
i could have
sworn that i...
did you see it?
I thought i did.
What did you see?
I don't think
i ought to tell you.
You might report me
for drinking on duty.
Go ahead,
what did you see?
It was corwin,
mr. Dundee
big as life in a
sleigh with reindeer
sitting next to an elf
and riding up
toward the sky.
That's about
the size of it
ain't it,
mr. Dundee?
Flaherty, you better
come home with me
and we'll pour out
some hot coffee
and we'll pour
some brandy in it
and we'll...
and we'll thank god
for miracles, flaherty.
A word to the wise, to all
the children of the 20th century
whether their concern be
pediatrics or geriatrics
whether they crawl on hands
and knees and wear diapers
or walk with a cane
and comb their beards.
There's a wondrous magic
to christmas
and there's a special power
reserved for little people.
In short, there's
nothing mightier than the meek.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
this is james arness.
You know, it's only a short hop
fromthe twilight zone
to dodge city andgunsmoke.
Saturday nights,
over most of these stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org