Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it
is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
I have an appointment
with mr. Feathersmith.
Oh, yes, mr. Deidrich,
he's expecting you, sir.
Right this way.
Oh, wow.
I could just
see him now.
That big, happy grin
on his face
just before he
draws the blood.
"Have a cigar, mr. Deidrich,
before i rip you to pieces.
"But i must have my
little fun first.
Have a cigar."
Have a cigar, mr. Deidrich.
Thank you, no,
mr. Feathersmith.
You asked me to come here
at 2:00; it is now 2:00.
What did you have
on your mind?
Hmm, you never have
cared for my habits
have you,
mr. Deidrich?
Whether i do
or don't
is not at issue,
mr. Feathersmith.
But the extent of time
you keep me here
is, on the other hand,
of considerable import.
I'm a busy man,
let's get on with it.
We've come a pretty far route,
haven't we, the two of us?
So?
So, it's odd
how our lives
seem to crisscross
back and forth.
I owe you a great deal,
mr. Deidrich, i really do.
I remember vividly one afternoon
when you called me into your
office, and said:
"Bill feathersmith,
i like your style, boy.
I want you in with me."
You remember that afternoon,
mr. Deidrich?
I shall never forget it.
I have given it
a good deal of thought
in the ensuing years
and shall never cease
to regret it.
You never did like me.
I wouldn't say that,
mr. Feathersmith.
I wouldn't say that i...
never did like you.
I have disliked
and detested you
with great cordiality.
I have found you to be
from the moment
you came into my office
a predatory, grasping...
conniving, acquisitive
animal of a man.
Without heart,
without conscience
without... compassion.
Without even a subtle hint
of the common decencies.
Shall we go on from there?
I give you this, mr. Deidrich:
You never were one to toady
around with phony euphemisms.
You always did speak your mind.
And you, mr. Feathersmith,
this is perhaps the singular
compliment i can dredge up:
You've always been a man
to speak yours.
So why don't you?
All right, then.
I'll dopreciselythat.
This... is my empire,
mr. Deidrich.
Mining, steel, electronics,
lumber, railroads,
minerals, manufacturing...
it's been a step-by-step,
piece-by-piece building up
of an industrial complex
that i take
pardonable pride in.
But there is one...
piece... missing.
That is to say, therewas
one piece missing...
the deidrich tool
and die company
employing 13,000 men.
A good and
substantial plant
in operation
some 40 years.
Not always perfectly managed,
but adequately managed.
Sufficiently well-managed to
make you move heaven and earth
to try to buy it on the first
monday of each month.
But thank heaven i won't
live to see the day
when you stick your greasy-ham
fists into it.
You call it well-managed.
You're speaking comparatively,
of course.
I'm speaking of
that little matter
of your financial problems.
I happen to know for a fact
that you secured a loan
for $3 million...
a loan payable on demand.
Here is the note.
I bought up that
note, mr. Deidrich.
I paid an exorbitant
amount of money for it...
more than it was worth.
But it was, well, shall i say,
an excellent opportunity-
an opportunity for our lives
to crisscross again.
So, to the point:
It reads, "payable on demand."
So, mr. Deidrich,
on demand, it is.
I am calling
this note.
I want it paid...
$3 million
not tomorrow...
not this evening
around suppertime...
now, mr. Deidrich,
this moment!
I want your personal check
in that amount
or i'll have to send
a few sign painters
out to the deidrich tool
and die company
and have them cross
off the name deidrich!
Feathersmith...
if you call that note...
you'll bankrupt me.
You'll kill off
everything i have.
Everything i own...
everything.
Witness a murder.
The killer is
mr. William feathersmith,
a robber baron whose body
composition is made up
of a refrigeration plant
covered by thick skin.
In a moment, mr. Feathersmith
will proceed
in his daily course of conquest
and calumny
with yet another
business dealing.
But this will be one
of those bizarre transactions
that take place
in an odd marketplace
known as... the twilight zone.
Miss pepper, miss pepper!
Yes, sir?
Take me down,
young man.
Take me all
the way down...
if there's anyplace
lower than this floor.
Excuse me, sir, uh, i
didn't know you were here.
Well, i am here, lafayette.
I am most assuredly here.
Andhereis the mountaintop.
High rung on the ladder,
way up on the mountaintop.
Like, now, what... let's see,
what was his name...
genghis khan?
Genghis...
khan...
feathersmith?
What's the matter
with me?
Who are you, anyway?
Hecate, sir, custodian
of the top three floors.
And so, you're hecate,
custodian of the top
three floors, hmm?
You... have
a drink, hecate,
custodian of the top
three floors.
Thank you, no sir,
but i appreciate that.
Tell me, how long
have you been
performing this
illustrious task?
34 years, sir.
I've been in this building
for 34 years.
I got a... got a gold watch
last year.
A gold watch...
34 years in the building.
Your aggressive self-assurance
unnerves me, hecate.
That's practically as long
as i've been in the building.
But i didn't start
here, hecate.
No, indeed, i started
in a little town
called cliffordville.
Cliffordville, indiana.
You ever hear of it, hecate?
It's a coincidence, sir,
i was born in cliffordville.
I grew up there.
Well, well, well,
we're very much alike.
Both from cliffordville
we both put on our pants
one leg at a time
and there,
the similarity ends.
Cliffordville,
hmm?
Well, that was areal
town, wasn't it, hecate?
A real place.
When a man could go up to the
moon if he had a mind to
and the legs to carry him
and fingers
to stretch out and grasp.
Hmm, not like
now.
Hmm...
no...
not like now at all.
Genghis khan...
feathersmith, hmm.
Alexander the great...
feathersmith.
I've got everything
there is to get...
but i'm still hungry.
He cried because he had
no more worlds to conquer.
What?
That was alexander the great.
He cried because he had
no more worlds to conquer.
I guess...
i guess maybe he was... kind
of like you, mr. Feathersmith.
You know something, hecate?
I wish i could go back
to cliffordville
and begin again, i mean
start all over.
You see, getting it,
that was the kick...
getting it, not having it.
Good night, mr. Hecate,
custodian of the top
three floors.
Don't forget
to wind your gold watch.
Just one minute.
You left me off
at the wrong floor.
This isn't the lobby.
How do you do, sir?
Who are you?
Devlin, first name's
not important.
I own this building.
I'm aware of that,
mr. Feathersmith.
but i'm not aware
of you having an office
here, whoever you are.
Oh, i just opened it up.
As a matter of fact
i've opened it
foryourconvenience.
Won't you sit down?
Why?
Why, because, we've
got some business
to transact,
you and i.
And there's no reason why
we shouldn't be comfortable.
Go on, mr. Feathersmith,
you were saying?
Hmm? Oh, the name of the town
was cliffordville.
Ah, yes, cliffordville.
And it was a pleasant town?
Of course it was pleasant.
It was better than pleasant.
There was a girl there,
name of gibbons.
Father was president
of the bank.
Beautiful girl.
And you enjoyed this,
didn't you, mr. Feathersmith?
I didn't have time to enjoy
anything. I worked! Worked!
I dug, i scratched, i pushed,
i drove.
I went up... up!
You understand that?
And now you're up.
You're all the way up.
And... you're simply bored.
That's what you are,
mr. Feathersmith, plain bored.
It's worse than bored.
I'm ruthless now.
I... just have no purpose,
no plans.
I have no drive because there's
no place to go.
What about this...
stuff on your door?
A very succinct suggestion
of the services i render,
mr. Feathersmith...
travel... time travel.
Miss devlin...
let's you and i
talk something over.
Indeed, mr. Feathersmith
i had intended
that we should.
Let me suggest
a possible transaction.
You say you're bored, you've
got everything you want.
The pleasure's not
in the possession
it's in the desperate struggle
to possess.
That's the sense of it,
isn't it, mr. Feathersmith?
Go on.
Let's do this:
Let's send you
back to cliffordville
the cliffordville
of years ago.
You can start
all over again.
Acquire, build, consolidate-
how does that sound?
Miss devlin, you are not
dealing with a fool now.
I am not one of your
"sell your soul
for a nickel"
country bumpkins.
Try this.
Send me back in time
to cliffordville.
But i want to look exactly
as i did then...
that's number one.
Agreed.
Number two:
I want to have a memory
of everything that's occurred
in the last 50 years.
I don't want that memory
impaired one bit!
Check again,
mr. Feathersmith.
I want that town
exactly as it was
with the same people
that i remember.
Allveryeasily arranged.
Anything else?
I want it
to happen right away.
Time is of absolutely
no essence.
You name the hour...
that is the hour
you shall have.
Now, as to the price.
Yes, mr. Feathersmith,
as to price.
Well, i suppose
thestandardpayment
is, um, well, i guess you'd
call it the soul.
On occasion,
mr. Feathersmith
that is
part of the transaction.
But in your case,
we got a hold of your soul
some time ago, i believe.
Let me check this.
Ah, here it is.
There was the crash of the
trans-mississippi debentures,
the company you'd bought
and then manipulated.
You ruined several hundred
people with that chicanery.
There were four suicides
as a result.
I believe the bulk
of your soul
went over to us
shortly thereafter.
There are several
other items here
under private life,
volume nine.
Business transactions...
subconscious thoughts
and dreams.
Ah, here we are...
indirect murders.
People you drove
to ruin and poverty
hopelessness,
ultimate death.
No, mr. Feathersmith,
i'm afraid your soul
is not yours to negotiate.
Then whatdoyou charge?
Cash.
The long green leaf
lettuce... currency.
I have your current assets
tabulated here.
Were you to liquidate
as of this moment
you'd be worth precisely
$36,891,412.14.
You're very
thorough.
We have to be thorough,
mr. Feathersmith.
Now, the cost for what
you ask is nominal.
The entire cost,
and that includes
transportation back, clothing,
retaining of your memory,
maintenance of the town in
its historically accurate form
including its citizenry
is, uh, $36,890,000
leaving you a balance of...
$1,412.14.
You robber!
Mr. Feathersmith,
$1,412.14
is... quite a little
nest egg, considering...
oh, perhaps, miss devlin,
perhaps,
considering i know
where the oil is
just outside of town.
Ah, that's 1400 acres
not discovered until, uh,
let's see, it was 1937
when they brought
in the first well.
And i know the nature
of the stock market-
which stocks will rise,
which stocks will fall.
I know every invention
that's been perfected
in the last 50 years.
I can get in
on the ground floor.
The ground floor?
Why, the basement, sir.
$1,412.14...
is a fortune.
Good, when do i start,
how soon?
I can handle
the liquidation for you.
Just sign this
power of attorney
and there's
no reason
why you can't leave
immediately.
Anything else?
I think not.
I think i might be able to
sweeten the pot a bit for you.
This very attractive banker's
daughter, for example.
I could fix that up
for you most handily.
Do away with a traditional
lengthy courtship...
the ritualistic
formalities of the time.
No, forget it.
I'm going to work
for everything.
That's the fun of it,
that's the kick!
I'm going to work
for everything!
You just send me back
with the 1,400-odd bucks
and watchmysmoke,
sister!
Ha, exemplary,
mr. Feathersmith,
really exemplary.
You're one
of the few remaining
rugged individualists
of our time.
It's a pleasure doing
business with you.
Now, good-bye.
You'll arrive in cliffordville
at noon tomorrow.
That's noon
of the year 1910.
And needless to say,
mr. Feathersmith,
i wish for you everything
that you deserve.
Little lady, you don't have
to wish anything for me.
I get everything
i go after, everything!
I believe you,
mr. Feathersmith.
I have no doubt
whatsoever.
This is your captain speaking.
We are crossing
the indiana state line.
For those of you
who are interested
we have just gained an hour.
Cliffordville.
This stop
is cliffordville.
Cliffordville.
The devil, you say.
All aboard.
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
What's the matter, can't you
pave the roads around here?
Hey, van winkle.
You want something,
sir?
Yeah, something.
That yellow flag bit...
what's the holiday?
Oh, them?
Yes, them.
Typhoid flags; they got
typhoid over there.
Typhoid? Haven't those idiots
ever heard of innocu...
oh, no, they haven't,
have they?
No, not this year.
Well, go back to sleep, rip,
i'll wake you when i need you.
Huh.
That's old man hecate!
You got a great future, jack.
A great future.
I beg your pardon, sir.
Mr. Deidrich, isn't it?
You, uh, have the advantage,
sir.
Yes, i do indeed.
But we'll get into that
later on.
Wonderful having this...
little chat.
Sit down, mr., uh...
mr. Feathersmith.
I'll only be
a moment, sir.
This is my
lunch hour
and i never let business
interfere with pleasure.
And i never let pleasure
interfere with business.
The name is
feathersmith.
I'm not a peddler, drummer,
or door-to-door salesman.
I'm here to make
myself rich.
In the process, you can
lick up a few crumbs.
I beg your pardon?
The widow turner's land,
is it available?
The widow turner's land?
There were
1400 acres.
1400 acres?
Is there an echo here
or would it help if i
hired an interpreter?
No, indeed, mr. Feathersmith,
no, indeed, it's just that, uh,
well, sir, you're talking about
a very valuable piece
of property.
I'm talking about
widow turner's land,
south end of town.
Indeed,
indeed, beautiful spot.
1400 extravagantly
lovely acres.
Singing birds
and constant sunshine.
It's a garden of eden
for a man with vision
and the potential
is unlimited.
It's a swamp for mosquitoes
and the potential is malaria.
Tell me who owns it and how much
they want for it.
Well, as a matter of fact,
that land was purchased
from the estate of the late
mrs. Turner by yours truly
in partnership
with a mr. Sebastian deidrich
here in town.
We each own half of it.
Deidrich, huh?
Well, do you suppose
that you and mr. Deidrich
could bepersuaded
to part with it
assuming the price is
within reason?
Well, as valuable
as that land is, uh...
well, sir, uh,
everything has its price.
How does $4.00 an acre
sound to you?
Lovely...
fine.
If i were an idiot.
But i am not an idiot,
mr. Gibbons.
I'll give you
50 cents an acre.
Why don't we strike toward
a compromise and say... $3.00?
Let's say 75 cents.
You're a driver of a hard
bargain, mr. Feathersmith.
However, both myself
and mr. Deidrich
might hold still... for, uh...
$2.00 an acre.
Hmm.
Mr. Gibbons, you wouldn't
hold still for a back rub
if you couldn't convert it
into currency.
One buck an acre,
and that's it.
A dollar an acre,
you say?
All right, a dollar
an acre, i say.
And in eight seconds,
it'll go down to 80 cents.
Going... going...
gone, mr. Feathersmith.
And i presume this will be
a cash transaction?
You just bring the deeds
to my hotel tonight
properly signed
and notarized
and i'll have
your money.
Well, now, sir,
this is the way
i like to have
a transaction.
No fiddling around.
Just two staunch
men of goodwill
who know
what they want.
Don't you agree,
mr. Feathersmith?
I agree with you right
down the line, mr. Gibbons
assuming both your
hands are visible.
And i amnota widow
or an orphan.
You have a daughter,
mr. Gibbons.
Why...
why, yes.
Oh, do you mind?
Oh, no, please...
joanna is her name.
Yes.
And as pretty a slice
of peach pie
as ever went on a hayride.
Mr. Feathersmith, that...
you're being insulting.
No, mr. Gibbons,
i am not being insulting.
I am being candid,
i am speaking my mind.
I know what i like,
and i ask for it
and i generally get it.
Now, let's meet
this little doll.
So i told daddy when he told me
that you were downstairs,
i said, "it's about time
we had a sophisticated man
in this town."
Didn't i say that, daddy?
Oh, have another bon-bon,
mr. Feathersmith.
Uh, no.
Oh, they're delicious.
Mm. This one's a cream.
Mm, a real good cream.
Oh, i just love cream.
Don't you like cream,
mr. Feathersmith?
Oh, well...
oh, i love them.
They're just goodie-goodie.
Well, anyway,
when it was july,
we all went to
my aunt bertha's in maine.
Have you ever been to maine,
mr. Feathersmith?
Uh...
i love swimming.
I just adore the ocean.
I'm the best swimmer
in my class, huh, daddy?
Have another bon-bon,
mr. Feathersmith.
No thank you.
They're goodie-goodie.
Hmm?
Oh, oh.
Wh-why don't you
sing for us, joanna?
I'm sure mr. Feathersmith
would love that.
Oh, i think he'd be bored with
music on this hot afternoon.
Wouldn't you, mr. Feathersmith?
Oh, well, if you insist.
? every little movement
has a meaning all its own?
? every thought and feeling?
? by some
posture can be shown?
? and every love song
that comes a-stealing?
? o'er your being
must be revealing?
? all its sweetness...?
Ah, you, uh...
you don't have
another daughter?
That delightful
little thing
is my one and only.
Sings beautifully,
doesn't she?
Oh, yes,
like a bird.
A ruptured rooster.
Well, you're right
on time, mr. Feathersmith.
I always am.
Hmm, i don't believe you
two gentlemen have met.
This is mr. Deidrich.
And this is mr. Feathersmith,
mr. Deidrich.
I presume you brought
cash, mr. Feathersmith?
1403 acres...
here is $1,403.
You, uh, you
seem to put
all your eggs in one
basket, mr. Feathersmith.
I wouldn't
let that
concern you,
mr. Deidrich.
You see, i have
an exclusive contract
with the hen.
Beers all around.
Well, gentlemen...
shall we get down
to cases?
When it comes to a fast shuffle
you're involved with
a very knowledgeable dealer.
Comment, mr. Deidrich?
Ah, you have the floor,
mr. Feathersmith.
You seem anxious
to have it.
It's just a human frailty...
i mean, to gloat just a bit
when one has just skinned
a couple
of professional skinners.
Which incidentally, is
what i've done to you.
A buck an acre, and you're
sitting here thinking
that whenthispigeon
flew into town
you plucked him bald.
I sent a telegram
to a geologist.
He arrived on the 4:00 train.
He spent the day out
at the widow turner's land...
made some preliminary
soil tests.
Care to hear the results?
Feel free,
mr. Feathersmith.
I'll oblige,
mr. Deidrich.
That crummy swampland you
sold me for a buck an acre
is worth
half a million times that.
There's oil
on that land
mr. Gibbons, mr. Deidrich-
oil, black gold.
There's enough oil
in that land
to produce 500 barrels of oil
a day
for the next 1000 years.
And you sold it to me
for a buck an acre!
I swear, i could almost
feel sorry for you.
Well, uh, maybe
you don't understand.
We understand you,
mr. Feathersmith.
I saidoil!
Oil, yes, yes.
Well, how's that for a small
shocker to end the day?
Well, at the time,
it made us gulp a bit, too.
At the time?
Four years ago, the first
geological tests were made
and we were told about the oil.
Four years ago!
Indeed, there
were samples taken
of the soil
at that time, too.
There was never
any doubt
that the land
had oil under it.
6,000 feet under it,
mr. Feathersmith,
which means it might
just as well be on the moon.
The moon?
The oil can't be taken out
of the ground.
It just can't
be taken out.
What do you mean,
it can't be taken out?
You could drill down five miles
if you needed to.
Well, youcould perhaps,
but nobody else
on earth could.
And at that, you'd better
get up off that seat
and inventing some new kind
of a drill.
Of course, i...
i forgot.
It was 1937 when they...
when they...
uh, problem,
mr. Feathersmith?
Not feeling
too well?
Something, uh, a little
queasy, perhaps?
Oh, it's something
i ate, i think.
Something you ate,
no doubt
like, uh, likecrow,
mr. Feathersmith?
Mr. Cronk, this here
is mr., uh... mr., uh...
feathersmith.
Mr. Feathersmith
says he'd like
to talk to us
about... i guess you'd
call it "inventions."
What kind
of inventions?
It's something that'll turn
this two-bit tool shed
into a factory.
A self-starter.
You want
to enlarge
on that,
mr. Feathersmith?
What do you mean,
enlarge on it?
It's a thing you press
with your foot
that starts an engine
with an electric motor.
Well, uh, what's
it used for?
What's it used for?
It's used to make
200 million bucks.
What goes into it?
Are you all there?
It's a storage
battery, a motor...
it's a gillhookey
that starts the motor.
I've given you
the principle
all you have
to do is build it.
Make me a set of blueprints
and specifications
and i'll build it.
Look, i am not
a crummy draftsman
or a two-bit
blueprint man.
I'm a promoter,
a financier.
I'm going to give
you the backing
i've given you
the principle
all you have to
do is build it.
Not without blueprints,
specifications.
Now, what was
the other stuff?
Other stuff...
what isn't there?
There's everything.
There's everything
under the sun.
And you rube sit around here
fixing tricycle pedals.
There's radio.
There's television.
Plastics...
ever here of aluminum?
Aluminum airplanes?
You foggy-headed carriage
builders,
we could make ourselves
$8 billion!
Sure.
Of course we could.
Wait... there's nothing
standing in our way.
All it takes is just
a little imagination.
Just a little drive.
Let's talk it over.
Let's see what appeals to you.
Uh, what appeals to me?
Well, uh...
how about a nice, handsome
perpetual motion machine.
What's it used for?
To make 200 million bucks,
that's what it's used for.
Listen, are you all there?
It's a storage battery,
a motor...
it's a gillhookey
that starts the motor.
I've given you the principle,
all you have
to do is build it.
Now, look, i am not
a crummy draftsman
or a two-bit blueprint man.
I'm a promoter, a financier.
I'm going to give you
the backing.
I've already given
you the principle,
now all you have to do
is build it.
There's everything,
everything under the sun,
and you rube, you sit around
here fixing tricycle pedals.
There's radio,
there's television...
plastics... ever hear
of aluminum?
Aluminum airplanes...
you foggy-headed
carriage builders!
We could make ourselves
$8 million.
Jesus, this place...
the goals
of a 75-year-old man
she, she didn't
change me inside...
tha... that's why
i've been so tired...
why, why i can't function,
why i, i can't operate.
That's why
i can't make out...
because inside, i'm already
the way i was...
well, mr. Feathersmith.
Why, mr. Feathersmith, dear boy,
you look out of sorts...
flagging, peaked, drooping,
and not at all well.
You miserable, you...
now, let's be fair
about this, mr. Feathersmith,
and let's be reasoning
and rational and thoughtful.
I'm a... 75-year-old man.
Discerning of you.
Nothing was mentioned,
mr. Feathersmith,
about changing
yourchronologicalage.
You said you wanted
to look 30
which is precisely
the way you look.
We said nothing
about your insides...
your heart, your veins,
your kidneys, your bladder...
just your appearance.
That was all that was touched
upon in the contract.
But this place... this town...
hmm, indeed.
You wanted it as it was.
That was a specific clause
in the contract.
It's really not my fault
your memory is so imperfect.
As to the possibilities
of investments...
well, you knew
that oil wasn't
reached until 1937.
Your problem is that you leaped
before you looked.
But, but everything else...
everything else was wrong...
the girl... the deals...
inventions, stocks,
bonds, everything...
it didn't work.
It just... it just simply
didn't work.
Of course it didn't.
Of course, because you,
mr. Feathersmith,
are a wheeler and a dealer,
a financier, a pusher...
a brain, a manipulator...
a raider.
Because you are a taker,
instead of a builder.
A conniver,
instead of a designer.
A user...
instead of a bringer.
Well, mr. Feathersmith,
you are what is commonly
referred to
as being behind
the old eight-ball.
Look, look, i
don't want much.
Send me back.
Send me back to 1963,
back to where i was.
1963? Is that what you want?
That's all i want,
i swear to you.
That's all i want.
You understand, of course
that icansend you
back to 1963.
But it will be a 1963
predicated on what's occurred
in the past 24 hours.
I don't care, i don't care.
I think i might be able
to arrange
putting you back
in your own time.
But, mind you,
mr. Feathersmith,
this is nothing more nor less
than a gesture of... sympathy.
Ooh, hurts me
to mouth the word.
But frankly, you are
such a totally abject...
unhappy-looking creature,
that i can't find it
in my, uh, wherever you
find the heart...
to leave you here.
There's a train out of here
at midnight, a special train.
Oh, bless you, miss devlin.
I'll never forget... i swear
to you, i'll never forget.
There is a small surcharge,
mr. Feathersmith.
A surcharge?
$40.
$40?
Things
docost.
I, i don't have $40.
I don't,
i don't have five dollars.
How about that?
This is your night.
You have two negotiable items.
All you need do
is liquidate them.
But, but...
but who would buy them?
That i wouldn't know...
mr. Feathersmith.
But... you...
what'll i do,
what'll i do?
You've got
about ten seconds.
Find yourself
a customer.
It's as simple
as that.
Here, hecate!
Hecate!
Here, it's
a bargain!
Constant sunshine,
singing birds...
14...
all aboard!
1400 acres!
Please, it's a bargain!
Hurry, it's yours
for 40 bucks!
Yes, you
want something?
Oh, i was going
to clean up, mr. Hecate.
All right,
clean up.
Hmm, marvelous old place.
Really great old town.
Uh, sir?
Cliffordville.
Cliffordville, indiana.
I grew up there,
got my start there.
Oh, that,
that's a coincidence, sir.
I grew up there.
Name is feathersmith.
Hmm.
Well, how similar we are,
mr. Feathersmith.
We both came from cliffordville.
We both put on our pants
one leg at a time.
And here we wind up
in the same building
each with his own particular
function, huh?
Oh, oh, yes, sir, each
with our particular function.
Oh, they, they... they
gave me a, a watch.
Four years ago.
It was on the 40th anniversary
as custodian.
Well, now, maybe
for the next 40 years
if you really apply yourself,
mr. Feathersmith,
i'll buy you a fob.
Mr. William j. Feathersmith,
tycoon.
Who tried the track
one more time
and found it muddier
than he remembered.
Proving with at least
a degree of conclusiveness
that nice guys don't
always finish last.
And some people should quit
when they're ahead.
Tonight's tale
of iron men and irony
delivered f.o.b.
From the twilight zone.
On our next excursion
into the twilight zone
we borrow an imposing array
of talent
and call in the services
of a distinguished author
named reginald rose,
and some exceptionally fine
acting talent
in the persons of
mr. Pat hingle, miss nan martin
and miss ruth white.
They appear in a story called
"the incredible world
of horace ford."
And it's an incredible world
indeed.
Harvey bender?
Who's harvey bender?
What's the matter?
Just stop it.
He was one of the kids
last night.
What are you talking about?
I saw him last night.
Don't you know
that's impossible?
I know what i see.
He was ten years old
when you were ten years old.
He's as old as you are.
I tell you, i saw him.
He's a grown up man.
Oh, you think so?
You think so, do you?
Let me tell you, i saw him last
night on randolph street.
And i saw george lambert
and i saw cy wright.
And they are still kids.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org