Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Good evening, happy
family members and stockholders
of the w.v. Whipple
manufacturing corporation.
This year, as you've
already perceived,
we are bringing you the story
of your company's progress
via the motion picture screen.
This is our main operating plant
in the midwest.
You will note
the number of employees
attending the assembly line.
In this one plant,
your company employs 34,827 men.
Added to 13 other major
whipple plants
across the country,
we employ a total
of close to 283,000 personnel.
And now, to the stunning
and exciting news
which i believe you'll agree
shows, once again,
that at whipple's,
we only take forward steps.
Now, family members,
and stockholders
of the whipple corporation,
thisis the x109b14
modified transistorized
totally automatic
assembly machine
which eliminates
61,000 jobs,
73 bulky, inefficient machines,
81,000 needless man hours
per 11 working days
and $4 million
in expenditures each year
for employee hospitalization,
employee insurance,
employee welfare and
employee profit participation.
Even as you stockholders
are watching this film,
the first model of the x109b14
modified transistorized machine
is being placed into operations
here in our midwestern
main plant.
Within six months,
our entire production facilities
will be totally automated.
Ladies and gentlemen,
from now on
whipple will operate
from a brain center
with machines such as this one.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the whipple family,
this ends
our 1967 year-end report.
Well, hanley,
will that bring
the stockholders
to their feet
cheering?
Not that i need
encouragement.
The movie speaks
for itself.
It does, indeed.
You didn't
like it, hanley?
I'm a chief engineer,
mr. Whipple.
My duties consist
of plant management.
I'm not a film critic.
Look, i didn't expect
four stars, hanley.
But as plant manager,
i wanted your point of view
on the film's content.
I thought you'd have
some enthusiasm
for the changes
we're planning.
Doesn't it give you
the lay of the land?
Can't you answer that?
Oh, yes.
It gives me
the lay of the land.
Tell me
do you really expect
to automate in six months?
Four months is
a better guess.
Lots of things
are going
in the trash heap.
Time clocks,
for instance.
There won't be anybody
to punch in or out.
I'll donate them
to a museum.
Something,
hanley?
Yes, something.
Something like
a lot of men out of work!
That, unfortunately,
is progress, hanley.
You're a solid man
on assembly line planning.
But when it comes to progress
you're a foot-dragger.
Sweetheart, you and i
are going to spend
a lot of time together.
Indeed, we are.
Indeed, indeed, indeed we are.
These are the players,
with or without a scorecard:
In one corner, a machine;
in the other,
one wallace v. Whipple, man.
And the game?
It happens to be
the historical battle
between flesh and steel,
between the brain of man
and the product of man's brain.
We don't make book on this one,
and predict no winner
but we can tell you that
for this particular contest,
there is standing room only
in the twilight zone.
You know what
your trouble is?
You're holding on tight
to this 19th century.
I'm holding tight
to some principles-
principles that have
to do with firing.
The regret for
the wholesale firings
of men who've worked here
from 20 to 30 years.
Regret, indeed,
it's come to regret?
I'll let you
handle the regrets.
That'll be your
responsibility.
Have a sign made
for your desk.
"Mr. Walter hanley,
plant manager
in charge of regrets."
Tell me,
why are you so eager
to replace men
with machines?
Did it ever
occur to you
that you're trading
efficiency for pride?
Pride?
Yes, pride!
Craftsmanship.
What a man feels
when he makes something.
What does your
machine feel?
Anything?
Anything at all?
What the devil
can i do with pride?
Can it, bottle it,
wrap it, produce it?
I'm not selling pride,
i'm selling product.
Your father...
what about
my father?
He ran this plant
for 40 years.
He had an eye
for profit.
He was never
inefficient, but...
but what?
He had something else
on his mind.
What else did my father
have on his mind?
Good will.
And the welfare
of the people
who worked for him.
Good will and the welfare
of the people
that worked for him, indeed.
In 40 years, my father doubled
the size of his plant
while his competitors
quadrupled theirs.
His competitors,
who were less concerned
with the good will
and welfare
of the people
that worked for them.
They paid a fair wage
and got a fair day's work.
But, if they could find
a machine to replace a man
they did it.
But they
didn't have
plant managers
like yourself
who went off
into a crying jag
every time
a pink slip
was attached
to a time clock.
What's the name
of the plant foreman?
Dickerson, dickerson,
that's his name.
Get him up here for me,
will you?
I'm going
to indulge in
that heartfelt compassion
you hunger for.
I'm going to give him and
his staff four months' notice.
Now, hanley, is that
compassionate or isn't it?
Now, go get him, please,
get him up here
hold his hand, dry his eyes,
pat him on the head
but get him up here.
So that's about the size
of it, mr. Dickerson,
you may tell
the entire day shift
that they'll be pink-slipped
as of the first of july.
We're here to set
it up, mr. Whipple.
Oh, fine, i've checked
the machine over.
Just put it downstairs,
but treat it gently.
Handle it with care.
Now, you realize that this
somewhat wholesale discharge
has nothing to do
with dissatisfaction
on your part
or that of the men.
It's merely progress,
mr. Dickerson.
Out with the old,
in with the new-
automation.
That'll be all.
Yes, mr. Whipple.
That will be all.
Did you ever notice,
mr. Hanley,
ever notice how it looks
like it had a face?
An ugly face.
A miserable, ugly face.
Whipple, he thinks
it's a machine.
It's not a machine,
it's an enemy.
It's an opponent.
I swear, we've got to hate
a thing like this.
Getting awful late, dick.
Should have closed
half an hour ago.
You know what
these are?
Pair of hands?
Yeah, pair of hands.
You know what
else they are?
They're obsolete,
they're off the market.
They're like wooden wagons
trying to roll down a freeway.
Flesh and bone
and muscle and nerve
but that don't cut
mustard anymore.
I want to tell
you some...
i'm going
to tell you something.
There isn't amachine made
that can beat a man.
Isn't one...
i'll prove it
to you!
I'm going over there right now
and i'm going
to prove it to you.
I'm going to take
that new machine of whipple's
and i'm going to turn it
into nuts and bolts.
And if that slob with
the key chain gets in my way
i'm going
to strangle him with it.
Dickerson!
The watchman
called.
He said
you're drunk
and barged right
past him.
And he's right,
mr. Whipple.
Iamdrunk.
And i did barge
right in.
I've worked here for 30 years!
And i've been foreman
for 17 of them.
In my book, that gives me
some rights, mr. Whipple.
Well, you've got
the wrong book, dickerson.
You're drunk, disorderly
and trespassing
on private property
and subject to arrest.
Tell me something,
mr. Whipple.
When you're dead and buried,
who will mourn for you?
Shall i tell you
the difference, mr. Dickerson,
between you and it?
That machine costs
two cents an hour for current.
It lasts indefinitely.
It gets no wrinkles,
no arthritis,
no hardening of the arteries.
That one machine is a lathe
operator, a press operator.
Two machines replace 114 men
that take no coffee breaks,
no sick leaves,
no vacations with pay.
And that, in my book,
is worth considerably more
than you are.
They should have stopped you
a year ago!
Somebody ought to held you down
and put a bit in your head
and poured in some reminders
that men have to eat and work.
And you can't pack them
in cosmoline
like surplus tanks!
Or put them out to pasture
like old bulls!
I'm a man,
mr. Whipple!
You hear me?
I'm a man!
And that makes me better
than that...
hunk of metal, you hear me?!
Better!
What should i do?
Stop him,
stop him!
He has a crow bar!
I don't care!
No, you can't
do that!
You see, machine?
It... took more than...
you to beat me.
It... it took a man.
Oh, hanley, i've
been expecting you.
No doubt.
They told me
you were at the hospital.
I just came from
the hospital.
Fortunately for you,
mr. Whipple,
dickerson's
going to live.
Fortunately, other than
protecting my property
i have no
involvement in that.
Are the technicians
downstairs?
I asked you a question.
Are the technicians
repairing that machine?
It appears so.
Ah, good.
Oh, hanley,
this should interest you.
This is a tape-controlled
seven axis.
It's called a sentry.
Know what it does?
It keeps an eye
on every operation
in the entire plant.
It keeps absolutely
accurate data
on man hours, cost
hours, product rejects,
just everything!
The most sophisticated
machine i've ever seen.
I just bought it.
How many men
doesitreplace?
This should
please you-
only one,
just one!
As a matter of fact,
it replaces you.
That's only
right, mr. Whipple,
since the point
of my coming today
was to give you
my notice.
Oh, good,
good.
I suspected
as much.
You're a
sensible man
and i'm sure you know
that an industrial team
has to be a
compatible team.
And when two men rub
each other the wrong way,
well, it's unrealistic
and impractical
that they try to stay
on the same team.
In spite of the fact you
think i'm kind of an ogre,
some sort of a
heartless scrooge,
i'm not going to
forget the many years
of hard work you put in
for me and my father.
I'm going to see that you get an
extremely liberal severance pay
and what i'm sure
you'll agree
is a far better
than average pension.
That's very generous
of you.
There's something
i'd like to give you,
if you don't mind.
No, what is that?
That's for you
from me.
For your lack of
sensitivity, compassion.
Your heartless manipulation
of men and metals.
You can take
my severance pay,
my pension, and
your good-bye speeches
and feed them
into your machine.
Because when i walk away
from you,
i walk awayclean.
And that, mr. Whipple,
is one hell of a trick!
A new watchman device.
Take out your i.d. Card
and hold it
in front of the door.
There are built-in
electric eyes.
Yes,
mr. Whipple?
Oh, run a control
check, please.
I already have,
two hours ago.
I did it right
after lunch, too.
And if you
recall, sir,
i did it this
morning, as well.
Ever heard
of preventative
maintenance?
It's my job,
mr. Whipple.
What you're asking of
me isn't maintenance.
It's not
preventing a thing.
Oh, indeed, and i suppose
you know what's needed in this
plant and what isn't needed.
I know that running
equipment checks
ten times a day
is a waste of time,
a waste of effort,
and it's becoming
an idiotic ritual around here.
Young man, your presence is
a necessity of the moment.
Notice i stress "of the moment."
Uh, a case in point.
Case in point.
Now, stay here,
observe this.
Dear sir
yours of the 14th
received and acknowledged.
Now is the time
for all good men
to come to the aid
of their country
etc., etc., etc., etc.
A perfect letter.
Not one error
or erasure.
Typed at conception.
Am i getting through,
young man?
You mean secretaries
are obsolete now.
Precisely, obsolete.
And do you know
what else it means?
It means no more powder rooms,
no more coffee breaks.
No more work stoppages
due to sundry inconveniences
such as maternity and all that.
Inconveniences like maternity?
You'll have
to forgive me, mr. Whipple.
But if we keep this up
we'll have wonderful products
but mighty few people
to buy them.
Happily that is not my concern.
Providing efficiency-
that is my only concern.
Mr. Whipple?
Have you looked
around this place,
lately?
Looked around?
The cafeteria, for example.
It's like a cave.
Not a soul in there.
Just a few vending machines
and music through
a loudspeaker.
Have you seen
the parking lot?
It's a desert.
No cars, no people.
How very enlightening.
This place has
everything now
for efficiency.
Do you know
what it lacks?
No, tell me.
Voices.
Laughter.
Whatever makes people
feel for people.
That's what it lacks.
This is a lousy
place to work.
Then i'll spare you
further suffering.
You're discharged.
I've been expecting that.
Actually, i've been wanting it.
I can't work here anymore.
It's too darn lonely.
And another thing, mr. Whipple,
to do with
equipment checks
and preventative
maintenance?
It might be a
good idea if you ran
an equipment
check on yourself!
Equipment check on myself!
What insufferable rot!
Did it occur to you
that you're trading efficiency
for pride?
When you're dead and buried
who will mourn for you?
I think it might be a good idea
if you ran an equipment check...
on yourself!
Did it occur to you that you're
trading efficiency for pride?
When you're dead and buried
who will mourn for you?
I think it might be a good idea
if you ran an equipment check...
on yourself!
I think it might be a good idea
if you ran an equipment check...
on yourself!
Did it occur to you that you're
trading efficiency for pride?
When you're dead and buried
who will mourn for you?
What'll it be
mr. Whipple?
Beer, please.
To other days,
mr. Hanley.
And to other toasts.
I'll drink to that,
mr. Whipple.
How are you finding retirement?
Oh, tolerable,
mr. Whipple, tolerable.
I manage to...
i manage to keep busy
not as much as i'd like...
my wife says i'm underfoot,
but i do all right.
But you know, it's kind of nice
to sleep late in the mornings.
It's important.
Uh... this retirement, i mean.
Very important.
A man should have time
for leisure when he grows older.
It's important
he have time for leisure.
That's so, mr. Whipple.
You know, when the
board of directors
first indicated to me
that they thought i was
somewhat overtired,
should relinquish some
of my responsibilities,
well, if the truth
were known, mr. Hanley,
i did feel some sort
of antipathy for them,
but, uh, they were right.
They were quite
right, you know.
But with the perspective
of time,
i realized they'd moved me
out of there.
I'm not married, you know,
and things get a little dull.
Well, no, not, not dull, really.
I, uh, i manage
to keep myself busy
but there are times
when i wish... when i...
it's not right, hanley.
It's-it's not right.
Cold, dispassionate,
impersonal...
they-they chuck a man out
right in his prime.
Chuck him out
like he was some kind of a part.
Said i was neurotic
about things.
Said that being alone
with the machines
had warped me.
That was the expression
they used- "warped."
It's not fair, hanley.
It's not fair.
A man has value.
A man has worth.
They just snap their fingers,
and they bring in a replacement.
They just bring in
a replacement.
It, it isn't fair, hanley.
It, it isn't fair,
the way they diminish us.
There are many bromides
applicable here-
too much of a good thing,
tiger by the tail,
as you sow, so shall ye reap.
The point is that too often
man becomes clever
instead of becoming wise,
he becomes inventive,
but not thoughtful.
And sometimes, as in the case
of mr. Whipple,
he can create himself
right out of existence.
Tonight's tale of oddness
and obsolescence
from the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Onthe twilight zonenext trip,
we move into the area
of authentic folk singing.
But this is folk singing
like you've probably
never heard before.
The words and the music
in this item are haunting indeed
and this one provides
one of the more odd excursions
into the places of shadow.
Gary crosby and bonnie beecher
star in a most unusual tale
by anthony wilson.
It's called
"come wander with me."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org