Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound...
a dimension of sight...
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Yeah.
This is grady.
Who?
What paper?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so you're the creep tha...
i said creep!
Yeah, i know who you are.
I know who you are.
Sure, i read your column.
Every time i read it,
it makes me sick.
I want to use a stomach pump!
Don't try and nuzzle up to me
with that "mr. Grady" stuff.
Three years ago
you stuck in the shiv!
Listen to me, i had nothing
to do with horse doping.
Nothing- you understand that?
Uh-huh.
Sure, a couple of taps
on the typewriter
and i get a 60-day suspension!
You can talk pretty safe
now you're 50 blocks away.
If you were here
in this room now,
i'd scrape you off the wall
and put you in a cup!
How does that grab you?
This is a statement
to the press!
Grady to the press, you fink.
You hyenas down there.
Listen, and don't forget
to spell the name correct!
G-r-a-d-y!
You chump.
You stupid, rotten chump.
Just on account
of a couple of fixes, huh?
Big boys walk away
with all the big dough.
What do you walk away with, huh?
A bagful of change.
What are you going to do now?
I know what you'll do.
You get a carriage,
and you'll drive lovers
through central park.
Grady, you kill me.
You... you kill me, boy.
Yes... you runt!
You shrimp!
What are you going
to do now, pal?
What can you do?
The name is grady-
five feet short
in stockings and boots,
a slightly distorted offshoot
of a good breed of humans
who race horses.
He happens to be one
of the rotten apples,
bruised and yellowed
by dealing in dirt,
a short man with a short memory
who's forgotten that he's worked
for the sport of kings
and helped turn it
into a cesspool,
used and misused
by the two-legged animals
who have hung
around sporting events
since the days of the coliseum.
So this is grady,
on his last night as a jockey.
Behind him are hialeah,
hollywood park and saratoga.
Rounding the far turn
and coming up fast on the rail-
is the twilight zone.
How goes the world, mr. Grady?
Who...?
What...?
Little tight on the turns?
Bogged down by a muddy track?
How goes it, mr. Grady?
It's a gag.
Huh?
It's a gag, huh?
All right, now.
Look you...
you made your point.
Where are you?
Where am i?
I'm between the frontal lobes,
mr. Grady.
What?
Inside your head-
securely nestled
in the gray convolutions.
Convolutions?
Just what is that
supposed to mean?
I'm inside your head, mr. Grady.
My head?
How you like it in there, huh?
How you like it in there?
Are you comfortable?
Huh?
Excuse me for laughing.
That's a funny question.
Comfortable inside your head?
It's like sleeping in the midst
of a parade on 42nd street-
noisy, crowded, uncomfortable.
In fact, i'm sick of it.
If you're sick of it, get out.
You're sick of it.
Get out of there.
I wished i could.
It would be much more
comfortable outside
instead of being cooped up in
that tiny little brain of yours.
Who are you?
I'm your memory,
your conscience, mr. Grady.
I'm every one of your
aspirations and recollections.
I'm every one of your failures
and defeats.
I also wear the wreaths
of all your victories.
I'm what you call
the "alter ego."
Ego.
Big deal.
Big deal!
What do you want?
I think the apt question
would be, "what is it you want?"
It's a hot one, huh?
What do i want?
I don't need a thing.
You really are a
dumb little runt.
That's what you call
yourself, isn't it?
"Runt" or was
it "shrimp"?
Why don't you get out of here?
How do i get you out of here?
You don't,
you don't.
You live with me.
In fact, you
might find me
very interesting.
I know you very
well, mr. Grady.
There isn't
one thought
that crosses
your mind
that i'm not
aware of.
There isn't one
ugly recollection,
one bitter little shame
that i'm not aware of.
Bitter little shame.
You don't know me
from man o'war.
I got no bitter recollections.
Oh, come now, mr. Grady.
Look, shall we look
at the record book?
1961- hialeah.
Suspended for riding
infractions.
It wasn't my fault.
1962- six month suspension
for failure to report
a bribe offer.
I was framed.
And now most recently
the crowning touch
to an illustrious career
lifetime suspension
for race fixing, horse doping.
I didn't dope any horses.
Career's shot.
Roughly eight dollars
in your jeans.
I don't need you.
It won't be any time at all.
Two year's time i'll be back up
riding five or six
winners a day.
You'll drive a carriage
with lovers in it
through central park.
Knock it off!
No, you need me, mr. Grady.
In fact, you have
desperate need of me.
Knock it off!
Where are you now?
Huh?
Ah, you fake!
I need you
like i need pneumonia.
Like i need a fractured leg,
that's how i need you.
Who do you think
you're talking to anyway?
you're talking to?
I make one phone call
to hencheck,
one phone call,
and in an hour's time,
i'm on my way to puerto rico
riding in the warm sun.
Two years time, i'll be back
here riding in silks.
Why don't you call
mr. Hencheck?
Go ahead, give him a buzz.
I'll show you, loudmouth.
I'll make you eat
every rotten word.
Hello, this is grady.
Hencheck there?
I want to talk to him!
Listen to this.
Hello, hencheck, it's grady.
What's to be surprised about?
You had your boat race,
so you made your pile.
I'm down to my last eight bucks.
I figure it's time
that grady got his, see?
I figure that...
hencheck.
Very unappreciative.
Well, that's the breaks.
They take, they never give.
What's to do now?
Write a will and take gas?
Look, i could nickel-and-dime
or i could buy and sell him
a year ago.
I don't need him.
I don't need you.
I don't need nobody.
I was a big man once.
I can be big again.
Wait and see.
You know,
it was just a year ago
you were strutting
around the country,
you wore nice, shiny shoes,
new clothes, tipped big.
You had some compensation
then, mr. Grady.
Compensation?
For the fact that
you're a little runt.
For the unpleasant realization
that all your life
you've had to stand on tiptoe
to look at what's around you.
I wish you were here right now,
hear me?
I wish you were here right now.
Just look down...
under your feet.
Mr. Grady, you know
what you want?
You want to be respected.
Up on a horse you're a man.
On the ground
you're a half-pint.
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up, you understand?
Easy, mr. Grady.
Easy does it, easy does it.
Now we get to the moment
of truth- the ultimate.
Now you hit pay dirt, kid.
You get whatever you want.
What do you mean
"whatever i want"?
Tell me, what is it you want
more than anything else
on the earth?
This is the moment, this is it.
What is it you want, mr. Grady?
Name it- it's yours.
What do i want?
I want to be the biggest.
Hear me?
Yeah, that's what i want.
I want to be the biggest.
I want to be big!
Damn you, i want to be big!
Have a good rest, mr. Grady?
Yeah. Yeah.
I had a good rest.
This is wild.
Like what you see?
What is this?
Am i dreaming?
Is this is a dream?
A dream- oh, come now.
Look, touch the dresser.
Yeah.
Yeah, i'll touch it.
Yeah, that's it.
Now touch the overhead beam.
Yeah.
These are all
very solid objects-
width, height,
thickness and reality.
Yeah...
yeah.
Hey, what is this?
You had your heart's desire.
You didn't ask for a two-hour
escape with morpheus.
You wanted stature, mr. Grady.
You wanted size.
You wanted a view from a long
way up and a long way out.
Yeah, i wanted size.
You wanted to be big.
Well, look at yourself.
You're big.
You're mr. Big.
You're hercules, you're the most
sizable thing since paul bunyan.
You don't have any complaints
that you want
to trot out, do you?
Complaints?
Do i have any complaints?
No, i have no complaints.
Hey, you know
what this calls for?
This calls for a-a celebration.
Look, hey, here, hey,
you drink, don't ya?
Huh? You drink?
Go right ahead.
Be my guest.
Yeah, well,
here's mud in your eye.
Too bad you can't
enjoy this with me.
I'm joining you,
i'm joining you.
Believe me, i'm feeling
the hot little ripples
just as you do.
You do, huh?
Yeah?
Well, you stay right in there.
You stay there.
I'm gonna have some fun,
you understand?
I'm gonna have some fun! See?!
Ooh, careful, careful.
You don't want to go
through the floor.
Hey...
mr. Grady.
Mr. Grady!
Yeah.
Like the view, do you?
I love it. I love it.
You know what
i'm going to do now?
I'm gonna make a call,
a telephone call
to somebody very special,
a very, very special girl.
And when she hears about this...
she's going to flip.
Really, pal,
are you that attractive?
Tell me, does size mean
that much?
You bet your bottom dollar
it does.
You know she used to lean over
and pat me on the head.
Hello, honey.
Hello, doll.
You know who this is?
This is grady.
Yeah.
Wait a minute, honey,
don't brush me off.
This is your ex-meal ticket,
an eight-course meal ticket
at that!
Now listen to this, honey...
i'm big.
Understand that?
I'm b-l-g.
Big, big, big, big, big.
I don't know, i may be six,
seven, eight feet tall.
I don't know.
The lakers will be scouting me
any day now.
Huh?
What a minute,
you don't talk to me like th...
you don't talk to me like that,
i said.
You heard what i...
i'll slap your face off!
You no good alley cat!
That's great-
that was wonderful.
You managed to flex
your muscles
in a most impressive fashion.
At this rate you're going,
women all over the world
will be flocking
to your doorstep no doubt.
Well, i can call 12 girls.
Just because i struck out
this time,
i could call 12 girls prettier
and nicer than that one.
You don't believe me, do you?
So far you just haven't
impressed me.
Well, i will.
I will.
Yeah.
What do you mean, too loud?
Oh.
How's that, mac,
is that better?
Good.
Hmm?
What time?
Yeah.
Yeah, i'll be expecting
his call.
Thank you.
Yeah.
He knows the number, doesn't he?
Fine, fine. Thanks.
What was that all about?
That was a fellow telling me
that a lawyer was going to call
me from the racing commission.
Hey, tell me,
who are you?
My imagination?
You, uh, you don't have very
much imagination, mr. Grady.
Wait a minute,
who are you, what are you?
I mean, what's all this
"alter ego" jazz?
Well, i'll tell
you, mr. Grady.
I'll try to make it
as simple as possible.
I'm the fate every man
makes for himself.
You generally find me
down at the bottom
of the barrel.
I'm the strength
dredged up
in desperation.
I'm the last gasp.
That's supposed
to be clear, huh?
You're nothing!
Nothing, understand?
Oh, i'm something.
Really, i'm something.
In some cases
i'm something very good.
In some cases- depending upon
the person i'm representing-
i can work miracles.
You do?
I come with heroism,
sacrifice, strength,
and even better than that,
i can epitomize
everything noble in men.
You can, huh?
Now, in your case, mr. Grady,
your requirements
were quite small.
What do you mean, quite small?
Your dreams
were rather insignificant,
your aspirations
hardly worth mentioning.
I mean to say, if you had asked
to win the kentucky derby,
and win it cleanly
and with honor,
that would've been quite
a moment, wouldn't it?
Yeah.
That'd been the greatest.
Or if you'd asked to perform
an act of heroism, let's say,
that would've been qualification
for the respect you seek.
This, too, would've been
exemplary, right?
I suppose that would've
been all right, yeah.
But as it is, mr. Grady,
what was your heart's desire?
Well, i...
wanted...
i wanted...
i wanted to...
to be a big man.
That's right, yes.
Big in the sense that your
hands can smother a telephone,
your face can overshoot
its reflections in the mirror.
You come real cheap.
I don't come cheap.
All i ever wanted out of life
was the fact that
i could walk down the street
and people not stare at me
like i was a freak!
I am not cheap, buddy.
I don't come cheap.
I've got my heart's desire.
Yeah?
Yes, mr. Newman.
Yes, sir.
Really?
Really? Do you...?
Thank you, sir.
You don't know how much
this means to me.
Thank the members of the board,
and thank everybody that went
to bat for me, will you?
Just... just thank them.
Tell them how much
i appreciate it.
Thank you very much, mr. Newman.
And listen, tell everybody
they don't have to worry
about me anymore.
I'll play it straight.
I mean, no worries.
Cut-and-dried, you understand?
When grady's up,
the worries are over, right?
Thanks, mr. Newman.
And thank everybody for me.
Right. Good-bye.
What do you think now,
loudmouth?
Everything's going my way.
One phone call
and you're top dog, huh?
You know who that was?
That was the racing commission.
A lot of owners
have signed a petition.
They want me to ride again,
do you understand that?
They want grady to ride again.
I'm going to ride again.
What's so funny?
Eh?
What's so funny
about me riding...?
Eh...
i'm going to ri...
wait a minute.
I'm too big.
I'm too big!
I can't ride!
Wait a minute!
I can't wear my clothes!
I'm too... i'm too big!
I'm too big!
Hear me?
I can't ride!
No!
Please, please...
please make me small!
Please, i'll never ask
for anything again.
Please make me small.
Please!
Oh, god.
Youaresmall, mr. Grady.
You see, every time you won
an honest race,
that's when you were a giant.
Right now they just don't come
any smaller.
The name is grady,
ten feet tall,
a slightly distorted offshoot
of a good breed of humans
who race horses.
Unfortunately for mr. Grady,
he learned too late
that you don't measure size
with a ruler,
you don't figure height
with a yardstick
and you never judge a man by
how tall he looks in a mirror.
The giant is as he does.
You can make a parimutuel bet
on this- win, place or show-
in or out of the twilight zone.
And now mr. Serling.
Next ontwilight zone,
a show that might very aptly
be called a living end,
and, with comparable aptness,
is called "living doll."
It's written by colleague
and cohort charles beaumont,
and stars telly savalas,
and costars mary laroche.
Mr. Beaumont supplies us
with a little weirdy
involving a man and a doll.
It comes well recommended.
Next time out, "living doll."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org