Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Nut.
Hello?
I'd like to speak
to mr. O'connor, please.
That's correct.
I'd rather not say.
It's rather personal.
Hello, is this mr. O'connor?
Mr. O'connor, you have a man
working for you in personnel-
a young man
named alfred brewster.
That's right- been with you
about a year and a half.
The man's a communist.
That's right.
The man's a communist,
a menace to society-
should be discharged
immediately.
Never mind how i know-
i know, that's all.
I'm going to check back
with you in a few days,
and if he's not been discharged,
i'm going to take
this whole matter to a superior.
That's correct.
Bye, mr. O'connor.
School superintendent, please.
Hello, is this
the school superintendent?
Well,
this is a concerned citizen,
and this call has to do
with a teacher in your employ.
His name is...
farwell... william j. Farwell-
teaches at your
north end high school.
That's correct.
Well, the man
is morally objectionable.
He's a drinker, a carouser,
and i have it on good authority
that his relationships
with his students
are questionable at best.
He should be
discharged immediately.
Well, never mind who this is.
I happen to be giving you facts
and these facts are
what is at issue.
Well, you'd best check on him.
That...
you most certainly should.
And immediately-
that's... that's correct.
A rather full morning's work,
wouldn't you say, pete?
Eleven names.
Of course,
it's questionable at best
as to what concrete
results we can expect,
but at least,
the seeds have been planted;
the opening guns fired;
the first attack rendered.
Look at them, look at them
out there- the dregs, carrion,
leeches sucking us dry,
carrying evil around with them
like cold germs.
Well, we're going to have to
face it sooner or later, pete.
Phone calls are one thing,
threats and exposures
simply expedients.
Oh, no, pete, my old friend,
we're going to have to embark
on a much more ambitious course
and it must be today, pete.
It must be this afternoon.
4:00, pete.
That's when we'll make it occur.
We'll make it occur at 4:00.
At that moment,
that precise moment,
we shall destroy evil.
This is both my charge
and my obligation, pete,
to destroy evil,
and we shall do it at 4:00.
I'm not quite sure
of the method yet,
but that will come to me.
That will come to me assuredly,
and it will be a revelation.
It will be
the expiration of immorality,
the exordium of the end.
4:00, pete,
that's when we'll make it happen
through whatever form i choose.
Four o'clock.
That's oliver crangle,
a dealer
in petulance and poison.
He's rather arbitrarily
chosen 4:00
as his personal
gotterdammerung,
and we are about to watch
the metamorphosis
of a twisted fanatic,
poisoned by the gangrene
of prejudice,
to the status
of an avenging angel,
upright and omniscient,
dedicated and fearsome.
Whatever your clocks say,
it's 4:00-
and wherever you are
it happens to be
the twilight zone.
Yes, what is it?
There's special delivery stuff
for you, mr. Crangle.
Well, bring it in-
the door's not locked.
Something else,
was there,
mrs. Williams?
Something else?
No, nothing else.
Nothing else,
mr. Crangle.
You sure get
enough mail, anyway.
Somebody would think
you ran sort
of a mail-order business.
What i do is
none of your concern.
I pay my rent on time
and i mind my own business.
You should learn
a respect for privacy.
Well, i...
well, i nev...!
"Well, i...! Well, i...!"
Have you any more pertinent
remarks to make?
If not, then i would be
grateful if you left me alone.
I have a great deal
of work to do.
I can believe that.
You should,
mrs. Williams.
You may thank me one day.
That is...
assuming you're around,
and assuming you retain
a capacity for appreciation.
And what's that
supposed to mean-
"assuming i'll
be around"?
Are you threatening
me, mr. Crangle?
My dear lady, i don't
threaten people.
I compile them.
I compile them and i...
investigate them...
analyze them.
Then i
categorize them,
and i judge them.
If they're impure
and evil,
then they must
be punished.
If, on the other hand,
they're simply
misled or naive
or unsophisticated,
then i point out
to them the right way.
Oh, is that...?
What i mean is,
is that what you do
for a living, i mean?
Indeed.
Here.
"Mrs. Chloe williams,
age 54, widow;
"married
to john alistair williams;
none;
"husband's political
curiosity..."
"ignorance."
That is merely
a preliminary report,
mrs. Williams.
The research
in depth on you
is in that master
file over there.
Nut.
All rested up,
are you, pete?
Had your little nap?
That's good,
my young man.
We're going
to have
an exciting
afternoon.
Things are
going
to happen
at 4:00.
Indeed
they will.
What's going to happen at 4:00?
What's going to happen indeed?
Why, at 4:00,
we're going to expose evil-
strip it bare,
push it out into the light
dissect it,
pinpoint it,
eliminate it,
exorcise it,
denude it,
destroy it!
Oh!
Something else,
was there,
mrs. Williams?
Uh... uh, no, no,
nothing else.
I'm looking
for a mr. Crangle.
I was told he lives here.
Oh, yes, with a vengeance
he lives here.
He lives right up there.
That's where he lives.
But i tell you, young woman,
i wouldn't go in there
without police protection.
That man's got a
leak in his attic
a mile wide.
Mr. Crangle?
Mr. Crangle!
Well?
My name is lucas.
I was wondering
if you would speak
with me for a moment.
Lucas... lucas...
ah! Kurt j.
Lucas, age 27,
intern, east
side hospital?
That's my husband.
Is he indeed?
Well, now, your
husband, you say.
Come in, come
in, come in.
Please.
Now...
what about
your husband?
Why, mr. Crangle,
why are you trying to hurt him?
What has he ever done to you?
To me?
Why, nothing to me.
That is, nothing personally.
I don't know your husband.
I knowofhim.
I know of his background,
but we've never met.
He's a stranger then
to you, isn't he?
He's a perfect stranger.
A stranger, yes,
but not
a perfect stranger.
As a matter of fact,
your husband, mrs. Lucas,
happens to be
most... imperfect.
And when you observe
that he has
done nothing to me,
let me hasten to
illuminate you on this.
He has done a lot
against society.
My husband, for
your information,
is a dedicated
young doctor.
He has only one
abiding interest
and that is to heal,
to stop pain.
And to kill!
That's his other
abiding interest
that you have
conveniently skipped.
L, l, l, l, l,
l, l, l...
l-u... l-u-c... here we are.
"Lucas,
"kurt j., m.d.,
second-year intern
east side hospital."
These facts came
to my attention.
"On the night
of march 12, 1961,
"while serving in
the emergency ward
"he permitted the death
of one mrs. Angela rienti
"by failing to
relieve pressure
"resulting of
a brain injury
from a traffic accident."
It was
too late-
he got to her too late.
He was taking care
of half a ward,
and when he got to her,
she was already dead.
He should have gotten
to her earlier.
That's about the size
of it, mrs. Lucas.
By what right, i must
ask you, mr. Crangle,
by what right
do you presume
to pass judgment
on my husband?
You're not even
a medical man.
You don't know
a thing about it
and yet you write
letters to the hospital,
dozens of letters,
accusing my husband
of being a murderer.
You're a filthy,
miserable...
tell me,
have they... discharged
your husband yet?
I've been expecting
it momentarily.
They have not.
It would take more
than letter writing
from a crank
to make that happen.
Your husband
is an evil man!
I will not put up
with evil in any form-
communists, subversives,
thieves, harlots-
evil, all of them,
and i will not
countenance evil.
Do you hear me?
I will absolutely not
countenance evil.
Hmm.
You're probably
unaware of it,
mr. Crangle,
but my husband is
a very sensitive man.
The people at the
hospital told him
to overlook
the letters,
forget about them,
but they're
killing him.
Tell me, mr. Crangle, why...
why do you do it?
Why?!
Why?
You ask me why?
Why, because
they're evil.
That's it.
There's nothing
complicated about that.
They're evil-
all those little bugs
out there- bacteria.
That's what
they are.
your husband is-
bacteria.
Those little...
that's it!
That's
precisely it!
what i'll do.
I knew i would get the clue.
I said "little people."
"Little people"?
That's what i'll do-
i'll turn all the evil people
into little ones.
You understand?
I'll make
every evil man three...
no, two... two feet tall.
At 4:00
in the afternoon,
at precisely 4:00,
every evil man
and woman
will be exactly
two feet tall.
A revelation...
an absolute revelation.
They'll all be
two feet tall!
"It is rather for us
to be dedicated
to the great task
remaining before us."
"All men are created equal."
We have a visitor
coming, pete.
Come in!
Come in, come in.
I'm oliver crangle.
I'm the one
who called.
My name is hall,
mr. Crangle
federal bureau
of investigation.
Our office had
a call from you...
indeed, indeed, indeed,
i placed the call.
Please, please,
sit down.
Now, i called
you here
because i felt
that the f.b.i.
Should know.
I also notified
the police
and the... the
fire departments.
I even had a call
in to washington,
although that call
probably won't
even go through.
It's my understanding
that the reds are
in complete control
in washington now.
They've probably
taken over
the switchboard, too.
The reds, mr. Crangle?
Oh, yes, the reds.
And it's a complete conspiracy,
you know.
All the evil people of the world
have banded together-
communists,
subversives, thieves-
it's a total,
worldwide
conspiracy.
Now, mr. Crangle,
on the phone you said
that you had
some sort of plan...
oh, yes, yes,
yes, yes,
that'll all take
place at 4:00.
Now, you see, mr. Hall,
i have spent many years
doing this kind of work.
I've made
a complete study of evil.
Oh, yes, i made a study of it.
I listen to the radio.
I watch television.
I cut out newspaper clippings.
I write letters to employers,
make phone calls late at night.
There's the most
efficient method, right there.
Calling these terrible
people constantly late at night,
waking them up-
waking them up, speaking
my charges and hanging up.
Very frustrating
for them.
Yes, i'll bet.
Oh, yes, indeed.
You know, they go
out of their mind with fury.
They don't like
to be woken up late at night,
i can assure you.
Who does, mr. Crangle?
With these people, it's
absolutely necessary.
But to the point, mr.
Hall, to the point.
It is now... 3:27.
In exactly 33 minutes,
all the evil people
in the world
will become half-
no, a third
their present size.
All the uncaught
murderers
and the tyrants,
all the bullies
and the wrongdoers-
all of them,
every one.
Nut.
Well, what do you think of it,
mr. Hall?
Mr. Crangle, how do you
go about doing this-
shrinking people?
Why, i... i
merely will it.
That's all.
In the past, several other
methods had occurred to me
to stop evil from spreading.
How does evil spread?
Hmm?
By public transport.
So i had it in mind
that i might take the stiffness
out of airplane propellers.
You understand?
Props hanging limp...
like empty banana skin.
Then it occurred to me
that i might change
all the wheels in the world
from round to square.
Or perhaps triangular.
So they'd stub in the asphalt
and stop them.
Mr. Crangle...
this... you know, mr. Hall,
this is hard to believe.
This idea just occurred to me-
about the change in size-
just a short
while ago.
Some benighted woman
was in here
and she inadvertently
gave me the idea-
turn all the evil people
into two feet tall.
And what could be simpler?
Think of it.
Think of how
inefficient
this would
make them.
Why, they couldn't handle
delicate scientific instruments,
adding machines, typewriters
or telephone dials.
Why, soon enough, they'd
be extinct, like dinosaurs.
Nut.
Mr. Crangle...
yes?
I'd like to ask you
a question, sir.
I hope you won't
take offense at it.
Oh, no, no,
please, go on.
Have you ever had
any psychiatric help?
What?
Psychiatric help.
Mr. Crangle, you don't
seem rational to me.
I... i think you've developed
some kind of obsession here.
I think you
need some help.
Help? I need...
why should i need help?
I'm not evil.
I'm very sorry,
mr. Crangle,
but there isn't much
we can do about this.
What do you mean?
The law enforcement
agencies
will have round-the-
clock schedules.
Don't you realize
how many evil people
you'll find?
Why, they'll be all
over the sidewalks,
all over the streets!
You'll have to
build more jails,
more electric
chairs, gallows.
Well, what about
it, mr. Hall?
What are you going
to do about it?
Nothing-
not a thing.
We have something
in this country
which makes all of that
quite unnecessary.
What's that?
It's the law,
mr. Crangle,
we have the law.
We like people's help
and their support,
their cooperation,
but interference is
quite another matter.
Oh, i get it now.
I understand.
I understand perfectly.
Why, i was an idiot
not to have realized
it sooner.
Of course.
Of course
you people
have gotten
into the f.b.i.
Stands to reason.
You've infiltrated
every place.
Let me tell you
something, mr. Hall,
let me tell
you something.
For the next 15
or 20 minutes,
you enjoy yourself
to the utmost,
because you'll
be two feet tall!
Two feet tall,
mr. Hall,
that's what you're
going to be!
Two feet tall,
do you hear me?
You and all
the rest of them-
all the evil people.
They're going to be
two feet tall!
Nut.
Oh, judgment day.
Judgment day is upon us.
Won't be long now.
You... 4:00.
You evil!
Evil!
It's happening,
pete.
It's happening
right now.
Everyone, all the evil ones-
they're all turning
into tiny little gnomes.
Nut.
Certainly, peter.
This is kind
of a celebration.
Nut.
At 4:00, an evil man made
his bed, and lay in it,
a pot called a kettle black,
a stone thrower broke
the windows of his glass house.
You look for this one
under "f" for "fanatic"
and "j" for "justice,"
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
As it happens to all men,
a newcomer takes his first step
into the twilight zone next week
when mr. Andy devine joins us
for a show called
"hocus-pocus and frisby."
He plays the role
of a storekeeper
of the cracker-barrel variety,
who stretches the truth
like most people pull on taffy.
This one is for laughs
and for the congenital liars
amongst you.
Next week, mr. Andy devine-
"hocus-pocus and frisby."
Red cross
looks to you for help.
When you help, we can help.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org