Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Say, doris,
i lost one of my cuff links.
Oh, i'll see if
i can find it.
No, i found it.
That's all right, then.
I found it
in your jewel case.
And i found
some other items.
Oh?
What about them?
You tell me.
There's nothing
much to tell, really.
I decided to bring back
some souvenirs.
Souvenirs?
A human finger?
A sacred death stone?
A vulture's claw?
Baubles of a witch doctor.
That's all these are to you,
souvenirs?
Of course.
Nothing else?
Are you sure?
Certainly, i'm sure.
Then you won't mind if i
dispose of them, will you?
Alan, don't!
Please don't!
Please don't, alan!
Why not?
No!
All right, now,
are there any more
souvenirs?
We aren't in africa any longer,
we're here in new york.
Do you understand
what i'm saying?
This is for weak people,
ignorant, uncivilized people
who don't know any better,
not for you, or me.
Doris, we've done
nothing wrong.
We have nothing
to fear.
Least of all
from a bunch of witch doctors
5,000 miles away.
What are you afraid of?
Africa.
Do you remember
what the old shaman
said long ago
when the men
started drilling?
He said we were
wounding the land,
hurting it,
making it bleed.
Alan, he said that land
would make us pay.
Doris, we left
africa weeks ago.
Did we? Well, i wonder.
Alan, sometimes at night
i can feel it,
all around me,
like some huge, dark animal.
Alan, please.
Please don't
let them go there.
Tell them it won't work.
Stop them now while
there's still time, please!
It's my job to engineer
a hydroelectric project,
not pander to ignorant
witch doctors.
I'll try to be back early.
You'll never be back.
Don't open the door.
The carcass of a goat,
a dead finger,
a few bits
of broken glass and stone
and mr. Alan richards,
a modern man of a modern age,
hating with all his heart
something
in which he cannot believe
and preparing-
although he doesn't know it-
to take the longest walk
of his life
right down to the center
of the twilight zone.
Levelling and drainage
have already been started
as well as preliminary work
on the dam itself.
Our time of completion
will have to be upped
by three to six months,
but this shouldn't affect
our general cost
more than
a few thousand dollars.
Well, it's
getting very late.
Before we make
a decision,
i have a few questions
if you don't mind.
Certainly, sir.
I'm sure you've
considered this
carefully,
but, for my
own curiosity,
what about
the natives?
Natives?
What about them, sir?
Well, what's
their attitude?
How are they
reacting?
As far as i know...
well, the kekouyu
are a violent people.
They resent
the loss of their homes.
They resent the enterprise
even though
they'll benefit eventually.
They resent us.
But i doubt they'll cause
any serious disturbance.
Except... for uchawi.
Uchawi?
Uh... witchcraft.
A number of
shamans decided
to put a curse on everyone
connected with the enterprise
effective upon the decision
to go ahead with the project.
What sort of a curse,
mr. Richards?
The usual:
A slow,
painful death.
Now, gentlemen,
i assure you,
there's nothing at all
funny about uchawi.
Oh, you're
not serious.
I am, i've seen it work.
I have seen healthy men
sicken and die
within ten minutes of the time
set by the witch doctors
who cursed them-
healthy men. And women.
They weren't touched.
They weren't poisoned.
They weren't harmed in any way.
They just died.
Don't talk rubbish.
Alan...
wait a minute,
just a second.
Mr. Sinclair.
What time is it?
Oh, say,
what's this
you're wearing
on your watch chain?
Why, it's...
a rabbit's foot,
isn't it?
Why do you
wear that?
Now, see here.
It's for luck,
isn't it?
Well, what's that
got to do with magic?
Sinclair carries
the severed foot
of a dead animal
for good fortune
and can't see what
that's to do with magic?
Hardy is amused.
Although it's known
he's a superstitious man
or have you finally
given up astrology?
Well...
now, here's a 20th-century man
who allows the stars
to make his decisions.
And a fine job they've done
of it, too, young man.
That's exactly what
a kekouyu witch doctor
said to me
when i suggested
panther bones
could not
foretell the future.
You needn't smile,
mr. Templeton.
I've seen you
knock on wood
more than once.
Oh, alan...
mr. Fleming,
when did you last
walk under a ladder?
Throw salt over
your shoulder?
All right,
mr. Richards
you've made
your point.
A multl-billion corporation
run by witches...
warlocks.
In a 40-story building
that doesn't even
have a 13th floor.
Now, gentlemen, i...
mr. Richards!
Chad.
Tell me something
if you wanted to get
hold of a dead goat
on an hour's notice,
where would
you go?
To a psychiatrist.
No, i'm serious.
Well, so am i.
You really want
a dead goat?
No.
Then what are you
talking about?
I'll do it.
Hey.
What's this?
That, my dear chad,
is kipitu.
A protective amulet.
Where did it
come from?
Doris.
You see, if this
is a lion's tooth,
i gather i'm being
protected from lions.
In, uh, new york city?
Yeah.
Well, got to admit
they're doing a fine job.
This is how doris
looks at it.
What will you do about doris?
I don't know.
She's sick,
isn't she?
So are half the city's people!
My wife carries
a lion's tooth,
the company president,
a rabbit's foot-
it's all the same,
same rotten disease.
It's eating away at
the strength, the will,
the very soul of me.
Hey, hey, alan.
Think you better
have another drink.
Hmm-mm.
Alan, take it easy.
A guy doesn't get
this worked up
about something
he doesn't believe in.
What do you mean?
Oh, nothing.
Come on.
Look, it's 3:00.
Doris will be worried.
No, i called her,
i told her i'd be late.
Did you pay?
Yeah.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Hey, chad!
Hey.
Anybody there?
Hello?
Cab, mister?
Shuler house.
Right.
Driver, the light's green.
You can go now.
Driver.
The light's green.
Oh.
Hey, excuse me, mister.
I've had nothing
to eat for two days.
I'd surely appreciate it
if you could help me out.
Sure...
sure, sure.
Yes, sir.
God bless you, mister.
Hey, wait a minute.
Where's that sound
coming from?
What sound was that?
Those drums.
I don't hear
no drums.
Listen.
You mean to tell me
you can't hear that?
Huh, you'll have
to excuse me.
My ears aren't as good
as they used to be.
Say, wait a minute.
How would you like
to make some money?
Doing what?
I'm trying to get home
on the other side
of the park.
If you walk with me,
i'll give you ten dollars.
Now, don't tell me
you can't hear tha...
hey!
Come back!
Hey, come back!
Look, i'll give you $20!
Come back.
Some superstitions kept alive
by the long night of ignorance
have their own special power.
You'll hear of it
through a jungle grapevine
in a remote corner
of the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week onthe twilight zone,
we bring to the television
cameras a most unique gentlemen
whose own
very special brand of clownship
has long ago become
a milestone in american humor.
Mr. Buster keaton
appears in "once upon a time."
A script written especially
for him by richard matheson,
this one is wild, woolly
and most unpredictable.
Onthe twilight zonenext week,
mr. Buster keaton
in "once upon a time."
Remember, the mentally ill
need your help, not criticism.
Learn how.
Write:
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org