Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it
is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Uncle simon?
Uncle simon, do you want
your hot chocolate upstairs?
Uncle simon,
do you hear me?
Do you want your hot
chocolate upstairs?
Uncle simon?!
Garbage-head!
I'm right behind you.
There's no need
to yell.
Well, my wilting blossom,
what's on your mind?
Your hot chocolate
is ready.
You told me you were
going to take a nap.
Sometime try extending
yourself, uncle,
just sufficiently
to let me know where
you are on occasion.
Well, barbara, i think
i can narrow that down for you.
If i'm not upstairs in my
bedroom or in the study,
then i'm downstairs
in my laboratory.
Wherever i am, you can bring
the hot chocolate.
And if i'm not...
i've dropped dead en route,
and you can bring me a bottle
of formaldehyde and a rose.
You're such a
humorist, uncle.
You should have gone
into burlesque.
Well, i guess i'd have been
more comfortable there than you.
You ever dance, barbara?
I'm very busy,
uncle simon.
You ever cut loose
and dance a fast
charleston?
No, most unlikely,
most unlikely.
You know, you're
the only woman i
know who looks
as if underneath
her clothes, she
wore clothes.
You have all the grace
and femininity
of a high-button shoe.
And you, uncle simon...
go on.
Let's see if you can compensate
for the fact
that you're
a passionless vegetable
by speaking
your mind.
If i'm a passionless vegetable,
it's because my gardener
is an ancient relic
made out of dry skin
and ice water.
Not bad, not bad, not bad.
You know, if i prod you
hard enough,
you can scramble up
to the occasion,
or at least part way.
Well, my angular turnip,
what else is new with you?
You say you made some
hot chocolate today, hmm?
Any other soul-
stirring projects
you applied
yourself to?
I see you tried to open the
drapes in the bedroom and hall.
I see that you
closed them.
You asked me
what i had done today,
and i'm telling you.
I cleaned up after you.
I tried to clear away
some of the debris
you always leave behind.
And what is this
contraption, hmm?
A room-straightener,
perhaps?
Tell me, uncle scientist,
where does this belong?
Put it back where it was.
You've been told
a thousand times
not to disturb things.
I could have put
it away when i swept
out the cellar,
but as usual, your
laboratory door was
securely bolted.
I would like to find out
what you putter around with
down there.
Yeah, i'll bet you would,
and someday you shall.
Someday, you will be owner
of this decaying barn,
and then you can do
as you please.
Until then, keep
your spindle-shanked carcass
out of my laboratory,
and your probing nose
out of my business.
Now, go and get me
some hot chocolate,
and use the english
bone china cup.
If it's not hot enough,
i'll throw it on the floor.
Barbara... question.
Go on.
Why do you stay here?
I was under the impression
that i was needed.
You are.
That explains
why i keep you here,
but it doesn't even remotely
suggest why you stay.
You would like me to be
quite honest, i presume?
Indeed. You may be short
on beauty,
but a lack of candor
has never been
one of your deficiencies.
I stay...
i live for the moment
when i can see you buried.
When i come back
from your funeral,
i'm going to open
a bottle of wine.
I want to be compensated,
uncle simon,
for 25 years
of being shrieked at,
insulted, berated, humiliated
and stepped on like an old rug.
Is that sufficiently honest
for you?
Well, i wish you well,
my good and faithful barbara.
But unasked, i offer you
this observation:
If you had an ounce of gristle
or an inch of intestines,
you'd have murdered me
years ago.
And as for your 25
years of abject misery
and unspeakable indignation,
you deserve it, kid.
Now go and get me
some chocolate.
Mr. Simon polk,
who has lived out his life
in a gleeful rage.
And the young lady
who's beat the hasty retreat
is mr. Polk's niece, barbara.
She has lived her life
as if during each ensuing hour,
she had a dentist's appointment.
There's a third member
soon to be seen.
He now resides
in the laboratory,
and he is the kind of character
to be found
only in the twilight zone.
Well... what have we here?
I was looking for...
looking for what?
I... thought perhaps
you might show me
what you were building.
Indeed. You'd like to
know, wouldn't you?
That's the only
character trait
you share with normal
curiosity.
Ineffable curiosity.
Well, one day, you'll
know what i'm building,
but until then,
you night-crawling
imitation of the
female gender,
if i catch you sneaking
around outside my door,
i'll break your head.
Now, go on upstairs
and engage yourself
in a nerve-wracking
game of dominos.
Tell me, uncle simon...
why do beasts like you
stay alive so long?
What's that again?
You heard me.
Why do decent men die,
and animals like yourself
keep living on?
Because, in most cases,
mine in particular,
we have something to live for.
I have you
to live for, you
crooked-seamed grubber.
That's why i keep
this decrepit old heart beating
and these over-the-hill lungs
breathing.
I know how dedicated you are
to seeing me die.
Who came here 25 years ago
when you were crippled and sick
and couldn't move?
Who came here and nursed you
and kept you alive?
You did!
You did,
you scrounging female ape.
Now let's get down to cases.
Why did you come?
Was it out of love, barbara?
Was it out of a
palpitating compassion
or a flagpole-
stiff loyalty?
I'll tell you
why you came.
You stayed on month after month,
year after year,
because every prayer
that came out of your mouth
was a supplication that i'd die
before the next morning.
So don't go mouthing
your sweetnesses at me,
you thin-lipped,
toothpick-legged conniver.
Everything you did for me,
you did for greed.
Greed!
Greed so big, so thick, so heavy
that it blotted out
even the hatred inside you.
But let me tell
you something, you
money-sick crone.
You'll get paid off
in due course,
but before that, you'll pay
through every bone in your body.
You'll pay, you ugly
harpy, you, you...
barbara... help me.
Barbara... why
won't you help me?
Why don't you
help me, barbara?
What's that?
What's that, uncle?
I didn't quite hear you.
Speak a little louder,
would you?
Tell me what it is
that you wanted.
I think my
back is broken.
You say you want
some hot chocolate?
Do you want it
in the english bone china cup?
What is your pleasure,
uncle?
You say you want me
to close the drapes
and shut the windows?
Barbara...
barbara...
barbara?
You want barbara?
She's right here, love,
standing right above you.
Can't you see her?
Can't you hear her,
you ancient albatross
with a dirty mouth?
Uncle simon?
Please... don't die
quite this moment.
If you can hold on,
try, try just for a second.
I want to tell you
something.
I want to make
an announcement.
As of this second,
as of this very second,
i have quit suffering
because of you.
I am no longer sowing,
uncle simon.
As of right now,
i am going to reap!
Hey, world, i'm back!
I'm really back!
If you give me
the sense of it,
i can dispose
of some things.
That is the sense of it.
The will
very explicitly requires
that you throw away nothing.
You keep everything
intact.
I see.
The house,
its furnishings...
everything goes to you
in perpetuity.
The proviso is, of course,
that you remain here.
Where would i go?
This is my home.
Of course, of course.
But, uh, the document
is quite clear in its intent.
Everything will remain
in your name
so long as you are
on the premises.
The same thing applies
to the various securities
and the cash,
which is quite sizable.
It's been set up
in trust.
You're to draw
the interest accruing
so long as you remain
in the house.
Where could anybody find a man
with a heart as big as his?
Uh, now this...
this is a codicil
your uncle had delivered
to my office.
His instructions were
to include it in the will.
"Add this codicil...
additional stipulation..."
uh... hmm.
The sense of this
is that to qualify
for the other legacies,
there is one additional
stipulation:
You're to care for all
of your uncle's experiments.
"Care for"...that's odd...
i don't understand,
mr. Schwimmer.
Just exactly what experiments
did he mean?
I have no idea.
But, uh, it reads as follows:
"My beloved niece, barbara,
"will be responsible
for the well-being
"of my latest experiment.
"She will look after it
and see to its wants and needs.
"A member of the law firm
of schwimmer, schwimmer, king,
"bathrick, pepperin,
and schwimmer
"will visit each week to see
this stipulation is adhered to.
"In the event my beloved
niece barbara fails to comply
"with the provisions hereof,
i hereby give and bequeath
"all property,
both real and personal,
to the state university."
Now, the sense of that,
miss polk...
just what is the sense of that?
I gather it depends
on the nature of the experiment.
He refers to it as "it."
You have no idea what "it" is?
No idea at all,
except that whatever it is,
it must be in the laboratory.
Well, nothing in here
of any consequence.
How do you do?
I'm a mechanical man
built by your late
uncle simon polk.
Your opening the door
has activated
all of my operating relays.
Be patient with me,
because according
to plan...
according to plan...
according
to plan...
according to...
it will be several days
before i can function
at maximum capacity.
I bid you greetings.
Hello, barbara.
Bar-bara!
I'm going out,
frankenstein.
If you need anything,
like a can of lubricant,
get it yourself.
You must not leave.
Mr. Schwimmer
is coming tonight.
A week has gone by.
Isn't mr. Schwimmer coming?
Yes, mr. Schwimmer
is coming.
He'll be here at 8:00.
Good.
Good?
Good for what?
He will see that i am
functioning properly.
You see, i am
like an infant.
I am maturing gradually.
Soon, i will have
all my faculties.
I will be able to perform
all my functions.
I will be a whole being.
How nice.
How perfectly grand.
How exciting.
You'll be a whole being.
Then what will happen?
I will take on human attributes,
those which your uncle simon
saw fit to give me.
My uncle simon, hmm?
There was a prince of a man.
A... a brilliant man.
This is interesting.
This is very interesting.
It's coming through now.
What is?
A... a craving.
A new craving.
Hot chocolate.
I would love a cup
of hot chocolate.
Miss polk.
Well, you look
lovely, miss polk.
And how is...
how is young master polk, hmm?
You took those keys
off the desk.
Give them back to me.
Oh, no, i must keep the
laboratory door locked.
You must not come down.
It is my room.
It belongs to me.
Barbara...
won't you bring me
some hot chocolate?
After you bring me
my hot chocolate,
would you please
close all the windows
and pull the drapes?
I don't like
the light.
the draft.
(speaking in
what is the matter, barbara?
Tell me, please,
what is the matter?
What is the matter?
What is the matter,
you peanut-headed
sample of nature's
carelessness?
Barbara... barbara...
help me...
help... me...
ah, how are you this evening,
miss polk?
He, uh... itis rather quiet
these days.
Doesn't seem to say much.
He makes his wants known.
Pity about his... his leg,
but he manages to get around,
doesn't he?
Indeed, he does.
Well, i'll see you next week.
Take care of yourself.
No need to show me out.
Barbara.
Barbara?
Barbara, my dear,
if you could prevail
upon that raggedy ann carcass
of yours to exert itself,
i'd like a cup
of hot chocolate.
I would like it
in the english bone china cup,
and if it's not hot,
i'll throw it on the floor.
All right, i'll make some.
Speak up, you lint-headed clod.
I couldn't hear you.
I'll make some hot chocolate.
Move, you topping lotus-eater.
Be sure it's hot.
Do you hear me?
Make sure it's hot.
What does it take to make
you move, you bovine crab?
I'll fix it
for you now.
You'll fix it for
me now... what?
I'll fix it for you now...
uncle.
A metal man
who'll go by the name of simon,
whose life as well as his body
has been stamped on for him.
And the woman who tends
to him-
the lady barbara,
who's discovered belatedly
that all bad things
don't come to an end,
and that once a bed is made,
it's necessary you sleep in it.
Tonight's uncomfortable
little exercise
in avarice and automatons
from the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next ontwilight zone,
an eminent performer
of stage and screen,
mr. Richard basehart,
in an odd-ball excursion
that we call
"probe seven, over and out."
On occasion, we'll come up with
a wild and woolly denouement,
but this particular opus
has an unpredictable ending
that we doubt if even
the most seasonedtzfans
will be able to pick up before
it happens on your screen.
Next ontwilight zone,
"probe seven, over and out."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org