Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Room for one more, honey.
This is miss liz powell.
She's a professional dancer
and she's in the hospital
as a result of overwork
and nervous fatigue
and at this moment,
we have just finished
walking with her
in a nightmare.
In a moment, she'll wake up
and we'll remain at her side.
The problem here is
that both miss powell and you
will reach a point
where it might be difficult
to decide
which is reality
and which is nightmare:
A problem uncommon perhaps
but rather peculiar
to the twilight zone.
Hiya, kitten.
You lose your
way, barney?
Hey, you're looking
great, kitten.
You're looking
just great.
It's been a long
time between talks.
Look what i
brought you, honey.
I had it blown up.
Why, we'll get it
blown up real big
and we'll put it in
front of the chl-chi
when you open there.
Where you been, barney?
Well, i...
you know how i feel
about hospitals, kitten-
they kind of depress me.
You ought to try
it in here
lying on your back
for couple
of weeks, barney.
Pretty soon you feel like
you're lying on a glass slide
and all those creeps are looking
at you through a microscope
and the only time the sun shines
is when it's visiting hours.
Gee, kitten, what a mind
you've got- what a mind.
That's what bugs you, isn't it,
barney?
My mind.
You think i left it in a bus
station someplace, don't you?
Well, if you keep on talking
nutsy like this
i got to think
there's something wrong, kitten.
Barney, you got
to believe me.
You're the only one.
You're really
the only one
i thought would
believe me.
When you didn't
show up...
when you didn't
even call
i got this wild idea
that you'd given me up
that you figured i was
some kind of a cuckoo
who'd left
the world behind.
Oh, no.
But barney, you
got to believe me.
You're the only one.
They aren't dreams.
They happen- just
like i say they happen.
I know, kitten,
i know.
Barney, don't.
Don't write me
off, will you?
You got
to believe me.
Well, good
afternoon.
Oh, i was just
leaving, doc.
No need- i'll
just be a moment.
Well, miss powell, you're
looking as beautiful as ever.
I was just
telling her
the same thing
myself.
I'm barney kavener,
liz's agent.
How do you do?
You make
an old doctor
wish he were
a young intern.
You make me wish
the same thing.
You must be
great
at funerals,
laughing boy.
We're a little feisty
today, aren't we?
We are not feisty.
We are just a little tired
of ten people an hour
walking around our bed
like we were some kind
of a freak or something.
Why don't you guys
get off the dime?
There's nothing
wrong with me.
There most assuredly
isn't, miss powell.
That's what we've been
trying to tell you.
You're in excellent
physical condition
a little overtired,
that's all
a little overworked,
perhaps.
I guess
a dancer's life
isn't the easiest,
is it?
Well, talent like this makes it
look easy, doc.
I've been this little lady's
agent for 12 years
and i'm here to tell you
that she's the best
little stripper...
dancer.
...dancer
that ever came
down the pike.
Just listen to him
laugh, barney.
Boy, he's great
for your morale.
Well, doc, what's it
going to be tonight?
A big discussion
about freud and dreams?
You don't seem interested
in dreams, miss powell.
In this story, you recount
you keep rejecting the
fact that itisa dream.
You know it.
As a matter of fact,
i don't know it.
I know quite the reverse.
I say it is a dream.
Now, let's run through it again.
You say it always happens
in perfect chronology.
You wake up.
You feel thirsty.
You reach for the glass.
You hear the clock
ticking loudly.
Very loudly.
It unnerves you.
The glass slips out of your hand
and breaks on the floor.
And then i hear
the footsteps
outside.
Footsteps?
Whose footsteps?
Miss powell seems to feel
they're the footsteps
of a nurse.
They are the footsteps
I hear them.
They come down the corridor
and stop outside my door.
I jump out of bed.
Now, miss
powell...
i open the door and i see this
nurse going into an elevator.
I follow her.
The elevator goes down
to the basement floor.
Down at the end of the hall
room 22.
What kind of room?
It's the
hospital morgue
mr. Kavener.
Miss powell
seems to feel
the nurse comes
out of the morgue
looks straight at
her and says...
"room for one more, honey."
That's what
she says, barney
"room for one more"
and then she points
to that room-
that room where
all the stiffs are.
Odd dream, wouldn't
you say, mr. Kavener?
That's a
weirdo, doc.
That's a very
weird dream.
It isn't a dream.
Miss powell claims
it's one of our nurses
assigned to
the basement floor.
How should i know
if it's one of
your nurses or not?
All i know is this dame
comes out of that room
looks at me and says
"room for
one more, honey."
You bring her in here.
I'll point her out.
Boy, will i
point her out.
I know her face as
well as i do my own.
Very well.
Let's see.
This is
miss jameson.
She's the
night nurse
assigned to the
basement floor-
the only nurse
i might add,
miss powell.
Look at her.
Well, miss powell?
Is this
your phantom lady?
No, this woman is tall
and she's got
this crazy
kind of a smile
on her face.
That will be
all, thank you.
Well, miss powell,
it obviously is a dream.
If it were a nurse
in our hospital
it would have
to be that young lady
and since it is not
you'll have to admit
it's very unlikely
that the woman
you saw
could have come
out of the morgue.
I know what i saw.
I know what i did.
I'll tell you what,
miss powell
to prove my point
let's try
something different.
Like what?
You say
it always happens
in such
pure chronology-
that your actions
are always the same.
Tonight when
you're dreaming
or as you say,
when you're waking up
don't reach
for the glass.
See if breaking
the routine of it
won't stop it
from happening.
Now, that
sounds
like a groovy
idea, doc.
Why don't you try it, kitten, huh?
Why don't
you try it?
Barney, will
you tell him?
When the same thing
happens to you
for six nights
in a row!
Overwork, fatigue,
tiredness...
a nightmare
at this point
would not be abnormal,
mr. Kavener.
A nightmare in this case
would be the norm.
Well, miss powell
let's see what
this evening brings
shall we?
Yeah, well, i...
i got to be running
along, kitten.
Now, you stay hip
to what the doc here
is telling you.
I'm sure glad to
see you feeling...
looking
so good again.
Thanks a heap,
barney.
You know, you
couldn't boost morale
if it weighed
a quarter of a pound
and you had a derrick.
Thanks for coming over.
You must do it
again sometime
only make it next
year, will you?
Oh, kitten,
baby.
Get out, will you,
barney?
Sure, liz...
sure.
Remember about tonight,
miss powell.
When you feel a compulsion
to repeat the nightmare...
don't do it.
Now, relax.
Get to sleep.
I think we're on our way
to recovery.
We're just delighted
that we feel that way.
Room for one more, honey.
Don't leave her
until she's asleep.
Well, i think
she'll sleep now.
Good.
That's odd.
Now, that's
really odd.
What is, doctor?
This afternoon when
i was talking to her
she was telling me
about this... this dream.
What about it?
Following someone
down the corridor
getting into
the elevator
going down
to the morgue.
Morgue?
Yes.
She's never been
there before.
Patients aren't
allowed there.
And yet,
when she tells me the story
she mentions room 22.
Room 22?
Well, if she'd
never been there
how would
she know?
How would she?
Everything packed?
That does it.
Your agent is here. He said
to phone down to the lobby
when you're ready.
He'll meet you
at the elevator.
My cup runneth over.
Is there a back
door to this place?
Well, he seems like
quite a devoted man.
Oh, he's devoted-
to ten percent
commission
and 12 hours'
sleep every night.
Well, are we ready to leave?
All ready,
doctor.
Ready and overdue.
Let me take that
for you.
Send me a postcard from
miami beach, will you?
Sure.
Miss powell...
theyweredreams.
Just a part of your fatigue.
You were susceptible
to nerves.
That's what happens
when a mind is overwrought.
It plays tricks.
I don't want to see you back
here again, miss powell.
The next time i see you,
i'll be at a ringside table
and i'd appreciate, uh...
a subtle wink.
Miss powell?
Yeah. Yeah, i'm ready.
You're all set,
miss powell.
That's the nonstop to miami
departing from area c
in approximately five minutes.
Your seat assignment's
on the envelope there.
Thank you very much.
Did anyone
ever tell you
that you have eyes
like a tarantula?
Oh, i'm sorry, miss.
I didn't mean to stare.
Forget it.
Is that area c out there?
Yes, ma'am.
Flight 22
is loading now
and you can get
aboard anytime.
Uh...
is there anything
wrong, miss powell?
What flight?
22-
nonstop to miami
right out through
that door-
you can board now.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Passenger porter, please report
to ticket confirmation desk
immediately.
Passenger porter, please report
to ticket confirmation desk
immediately.
It's that... that crazy feeling.
I'm thirsty.
I'm thirsty but...
but i'm awake.
It's that same feeling
This isn't a dream.
This couldn't be a dream.
I think
you'd better
hurry up a
little, miss.
That's your flight
ready for departure
out there.
Room for one more, honey.
This couldn't be a dream.
It's not a dream.
It just couldn't be- not now.
It just couldn't be.
Miss elizabeth powell,
professional dancer.
Hospital diagnosis:
Acute anxiety brought on
by overwork and fatigue.
With rest and care,
she'll probably recover
but the cure to some nightmares
is not to be found
in known medical journals.
You look for it
under "potions for bad dreams"
to be found
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling, creator
ofthe twilight zone
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week you'll find
each of your names
on the passenger manifest
of this jet aircraft
that travels from london
to new york city.
You'll sit in these seats
and you'll go through an
experience unique beyond words
and tense beyond anything
i believe you've ever seen.
You'll be departing next week
at about this time
in a vehicle we call
"the odyssey of flight 33."
But prepared for a stop midway
in the twilight zone.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
be sure and see the colgate-
palmolive company's
new comedy show
my sister eileen
wednesday night on many
of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org