Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Billy-ben?
You're late.
Sure i'm late,
pretty thing.
I've been in
town today.
How come you didn't
take me with you?
Well, i did the
next best thing.
I thought about you
every step of the way.
You got a sweet
and lying tongue.
You are a fair thing.
What'd you do in town?
Will you stop that?
What are folks gonna say?
Well, ain't nobody out here
except you and me
and the man in the moon.
You're a right high-spirited man
to have walked to town and back.
Well, i went for
a right high-
spirited reason.
Now close your eyes.
I got something for you.
You can open them now.
It's the prettiest thing
i ever did see!
Oh, billy!
I'm proud enough to cry.
I love you...
with all my enduring life.
And i the
same for you.
Can i show it
to everybody?
If that'd bring
you pleasure.
How the girls
are going to envy me.
Folks.
Now that everybody's here,
i'm proud to bid you welcome.
Now, i want everybody to dance
until you wear out the fiddler.
And i want everybody to eat
until you had to let out
your belts to the last notch.
The land was good
to me this year.
The good lord
blessed it
with rain
when rain was needed
and a kindly sun
to follow.
And this barn is heavy
with the yield of it.
Amen.
But that's just
one of the reasons
we're celebrating
here tonight.
A decent, good and true man
has come to me
and asked for the hand
of my daughter, ellwyn,
and she has
my endearing love
and my blessing
to marry...
billy-ben turner.
And now,
good people,
the food and drink
are at your pleasure.
Wonder what's wrong
with jess-belle.
Going home early,
i reckon.
Why don't you go see
if you can't talk
her into coming back?
She'll come back
if she's of a mind to.
Well, evening's
young yet.
It'd spoil my party
if folks leave early.
Well, l-i...
go on ahead,
honey.
Go on.
Jess-belle.
Don't you
come near me.
I thought you might want
to wish us well, jess.
You'll have nothing from me.
No need for you to take on so.
What'd you want me to do?
Run in there,
throw my arms around her,
tell her how glad i am?
Jess, i'm sorry.
Remember the night
we clung together
in the sweet night grass
down by eagle rock mountain?
The moonlight made us see
a silver mist on the fog below.
I remember.
The day we ran through
the scotch broom field,
and the sun was
blazing hot,
and we fell
together...
and you touched me?
The fire in me burned
as hot as the white sun.
The fire's turned
to ashes now, jess.
It still
burns- here.
But it's different
with ellwyn and me.
Pretty clothes
and her daddy's land?
Is that the difference,
billy-ben?
No. No, that's not
the difference.
I... i love her
in a... quiet way.
You know, it...
i don't want to hear.
Billy-ben.
Tell your love a thing from me,
will you?
What's that?
Tell her not to start making
her wedding dress right yet.
Why should i tell her
a thing like that?
She ain't married you yet,
billy-ben.
Maybe she never will.
? fair was elly glover?
? dark was jess-belle?
? both they loved the same man?
? and both
they loved him well.?
The twilight zone has existed
in many lands, in many times.
It has roots in history,
in something that happened
long, long ago,
and got told about
and handed down from one
generation of folk to the other.
In the telling, the story gets
added to and embroidered on
so that what might have happened
in the time of the druids
is told as if it took place
yesterday
in the blue ridge mountains.
Such stories are best told
by an elderly grandfather
on a cold winter's night
by the fireside...
in the southern hills
of the twilight zone.
? graveyard dust?
? and breast of dove?
? bubble, bubble?
? wine of love...?
Granny hart?
Well, what you bothering
an old woman for
this time of night?
I got to talk to you.
Well, sit down.
Folks say you
got a power.
Oh, folks say
a lot of things.
They say mose crowley's
cow sickened and died
when he shot that
hawk you used to keep.
Well, that hawk
was my pet.
He used to roost
in that big black pine
right outside the door.
When molly unger's
baby was a-dyin'
of a fever,
she went somewhere and
got a potion for him.
Folks say she
came here.
She did.
And that little baby lived,
didn't he?
Lived?
But he's accursed with fits.
Oh.
His mama won't let
him out of the house.
What else do they say about me?
They say you're a witch.
Oh, sugar,
if i was a witch,
i'd be out riding around
on my broom
instead of sitting
'round here alone,
minding my own business.
Whatever you are...
will you help me?
Well, it depends, sugar.
I want to win
a man's love.
Well... womankind, jess,
got her own kind
of witchcraft for that.
He was mine for a while.
Came sneaking off at night,
kept a-quiet what went on
between him and me.
Never took me anyplace
for the world to know.
He made me promises.
He made them when his face
was hot as blood.
Forgot them as soon as he was
ten feet from my door.
Honey...
you don't know much
about men, do you?
Only him.
What man?
Billy-ben turner.
Oh, he is a pretty one
with nice, big, strong arms
to hold a gal.
Can you make him
love me the way he
did a long time ago,
when a night wouldn't
pass but what he had
to come to see me?
How much money
did you bring me?
I don't have
any money.
Well, how did
you expect to pay me?
I'll give you my
pearl hairpin.
It's a real pearl,
brought back
from overseas
by my daddy in
one of the wars,
and the stick's
real silver.
Take it
out of my sight.
Is that all you got
to offer me?
That's everything
on earth i own,
except the clothes
on my back.
Well, honey,
you better run along home
and live your life
without billy-ben turner.
I don't have any
life without him.
You got to help me.
Well, i got something
i could give you, but...
the price is high.
What is the price?
You'll know
in the midnight hour of time.
Whatever it is, i'll pay.
Drink.
Does he love me now?
After his eyes fall next on you,
he'll never look
at another woman
as long as he can look
at you.
? then form a ring?
? flick that ring
with a corner swing?
? now do-sl-do to your own
down the line?
? now promenade,
go two by two?
? walk back home
like you always do?
? now you all join hands,
form a ring?
? circle right
with the pretty little thing?
? now break that ring
with a corner swing?
? go back home, do-sl-do?
? now it's promenade,
go 'round the town...?
I never
in my life...
what come
over that boy?
Whatever it was,
he'll answer
to me for it.
It's a shame
and a disgrace.
If billy-ben expects you
to marry him after this,
he'll have
to think again.
He won't be marrying me.
Well, i'm glad to see
you got spirit, child.
I'd still have him
if i could.
If he were to come back
in here this very minute,
i'd just go running
to him.
I'd not allow you
to shame yourself
like that.
He won't be back.
I won't even get
the chance.
Jess-belle bewitched him.
You're enough
to drive a man crazy.
You're sure a master
hand with the sweet
words, billy-ben.
When we're married,
it'll be a hateful thing
to leave you in the morning.
I won't let you leave.
Going to lock
the door
and keep you
home all day.
How'll we live
if i don't work my land?
When you're
in the fields,
i'll hide behind
a juniper tree,
sing songs to tease
you home again.
And where will
the money come from
for the pretties
i'll buy you?
What will
you buy me?
I don't know,
maybe dresses of silk
and combs
for your hair.
Looks like the
moon's going down.
I better go.
I won't let you.
I'm going to keep you here
all night.
I can't.
Why not?
Mama's home, and
she's waiting for me.
Why, you never worried
about mama before.
Let go of me,
billy-ben.
I want you to stay here
with me.
Billy-ben,
let go of me!
Sorry.
It don't matter.
Nothing can change
the love i hold for you.
Then take me home.
Good night.
Just one more kiss.
No.
Who's that
brought you home?
Oh, jess-belle,
don't go right to bed.
Come sit a spell
and tell me
about the dance.
Jess-belle, don't...
? by day, she knew
a woman's form?
? by night, a witch's spell?
? for love of billy turner?
? accursed was jess-belle.?
Well, i didn't mean
to frighten you.
Hold out your hand.
I got something
for you.
Elly's ring.
Jess-belle's ring.
It belongs to
the one i love,
and the one i
love is you.
Every minute i'm
away from you
is a suffering
and a torment.
Suffering and torment.
You know what suffering
and torment means?
Sure.
It's having a girl that
your heart's craving
and have her
keep putting the
wedding day off.
All kinds of torment
in the world, i reckon.
What would you know
of torment, girl?
There's a torment comes
from buying something
and finding out
the price is dear.
What did you buy
that cost so dear?
Something i love.
Do you still love
it, though the
price was high?
Better than life.
Better than me?
Ain't nothing i love
better than you.
I went to see
the preacher today, jess.
What'd you want with him?
Well, you wouldn't set the date,
so i went ahead and set it.
He's going to marry
us come next sunday.
I can't be ready by then.
Why not?
I talked to
your mama.
She said your
wedding dress
will be sewed.
And my house is clean.
Everything new
and waiting for you.
You haven't changed your mind,
have you, jess?
No.
Then why do you keep putting off
the wedding date?
I can't tell you, billy-ben.
Shouldn't be any secrets
between us.
I'm going away from you
for a while.
I'll give you my word
when i come back.
Oh, stay now, jess.
I got a craving
to be with you
every minute.
Let go of me, billy.
I never knew a man
could have such a love
as i hold for you.
There's no peace from it.
It burns night
and day.
I got a terrible
yearning.
Didn't you hear me knocking?
I never let trouble in the door
if i can help it.
How you know i'm trouble?
Why, child,
there ain't much i don't know.
Well, then if
you know so much,
maybe you can help me.
Well, i already helped
you once.
You want to change
your mind
now that you got
what you wanted?
I haven't got
what i want.
Oh, don't tell me
you haven't got the love
of billy-ben turner.
I got his love,
all right,
but i can't take it
for fear he'd find
the price i
paid for it.
I tried to find pity
for him and for me,
but i can't.
It's like my heart's
been cut out
and stone put where
the heart was.
Oh, that ain't
your heart, honey.
What then?
Oh, there's lots
of names for it-
some folks
calls it "soul."
That was in the
bargain, too?
Oh, that's always
in the bargain
if you barter...
with witches.
You said you
weren't a witch.
just had power!
You might as well know
the truth, honey,
now that you're one, too.
I changed you.
Well, then change me back.
Let me be a woman again.
Oh, you can't never change.
What you are,
you're gonna be till you die.
Then i hope i die soon.
Well, you're looking
at it all wrong.
Be a witch.
Take a witch's pleasure.
Take the man you bargained for.
Don't you think i want to?
How long do you think
i'd keep him
if he finds out what happens
when the clock strikes 12:00?
That's worst of all-
not knowing
what i'm going to do,
waking and not
knowing what
i've done.
Change me back.
Please, i'll pay.
I promise i'll pay.
Well, your promises
ain't much good.
You're already trying
to get out of paying
for the first favor i done you.
I can't live this way.
Please!
Take the man you bargained for.
Give him a witch's love.
I can't do that to billy-ben.
You paid the price.
Take what you paid for.
I can't do that
to billy-ben!
Billy-ben.
Oh, jess.
I've been out
of my mind.
I searched this whole
county over for you.
Cursed myself every
step of the way
for upsetting you
the way i did today.
Jess, you hellcat,
where you been?
I went away... to think.
And did you
think of me?
You were all
i thought about.
And did you think
of me with love?
Yes, billy.
Jess... i won't
crowd you
on the wedding
day again.
Now, whatever's
been troubling you,
you don't even
have to tell me.
You just settle it
and you can set
your own day
for the wedding.
There will be no wedding,
billy-ben.
Oh, j-jess, don't say
a thing like that.
There will be no wedding.
No wedding
between you and me.
I'd as soon hear
my death bell as
what you're saying.
I'd as soon hear
my own death bell as say it.
Then forget
it was said.
Oh, i love you, jess,
and i want you
to be my wife.
That's all i know.
You would not want me
for long.
One night, you'd turn
away from me.
Oh, curse me
for a fool
if that day
would ever come.
I set you free
from any promise, billy.
Take this.
No, it...
this belongs here.
You hear that?
It's a night bird
calling its mate.
His mate won't come.
I saw her on the trail tonight
winging up against the sky.
The nighthawks swooped up
out of the pines
and tore her breast open.
She fell at my feet
and ran off
in the bushes to die.
It was just an omen, jess.
It don't mean
you're going to die.
Billy-ben...
if old man death came
walking down eagle rock trail,
i'd run to meet him...
and i'd beg him on my knees
to take me with him.
Jess, what's cursing you?
I got a right
to know.
It's late.
I got to go!
Wait, jess.
Billy-ben, if you
love me, stand aside!
Jess?
Jess-belle?
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
? an awful night
was spent by all?
? on eagle rock who dwell?
? strange things were seen
by moonlight's pall?
? but none saw jess-belle.?
Take the man you bargained for.
Give him a witch's love.
Nothing can change you, sugar.
Witch you are,
and witch you'll always be.
You've paid the price.
Take what you've paid for.
Take what
you've paid for.
Take what you've paid for.
Billy-ben?
Jess.
Jess, what's the matter?
Now, why has something
got to be the matter?
I just wanted to see you.
I never saw
such a night.
The animals kept moving around
and crying out.
Cow got fractious
and tried to kick out
the side of the stall.
The sheep was bleatin'.
Look-look like
they were looking
in the jaws of wolves.
I had to go out there
two or three times
and quiet 'em down.
I'll fix your
breakfast for you.
Well, now, that's my girl.
I'll, uh, fix
the fire for you.
I'll fix it for you
every morning.
And your dinner and your supper,
too, if you let me.
Well, honey, haven't i been
begging you to do just that?
Then next sunday,
come what may,
i'll be your wife.
Hello, jess.
You're a long way from
home, elly glover.
Lots of wildflowers around here.
Saw a patch of old maid's fern
up on the mountain.
I notice a lot of vixenwort
around here myself.
I just came
from billy-ben's.
Fixed his breakfast
for him.
Well... i reckon
that's no concern of mine.
Circuit preacher's
gonna marry us
when he comes around
next sunday.
Well, i wish you happiness...
for his sake.
You still love him, elly?
The last time
i saw billy-ben turner's face,
he was under a magic spell...
and even the love i hold for him
couldn't break it.
There's ways,
but such ways end bad.
What ways you talking about?
I think you know.
Jealous, ain't you?
No.
I'm heartsick
to see wrong done
to a good man.
I got news there's a wildcat
loose in the county.
Ain't you scared
to be up here alone?
I'll be home by dark.
That cat won't venture out
until nightfall.
Can't tell what a wildcat
will do.
Well, i reckon
we don't have much to fear.
My daddy says that killer cat's
going to be dead by morning.
Oh?
Since when your daddy been able
to look in the future
and tell what's going to be?
Why, he's going hunting
for that cat tonight.
Him, and obed miller,
and billy-ben, and all the men.
Billy-ben never said nothing
to me about going.
Obed miller just went over
and asked him.
I reckon that cat
better stay home tonight
if it's smart.
I reckon.
What's the matter
with you tonight, jess?
You just as nervous
as a fox in a forest fire.
You gonna take all night
with that hem, mama?
You never would've had
such a fine dress
without billy-ben havin'
given me the money.
You know that, don't you?
Saw old elly glover today.
She was picking wildflowers
up on the mountain.
How'd she look?
Looked sickly,
like she might die soon.
I didn't even know
the poor thing was ailing.
Looked terrible.
There, now you
can get out of it
and hand it to me.
I ought to make
some of that tonic
i used to make
and take it to her.
You and your tonics.
You're worse
than granny ha...
granny hart?
Well, everyone knows
she sells them old potions
and things.
She ain't sold none
to you, has she?
Don't talk crazy talk.
Is that what made
billy-ben turner blind
to every other woman on
earth save jess-belle?
Where would i get
the money
for potions and powders?
That old woman don't
always ask for money.
That's what makes my
heart turn cold as ice.
Jess, how did
you pay her?
Oh, god, jess, how
did you pay her?!
With my flesh
and my blood...
and my soul...
and my brain...
and my sleep...
and my hands...
and my heart and my head.
I paid dear
for billy-ben.
Jess!
Kneel down with me.
It's too late, mama.
We'll pray to
god to help you.
My prayers aren't answered
in heaven anymore.
I'll think of a way
to help you.
You can do one thing
if you want to see me alive
in the morning.
Bolt my door
when i go to bed tonight.
No matter what happens,
don't open that door
until morning.
Hold it, men.
I think old blaze
has found something.
Let's go.
I think he's struck trail.
What's the matter, blue?
You having
a bad dream?
Something scare you?
You're going to be
all right now.
Just calm down
and go back to sleep.
It's going to
be all right.
Elly!
Elly.
I ain't ever seen no cat
with spots like that.
A witch.
That cat was a witch.
Well...
our work is done
for this night.
Come on, elly.
Come on.
What ails you, billy-ben?
Nothing.
I'm all right.
I'm enduring glad
to see you, elly.
Well...
good to see you,
too, billy.
It's been a long spell.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd let me come
and sit up with you
some night soon.
Well...
that'd be right fine.
Come anytime you want.
? warm was elly glover?
? cold dead was jess-belle?
? and husband
would be billy-ben?
? of the one he loved so well.?
Well, miss ossie.
Billy-ben.
Won't you come on in?
Oh, well, i won't stay
but just a minute.
I... i just wanted
to wish you
all the happiness
in the world
on your wedding day.
Oh, now, i
appreciate that.
But aren't you coming
to the wedding?
Oh, well, i wouldn't spoil
the day for elly.
She'd see me
and think of jess-belle.
There's no shadow
of jess-belle
between elly and me.
God grant
there never will be.
Uh, i was just
having some coffee.
Won't you sit down?
It's been a
full year now
since jess-belle's
been dead.
How do you know
she's dead, billy-ben?
I saw her die.
Now, don't ask me
to tell you any
more than that.
I brought you something
i thought you ought
to have, billy-ben.
It used to belong
to jess-belle.
Poor jess.
I appreciate
it, miss ossie.
I brought it
for a special reason.
It's made of silver,
and silver is one thing
a witch is scared of.
What witch would
want to harm elly?
I've got a terrible thing
to tell you, billy-ben:
A secret about jess-belle.
I know a secret
about jess-belle myself.
The same night
that she disappeared, we talked,
and not meaning to, she...
she mentioned granny hart.
And then i found out something
i'd sooner be dead than know.
Jess-belle was witched.
I didn't know it myself till...
that night she died.
She ain't dead, billy-ben.
But i was there.
I fired one of the shots myself.
I've spent many
a restless night
grieving about that.
Billy-ben...
some months back,
i went into
jess-belle's room...
and there
on jess-belle's pillow
was a wart toad sitting.
Now, l-i grabbed a broom
and i brought that down
with all my might
on that ugly thing...
and it just disappeared
in a cloud of smoke
and went floating out
through the window.
Well, may-maybe it was
just a cloud of dust,
and-and the toad, uh,
fall onto the floor.
No, it was the spirit
of jess-belle.
Miss ossie, now, i saw her die.
Billy-ben, don't you know
you can't kill a witch?!
They just change
to something else!
But if a person's good
and strong,
a witch can't harm them,
i've heard.
It's said.
Well, then... elly has nothing
to fear from jess-belle.
I'm sorry, miss ossie,
but i got to hurry.
I'm going to be late
for my own wedding.
I hope and pray there won't be
nobody there who...
who wasn't invited.
To have and
to hold
from this
day forward.
To have and to hold
from this day forward.
For better, for worse;
for richer, for poorer.
For better, for worse...
In sickness
and in health.
To love and
to cherish
till death
us do part.
To love
and to cherish
until death
us do part.
According
to god's holy
ordinance,
i thereto plight
thee my troth.
According to god's
holy ordinance,
i thereto plight thee my troth.
Join hands.
Those whom god hath joined
together,
let no man put asunder.
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
Aren't you forgetting
something?
Well, not to
my knowing.
Oh, there you go.
You know you're acting
like a husband already?
Are you going
to let your bride walk
across your threshold?
Welcome home, darling.
Thank you, billy-ben.
There's no knowing
how happy i am.
This day has brought me
the happiest, happiest
moments of my life.
Billy-ben?
Something has hold of my arm!
I don't see nothing.
Let go!
What's come over you?
I... i never
did that, billy.
Not of my own will.
Something took hold
of me.
Well, i saw nothing.
There's something
here, billy-
something we can't hear
nor see,
but i can feel it.
Something... evil.
Something... cold.
Take me home, billy!
Elly, you are home.
But something
don't want me here!
I know what it
is that's trying
to chase you out.
But, elly... elly!
You will stay,
you hear?
You will stay.
Now, i've got to go
away from you
for a little, short time.
Do you trust
in the lord?
Yes.
Well, then hold his word
in your hand...
and his word'll protect you.
But if the devil himself
should come into this room,
do not leave
that chair.
The door's open.
Granny hart?
I'm just curling
my hair
so's i look pretty
for you, billy-ben.
Granny, i... i'm short on time.
Ain't i a beauty?
How'd you like me
for a sweetheart?
I already got a sweetheart,
and i just made her my bride.
Elly glover...
of the golden hair?
She's a beauty, too.
Well, i'll not have
her beauty long
unless you help me
rid myself of a witch.
Jess-belle don't like
you being married, do she?
Your jess-belle,
all right.
Oh, i know.
I witched that gal
so she could win your love.
I never wanted
no witch's love.
Humans don't know nothing
about loving.
Well, i know
enough, if...
anything happens
to elly,
i couldn't
go on living.
Oh, jess-belle
ain't going to hurt
your little bride.
She's just teasing
and having a good time.
Granny, i left
my wife alone.
Now, i got to
get back to her!
Nothing is holding
you here, boy.
You got to tell me
how to rid myself
of jess-belle.
Well, i don't
hardly know no way...
unless'n you kill her.
You can't kill her.
All she does is go
up in a puff of smoke
and then she comes
right back again!
There's ways.
Well, tell me.
How you gonna
to pay me?
Well, what do you want?
A lock of your hair.
You'll not trick
me like that!
It takes lots of money
to learn how to kill
a witch.
You go home...
make a figure
of jess-belle.
Then put on it clothes
that jess-belle has worn.
Then, if you have
the courage,
stab it through the heart
with silver.
It's got to be
a dress she wore.
She wore it... once.
And billy-ben...
when the time comes,
if your hand fails you,
remember there
was a good part
to jess-belle,
and that part of
her would bless you
for ending what
she's now become.
I told you to stay in the house.
You all right, elly?
That thing you felt in our house
was the spirit of jess-belle.
She was a witch.
But i know
how to get rid of witches.
You'll never be rid
of me, billy-ben.
Jess-belle.
Come on, billy-ben...
dance with me...
in the moonlight.
Elly.
Elly!
May hell swallow me up
if i've killed you, too.
Billy-ben?
You just rest
a minute.
What are we doing here
like this?
Don't you remember?
I remember a wedding.
Did i dream that?
No.
You're my pretty
little bride.
Well, then...
i should be cooking you
some supper.
Billy-ben, look!
My mama says when you see
a falling star,
that means a witch
has just died.
So i've heard tell.
? fair was elly glover?
? dark was jess-belle?
? both they loved the same man?
? and both
they loved him well.?
Next ontwilight zone,
a most unusual program
called "miniature."
The very eminent
charles beaumont takes us
into a brand-new realm
of science fiction and fantasy
that is at the same time
intriguing
and strangely believable.
Uh, e-excuse me.
Oh, yes, sir?
I guess this
may sound silly,
but how did they
manage that?
How do they manage what?
In there, in
the glass case?
Oh. Well, i couldn't say
exactly.
According
to the museum officials,
the girl.
Have you seen her?
Yes.
W-well, is-is she all right?
L-l-i've been worried sick.
Be careful.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org