Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind.
A journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
When was that
picture taken?
Why, i don't think
i remember, my dear.
You're looking at
that album again?
It seems like that's
all you do lately
is look
at that album.
When was that picture taken?
Oh, it's a lovely picture of you, nelda.
Thank you, ma'am.
Let's see. That
was taken the summer
after dr. Loren retired
from the laboratory.
You're holding those
lovely yellow roses
that jensen
planted for us.
You don't look
any different now
than you did then.
That's kind of you,
miss jana.
Jana, nelda will put
that away for you.
That's all right,
father.
I'd like to put
it away myself.
You're not chilly,
are you, jana, dear?
Shouldn't be.
72 degrees
in here.
Isn't it,
william?
Isn't it
72 degrees?
Exactly. The
optimum temperature.
Of course.
The optimum temperature.
And the fireplace- designed
for perfect heat radiation.
The chairs, for
maximum comfort.
And the windows
for the most efficient light,
and proper ventilation.
Oh, yes, and the ceilings
for the most desirable
acoustical qualities.
Everything built to
perfection, father.
Everything designed
for a perfect life.
Oh, please
continue, nelda.
That's it.
Haven't you had enough
of that, mother?
Why, jana, dear
you know it helps
my appetite.
Almost 6:00.
Nearly time
for dinner.
Why don't we eat a little
bit earlier tonight?
Or a little bit later?
Why don't we go out
to a restaurant?
A restaurant?
Why, jana, my dear,
why in the world would
we go out to eat
in a restaurant?
I don't know.
It's just that it
would be different.
Yes, it would
be different.
We'd walk
through the rain
and get ourselves
sopping wet.
Then we'd eat some greasy, unpalatable food
served off of dirty,
unwashed plates
and after that it would
be a moot question
whether we'd succumb
to ptomaine or pneumonia.
Will that be
all, ma'am?
Oh, just a little
bit longer, nelda.
Don't make her
do that anymore!
What is the matter with you?
It's just that outside there must be
the clean, beautiful
sound of rain.
And in here
those constant animal grunts of pleasure.
Jana!
Yell at me, father.
Please yell at me.
I can't tell you how delighted
i am to hear you yell at me.
It proves that you've got lungs.
Lungs and a mind and
a mouth and a voice.
Oh, father, we're
atrophying in here.
We sit here day after day
and year
after year
while that clock
turns and turns.
And we decay with every minute
while nelda the maid
and robert the butler
and gretchen the cook
and jensen the handyman...
jana!
While these domestics do everything
but our
breathing for us.
Nelda, will you
leave us, please?
Yes, sir.
Nelda!
I'm speaking
to you, nelda.
Yes, miss jana?
Don't you agree
with me, nelda?
You were saying,
miss jana?
I was about
to say that...
i was about to make
mention of the fact...
please don't stop
on my account, jana.
We have no
secrets here.
Don't we?
No secrets. Is
that it, father?
Why, that's all we
do have- secrets.
That's how
we live-
by shutting
off the world,
turning our
backs on it,
while you soundless, fleshless
things glide around here
and, with your efficient
ministrations,
turn my father and
my mother into jelly.
If i may say so,
miss jana,
you sound jealous.
You said yourself, jana,
that i designed and
built to perfection,
and i made these people
quite indestructible.
It's like living with ghosts.
Oh, no, my dear. Not ghosts.
Ghosts are those
who have died after living,
but these people had no life
until i gave
it to them.
The residence
of dr. William loren,
which is, in reality,
a menagerie for machines.
We're about to discover
that sometimes the product
of man's talent and genius
can walk amongst us untouched
by the normal ravages of time.
These are dr. Loren's robots,
built to function
as well as artistic perfection.
But, in a moment, dr. William
loren, wife and daughter
will discover that
perfection is relative-
that even robots
have to be paid for-
and very shortly will be shown
exactly what is the bill.
Tonight, florient unscented,
the new kind of room deodorant
that kills bad odors
yet leaves no fragrance,
brings you...
ah. I believe i'll take
the meerschaum tonight, robert.
I'll prepare it, sir.
Will there be
anything else, dr. Loren?
I think not tonight,
robert.
Good night, sir.
Good night, robert.
Oh, uh... robert?
There's no need.
I'll light your pipe
tonight, father.
Well, jana, shall
we talk of it now?
Shall we talk
of what?
Why, i think
that's quite obvious.
Suddenly, inexplicably,
your mother and i find
you're unhappy.
You're rebellious.
Do you think that
pleases us, jana?
I don't know.
I explained to you
a long time ago
why i did what i did-
why i retired
from the world,
and why i built
these people.
What you've done
to yourselves
is an atrocity.
But what you've done
to me is worse.
You've turned me into a freak-
an unsocial, unworldly,
insulated freak.
Shall i tell you
what else i've
done for you, jana?
I've kept you from harm.
I've protected you
against disease.
And insulation in this
20th century is no crime.
It's a service.
You've never had to look
into the face of war
or the face of poverty
or prejudice.
Well, you've
been isolated, yes,
but what you think
of as imprisonment
just happens to be asylum and
security, yes, and survival.
Asylum in
a hothouse?
Security in
a mausoleum?
Survival as a vegetable survives.
What you're becoming,
and what you're
making me become...
a vegetable.
Thank you.
Yes, sir.
Oh.
Now, madam.
There's a good girl.
Will that
be all, ma'am?
Yes. Thank you,
nelda. Good night.
Good night, ma'am.
Nelda!
Time is running out, father.
Instead of controlling,
you're being controlled.
Why, you're becoming dependent.
You're both reaching a point
where you won't be able
to exist without them.
Destroy them, father.
Get rid of them.
Dismantle them.
Jana!
Jana, they're
not just machines.
Do you know how many
thousands of hours
i've spent in
developing them
and perfecting them?
Do you realize how... how
marvelously intricate they are?
How scientifically
precise?
Not just arms and legs
that move, jana.
They're creatures.
They have minds
and wills.
They have memory
tracks, you see?
I've given each one of them a
memory of his own, haven't i?
Yes.
And all of them can
recount to you in detail
everything that's
happened to them
since their
early childhood,
and they had no childhood.
They were born just as you
see them now, weren't they?
Yes.
Looking the way they do,
acting the way they do,
but each with
his own talent.
One of them was
built as a cook.
Another was built
as a maid.
The butler was
manufactured as a butler.
The handyman knows nothing
but being a handyman.
Jana, you're not asking me
to dismantle machines.
You're asking me
to destroy
that which has life.
Life?
They're just highly
complicated toys.
Father, you've
turned this house
into a playroom.
Why, jana, dear.
Listen to your mother.
You're acting like
a willful child.
A willful child?
I'm acting like
a woman, mother,
who wants something
more out of life
than just to be massaged
five times a day.
Or a man
who thinks paradise
is having his pipes
filled and refilled,
and his slippers
put on and taken off.
You've got to get
rid of them, father-
nelda, gretchen, suzanne-
all of them.
That is quite
impossible.
I'll give you a choice-
get rid of them
or i'll leave.
You can't leave,
jana, dear.
Why, you simply
can't leave.
Well, what would
happen to you?
Who'd look
after you?
What would you
do out there?
I'd be with normal
people, mother-
people who live
and work and then die-
but do it properly,
the way god intended.
That's where i want
to be- out there!
I want my freedom.
Jana, it just
isn't possible.
I want my freedom!
Miss jana,
you'll forgive me
but that was most
intemperate of you.
I consider that
unforgivable behavior.
Jana, you must have
respect for your parents.
I agree. You must
show respect.
Stop it!
You're jokes.
That's what you are.
Hysterical jokes,
with your sad little homilies
and your mouthed cliches.
You're nothing but walking record players.
That's all
any of you are-
walking record
players.
Jana, you're
making it difficult
for me to be patient.
Very difficult indeed.
I do apologize, father.
I know how accustomed
to perfection you are,
and i hate to throw a stone
in that serene pool of yours,
but you forgot
something.
Do you know that?
You forgot something.
They may be indestructible,
father, but you're not!
Jana.
Jana, dear,
you don't really
want to leave us,
do you?
I thought i made it
quite plain, father.
I want you to
open the windows
and let the air in.
I want you to
let the world in.
By destroying my
whole life's work.
Jana, we've loved
you very much.
If you could only see
that all of this has been
just as much for you
as for ourselves.
Oh, jana, we love you
more than words can tell.
I know that, father.
I know that.
Then... then
you will stay.
Oh, please stay, jana.
I beg of you, please.
No.
Jana, i'll do what
you asked me to do.
I promise you.
I'll do it right away.
Nelda, gretchen, suzanne-
all of you-
rest in peace.
Robert.
Sir?
I want you to take
all the servants
downstairs to my workroom.
Just stay there
until i come.
Have our services
been unsatisfactory, sir?
Robert, i have
given you an order.
You are, all of you,
to go downstairs
and wait for me.
But i've been
an excellent butler, sir.
You know i have.
I think you'll agree with me.
I came very well-
recommended, sir.
There isn't a more
efficient maid
in the entire
country.
I can fix anything
that has to be fixed.
No more!
Robert,
you have your orders.
It's all over.
We're alone
in the house now.
Alone, william?
Yes, my dear.
Quite alone.
You and i and
our daughter.
I've become so
accustomed to them.
It'll be difficult
at first,
won't it, william?
Yes, my dear, a little,
in the beginning.
Oh, mother.
We're going to live
like normal people
do you understand?
Normal people.
We're going
to give parties
and we'll take trips
and we'll make friends
and i'll find
a young man.
I'll find a young man
and, before you know it,
we're going to
have grandchildren.
Oh, father,
grandchildren.
What's the matter?
What is it?
It's what you said
about grandchildren.
You see, what your
mother means, jana...
what she means is it's
perfectly normal and natural
for parents to think
of their children
as children.
And then, when
suddenly they grow up
and they talk of having
children of their own,
it's a little
difficult for parents
to absorb quite
so quickly.
Something's
not right.
Something's not right.
Something's
not right.
What is it?
Why aren't any of my pictures
in the photo albums?
There are no pictures
of me here at all.
Jana, dear, there are
many pictures of you.
Here's a picture
of you at easter.
Why, there are
pictures of you
decorating the christmas tree last year.
Not as a little
girl, mother.
There are no pictures of me
as a little girl.
Pictures of you and
father and the robots.
Always pictures
of the robots-
10 years ago,
20 years ago-
but no pictures of me. Why?
I want you
to tell me why.
Why?
It's not true.
Oh, it couldn't be true.
Please tell me it's not true.
Jana...
you are our daughter-
you know you're our daughter-
and you remember everything
from your childhood.
You remember the
schools you went to,
the children you played with,
and you remember all
the places you went to.
You do remember
them, jana?
You've got to.
Why have i got
to remember them?
Because you
fed them to me?
A memory track.
What am i?
Oh, please,
tell me what i am.
It doesn't make any difference.
It doesn't make any
difference at all, jana.
We were childless.
We had nothing of our
flesh to leave behind-
nothing of our hearts,
nothing of our love.
So, you see...
we got you.
You made me.
You built me.
You manufactured me.
Of course, the maid
was built as a maid,
the butler manufactured
as a butler,
and the cook and the handyman,
all for a particular purpose.
And the daughter...
you built a daughter!
Jana, i created you
as a thing of love.
It doesn't matter
what you are
or how you got here.
You're our daughter.
Jana, you've got
to understand that.
You're our daughter.
I can't be
your daughter.
I'm a thing.
I'm a machine.
A machine!
Jana, jana.
No pain.
No pain at all!
Jana, stop it!
No pain.
No love.
I can't
even feel love.
Oh!
William, what
will we do?
Everything's
changed now.
She'll never
be the same.
What will we do,
william?
William,
you wouldn't.
No, i couldn't do
anything like that.
I couldn't stand not
having her here anymore.
I just couldn't
stand that.
Jana, jana, jana...
just a little
to the left, nelda.
Not quite so hard.
Of course, mrs. Loren,
of course.
Should you be worn out
by the rigors of competing
in a very competitive world,
if you're distraught from
having to share your existence
with the noises and neuroses
of the 20th century,
if you crave serenity
but want it full-time and
with no strings attached,
get yourself a workroom
in the basement,
and then drop a note
to dr. And mrs. William loren.
They're a childless couple
who've made comfort
a life's work,
and maybe there are a few
do-it-yourself pamphlets
still available
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
An attractive
and rather imposing room
lived in
by a man named templeton.
And, like most rooms,
suggestive, really,
of only a part of the man-
the outside part.
Our story next week
takes off from here.
Mr. Brian aherne lends us
his considerable talents
in a script by e. Jack neuman
called
"the trouble with templeton."
It can best be described
as poignant, provocative,
and a highly-diverting trip
into the twilight zone.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
be sure and see
the colgate-palmolive company's
new comedy show
my sister eileen
wednesday night
on many of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org