Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
What's happening?
Well, i think he's dead.
I believe
it's salvador.
Where is the telegrapher?
Parece que esta muerto.
Quien es?
Es salvador.
Rudolfo...
rudolfo, i wish
to send a telegram.
Telegram now?
But this is
after hours.
What's the matter
with you, sanchez?
Please, do you know
what time it is?
I close at 4:00.
For 23 years,
i close at 4:00.
Because you are
a policeman,
you think you got
the privilege to...?
Salvador?
How?
I will send a telegram;
it will explain.
You will
tell it to me?
I will tell
it to you.
Send it as
i tell it.
To the prefect of
police, state capital.
Prefect of police?
Send it, rudolfo,
send it!
Don't censor it!
Unidentified aircraft-
or something-
crashed into the hills north
of our village late last night.
Object is metal
and circular.
Officer emmanuel salvador
and myself
investigated the
scene of the crash.
Found evidence of footprints
and broken brush.
Salvador
followed same.
I heard
several shots.
Found body of
officer salvador.
Say that i followed the
figure of the monster
in the darkness.
I fired several shots.
I believe i wounded
whoever it...
whateverit was.
The place is mexico,
just across the texas border.
A mountain village held back
in time by its remoteness,
and suddenly intruded upon
by the 20th century.
And this is pedro,
nine years old-
a lonely, rootless little boy
who will soon
make the acquaintance
of a traveler
from a distant place.
We are at present 40 miles
from the rio grande,
but any place and all places
can be the twilight zone.
Who did it, sanchez?
Please, doctor,
i do not know.
Some, some giant thing
escaped in the darkness.
I fired several
shots, and...
later, i found
some bloodstains.
They're sending some army
men from the state capitol.
They will take over.
Some "giant thing"?
Not the darkness,
or perhaps your fear?
You doubt me, doctor?
No, you're the law and order
in this village, sanchez.
Be the sanity as well.
You have frightened
all these people.
I just want to make sure
that the source of the fear
is not an illusion.
This, doctor- is
this an illusion?!
All right, go to
your homes, everybody,
and lock your doors.
I want no one on
the streets tonight.
We're in danger.
I found all i
wanted to know.
Take the body
to the priest now.
Drink up, doctor;
i want to close now.
I have no doubt.
What stalks
the night, manolo?
What stalks the night?
Whatever it is, i
want my place locked...
thank you for coming,
stargazer.
I am cursed
in my old age
by having
this astronomer
on my payroll.
Still looking at
the stars, pedro?
So, what do you learn
from the
stars, eh?
Have they
ever told you
to sweep this
place properly
or to clean
a glass?
It is said there is life
on some of them.
Oh, this is a fact?
Then you and the
man in the moon
have nothing in common,
because you
aren't alive.
Here, go get
some water
and come
right back.
Doors should be
locked tonight.
He's a strange little boy.
Where'd he come from?
Who knows?
He's son of abracero,
it is said.
The authorities are in
here three times a week
asking me why he
does not attend school.
They ask me, ha!
The boy is not of my flesh.
I know nothing of him.
He cleans the place for me
and serves table,
and he has a room in the back.
Hey, i overpay him,
believe me,
but i am not
such a rich man
that i can
certainly afford
to run an orphanage
for little
street urchins.
He doesn't have
any friends, does he?
Him? Why should he?
He has a mind
like an old man.
He's not normal.
Go look for him
out in the night,
and you'll see him
standing there
looking up
at the sky.
Did you ever
see him smile?
I ask
you this.
Did you ever
see him smile?
Why would he smile, the boy?
What is there
to delight
him?
His poverty?
Why should he smile?
Perhaps, manolo...
perhaps on
some occasion,
some festive
occasion,
instead of handing him
a broom or a tray,
extend him a hand.
Keep the boy inside
tonight, manolo.
Shall i see you home, ignacio?
No, thank you,
pedro.
With me, darkness is a friend.
But you stay inside.
I'm locking up
now, doctor.
I must ask you
to leave.
So, manolo...
my friend,
wear a smile,
and you'll doubtless live
to see the morning.
Are you still open?
I thought perhaps i
could have some wine.
¯como estas?
Bien.
Please
sit down, sir.
I will get
you wine.
I am sorry, senor,
but the place is closed.
We are closed now,
and no longer serving.
There is a curfew.
Is this not
true, doctor?
Is there not
a curfew on?
I won't stay but a moment.
Just...
long enough
for a drink
of wine.
I... i'm ill, i think.
But i promise you i won't stay.
Please.
That's not wine.
The bottle
didn't break,
so it couldn't be...
i didn't want
to hurt him.
He gave me
no choice.
I must explain.
Please...
please...
listen to me for a moment.
I tried to explain before
to that policeman
or soldier,
or whoever it was.
I tried to tell him
that i came in peace.
He wanted to kill me.
I tried to get the gun
away from him,
and it went off
against his body.
And then the man who came
afterwards kept firing at me.
Please... please...
please...
you'll be all right soon.
The doctor has said so.
He will make you all well again.
It's very odd, pedro,
very odd, indeed,
that there's
only one person
who feels neither
fear nor anger,
and this is a boy.
It is because we are alike.
You are a stranger,
and in a way,
i am a stranger, too.
Pedro, the poncho...
what?
In the pocket.
Get it.
It's a gift.
Put it away.
I'll tell you later on.
For a badly wounded man,
you have
a strangely willful pulse.
I might go a step further
and say that i wish mine
sounded like yours does.
Pedro, bring the lamp
close to the bed.
Si, doctor.
Ether?
I'm going to start
digging in there
for at least
30 minutes.
No anesthetic, doctor.
Pedro, i think
this is a good time
for you to go out
and look at the stars.
You have a good
friend, senor.
Doctor, you must
give him something.
Pedro, i will
tell you something.
I'm a very
obliging man,
but your friend does not
want the pain deadened.
And i always say, every
man to his own taste.
Whiskey. If not the best,
make it the strongest.
The stranger
travels light.
Just the clothes
on his back, and...
and these inside
his chest.
He was very brave, doctor.
Not a sound from him.
Not so much as a cry
all that time.
Yes, very brave.
Pedro, come here.
What else do you
know of him, pedro?
I know nothing else
except that he is my friend.
Yes, this may be true,
but it does not
explain the man, does it?
For example, it does not explain
how a man can have
two bullets inside his body
and have them removed
without a whimper.
It does not explain
how this
man's pulse
can be as strong
and as steady
as if there was
nothing else wrong
with him than a cold.
And it does not explain
why this man is alive
when he should be dead.
We got to him
just in time, doctor.
No, pedro.
We got to him about
three hours too late.
We got to him
where by the laws
of every book
on common sense
he should have
bled to death.
But he didn't.
So, stay by
your friend, huh?
And look
after him.
Si, doctor.
Manolo.
When i was in there,
i heard the door unlock.
Oh, i...
i went out, doctor.
I went out to tell sanchez
that when the army came,
they would not
have to go walking
through the hills at night.
They would only have to come
here to find what they want.
At your baptism, they forgot
to give you a proper name.
What would that be, doctor?
That would be judas, manolo.
You must be tired, pedro.
It doesn't
matter, senor.
I can sleep
anytime.
Now you
must sleep.
You have a poet, pedro.
I read him- robert burns.
He said, "the best-laid schemes
o' mice and men
gang aft a-gley..."
like my plans.
I came here to give, and
all i've done is to take-
your bed, your room.
Even my clothes-
i stole them.
I've often wondered why it is
that men fear the unknown.
Like children,
they're afraid of the dark.
The only person
i've met
who isn't afraid
of the dark
is a child.
Because i am an odd one.
We are both odd ones,
mr. Williams.
You come from a long way off,
don't you?
From the stars?
From beyond the stars, pedro.
For a reason?
For many reasons.
And this thing
you've given me...
just a gift.
A gesture, really.
A small gift
to show them
that i came
as a visitor
not an invader.
I must get back
to my ship, pedro
see if i can repair it.
And then
i must leave.
For good, senor?
For good and all?
Oh, no, pedro,
there's no such thing
as "for good and all."
There is only forever.
I will come back sometime...
or others like me.
Where you're from,
is there a god?
The same god, pedro.
I wonder...
what?
If god were to come to earth,
would they find him so strange
that they would be afraid,
and would they shoot him?
Did not his son
come once, pedro?
And they nailed him to a cross.
And then spent 2,000 years
learning to believe in him.
All things take time, pedro.
Soon,
pedro, soon
your people
will no longer
be afraid of me.
They will not be afraid,
and then...
then i can show them the gift.
I am
sanchez, sir.
I am the local
police officer.
And the fugitive?
Inside there, sir.
It was i, myself
who shot him
and brought
him down.
The bartender tells me
that he lies in a bed
too weak to move.
You are a brave man,
officer sanchez.
But please explain to me
if he is only one man
and is too weak to move,
why do you need us?
You, you do not
understand, sir.
This is not a man;
this is a creature.
Who knows what
are his powers?
You- you are
the owner?
This is manolo, si.
The person you seek
is inside, captain.
I have held him here for you.
Oh, i am
in the presence
of such courage,
mr. Bartender.
A village
of lions.
Sergeant,
in here with me.
The two of you,
wait outside.
Excuse me, captain.
The man is too
ill to be moved.
Oh?
And you would be...?
I am the doctor here.
I have been treating the man.
He was wounded,
captain,
after killing one
of our policeman.
Why don't you
let captain
do his duty,
doctor?
I will be very happy
to let the captain do his duty,
but first, i must be
cognizant of my own.
The man is my patient;
he's been badly wounded.
He can do no one any harm.
Hmm.
Unfortunately, doctor
my orders from
the state capital
were to bring back
a killer,
not a patient.
Get out of
the way, pedro.
They have come
for the monster.
No! He
must live!
The doctor
said he must
stay here.
Here he is, captain.
Have the men surround
the street immediately.
He cannot have gone
very far.
If there is ever a need here
for a town jailer,
mr. Bartender,
i hope you do not see fit
to run for the office!
Que dios nos proteja!
The soldiers
will protect us.
There he is!
Officer, i found him!
He's here!
You're under arrest, senor!
You will come with us.
The charge is murder.
Death was an accident.
I come in peace.
You will put up
your hands
and walk toward me.
Mr. Williams! Mr. Williams!
Pedro, the gift.
Show them
the gift.
Give it to
the doctor.
He will explain
it to them.
Destroy it.
Burn it! Burn it!
It is the devil's work.
Destroy it!
It's the devil's work!
Burn it! Burn it!
Why did you do it?
Why?
Que dios nos proteja!
Calm yourself.
Pedro!
Look out for the boy!
Somebody stop him.
He's attacking the boy.
He's going after the boy!
Somebody stop him!
He's attacking the boy!
All right,
that's the end of it.
Everybody,
back to your homes.
Clear the streets.
Arrange for someone
to pick up the body.
What was it, doctor?
Black magic?
Something from satan?
Read it.
"Greetings to the people
of earth.
"We come as friends,
and in peace.
"We bring you this gift.
"The following chemical
formula is a vaccine.
It's a vaccine against
all forms of cancer."
That's all there is.
The rest
has been burned.
So we have not
just killed a man.
We have killed a dream.
Oh, que noche,
que noche!
Come, pedro.
Come home with me, son.
Madeiro, mexico- the present.
The subject- fear.
The cure- a little more faith.
An rx off a shelf
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week onthe twilight zone,
a return visit
from an illustrious young actor,
cliff robertson.
He stars
in one of the strangest tales
we've yet to throw at you.
It's called "the dummy,"
and it involves a ventriloquist
and a piece of painted wood-
a unique slab of carved pine
who decides that lap sitting
is for the birds,
and who takes things
into his own wooden hands.
Now, this one we recommend
to the voice throwers
across the land.
We hope we see you then.
Chesterfield king extra length-
sure, and more,
for only chesterfield king
gives you the wonderful taste
of 21 great tobaccos.
Try a pack.
This is james arness.
You know, it's only a short hop
fromthe twilight zone
to dodge city ingunsmoke.
Saturday nights
over most of these stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org