Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Evening, ma'am.
Are you miss scott?
That's right.
Well, i'm trooper
franklin, miss scott.
May i come in
for a moment?
Thank you.
Attractive place.
That's gracious
of you to say so.
What else is new?
You came into
town this morning?
It's an unhappy pilgrimage
that i'm forced
to make every week.
No one will deliver my supplies,
so i have to get them myself.
Was there anything else,
trooper franklin?
Uh, mr. Barth
down at the general store
said something
about you telling him
you'd seen some kind of lights
in the sky last night.
So?
Well...
i just thought i'd, uh...
come up here and ask you
a few questions about it.
That's intrepid of you, trooper.
I did see
something last night.
I did mention it to that
pickle barrel wheeler-dealer.
I mentioned it because the
run of dialogue is so dull
it makes me want to retire
from the human race.
I'm up to here in rainfall,
wind velocity,
snowfalls and
gripping bingo games.
So i thought i'd
inject something new
into the dialogue.
I see.
Well, uh...
what kind of lights
would you say they were?
If you're looking for a red-hot
gun-'em-down battle against evil
head north because
you won't find it here.
You're here from
new york, miss scott?
Is that a misdemeanor?
No, no, not
at all, i...
i was just interested.
We heard you'd
taken a place up here.
A cabin, you living alone.
You were some sort
of a... fashion editor?
Yes.
I was some sort
of a fashion editor.
My yearly salary would have
bought the main street
of that rinky-dink
whistle-stop down there.
I had what is euphemistically
known as a nervous breakdown.
So i came up here to be alone.
Said journey being the
biggest rock i ever pulled
because you can't be alone here.
You have to share
your private life
with country bumpkins.
And, um...
gilbert and sullivan
state troopers.
Repeating, trooper,
since your ears seem to flap:
There is nothing for you here,
so why not run along?
I think you're quite right.
There isn't
much here for me.
Or, for that
matter, anyone else.
What's that
supposed to mean?
That's supposed to mean
that in your book
anyone who hasn't bought
their clothes on fifth avenue
is considered a bumpkin.
And everybody
who doesn't
broaden their as
is considered
provincial.
And that elusive
thing called culture
is really only
an inheritable legacy
available only
to insufferable snobs
of which, miss scott,
i'm afraid you are
a charter member.
What's happened?
You're not frightened,
are you, miss scott?
I'm afraid you put me
in the wrong sorority,
mr. Franklin.
I'm a charter member,
but not of snobs.
I'm the founder and
the chairman of the board
of the society
of frightened people.
So frightened that
they can't face the world
and they go away
to little mountain retreats.
They act superior
because they think it hides
their tensions and neuroses.
Thank you for
an honest answer.
Why don't you rustle
up some hot coffee
for the two of us?
I'll go out
and check around
and stay with you
an hour or so to see
if it comes back.
I'll drive you back
into town if you'd like.
What was it?
The noise
and the lights?
A meteor or maybe an
aircraft off its course.
Those would be the
rational explanations.
Give me an
irrational one.
Maybe something
from outer space.
"There are more things
"in heaven and
earth, horatio,
than are dreamt of
in your philosophy."
That's shakespeare,
miss scott.
but what is that?
The major ingredient
of any recipe for fear
is the unknown.
And here are two characters
about to partake of the meal.
Miss charlotte scott,
a fashion editor,
and mr. Robert franklin,
a state trooper...
and the third member
of the party, the unknown,
that has just landed
a few hundred yards away.
This person or thing
is soon to be met.
This is a mountain cabin
but it is also
a clearing in the shadows
known as the twilight zone.
Mr. Franklin,
did you see anything?
Not much.
You better go back inside.
I'll be right back.
Haven't you ever heard
of an emergency brake?
Yup, heard and used.
But this emergency brakewason.
There's only two of us
and neither of us
were near the car.
Who pushed it?
Maybe nobody.
Maybe the brake just gave out.
You believe that?
For the time being.
That's the only explanation
i can conjure up.
The radio's dead.
No power
at all.
You got a phone inside?
That's one concession
to privacy that i didn't make.
I've got a telephone
and some coffee.
At this moment, both are
luxury items in my book.
Oh, uh, better lock it.
You've just applied
for membership, hmm?
My club for
frightened people.
Lady, i've been
in two wars,
and i've been a policeman
between and after.
And i'm not
ashamed to say
that i've racked
up more scared hours
than most rabbits.
Thank you for
an honest answer.
Miss scott, maybe
you can learn this,
maybe it'll help you.
But being frightened... it's a
normal, natural human function
just like breathing.
It's how you react to fright,
that's what really counts.
You can get the shakes
and crawl under a bed
or you can clench your fists
and go about your business.
You can clench your fists,
but i'll be under the bed.
Being frightened hasn't
hurt your sense of humor,
has it?
You got two beds?
I might like
to do a little crawling
under one of them myself.
Your phone is dead.
I'll tell you this much,
miss scott.
Despite all you may have heard
about officers of the law,
we react
like normal human beings.
A roaring fire,
a mountain cabin,
hot coffee...
you know, if i live long enough
to retire,
it doesn't sound like
a bad later life, does it?
What's the matter?
Listen, don't
you hear it?
It's up there.
Where?
Oh... it's
on the roof.
Is there an attic
or something?
No.
Is there some way
to get up on the roof?
Not from inside.
Oh, please, please don't
go out there, please.
Now, lady, you may have
been a hot fashion editor
but when it comes
to greeting intruders
you're something
else again.
Now, you lock
this after me.
And don't open it
until i tell you to.
No, you bet
your life i won't.
Who is it?
It's me.
Well...
did you see anything?
I didn't imagine it,
did i?
There was something
up on the roof.
Sounded like footsteps.
Did you find anything?
There's nothing on the
roof, nothing at all.
Not on the roof, anyway.
Maybe it's just, maybe it's
just a little imagination
seeping into
the both of us.
Maybe it's the night, maybe
it's the loneliness up here.
If there was
something on the roof
it would have
crushed this house flat.
Why?
Because the thing,
or whatever it is,
moved the car back
to where it was
and i think i know
how it was done.
It was carried
in somebody's hand.
There are fingerprints
on the car-
big fingerprints.
And if they are
fingerprints,
then we shouldn't
have any trouble
finding our invader.
Because he must stand
better than 500 feet high.
Good morning.
Morning.
What time do you make it?
Uh, it's 6:00.
Ooh.
You get
much sleep?
Couple of hours,
off and on.
How about you?
About the same,
i guess.
I, uh...
i didn't hear anything.
I didn't either.
Well, let's greet the morning...
and whoever else
happens to be in it.
You got any, uh, friends,
a little bent upstairs?
Somebody who'd go to
these kind of extremes?
If i did have,
they'd have been committed
a long time before this.
What is it?
Take a look at this.
It's a footprint.
Yeah, that's what
it is, all right.
It's a footprint.
Look at the size of it.
Let's get out
of here, let's run.
Where to?
To the village, down the road.
Somewhere away from here.
Use your head, will you?
It's 30 miles to the village.
No matter what
direction
we turn
there's somebody out here
as high as a mountain
who could just reach down and
crush us with his little finger
block our way with his big toe.
What can we do?
I can try and fix
that car radio
and phone for help.
You can do whatever you like
but i'm not staying here.
I'm getting out.
Miss scott!
I can't believe it.
All right,
miss scott, take off.
I'll try and keep
this nightmare occupied.
Maybe you can reach the village
and get some help.
You think they'd ever
hear the end of my story
before they locked me up?
Honey, that's only
one of the risks
we have to take.
Why doesn't it
do something?
Now, that's a good question.
Because if it
wanted to destroy us
it could have done it
a long time ago.
Us, the village down below
and the whole state.
Go on, miss scott,
take off, will you?
No. No, as scared as i am,
i want to stay.
Yes, i want
to stay with you.
All right, but i
think i better fill
you in on something.
I've got to fight
that with this.
That's like trying
to bring down a bomber
with a peashooter.
But it's all we've got.
Uh, oh...
oh.
It's a balloon.
Fantastic.
It's...
unbelievable.
But that's what it is.
It's a balloon.
That's it?
Is this what we've
been frightened of?
A fugitive from
a thanksgiving day parade?
Not quite.
This is what we've
been frightened of.
Take a look at it,
miss scott.
Look at the source
of our nightmare.
Great leader, this
is earth explorer one.
Must report failure.
Burned trees, dug up shoe print
sprayed fingerprint
on earth vehicle
moved it by magnet,
inflated giant figure.
Entire operation ended by earth
man's failure to be frightened.
Repeat, failure
to be frightened.
Request permission
to depart earth.
Please, oh, please,
great leader
let us depart
before they crush us.
You know something?
I wish them luck.
Maybe the next place they land,
they can be the giants.
What of our next visitors?
What if they are giants?
Well, i think you'd
spit in their eye.
That's what i think.
Fear, of course,
is extremely relative.
It depends on who can look
down and who must look up.
It depends on other vagaries
like the time,
the mood, the darkness.
But it's been said before
with great validity
that the worst thing there
is to fear is fear itself.
Tonight's tale of terror
and tiny people
onthe twilight zone.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org