Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound...
a dimension of sight...
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
I know.
Iknow!
I know, and you are making me
all the later.
And lovesville to you.
Ivor is nervous.
So am l-
you've 25 minutes
to get to
the airport.
Won't they hold
the plane?
Not forever.
You'd better
shift gears.
I'm all packed,
except for my rings.
I'm going to take
all of them.
Oh, you kook.
It wasyouridea.
It was my idea it would
make good publicity
if the ring-a-ding girl
collected rings.
Now, you'd better haul
your fantail out of here,
or all you're gonna
see of that plane
is a vapor trail.
Oh, this just came
special delivery.
You can look at it
on the plane.
I adore presents.
Let the plane wait.
"Please accept the enclosed
as a token of affection
of your fan club
in howardville."
Do you know where
howardville is?
Doesn't everybody?
You'll see it if you look down.
We fly right over
the center of town.
Well, hooray for us.
Howardville happens to be
my hometown,
and my loyalest fans
are still there.
Do you know, i couldn't
have gotten here if it
hadn't been for them.
They actually took up
a collection
to pay my fare to hollywood.
What'd they send you-
the key to the local still?
Well,
let's find out.
Youfind out.
I'm going to get this
ice down to the car.
Bunny, come home.
Come home, bunny.
Bunny, this is hildy.
Come home
come home...
occupation, film actress.
Residence,
hollywood, california,
or anywhere in the world that
cameras happen to be grinding.
Bunny blake is a public figure.
What she wears, eats,
thinks, says is news.
But underneath the glamour,
the makeup, the publicity
the buildup, the costuming
is a flesh-and-blood person,
a beautiful girl
about to take a long and bizarre
journey into the twilight zone.
Yeah, okay, nancy.
Hey, we still going
to the dance friday?
Great.
Bud!
What?
I need that
picnic basket
out of the cellar.
Oh, look, i'll call
you right back.
Hey, can't i finish
reading the ball scores?
Now, buster.
I'm going to pack
the sandwiches
just as soon as i finish
cleaning this room.
Hey, you know, the
paper says rain.
Yeah, i know.
So does the radio.
But just in the north
part of the county.
Will you please get
the picnic basket?
And then clean up your
room... and mow the lawn.
Aren't there
any laws
against child labor
in this state?
Boo.
Bunny!
I don't believe it!
Oh, it has been so long!
I've looked forward to it so!
I think about you
all the time.
But how did you
ever get in here
without me
hearing you?
It's so good to be home!
I could just
shake you.
That is no way to
greet a celebrity.
But five years,
and not even one
speck of warning.
Oh, you know me-
glamorous,
unpredictable,
full of surprises-
the same old nut.
What made you decide to come
home out of the blue?
I thought maybe you'd
like to see me.
Oh, i'm tickled
to death.
And maybe
it was the ring.
Oh, it arrived.
What a project that was.
Everyone in town
chipped in a dollar,
and they let me pick it out.
Do you really
like it?
I love it.
Sis, is everything
all right here?
Areyou
all right?
Never better. Why?
Oh, i don't know.
Maybe i'm having
hallucinations.
Oh, don't drag
that on the floor.
I haven't even vacuumed.
Oh, that's the way you
do it in hollywood.
They teach you in drama class.
It's supposed to show
that you really don't care
and besides, you've got ten more
at home in the closet.
How do you like the walk?
You didn't learnthat
in drama class.
My one natural talent.
Oh, bunny,
we're so proud of you-
the whole
town is.
How long do we get to keep you?
Just for one day.
Oh, that's not
nearly long enough.
I'm stealing time as it is, sis.
I'm supposed to be in rome.
But i got to the airport,
and right at the last minute
i said, "shoot, i'm going home."
Aunt bunny!
Who is this
divine man?
Hello, aunt bunny.
Is it really bud?
Funny, i thought
it was rock, or
maybe cary.
Yeah, mom said you
were a screwball.
And she was right.
Gee, it is good
to be home.
I'm so anxious to
see everybody-
all my old
friends and all.
You picked
the right day for it.
You remember
the founder's day picnic?
How could
i forget it?
The year i won
the beauty pageant
was what really
got me started.
Well, the picnic is
this afternoon.
Everyone in
town will
be there.
Picnic?
Of course
you'll come?
Picnic!
Bud and i
have to go-
i'm on the
food committee,
and he's
the lifeguard.
Good morning,
ladies and gentlemen.
This is your young old friend,
ben braden,
howardville's answer
to arthur godfrey,
bringing you
the news and weather
and a very special hello to you,
bunny blake, wherever you are.
Bunny, please come home.
We need you, we need you,
we need you...
oh...
bunny, are you
all right?
Bunny, what is it?
Bud, call dr. Floyd.
Bunny!
I played a nurse
in a movie once.
The doctor
reminded me of you.
He was supposed to be
a kindly, gruff
old family physician.
I saw it.
The medical profession
should have sued.
Uh, i was faking...
about being sick,
i mean.
I just wanted
to see you.
Well, that's
flattering.
What's your diagnosis?
One tired little girl.
What do you do in
hollywood, anyway?
Me? I glow.
Wind me, and i light up.
Turn me on and i give off
incandescent sparkles.
Heck, doc, i'm a star.
Well, you've
been sparkling
a little too
much lately.
What you need is
sleep, rest, fresh air
and some of hildy's
good cooking.
I want you to take it
a little easy for a while.
Sorry, kindly, gruff
old family physician
but that is impossible.
There is a producer in
rome right this minute
pulling out what's
left of his hair
wondering where i am.
Tell me his name, and
i'll cable him you're sick.
But i'm not sick.
Your sister said
you were in shock,
that you seemed not to hear her
or even to see her
during
that seizure.
It was a performance.
Evidently a very
convincing one.
I told you, it was all an excuse
to get you over here.
There's something
i want to ask you.
Well?
You used to be a very big deal
on the founder's day committee.
Still am.
I'm the chairman.
Well, as one kindly, gruff
old family friend to another
would you do me
a very large favor?
I'll try.
Put off the picnic-
postpone it to another day.
Really?
You can't be serious,
bunny- why?
I've only got one day
to spend at home.
I want it to be
a plain, ordinary
apple-pie kind of day-
the way i remember.
I want to drop in
on old friends
and surprise them
at home.
You can see them
at the picnic.
It wouldn't be
the same-
there'd be crowds,
new people i don't know,
strangers
tugging at me for autographs.
I'd be miserable.
Bunny, you can't
seriously expect
that an entire town is
going to rearrange its plans
just to suit your whim.
Doc, i love this town,
and i love the people.
Would i ask them
to do this for me
if it weren't more than a whim?
I don't know what your life
is like away from here.
Perhaps in hollywood you can
make an unreasonable request
and your caprice is gratified.
But this isn't
hollywood.
Now, i'm going to
give you something
that will
help you rest.
"Ring-a-ding girl"...
but she don't fool cyrus gentry.
Miss high and mighty
coming back here
like she was somebody special.
Well, youare
special-
right now.
Maybe the most special person
howardville will ever have.
So, bunny blake...
help us...
oh, bunny...
i have written
you out...
excuse me, doctor.
Bunny?
Bunny!
Oh, hildy...
how's the patient?
Whereisthe patient?
She went upstairs.
Hildy, what's upsetting
your sister?
I wish i knew.
She seems to be
under a severe strain,
and she's acting
quite irrationally.
Now, you have
this prescription
filled out.
It'll relax her.
Try to keep her
as quiet as possible,
and by no means
let her go on her own.
I'll try.
It may be...
may be just fatigue.
Then again...
well, you just call me
if you need me.
Thank you, doctor.
Good-bye.
Bud?
Yeah.
This is a
prescription
for some medicine
your aunt bunny needs.
Would you get it filled
right away, please?
What's the matter
with her?
There's not a single solitary
thing the matter with me, hildy.
I'm really shocked at how old
dr. Floyd is getting.
I think the poor old dear ought
to put himself out to pasture.
He thinks you ought to get
some rest.
Why? I'm not
the least bit tired.
He's the one who needs to rest.
Did you notice
how his hand
trembles?
He left this
prescription
for something to
help you relax.
Now, bud's going to the
drugstore to get it filled.
And while we're waiting,
why don't you
just lie down and
try to take it easy?
Mm-hmm, and i can just hear
what people will say:
"Bunny didn't drop in to see
any of her old friends.
She's getting uppity,
and she puts on airs."
I can explain to them that
you weren't feeling well.
Bobbi woodson
used to be my best friend.
I've got to seeher.
And ben braden- do you remember
that excruciating crush
he used to have on me?
Whatever happened to ben?
He's still here. He runs
the television station.
Now, listen, bunny...
i could have married
that old boy.
I've got a good mind
to walk in and
surprise him.
Bunny, i don't want you
to leave this house.
Can't stand
being cooped up
in the house.
Sometimes in california
when i get that
closed-in feeling,
you know what i do?
I take off every stitch
of clothes
and i jump in
the old swimming pool
and i swim like
a ring-a-ding fish.
That must be
very interesting
for your neighbors.
Nobody's complained so far.
Bud, want to go
for a walk and say
"hey" to people?
Great.
The doctor wants
you to rest.
He also said i needed
some fresh air.
Will you at least wait
until bud comes back
from the drugstore
with your medicine?
I've got a better idea.
I'll drive to the
drugstore with you.
What could be
more restful than
a little drive?
Unless you're one of
those hot rodders-
are you, bud?
Uh, no, no, no.
Well, i am.
Well, are you going
to come with me,
or are you going to
stand all day talking?
Sure...
hey...
ring-a-ding!
Well, what do you think
of her, aunt bunny?
Ring-a-ding!
She's real cool,
but call me bunny!
"Aunt bunny" sounds like the
housemother at the playboy club.
Um... bud, is mr. Gentry
still the caretaker
over at the high school?
You mean old methuselah?
You'd have to blow
the school up
to get rid of
that old bird.
Well, be an angel and
stop just long enough
for me to run in
and say hello.
Yeah, well, hadn't we better
get your medicine first?
Bud, this is important.
Okay, okay.
Thank you.
So you finally got your fill
of hollywood, huh?
No, i like it out there.
It's not what you think.
Oh, isn't it?
We heard about all
those high jinks
you got into
out there.
Can't say i'd
be proud of it.
Just what brought you
back here, barbara?
Coming home was
an impulse.
Well, you sure picked a day for
it- founder's day picnic.
Not that you'd
be interested.
Oh, but i am, mr. Gentry.
That's why i need your help.
Myhelp?
I want you to unlock the doors
to the school auditorium.
Now, some people may show up,
and if they do,
i want you to let them in.
No, i can't do that,
i've got to go to the picnic.
Mr. Gentry,
i know you don't like me,
but this is important-
terribly important.
Always asking favors.
Always wanted to be treated
like somebody special-
barbara blake.
Well, barbara, maybe you forgot
that these doors are open
all day long.
Now, you want
to come here,
you walk in like
anybody else.
Thank you, mr. Gentry.
Mr. Gentry...
don't go to that picnic.
Well, what do you think
of the old town, bunny?
It's so good, i
wonder why i left it.
Why did you leave?
Oh, i guess i
could have stayed here
and doneblithe spirit
at the little theater,
and played an angel
at the church pageant
at christmas time,
but i was too ambitious
and too talented.
I don't mean that the
way it sounded, but...
i just knew i
had a talent,
and i had to find
a place to let it grow.
Otherwise, it
would have died.
And i would have ended
up a frustrated woman
pushing a broom around
a house i hated
and screaming at a
brood of children
i couldn't stand.
Can you understand
that, bud?
Yeah. Yeah, i
can understand that, bunny.
Oh, here's your prescription.
You want to go home?
Um...
the television station's
still down the street?
Yeah, right over there.
Mm-hmm, well,
i'll be back.
Hello?
No, i don't have it on.
She is?
Well, yes, of course i knew she
was in town, but i...
she's supposed to be at the
drugstore with bud.
All right, clara.
I'll call you later.
And i can't tell
you how exciting it
is to be home again.
Well, are you gonna be with us
for a nice, long visit, bunny?
I have to leave tonight- i'm
starting a new picture in rome.
Oh, that's too bad.
A lot of your friends
won't get to see you.
They can if they really want to.
Remember that one-woman show
i did in las vegas last winter?
We read about it.
Well, i'm putting it on
this afternoon
in the high school auditorium,
and i want everybody in town
to come as my guest.
You know, everybody here at home
has always been so nice to me.
It's kind of
a token of my appreciation.
Looks like we've got
a conflict-
the founder's day picnic starts
this afternoon.
Well, all i've
got to say is,
folks have a choice of
coming to see me at 3:00
or going to
riverside park
and getting bit
by a bunch of ants.
I don't know anything about it.
I thought she was
down at the drugstore,
and the next thing i know,
here she is on tv.
Oh, i don't know
which i'll go to.
The way i feel now,
i'm so ashamed
i don't want to show
my face anywhere.
I'll call you back.
Bunny? I'm
trying very hard
not to get
angry with you,
because i think you
have lost your mind.
Ooh, buddy boy,
i told you
there'd be
an explosion.
Bud, you may
be excused.
This is nothing
to joke about.
Half a dozen people
have called me already.
Well, what
do they say?
Well, they-they're
confused.
They want to know
whether to go
to the founder's
day picnic
or thisthing
you're putting on
at the high school.
Bunny, what are
you trying to do?
I owe this town
something, hildy.
It's just my way of
paying off a debt.
Well, it doesn't
look like that.
You look like
a show-off-
a big hollywood
celebrity
who's trying
to impress
a lot of
small-town hicks.
Sis, let's not fight.
Well... i can't condone
what you're doing.
I think it's best
that bud and i show
up at the picnic.
Is that howardville
down there, bunny?
That flyspeck
next to the river?
Is that the place
you want to go back to?
Forget it, bunny.
Hildy?
Oh, honey,
if this performance
means so much to you,
we'll be there.
Bunny, we're late.
Oh, one thing for sure.
They can't start the show
until i get there.
Bud? Bud?
Bud, we're waiting.
I can't find
my blue tie.
Well, wear
another one.
We're late.
You'd better fire
your weatherman.
Bud, hurry!
I'm coming!
Remember when we used
to lie in bed on rainy nights
and call to each other
when we were kids?
Fun, wasn't it,
being kids?
It was very good.
Looks like
it's starting
to rain a little.
We'll just have
to brave it.
I've got an
audience waiting.
I'll get
some raincoats.
Oh, no, sis-
you're going
in style.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain speaking.
We're running into
a little rough weather,
so fasten your seat belts,
please.
It might be a little bumpy.
It's going to get rough.
Scared, honey?
Natch... isn't everyone?
What was that for?
Hildy...
yes?
Thank you.
For what?
Just for being
my sister.
Holy cow,
listen to that!
Fire engines and ambulances!
Turn on the radio.
Good-bye, hildy.
Good afternoon,
and welcome to
the 3:00 edition...
hello?
Yes, what is it?
Yes, jim.
I'm out at the park.
I thought you ought to know.
Know what, jim?
It's terrible, hildy, horrible.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Jim, will you please tell me
what you're talking about?
The plane crash-
happened just a few minutes ago.
What crash?
Passenger jet, l.a. To new york.
That storm just-just
tore it apart.
It landed right in the middle
of the picnic grounds.
Hildy...
your sister, bunny...
bunny's dead, hildy.
Dead? Why, that's crazy.
She was a passenger
on that plane.
She and another woman
were sitting right
next to each other.
I just... i just saw them.
Jim, my sister
is right here now.
I saw the body, hildy.
Bunny blake is dead.
I'm sorry i have to be
the one to tell you, but...
...while governor nathan has
requested federal aid...
bunny?
Bunny!
Howardville was rocked today
bunny!
By news of a transcontinental
jet air...
bunny, where are you?
...87 passengers and crew.
The crash occurred...
bunny?
Bunny!
Bunny, where are you?!
...most of the local citizens
had planned to join
the annual founder's day
celebration.
A disaster of major proportions
was averted by the fact
that most of the citizens
in town are safe at this moment
attending
an announced performance
by our local celebrity,
bunny blake.
How many more would have died
had they attended the picnic?
Fortunately for them,
howardville chose
to see bunny blake.
Eyewitnesses at the scene
of the crash say
bunny was a passenger
aboard the ill-fated plane.
But other witnesses have sworn
she was here in howardville
this afternoon
visiting her sister.
Until the mystery is unraveled
only one thing is certain:
Bunny blake is dead.
Meanwhile,
local citizens are asked
to stay away from the area.
All howardville fire engine
companies are at the scene.
Police have blocked the
founder's day picnic grounds,
and we repeat, local citizens
are asked to avoid the area.
Names of the victims
are being withheld,
pending identification...
we are all travelers.
The trip starts in a place
called birth
and ends in that lonely town
called death.
And that's the end
of the journey,
unless you happen to exist for
a few hours, like bunny blake
in the misty regions
of the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Ontwilight zonenext time
again the services
of earl hamner jr.,
in a strange story,
a strange conclusion
and a very unusual brand
of justice,
dramatized in a show called
"you drive."
It's the story
of a hit-and-run driver
in a very special kind
of an automobile.
A consummately fine actor
named edward andrews
lives out a nightmare
partly of his own making.
Ontwilight zone,"you drive."
I hope you're going
to watch it with us.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org