Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Oliver pope by name,
office manager by profession.
A man beset by life's problems:
His job, his salary,
the competition to get ahead.
Obviously mr. Pope's mind
is not on his driving.
Stop! Stop!
Oliver pope,
businessman turned killer
on a rain-soaked street
in the early evening
of just another day
during just another drive home
from the office.
The victim, a kid on a bicycle,
lying injured, near death.
But mr. Pope hasn't time
for the victim.
His only concern is for himself.
Oliver pope,
hit-and-run driver,
just arrived
at a crossroad in his life,
and he's chosen the wrong turn.
The hit occurred
in the world he knows,
but the run will lead him
straight into the twilight zone.
How come you put
the car away?
I thought we were
going to a movie.
Oh, no, i've
got a headache.
Aw. Bad day
at the office, ollie?
Yeah, yeah,
they're all bad.
You know that
pete radcliff?
Well, he's after my job.
He didn't impress me
as that kind of
fella at all.
Please, why do you
have to disagree
with everything
i say?
Oh, now, ollie, you're
just tired and cross.
You've got a headache,
and you just take this
and you'll feel better.
What are you doing?
Seeing if you've
got a fever.
You might have caught
that flu bug
that's been going around.
I'm all right.
Please just
leave me alone.
Stop fussing
over me.
Ollie...
ollie, somebody's
fooling around
out in the garage.
In the...
i'll go take a look.
Who's out there?
What was it?
Uh, nobody there.
What was that
light i saw?
Well, it was
the car itself.
A faulty connection
or something.
The lights kept going on
and off by themselves.
A car shouldn't act like that.
I just paid the repair shop
$35 to have it put into shape.
Didn't see
the paper
while you were
out there, did you?
No.
Boy's late.
I guess it's the rain.
There was an accident
this evening
at the corner of third and park.
Could you... uh, well,
i'm a friend of the family's.
Could you tell me,
how is the boy?
Yes.
Uh... terrible.
Ollie, what on
earth is that?
Must be some jerk
waking people up
in the middle
of the night.
Ollie, that'syourhorn.
Isn't it terrible
about that little boy?
Only 12 years old,
and they don't
expect him to live.
I hope they find
the man who did it
so they can give him
what's coming to him.
How do you know
it was a man?
Didn't you get
that far?
There was a witness.
How do you expect
to do a day's work
on one little
piece of toast?
Well... i'm not
going to go
to the office
today, lil, i...
i don't feel
very well.
Okay, lie down then.
I thought
you fixed that.
I did.
You're sure there
wasn't somebody
in the garage
last night?
I told you,
it's that car-
it's old car, nothing
about it works right.
We've had a lot
of old cars
that didn't go
honking their heads off
in the middle
of the night.
I'm going to
get rid of it.
Well, i'm going down
and have it looked at.
Yes, yes, third and park.
Well, i don't know
what's the matter.
It just stopped
and it won't start again.
Could you please send
a tow truck right away?
I'm in the middle of the street.
Lil, what took you so long?
I never...
i never had such a morning
in my life-
that car...
well, what about the car?
Well, it's
in the repair shop.
I had to take a cab home.
What happened?
The strangest thing
i've ever seen.
It all started down here
at the corner.
I wanted to turn right.
I could not make that wheel turn
the way i wanted to go.
And then finally,
the car stalls
at the intersection
of third and park.
Stalled?
Yes, the motor died.
There i was right
in the middle of the street,
blocking traffic.
Why, even the police
couldn't get it started.
What were the
police doing there?
Oh, they weren't
after me.
It's the same corner
where that little child
was run down last night.
Police said to keep a look out
in case the criminal
returns to the scene
of the crime.
Did they say
if they had any leads?
Well, yes, they're
getting close to an arrest.
I hope they get him.
Nobody's safe with a
madman like that around.
I thought you said
the... the car
was in the repair shop.
Well, it is.
What are you
trying to do?
talking about?
You said the car was
in the repair shop.
Well, it was.
What's it doing here?
Wait a minute.
I'll get it.
Hello?
Yes, yes, speaking.
No, i didn't pick it up.
Yes.
Yes, i know where it is.
It's right here.
Didn't one of your
men deliver it?
No, no, no, i don't
understand it either,
but i'd like you to
understand one thing.
Don't bother
to send me a bill.
You didn't have the car
down there long enough
to even look it over.
What do you think
about that?
Was that the mechanic?
They said
they lost the car.
The nerve of that guy.
It's not lost,
it's right here.
Will you explain to me
how it got here?
They didn't deliver it.
Well, it didn't
drive itself home.
Wait a minute,
don't answer that.
Well, why not?
Well, uh, all right,
but if it's for me,
just say
that i'm not home.
Ollie, what on earth
is frightening you?
Nothing, nothing.
I just don't feel like
seeing anybody, that's all.
I don't know what it is,
but if you don't get over
these heebie-jeebies,
i'm calling a doctor.
Morning,
mrs. Pope.
Well, what
a nice surprise.
Ollie here?
Yes, he's in
the living room.
Can i see him?
Yes, just
for a minute.
He's kind of under
the weather today.
It's nothing
serious.
I think he's
just got
a touch
of the flu.
Guess who's here.
Ollie, boy.
Oh.
I hear the flu bug
got you down.
Well, no, no,
not quite.
I'll be back
in the morning.
Well, i hope so.
Gets kind of dull
down there without you.
Oh?
What brings you
out here, pete?
When you didn't
show up at the office,
i thought i'd clear
up your "in" basket.
Keep your hands off of my desk.
I've got some very important
correspondence in that basket.
Not anymore, i took care of it.
Your letters, sir,
all answered
and waiting for your signature.
All answered...
ollie!
I'm sorry, ollie, i...
only wanted
to do you a favor.
You can do me a favor.
Quit bucking for my job, huh?
I take one morning off
and you start making noises
likeyou're
the head of the department.
You got it wrong, ollie.
I was only trying to help you.
I didn't want things
to pile up on you.
Don't try.
You listen to me.
You think i enjoyed
sitting in that office
dictating your lousy letters?
I got better things
to do, buddy boy.
Nobody's holding you here.
Go do them.
You bet i will.
Pete...
i'm sorry, i...
shouldn't have blown up
at him like that.
Last night, a kid on our block
was run down.
I knew him.
He used to
come over
and play
with my kids.
There was one nice, decent,
fun-loving, ambitious little kid
and some maniac
smashed into him
and left him lying there
in the rain.
I know.
We've been
reading about it
in the papers.
Terrible shame.
Well, they're watching
the corner.
He'll show up,
they always do.
You don't happen
to know
how the little boy's
getting on, do you?
He died,
mrs. Pope.
About an hour ago.
Oh...
well...
i'll see you
to the door.
I think that's him.
That won't do,
you have to be sure.
That's him, i'm sure.
Wait here.
Could i see your
driver's license please?
Sure.
Mind if i ask why?
Where were you
last night at 6:15?
Home with my wife
and kids.
I got a witness
says you're wrong.
Ollie, what on
earth's the matter?
Oliver?
They arrested
that hit-and-run driver, lil.
Well, i'm glad to hear it
but is that any reason for you
to look white as a ghost?
The man they arrested
was pete radcliff.
Oh, i don't believe that.
Here, read for yourself.
Positively identified
by an eyewitness
at the scene of the accident.
I still can't believe it.
You can tell if a man
would do a thing like that.
Pete just isn't the type.
You don't know him
as well as i do.
Well, i suppose not.
You always have said
he was sneaky-
after your job
and all.
I don't have to worry
about that anymore.
Well, how can you
take satisfaction
out of somebody
else's misfortune?
I don't mean i got any
pleasure out of it.
I mean, i don't have
to worry about things
down at the
office anymore.
Now, thereissomebody
out in that garage.
I am not imagining it
this time.
There's nobody
out there.
Are you going to look?
That noise could have
come from anywhere.
It came
from the garage.
If you're afraid,
i'll call the police.
No- no.
I'll go.
Who's in here?
)
No... no...
ollie?
Ollie!
What?
Some nut's got
his radio on
as high
as it'll go.
It seems to me
like it's coming
from the cassidys'.
Oh?
Hey...
hey, you over there.
People are trying to sleep.
Look, pipe down, will you?
Lil, i...
i don't guess
they hear me.
I better go down there
and talk to them.
And now five minutes
of the late news.
An arrest has been made
in the case of the driver
who yesterday ran away
after fatally injuring
young timmy danvers.
The suspect, peter radcliff
of 509 harboro street,
has been positively identified
by mrs. Muriel hastings,
who witnessed the accident
at the intersection
of third and elm.
Funeral services for the victim
will take place
tomorrow afternoon
at trinity church.
And now five minutes
of the late news.
An arrest has been made
in the case of the driver
who yesterday ran away
after fatally injuring
young timmy danvers.
The suspect, peter radcliff
of 509 harboro street,
has been...
oh, i was going
to surprise you
with breakfast
in bed.
Oh... i'm not
an invalid, lil.
And i'm not
hungry either.
You know, i still think you
ought to call the police.
Why, honey?
Well, to find out
about those prowlers
in the garage.
It's been two
nights running now.
I'll tell you
what i'll do.
When i get back
from work tonight,
i'll put a lock
on that garage door.
Bye-bye.
Oh, ollie,
you better take a raincoat.
Radio said it might rain.
Oh, lil, it's not
going to rain.
Now don't you
stay down there working
if you get tired.
You come on home.
All right, lil,
all right, i will.
Aren't you going
to drive?
Well, i thought i
would take the bus.
Why?
Well, i don't
trust that car.
I mean, it's
falling apart.
Well, you just gonna
leave it in the garage?
No, no. I thought i'd
put an ad in the paper.
Somebody will take
it off our hands.
Bye-bye, lil.
Bye, ollie.
Who's there?
All persons attempting
to conceal criminal acts
involving their cars
are hereby warned:
Check first to see
that underneath that chrome
there does not lie
a conscience,
especially if you're driving
along a rain-soaked highway
in the twilight zone.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org