Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Yes, sir.
I've just arrived in town.
Do you have
accommodations here?
I can give you
a lovely front room
overlooking
the square.
Would you care
to see it?
I am sure it will
be satisfactory.
Yes? Anything wrong?
No, sir.
Mr. Schmidt?
That's what i've written.
Of course, sir.
Of course, what?
I... i just meant, sir...
i just wondered...
it's just that...
what?
You just wondered what?
It's just that...
you remind me
of someone.
Oh?
During the war.
Go on.
There were... there were
s.s. Stationed here.
They used to come to the inn
very often.
I spent the war years
on the russian front-
the panzer division.
Of course.
Was it a prison or
something you had here?
Something of
the sort, sir.
Was it a prison?
A camp, sir.
How's that?
A camp, mr. Schmidt.
A concentration camp.
Really?
Now, that's odd.
For the life of me,
i can't seem to recall
the name of this town.
Sir?
The name of this town!
What is the name of this town?
Dachau, sir.
Dachau.
Of course, dachau.
The camp, it's that group
of buildings
up on the hill, isn't it?
It is, indeed.
But most of us would like it
burned to the ground.
Mr. Schmidt, recently arrived
in a small bavarian village
which lies eight miles
northwest of munich-
a picturesque, delightful
little spot
one time known for its scenery,
but more recently
related to other events
having to do with some of the
less positive pursuits of man:
Human slaughter, torture,
misery and anguish.
Mr. Schmidt,
as we will soon perceive,
has a vested interest in the
ruins of a concentration camp,
for once, some 17 years ago,
his name was gunther lutze.
He held the rank
of a captain in the ss.
He was a black-uniformed,
strutting animal
whose function in life
was to give pain,
and like his colleagues
of the time
he shared the one affliction
most common amongst
that breed known as nazis:
He walked the earth
without a heart.
And now
former s.s. Captain lutze
will revisit his old haunts,
satisfied perhaps
that all that is awaiting him
in the ruins on the hill
is an element of nostalgia.
What he does not know,
of course,
is that a place like dachau
cannot exist only in bavaria.
By its nature,
by its very nature,
it must be one of the populated
areas of the twilight zone.
All right, pigs, up!
Time to greet
the morning.
On your feet, filth!
We have a nice day
ahead of us.
It's snowing.
Temperature's are
slightly below zero.
You will all assemble
in the square.
And dress.
We'll do some
exercises.
I and you!
Detention...
yes, i remember you.
We had some good times
in this building.
Such good times.
You'd like
water, number...
23575?
Is that what you'd like?
You'd like water?
But why should you care?
It's only been five days
since you've been fed.
Five little days!
Good afternoon, captain,
and welcome back.
We've been waiting.
That's right, captain.
We've been waiting
for a long time.
You're... you're becker...
alfred becker.
I remember you.
And well you should.
How well you should,
captain lutze.
You don't look
so bad, becker.
No, as a matter of fact,
you look quite well.
You don't seem to
have changed at all.
That's it...
you haven't changed.
Why, it's been...
it's been
15 or 16 years.
It's been 17 years, captain,
since you and i
last saw each other.
Really?
You're the caretaker
around here?
In a manner
of speaking.
It's odd how
paths cross, and...
we meet again
under somewhat
happier circumstances.
What was that?
It sounded like...
the wind, captain?
Wind?
Perhaps.
Perhaps it was the wind, eh?
Of course.
Of course it was the wind.
It was not the wind.
It was...
it was what,
captain?
Stop calling me captain!
I'm not a soldier anymore.
You never were
a soldier.
The uniform
you wore
cannot be stripped off.
It was part of you, part of
your flesh, part of your body.
It was a piece of your mind.
A tattoo,
captain.
A skull and
crossbones
burned into
your soul.
I was a soldier, becker.
No, captain, you were a sadist.
You were a monster
who derived pleasure
from
giving pain.
Listen to me, becker.
There's no more war.
That's all in the past.
There are no more camps.
It's ridiculous.
It's utterly ridiculous
to dwell on these things.
You did as you
thought best, and i...
i functioned as i was told.
What is
this noise?
Strange that it
should disturb you
so it never
used to, captain.
When your
victims screamed
you weren't
so sensitive.
But now, they
are not screaming.
No, they
are reacting.
They just heard you
offer the apology
for all the monsters
of our times.
"We did as
we were told."
"We functioned
as ordered."
"We merely
carried out
directives from
our superiors."
Familiar,
is it, captain?
It was the nazi theme music
at nuremberg,
the new lyrics
to thegotterdammerung,
the plaintive litany of
the master race as it lay dying.
"We did not do, others did."
Or "someone else did it.
"We never
even knew
that it was
being done."
Or "we did it,
but others told us to."
Captain lutze...
ten million
human beings
were tortured to death
in camps like this.
Men, women, children,
infants, tired old men-
you burned them in furnaces.
You shoveled
them into
the earth.
You tore up
their bodies
in rage,
and now you come back
to your scenes of horror
and you wonder that the misery
that you planted
has lived after you?
There's no point in talking
about this any longer.
I must leave you
now, becker.
I told you i had
to leave, becker!
Why did you come back,
captain lutze?
You changed your name.
You were quite safe down
there in south america.
What could possibly have
brought you back here?
One misses
the fatherland, becker.
One grows nostalgic
for the good old days.
I had thought...
i had hoped that
with the passage of time
sanity would have returned,
people would be willing
to forget the...
little mistakes of the past.
Little mistakes?
Little mis...?
You ask
too much,
captain lutze... far too much.
Why not ask for the earth
to stop revolving in its axis?
Don't ask
the impossible,
captain lutze.
Do not ask forgiveness
from those whom you
have destroyed to a point
past
forgiveness.
But time is short, captain.
We have something
to accomplish here today.
Accomplish?
What?
Your trial.
It is time
for your trial,
captain.
The court is convening
in compound six.
The court?
What is this nonsense?
Is this a joke?
No... no joke, captain.
Your trial.
You will be tried for
crimes against humanity.
By whom?
Who will try me?
You're insane, becker.
You were insane when i used
to string you up and...
when you used to
string me up, captain?
Suspended over
a hot pipe?
Feed me salt water
until my tongue swelled?
Burned me with
cigarette butts
all over
and laughed
when i screamed
to please put
an end to it,
to please have mercy
and kill me?
Your memory's quite good,
captain.
Quite good,
indeed.
Come.
Shall we go?
The court is waiting.
No!
Shall we proceed,
captain lutze?
Please.
Please let me
out of here.
This... this is...
this is inhuman!
I must get
out of here.
out of here!
We inmates of compound six,
dachau concentration camp
versus gunther lutze,
captain, s.s.
That he condemned to death
without a trial
1,700 human beings.
Indictment two:
That he did maim and
torture without provocation
thousands and thousands
of human beings.
No... no...
that he did
deliberately condone
the use of criminal
medical experiments
on women and children.
No!
No! No!
That he did
personally murder at least...
oh... oh, no! No!
No! No!
No!
That he did sign
and put into effect
specific orders
calling for the gassing
and cremating
of one million human beings.
I...
i fell asleep.
No, you were unconscious
for awhile.
I had such a dream.
You had no dream, captain.
Of course i had a dream.
I dreamt... there were people
in this room.
There was a trial.
Ghostly figures.
They are still here.
They have never left.
They walk the buildings
in the square outside.
You didn't bury them
deep enough, captain.
You didn't cover them up
with enough earth,
or perhaps the bullets
were too small a caliber,
or the flames
not sufficiently hot,
or perhaps
there wasn't enough gas.
Becker... becker, who are you?
Did you forget?
The caretaker.
This... this trial...
the trial is over,
captain lutze.
You have been
found guilty.
It's time to pronounce sentence.
You are going
to pronounce sentence?
Is that what you have
in mind now?
You will pronounce sentence,
and then you shall execute
that sentence?
Is that correct?
Pigs!
Filth!
You will all assemble
in the square!
You will pass sentence
on captain lutze!
You will crawl
out of your graves
to see that justice is done!
Where are they?
Where's the judge?
Where's the jury?
Where's
the executioner?
Shall i tell you
where they are?
In your mind.
You've hatched
them out of
your hatred.
You've planned
your vengeance
out of the crazy
quilt of your
imagination
sewed together with
thin little threads
of wishful thinking.
Why didn't i kill you
when i had a chance?
Why didn't
i...?
Becker?
Becker, i did kill you.
I killed you the night...
you killed me
the night the americans
came close to the camp.
You tried to
burn it down,
remember?
You tried to kill everyone
who was left.
In my case, you succeeded.
So i think it would be a waste
of time, captain, wouldn't it-
a waste of your
precious time-
of that little time you have
left to murder me again?
Captain lutze.
Captain lutze, you have
been tried and found guilty
of crimes against humanity.
It is the unanimous
judgment of this court
that from this day on,
you shall be rendered insane.
What is this nonsense?
What is this gibberish?
What is this madness?!
At this gate,
you shot down
hundreds of people
with machine guns.
Do you feel it
now, captain?
Do you feel
the bullets
smashing into
your body?
Do you feel the agony
of tortured lead?
On these posts,
by the anguished hour
you hung up human beings
to die a slow death.
Do you feel
their torture now?
In this room, captain,
the things you did
to human beings
are unmentionable.
How does their
torment feel?
Captain lutze, if
you can still reason,
if there's still any
portion of your mind
that can still function,
take this thought with you.
This is not hatred,
this is retribution.
This is not revenge,
this is justice.
But this is only
the beginning, captain.
Only the beginning.
Your final judgment
will come from god.
Well, he's so full
of sedatives now
he doesn't even know
he's on the earth,
but i want him
in the hospital,
and i want him
strapped to the bed.
Doctor?
What happened to him?
I drove him up here myself
not two hours ago.
He was
all right then.
I have no idea.
I only know that he is
screaming through pain.
No, it's more than pain,
it's agony.
And there isn't a mark on him.
He's insane,
a raving maniac.
But what could happen
in two hours
to turn a man
into a raving maniac?
That, somebody will have
to tell me that.
Dachau.
Why does it
still stand?
Why do we
keep it standing?
There is an answer
to the doctor's question.
All the dachaus
must remain standing-
the dachaus, the belsens,
the buchenwalds,
the auschwitzes, all of them.
They must remain standing
because they are a monument
to a moment in time
when some men decided to turn
the earth into a graveyard.
Into it, they shoveled
all of their reason,
their logic, their knowledge,
but worst of all,
their conscience.
And the moment we forget this-
the moment we cease to be
haunted by its remembrance-
then we become
the gravediggers.
Something to dwell on
and to remember,
not only in the twilight zone,
but wherever men
walk god's earth.
Rod serling, creator of
the twilight zone,
will tell you about
next week's story
after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, we see what will
happen to a world that,
with each passing hour, draws
closer and closer to the sun.
This is a nightmare in depth,
in which we watch
two doomed women spend
their last hours
struggling for survival
against a fiery orb
that moves over the top of
a hot, still, deserted city.
We call it "the midnight sun,"
and we also recommend it
most highly.
This is james arness.
You know, it's only a short hop
fromthe twilight zone
to dodge city andgunsmoke,
saturday nights,
over most of these stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org