Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it
is another dimension-
a dimension of sound...
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Couple of beers,
honey, huh?
Man, listen
to that squeak.
What do you expect?
Well, when we
get paid off,
he'll get all the
oil paste he needs.
If we can find any.
Well, why shouldn't we?
Because they don't
make it anymore.
That's crazy, there's
plenty of b2's around.
Name five.
Will he be all right?
If he don't get hit.
Well, it's no use
glaring at me
you know
he's shot.
That ain't true,
he just needs a little work.
Yeah, a little
$3,000, 4,000 overhaul
with parts they
don't make anymore.
Thanks.
The way
you tell it, pole,
you'd think he was ready
for the scrapheap.
Ain't he?
No, he ain't.
There's plenty of fight
left in maxo.
Well, is he going
to be all right?
Steel, i don't know.
He needs work-
you know that.
The trigger springs
in his left arm
has been rewired
so many times,
it's just about had it.
He's got no protection
on that side.
The eye lens
is cracked.
The leg cables
are worn- they
got no tension.
Even his gyro is off.
Not to mention
the oil paste
he ain't got.
We'll get him some.
Yeah, afterthe fight.
What aboutduring
the fight?
He'll be creaking
around that ring
like a steam shovel.
It'll be a miracle
if he goes two rounds.
It's not that bad, pole.
It's worse-
wait till that crowd
gets a load of battling maxo
from philadelphia.
We'll be lucky to get
our car fare home
much less 500 bucks.
They can't back out
of the contract.
The contract is
for battling maxo-
not this steam
shovel here.
Maxo's going to do all right.
Against a b7?
It's a starter b7- don't even
have the kinks worked out yet.
Aw...
battling maxo-
one-round maxo
the battling
steam shovel.
Will you shut up?
What are you always
knocking him for?
He's been doing all right
for five years.
He'll keep doing okay.
Okay, so he needs a little work,
a little oil paste.
We get the 500 bucks,
we'll get him that stuff-
new trigger spring,
oil paste, eye lens, everything.
Yeah, you'll do okay, boy.
You'll do okay.
Sports item, circa 1974:
Battling maxo, b2, heavyweight,
accompanied by his
manager and handler,
arrives in maynard, kansas,
for a scheduled six-round bout.
Battling maxo is a robot,
or, to be exact, an android,
an automaton
resembling a human being.
Only these automatons have
been permitted in the ring
since prizefighting was
legally abolished in 1968.
This is the story of that
scheduled six-round bout.
More specifically,
the story of two men
shortly to face
that remorseless truth:
That no law can be passed
which will abolish cruelty
or desperate need,
nor, for that matter,
blind animal courage.
Location for the facing
of said truth
a small, smoke-filled arena
just this side
of the twilight zone.
Oh, for...
tip him, huh.
What's the use?
Tip him!
Okay.
You know,
i don't get you, pole.
After seven months,
we finally get a bout
and all you can do
is complain.
Some bout-
maynard, kansas,
the prizefighting
center of the nation.
It's a start, ain't it?
What we earn here,
we can put maxo back in shape.
Huh, if he wins.
Hah!
You know,
i don't get you, pole.
He's our fighter.
Now, why do you keep
writing him off?
I'm a class-a
mechanic, steel,
not a daydreaming kid.
We got us a piece
of dead iron here.
Shh. Somebody will hear you.
Simple mechanics-
maxo will be lucky
to get out of the ring
with his head on.
Wrong. It's a starter
b7, full of kinks.
Just full of them.
Sure, sure.
Come in.
Mr. Nolan?
No, maxwell.
Nolan will be back in
a couple of minutes.
I'm, uh...
i'm kelly.
Battling maxo's
manager.
Oh, yeah.
And this is pole,
my mechanic.
Sit down. Nolan
will be right back.
Oh, thanks, thanks.
Uh... maybe
you heard
about my fighter,
mr. Maxwell.
Hmm?
You heard of my fighter?
Nope.
Oh, he was almost the world's
heavyweight champion once.
I... i used to be
a heavyweight myself.
Before the law was passed,
of course.
Yeah, i used to box under
the name of "steel" kelly.
They called me that because
i never got knocked down.
Not... not once.
Well, going to be
a great fight tonight, huh?
My boy took dimsey the rock
back in '71.
You remember that.
Nope.
It was all over the
east coast newspapers-
boston, new york, philly.
Well, that's where
we're from- philly.
Yeah, biggest upset of the
year- made the headlines.
Mr. Nolan?
Hmm?
Kelly.
I was wondering
if you'd make it.
Your fighter in shape?
Oh, yes, sir, my mechanic here
took him apart
and put him back together
before we left philly.
You're lucky
to get a bout.
We ain't used nothing less
than b4's in almost two years.
Fighter we had got ruined
in a car wreck, though.
Oh, you got nothing
to worry about, mr. Nolan.
My fighther's in top shape.
Hey, you know,
he took dimsey the rock
back in '71.
I just want a good fight.
Oh, you'll get it, mr. Nolan.
You'll get it.
Oh, uh, do you have a ready room
that we can use?
I like to give him
a last-minute check.
Number five, down the hall.
And your bout's at 9:00.
Yes, sir.
Oh, mr. Nolan, uh... i, uh...
you'll get your money
after you deliver a fight.
Yes, sir.
Okay, see you then.
Mr. Maxwell.
Oh, boy.
Five.
I want you to check
him over good, now.
What for?
Did you hear me?
Yeah.
He's going to take
that lousy b7.
Sure he is,
with his teeth.
I wish we'd have gotten
that oil paste.
I told you they wouldn't sell
any here- why should they?
Maxo is probably the only b2
in a thousand miles.
I hear morley's
coming out with
a b9 this year.
Hypertrigger in
both arms and legs.
All steeled aluminum,
triple gyro, triple-
twisted wiring.
Say it'll be able
to stand up after
knockdowns, too.
Well, is he okay?
Sure, he's great.
If this
doesn't blow.
Well, why should it?
It's subpar, i told you
that eight months ago.
Well, we'll get another
one after the bout.
Yeah, another 75 bucks
down the drain.
Look, he's earning us
$500, ain't he?
Go easy on that left.
If it don't work now,
it won't work tonight.
Save it.
Okay, set him so he don't
counterpunch.
Oh, they'll hear him
in the back row.
All right, try the rest.
He'll get more than two punches
thrown at his head.
Try the rest, i said.
Okay, put him
on automatic.
Oh, he's beautiful,
just beautiful.
We got to
put him on defense.
He'll get
chopped to pieces
if we let him move in.
No.
Oh, for...
he's a b2, steel, a b2!
He's going to get
slaughtered anyway
we might as well
save the...
but the contract
calls for him to
be on offensive.
Ah, what's the use?
Come on, let's
test him some more.
What for, he's...
will you just
do like i say?
What'd you do?
I told you not to
mess with that left.
So help you
if you broke it.
Ifibroke it!
Listen, this heap's been
going on borrowed time
for the past
three years.
Don't you talk to me
about breakages!
Open him up.
Sure, sure.
You just find
another mechanic
who could have kept
this steam shovel going
these last few years-
you just find one.
Fix it.
Steel, i...
fix it.
Steel, i can't.
Look, you broke it,
now you fix it!
Let go of me.
It's got to be fixed.
It needs a new spring.
Then get one.
They don't have them here,
don't you understand?
They don't
make them anymore.
Well, if they don't
watch the fights...
what?
If nolan and maxwell
don't watch the bouts.
What are you talk...
what are you, crazy?
You're out of your mind.
You can't do that.
We deliver a fight
or we don't get paid.
Come on, steel,
they'll never let you.
You can't make them
believe that...
listen, you can't do it.
Nobody knows what
maxo looks like.
Only those two guys
in the office saw me,
and if nolan and maxwell
don't watch the bouts,
well, why should
the crowd know?
Steel!
Well, the b2's bleed just
like any of the new ones,
and bruise and
the whole thing.
Look, i can wire
my sister.
She'll send us the
dough to get back east.
Steel, i know a guy in philly
wants to sell a b5 cheap.
We can scurry up
the cash with it.
Steel, use your head,
will you?
It's a b7-
you'll get mangled.
I'm not going to
let you do it, i...
you're going to help me
or i'm going to
beat your brains out.
You'll get killed, steel.
Then i will.
Hey.
You're late.
Where's the owner?
In the audience.
I should've told him.
I would've killed
you if you had.
You'll have to towel
me off between rounds.
Between what round?
You won't last even one.
What do you think
you're going up against,
another fighter?
You're going against
a machine, you big, dumb...
just do like i say, huh?
If i towel you off,
they'll know, won't they?
Look, they ain't seen a
b2 around here in years.
Nolan said so.
Anybody asks, just tell
them it's an oil leak.
Sure, sure.
Well, if it ain't
battlin' maxo!
Scrap iron, scrap iron!
Ladies and gentlemen!
The fifth contest
of the evening-
a six-round heavyweight bout
featuring, from philadelphia,
a b2, battling maxo!
Get that pile of junk
out of here!
Rattlin' maxo, you mean!
And his opponent, our own b7,
the maynard flash.
This is
your last chance.
Get out.
Stay away
from him, then.
Get that tanker a bicycle!
Get that junk pile out of there!
Don't do it.
Kill him, kill him, kill him!
Kill him!
No.
What a fighterheis!
Can you get up?
Steel, can you get up?
All right,
hold it, now.
Hold it.
The robe.
What?
Get the robe.
Hold it down,
that's enough, now.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the winner,
in two minutes and 20
seconds of the first round,
the maynard flash!
Get that pile of tin
out of here!
Rusty pile of junk!
Get out of here!
You big, dumb...
what?
Go get the money.
But...
now.
Oh, you get
the money, huh?
Did you get the money?
Half of it.
What do you mean?
He wouldn't pay five c's
for a one-rounder.
Are you kidding?
Steel, steel, there's
nothing we can do about it.
He's got a bunch
of toughs in there.
We're lucky he
didn't run us
out of town
on the rails.
Okay.
We'll take the bus back.
We'll take the bus
back all the way.
That'll cost us
about 60, 70 bucks.
That'll leave us 200 almost.
We can get a new lens plate,
trigger springs, oil paste.
Yeah, lots of oil paste.
Maxo will be good as new, huh?
We'll get some
good bouts,
maxo, huh?
That's all he needs
is a little overhaul-
oil paste, trigger springs,
eye lens.
Yeah, maxo's going
to be all right.
We'll show 'em
what a good
b2 can do
huh, maxo, right? Right.
Right, pole, huh?
Huh?
Sure, steel.
Portrait of a losing side,
proof positive that you
can't outpunch machinery.
Proof also of something else:
That no matter
what the future brings,
man's capacity to rise to the
occasion will remain unaltered.
His potential for tenacity
and optimism continues,
as always, to outfight,
outpoint and outlive
any and all changes
made by his society,
for which three cheers
and a unanimous decision
rendered from the twilight zone.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org