Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is
another dimension-
a dimension of sound...
a dimension of sight...
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Is this the boy from huong hoa?
That's right, sir.
We were caught
in ambush.
"Multiple shrapnel, abdomen.
Extensive tissue damage."
Well, we can't
touch him here.
We'll have to send
him on back.
What are his chances, sir?
Not very good,
i'm afraid.
"Phillips, pip."
"Pip." that's an odd name.
Well, private pip,
i wish you a long life.
Or, short of that,
someone to mourn.
No, please!
Submitted for your approval,
one max phillips,
a slightly the-worse-for-wear
maker of book
whose life has been as drab
and undistinguished
as a bundle of dirty clothes.
And, though it's very late
in his day,
he has an errant wish
that the rest of his life
might be sent out to a laundry,
to come back shiny and clean,
this to be a gift of love
to a son named pip.
Mr. Max phillips, homo sapiens,
who is soon to discover that man
is not as wise as he thinks-
said lesson to be learned
in the twilight zone.
Yeah.
Whew. It smells
like a brewery in here.
Nice, huh?
Nice, no.
Typical, yes.
You got a visitor downstairs.
Some kid.
Did i ever tell you
i love you, mrs. Feeney?
Often and endlessly.
Well, i do love you.
You're the
queen of women.
Mailman come?
Come and gone.
Anything for me?
Nope.
Nothing...
from the kid?
No. Not this time.
But don't worry about him.
He's all right.
You ain't going to do
yourself any good.
You know that.
An astute observation,
mrs. Feeney.
Oh, i love you and your
astute observations.
I mean it.
I really mean it.
I know.
How 'bout it,
mrs. Feeney?
It's to laugh, isn't it?
Isn't it to laugh?
Yeah.
Hi, mr. Phillips.
Come on in.
Do you want
a cigarette?
I got one.
Got two?
Thank you.
Uh... shady lane lost yesterday.
That's the way
of the world, georgy.
The rich get richer
and the long shots lose.
So what's to do?
You said he had a good chance.
You told me he ran good
on a wet track.
I said that?
Proving how little
i know about horses, huh?
What am i going to do?
I bet every nickel i had on him.
It's funny, george.
Can't think of a thing.
Oh. Big joke.
Lots of laughs.
Where'd you get the money?
Where'd it come from?
I got it.
From where?
From... from
where i work.
"Where you work."
A white-collar heist, huh?
I borrowed it.
You borrowed it,
sure, you borrowed it.
Without their knowing,
you borrowed it.
How right am i?
So what's to do, georgy?
I'll go to jail.
I'll make book on that.
Poor georgy porgy,
one of the breed-
johnny-come-lately wisdom
grafted
onto a second-guesser head.
So i ask again,
georgy,
what's to do?
Max phillips is outside.
I haven't seen
you in five days.
Seems like years.
Where's everybody?
Everybody's gone.
We settled
accounts tonight.
Where were you?
A reasonable question.
I took the wrong bus?
You give me the
wrong story now,
you'll wind up
under the wheels.
1,341 bucks. Hey!
Things are looking up.
It depends on where
you're doing the looking.
From where i sit,
i don't like the view.
I don't
understand you, maxie.
I treat you like
a favorite uncle,
and you double-cross me.
Egad, caught.
Kid by the name
of george reynold
placed a bet with you-
$300, and the horse
doesn't place
and yet, the dough
never got to me.
Why, maxie?
I'll bite. Why?
Because you gave it
back, that's why.
You welshed on me.
And i had to go out
and find the kid
and get my dough back.
I had to rough him
up a little bit
'cause he was stubborn.
That was a lot
of trouble.
For 300 lousy bucks.
Yeah, an awful
lot of trouble.
But you know
how it would be, maxie,
if i let this one pass.
It would be the first
of a long line.
Inside of three months,
i wouldn't have a shirt.
Kid must have
been persuasive.
Ask the kid.
He's been asked.
Look at his face.
If i don't get
that dough back,
i'm going to go to jail.
Don't you understand,
mr. Moran?
I'm going to go to jail.
You're tearing me
to pieces, kid.
Right in here.
You know what's the
matter with you, fella?
You listen to guys
like max phillips.
That was mistake one.
Max phillips never gave
anything away in his life.
How right am i, maxie?
Very right.
A heel
with a robin hood complex,
but thin and short-lived,
georgy porgy.
Remember that the next time
somebody tries to hand you
something for nothing.
Consider the source.
Yeah.
Who?
He's busy now.
All right, all right.
It's your landlady.
Says there's
a telegram for you.
Yeah, mrs. Feeney.
Open it up.
Department of the army?
Well, read it to me.
No.
No...
no, i'm all right, mrs. Feeney.
Thank you.
Pip is dying.
My kid is dying in a...
in a place called south vietnam.
There isn't even supposed
to be a war going on there,
but my son is dying.
It's to laugh.
I swear, it's to laugh.
Hey, max, oh, hey,
kid, i'm sorry.
My kid used to love
amusement parks.
I used to take him
on saturday night.
It ain't like the kid's
dead already.
What i mean is...
when i wasn't too drunk,
or when i wasn't
out conning for you,
i used to take him
to the amusement park.
You know something, moran,
i think you're wrong.
I think i've given
something away.
My kid, pip.
The good part of me.
The clean part.
The part i
was proud of.
Georgy, you
put this back
where it
came from.
Now, maxie, i'm sorry
about your kid, but...
no more! No more!
20 years ago, i should have
spit right in your eye.
20 years ago,
i should have known
how little time a man
has to raise his son.
A little belated
honor now, george.
You get out of here.
Walk as fast
as you can.
Don't look
behind you.
Moran, if your boy is
reaching for a cigarette,
tell him the smoke
bothers me.
If he's reaching
for anything else,
tell him i'll cut
his heart out
before he halfway
reaches it,
then i'll go
to work on you.
Get out. Get out of here!
Move!
I was going to change.
That's a fact, pip.
I was...
i was going to change.
I was... i was going to meet you
when you got off the boat.
So now there's no more bets,
and there's no more bottles...
...but, oh...
there's no more pip either.
Oh, god,
if i...
if i could just talk to him,
you see?
If i could just see him...
if i could just tell him...
all right, my friends,
that'll do it.
Let's see if he'll survive
for an hour.
If he can hang on for that long,
i think he'll hang on for good.
Well, good luck to you...
what was his name? Pip?
Good luck to you, pip.
Pip?
Pip.
Hey, pip.
Hey, pop,
i've been waiting.
Hey, pip!
Hey, pip.
Pip, my boy.
Pop, i've been waiting
for so long.
Hey, pip.
Oh, pip, hey!
Pip.
You're ten years
old again, pip.
How come you're
ten years old again?
That's what i am, pop.
I'm ten years old,
and it's saturday night.
You said to meet you
on the midway,
and i've been waiting.
I was afraid
you weren't going to come.
But i don't understand.
I really don't understand.
Sometimes you don't
show up, pop.
Sometimes when you're sick
or something.
You remember what
i used to say, pip.
You remember?
I remember.
I used to say
hey, pip, who's
your best buddy?
Hey, pop,
you're my best buddy.
Oh!
What do you want to do?
How about some rides, pop,
or some cotton candy?
Sure. Some rides
and some cotton candy.
Anything you want.
Anything at all.
But, pip, you're
ten years old again.
I don't understand that.
It doesn't make
any difference now.
We're here, and
we're together,
and we can go
on some rides.
Sure we can.
Sure we can, pip.
Let's go.
Hey.
Come on, pop.
Whoa!
Pop, help, help.
Ah.
How about this?
Ooh, neat.
Come on, dad.
Work the gun,
not the jaws.
You hit a duck.
Pip, you hit a duck.
You hit it.
Pip.
Who's your best buddy, pip?
You, pop.
You're my best buddy.
What's the matter, pip?
What happened?
Pip, what's the matter?
Pip, listen to me.
Pip.
Pip!
Pip. Pip.
Pip.
You have to understand this.
You have to try and listen
and understand.
Those times
when i wasn't around,
when i was out conning
and being a shill,
or when i was too drunk,
and when i'd drag you from
one rooming house to another...
it doesn't make
any difference now, pop.
It makes a difference, pip.
It does make a difference
because i want you to know
that no man...
oh, listen to me, son.
No man ever, everloved a boy
any more than i love you.
It was because...
well, because i dreamed
instead of did.
I wished and hoped
instead of tried.
But as god is my witness, pip,
i loved you.
See, i wouldn't be able
to put it into words
'cause there isn't any language,
but...
but i love you.
Pip.
You can't leave me now.
You can't go away from me now.
Pip.
Pip. Pip.
Pip!
Pip?
The hour's up now, pop.
I have to go.
I don't belong here.
You see, pop, the hour's up,
and i'm dying.
You... you're just a kid.
You're just a little boy, pip.
You can't die.
I want to spend the rest
of my life being with you
and doing things for you
and giving you things.
That's all that life
means to me anymore.
That's the only thing
that's important.
And, pip, i promise you
that they'll be no more bottles,
and no more con job, nothing,
and no more having to wait
for me.
Pip.
Pip!
I'm dying, pop.
I'm sorry,
but i have to go back.
Why, pip?
Why?
Hey, god?
Hey, god...
i'll make a deal with you.
I give you...
i give you the sodden carcass
of an aging, weak idiot.
I give you me.
All you have to give back
is pip.
Please, god, don't take my boy.
Please.
Take me.
You all right, pip?
Oh, sure.
I'm fine.
It's this leprechaun
grandkid of mine.
She wants to go on
the ferris wheel.
You want to
come with us?
Ah, no, thanks.
I'll just sorta walk around.
You know, this place reminds me
of your father,
god rest his soul.
He used to talk about taking you
here all the time.
Yeah, we sure had
some good times.
Oh, we had some wonderful times.
Look, we'll meet you
over by the ferris wheel
when we get off, huh?
Okay.
Have a good time.
Yeah. You watch
out, huh, pip?
Work the gun, not the jaws.
That's what my pop used to say.
Hey, pop, you're my best buddy.
You always were.
Very little comment here
save for this small aside.
That the ties of flesh
are deep and strong.
That the capacity to love
is a vital, rich
and all-consuming function
of the human animal
and that you can find nobility
and sacrifice and love
wherever you may seek it out-
down the block, in the heart
or in the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next ontwilight zone,
we dabble in the manly arts
with a show called "steel."
Written especially for us
by richard matheson,
this one isn't just
for prizefighting buffs
because the story
is above and beyond
anything remotely involving
the marquis of queensberry.
Rather, it's a tender, touching
and touch analysis
of some very bizarre people.
Lee marvin and joe mantell
take a walk in the twilight zone
next in "steel."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org