Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Oh, great-
just great.
Oh, never- never, never again.
Oh, sure...
you go right ahead
and sleep.
That's right.
Never mind
about how i feel.
I'm an hour late
to work but so what?
No skin off your
pretty little
nose, right?
Oh, boy.
What a wife.
What a doll of a wife.
You could have at least
taken my shoes off, you know.
I didn't want to go
to that stupid party.
"I ought to stay home and read."
"Oh, no, can't do that
and hurt old petey's feelings."
Oh, boy, oh, boy.
I go to work and suffer all day
and she sacks out until noon.
That's fair.
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy...
oh, what next?
Wilma!
Wilma, what have you done
with my razor?
Hey, hey, come on.
Come on, wake up.
Come on, will you?
I'm late.
Wilma- hey.
Never mind
the dramatics.
Just tell me where
you put my razor.
Don't do that.
What's the matter-
you sick?
Who are you?
What?
What are you doing
in my bedroom?
You mean this isn't
the y.m.c.a.?
Honey, will you knock it off?
I'm late- tell me
where you
put the razor.
Darling, i am in no mood
for jokes.
You get out of here.
Wilma... wilma?
How do you know my name?
It's on the marriage
certificate.
Remember?
Mister, i've never
seen you before
in all my life.
Cameo of a man who has just lost
his most valuable possession.
He doesn't know it yet.
In fact, he doesn't even
know about the possession-
because, like most people,
david gurney has never
really thought
about the matter
of his identity.
But he's going
to be thinking about it
a great deal from now on
because that is what he's lost
and his search for it
is going to take him
into the darkest corners
of the twilight zone.
Now, look, whoever you are,
i don't want any trouble,
but if you
don't leave
i'm going to
call the police.
Call the police.
Call the
fire department.
Tell them to bring
an oxygen mask.
There is a man dying.
I'm not bluffing.
If you don't
get out of here
by the time i count
five, i'll call them.
Oh, come on!
Cut it out, will you? One...
i am not amused! Two...
three, four, five.
All right...
give me the...
what is the matter
with you?
Don't touch me.
This is what i call
a delayed reaction!
Two martinis at midnight
and she gets stoned at
10:00 in the morning!
Look, i suggest
you go to bed
and sleep it off.
What are you
going to do?
Change my clothes,
if you don't mind.
Where are my socks?
What in the
name of...?
All right.
Would you mind
telling me
what is going on?
Where are
my clothes?
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
I do not know
what is going on
but i suppose
it's another one
of pete's ridiculous
little gags.
Well, you can tell him
that it didn't come off.
Now, i'm going to work
and when i come home,
you had better have
everything straightened out,
do you understand?
No, no, that's very
thoughtful of you
but i'm not much in
the mood for breakfast.
Thanks, anyway.
Nut.
Good morning, jim.
Good morning.
Hi, jack.
Good morning,
julie, fred.
Yes, sir,
may i help you?
George,
who's that?
That's mr. Cooper.
Would you mind telling me
what mr. Cooper is doing
at my desk?
Beg pardon?
I'm sorry, mr. Kline.
Without better security,
i'm afraid there's nothing
we can do for you.
Who the devil
are you?
How's that?
I said, who the
devil are you
and what are you
doing at my desk?
Yourdesk?
That's right- my desk.
I've had enough of this today.
Get out of that chair.
I'll do nothing of the kind.
Get out or i'll
throw you out.
There's no need
to get excited.
After the morning
i put in!
And would you
be kind enough
to take this
junk with you?
What's the
trouble, sir?
Look, jim, this little joke
has gone far enough.
He says this
ishisdesk.
Step outside, sir,
we can settle this.
There is nothing
to be settled
except i would like my nameplate
back and my picture.
I'm afraid i'll
have to insist.
I'm not budging.
Yes, you are.
Jim, you get your hand off me
or i'll see to it
that you're fired.
We'll talk
about it outside.
Put your hands up, mister.
What?
Put your hands up.
Has everybody gone crazy?
Walk three paces
in front of me.
Don't cause any trouble
or i'll have to shoot.
Move!
Call the police, sir.
George,
what is this?
All right,
keep moving.
Wilma!
Will you tell
these people
who i am?
Is that the man?
Yes.
What's your
name, mister?
Ask her.
She doesn't
know.
She doesn't know?!
After 11 years
of marriage?
Mrs. Gurney,
allow me
to introduce
myself.
I'm david
gurney-
your husband-
remember?
Don't stand
there staring
like idiots.
That's
who i am-
david gurney.
Jim, now,
please, will
you tell them?
Look, i've worked
with this man
for four years.
Now, tell them!
Julie.
Fred.
George, will
you tell them?
Tell them who i am!
All right,
let's go.
Wait a minute!
You say i'm not
david gurney, right?
I'll prove it
to you.
Let's see what you
have to say to this.
My driver's license
and credit cards-
what have you done with them?!
Wait a minute!
I'm david gurney.
I'm david gurney!
I don't care what you say,
i know who i am.
Mister...
gurney! Gurney!
David andrew gurney!
There's no need
for excitement...
oh, of course not!
All of a sudden,
everyone's telling me
i don't know who i am,
and you say there's no
reason for excitement.
Well, what do you expect
me to do, relax?!
No, i suppose not.
I know it must be
quite a shock,
but, look, if we're
to help you, mister...
you've got to face facts.
You see, this man
you think you are-
he doesn't really exist...
except in your mind.
Whether whole cloth
or from people you've met,
you've invented him.
There is no david
andrew gurney.
You're lying.
Oh, come, come. Why?
I don't know.
Why? Why should i...?
But you are;
you've got to be.
Now, listen, a man
doesn't live 35 years
knowing who he is,
and then, just because he's
lost his driver's license...
no, no, no, no.
It wasn't just that.
This woman, uh,
miss berenson-
the woman you think
you're married to...
knowi'm married to,
and her name isn't
berenson, it's gurney!
I see you're gonna
require more proof.
Well, that can
be arranged.
Come with me, please.
Oh, uh, you haven't met
your fellow patient.
That's winston churchill.
So he thinks.
Poor chap...
no one knows
who he really is.
Now, let me see how
i can prove it to you.
The phone- let me
use the phone.
Of course.
What number?
Klondike 5-2131.
Let me have an
outside line please.
Dr. Koslenko.
Hello, pete?
It's dave.
Pete, it's dave gurney.
Well, how do
you like that?
He's my best friend.
We went to
school together.
More?
Yes.
Yes, call
klondike 5-3472.
Seven, two.
Ask for mrs. Gurney.
I'd like to speak with
mrs. Gurney, please.
Just a moment, please.
Hello, mom?
Oh, thank god,
thank god.
Mom...
this is dave.
What's the matter, mom?
Don't you recognize my voice?
It's dave.
Your son.
Mom... mom, now stop it.
Don't do this to me, please!
Forgive the
call, please.
It was
a mistake.
Thank you.
You are david
andrew gurney.
You live at 2457
lime rock avenue.
That's right.
You're sure?
Yes, i'm sure!
Do you have
a telephone?
Certainly, i have a phone.
It's likely
that your number
would be listed in the
directory, isn't it?
Yes.
You'll notice
that that is...
the current edition.
Go ahead.
Now do you
believe me?
I don't know.
Maybe i should,
but i...
all right.
All right, if i'm
not david gurney,
then who am i?
That's what we're going
to try to find out.
In other words,
i'm crazy,
like that guy who
thinks he's churchill.
Is that it?
Let's just say-
mentally
disturbed.
I know it's very
difficult to believe,
but looking at
it logically,
there isn't
any other
explanation.
Sometime last night,
you had what
is known as
a total loss
of orientation.
You entered miss
berenson's house...
no, no.
No, no, no!
That's what you
want me to believe,
but it isn't true
because in spite of
everything, doctor,
i know who i am!
Either i am crazy
or somebody's going to
an awful lot of trouble
to blot me out.
Now, now, now...
why would anyone want
to blot you out?
How should i know?
But whoever or
whatever it is-
they can rig
every phone book
and they can pay off
everyone i know
but they can't get
inside my mind.
And i'll tell you
something else-
they can't think
of everything.
And what does
that mean?
Just that.
A man's life
is made up
of a million
details.
Some of those
details are private.
I've gone places,
i've done things
that i've never
told to anyone-
not even my wife.
Of course...
i'm sure that's
quite true.
Now, suppose we go
back to your room
and you think about it.
Oh, no-you
think about it
because i'm
going to find
one of those
details- now!
Sorry- got to get away.
Hey, hey!
Wait a minute.
Before you say anything,
give me a drink.
Anything in particular?
The usual.
Huh?
The...
the usual.
Irish whiskey.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Sam...
look at me.
Okay, i'm looking
at you.
Who am i?
How many guesses
do i get, huh?
No, think, sam.
Who comes in here
every friday night
for the last
three years?
My wife.
Who else?
A lot of people
come in here.
What about...
what about
dave gurney?
Who?
That's it, huh?
They got to him, too.
All right.
But how?
I kept this place a secret.
I never told anybody about it.
Would you like another drink?
Yeah.
Sam...
sam-
what would you do
if all of a sudden
everybody started telling you
you weren't you.
What?!
I mean, everybody-
your wife, your friends.
Everyone suddenly
couldn't recognize
you anymore.
They were saying
sam baker didn't exist.
I'd tell them to switch brands.
But you wouldn't
believe them?
Give me another one.
I think you've
had enough.
Oh...
i've had more
than enough, sam.
How do you
know my name?
Because we're friends.
Your wife's
name is pearl.
Your kids' names
are joey and linda.
You live in white oak.
You used to be a prizefighter-
"powerhouse baker."
Your picture's
on the wall
right next to
harry grebb.
Wait a minute...
are you all right?
I think so.
Keep your fingers
crossed, sam.
I may have found
that little detail
they overlooked.
What's the number again?
6708-777.
You sure?
Positive.
I lost the slip
but i remember
that number
because of
the four sevens.
Maybe your
wife's got it.
She doesn't know
it was taken.
I was going
to surprise her.
You sure it
was the 14th?
Yes, on a sunday.
We were at the zoo.
Oh, i'm sorry.
Hey, wait a minute.
Is that a seven
or a one?
Seven.
Is that it?
Yes.
Yes, that's it.
Are you okay, mister?
Yeah...
yeah, i'm fine.
Okay, that'll be $1.75.
Hey, wait a minute!
You owe me money.
Well, doctor,
what brings you here?
I might ask you
the same question.
To elude us, you
shouldn't have left
that stolen
car downstairs.
This man owes
me money.
Oh...
$1.81 to be exact-
for proof that
i'm not crazy.
I told you they couldn't
think of everything.
I suppose you
found a signature
or a receipt...
but that's not proof
because i could've signed
a signature anytime...
right.
...or had a card
printed up,
or faked a
driver's license.
Right.
But what about a photograph,
doctor?
What about a photograph of me
holding hands
with a girl who claims
she never laid eyes on me
before this morning?
How would you explain that?
Take it out and look at it.
Then think up some answers.
Well?
But i...
i saw her.
Look, look you saw her.
You saw my wife.
Oh, listen,
mister,
you didn't show
me nothing.
But i tell you she was there.
We were together!
No.
We were together.
We were together...
we were together.
We were together.
Together, together.
Together... together...
we were togeth... er...
dave?
Dave, honey, wake up.
Wake up, honey.
What?
Oh.
Oh, wilma, wilma.
Oh, wait a minute.
Let me get this
junk off my face.
Don't go away.
Oh, don't worry.
I won't.
What's the
matter, honey?
You sound
terrible.
Did you have
a nightmare?
Oh, baby, i hadthenightmare...
the granddaddy of them all.
That'll
teach you
to mix scotch and martinis.
Yeah,
that'll teach me all right.
I'm sorry i
didn't put you
in your
pajamas, honey
but i was
a little
out of things
myself.
You forgive me?
Yeah, sure, sure.
Well, you're in a rare mood.
Honey, what's wrong?
Are you ill?
Dave, why
are you
looking at me
like that?
Dave, honey?
Dave...?
A case of mistaken identity or
a nightmare turned inside out?
A simple loss of memory
or the end of the world?
David gurney may never
find the answer
but you can be sure
he's looking for it
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling, creator of
the twilight zone,
will tell you about next week's
story, after this message.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, we take a trip
through a galaxy
to few million light-years away
from your collective
television screens.
We'll land
on an uncharted asteroid
and then undergo an experience
designed for goose bumps
and palpitations
because, in the twilight zone,
next time out,
you'll see that monsters come in
all assorted sizes and shapes.
I hope we whetted your appetite,
and if so,
we'll see you next week.
Our show is called
"the little people."
Every litter bit hurts,
so think before you throw.
Keep america clean
and beautiful.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org