Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Now, you listen to me, baby...
this is ace talking here-
your old loverboy, ace.
We've been together
a long time, you and me,
and i've been real good to you,
haven't i?
I fed you, i took care of you,
gave you everything you wanted,
right, right?
Okay. Well, i think it's about
time you started paying off.
Oh, you m...
all right.
All right, sweetheart,
you've had your fun.
Now let's get down
to serious business...
although, i'm warning you,
you pay off, or you get out!
Only kidding, only kidding.
Kitty, another
quarter.
You ought to take
it easy, ace.
You're going to blow
a gasket one of these days.
That's very funny,
very funny.
Now, wait a second.
I'll flip you
double or nothing
for the meal-
what do you say?
You sure like to get kicked
around, don't you?
Never mind
what i like.
Double or nothing-
is it a deal?
Okay.
All right, a
quarter, kitty.
Look, ace, do you
always have to gamble...
come on, will
you, come on!
I can't keep on
losing forever.
You call it.
Heads.
Hey, let me see it.
Heads. Thanks.
That's a lucky quarter.
Mind if i borrow it?
Hey!
Oh... here's
your quarter.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
You ba...
it ain't fair, jimbo.
It just ain't fair.
Maybe your luck
will change, ace.
Yeah, maybe next time,
i'll get electrocuted.
Where you going?
Home and to bed.
Any objections?
No, honey, i wouldn't
blame you if you quit.
I can't; you owe me
three months' salary.
Good night,
big-time operators.
Night, kitty.
When you two going
to get married?
On what?
And with what?
I got a little
saved up.
You can use that.
Well, a little
ain't enough.
Girl like kitty
deserves the best,
and the best comes high.
Jimbo!
Jimbo, there's people
in there!
Come on, jimbo,
lend a hand, will you?
Portrait of a man who thinks
and thereby gets things done.
Mr. Jimbo cobb might be called
a prime mover,
a talent which has to be seen
to be believed.
In just a moment,
he'll show his friends and you
how he keeps both feet
on the ground
and his head
in the twilight zone.
They took them
to the hospital.
They'll be okay.
The doc says it's just a few broken bones,
nothing serious.
How'd you do
it, jimbo?
Do what?
You know.
This business of
the car up and down
and then... and the
sparks in the...
how, jimbo?
Come on, ace,
let's forget it, huh?
All right.
All right, if you
want to keep secrets.
Okay, it's your business.
Ace?
Yeah.
I'll tell you.
I can't exactly
explain it, ace, but...
well, you see...
i guess you might say
it's a power i got.
I can move things around
just by thinking.
What?
I know it sounds stupid,
but i can.
I don't know how come or why
or anything, but i can.
Like since when?
Well, like
since always.
I never thought
there was anything special
about it or anything.
I thought everybody
could do it,
you know, like breathing.
I guess i was wrong.
Oh, yeah...
um, how come i never seen
you doing this before?
Well, i had
to give it up.
Why?
Oh, you know,
it got me in a lot of trouble
in school,
and i started getting these
real bad headaches after-
like now.
Uh... could you do this again?
Sure.
Like right now?
Yeah, but i...
all right, show me.
I got a headache. Come
on, come on, will you?
Come on, show me.
Come on.
Now, do something
to this bed.
Go ahead.
Could you make
something move
that's a little
smaller,
like a quarter maybe?
Sure. The smaller,
the easier.
All right.
Give me a quarter,
will you?
Now, make that
come up heads.
You...
give me a seven.
Done!
You...
honest to...
oh...
what's the matter?
Oh, you big
stupid jerk!
We've been beating
our brains out
for four years working
that crummy joint.
We could've been
living like kings!
We could? How?
You'll see.
Honest, when i think
of all the dough that i...
hello, kitty, kitty.
Can you get
ready to go
on a short trip in
about ten minutes?
Well, never mind-
i'll explain
the whole thing
to you later-
but you don't
have to pack.
It's a short trip,
and be ready by 1:00.
All right.
$100 on number eight.
$100? Ace, that's
all we've got.
Shh. Take it easy, kitty.
Eight!
Come on, give
me that thing.
What's the limit?
$200. all right, 200 on four,
200 on black, and
200 on an even.
Ace, take it easy.
Shh, please.
200 on even,
black and four.
200 four,
black and even.
Okay.
There we go.
Four...
black and even.
Shovel it in, kid,
shovel it in.
Winner.
Yeah!
All right...
seven again.
Get down with this
lucky shooter, folks.
Same bet, same bet.
Get down with this
lucky winner, folks.
Come on, baby.
Seven
- a winner, winner, winner, winner.
Come on, keep going, baby.
A winner-
a frontline winner.
All right,
three... three...
sweetheart,
don't you think
you ought to quit now?
Your luck's bound
to change.
What do you mean,
change?
Jimbo and i
worked out a system,
ain't we, jimbo, huh?
And a two.
Double three.
There you are!
Have we got
a system, huh?
Ace, i got to quit.
My head's
killing me.
Are you out
of your mi...
okay, jimbo, okay.
Okay, we'll cash in
these chips, huh?
And then you get
an aspirin,
and you lie down
somewhere.
You'll feel 100% better.
Okay, pay off,
will you?
Boy.
Cigars, cigarettes,
chewing gum...
honey... i'll have
some of those.
Oh, i'm afraid
i can't change a bill
this size, sir.
Who asked you to?
Come on, jimbo.
Boy! Where's that... boy?
Uh, uh, get those boxes
and be very careful with 'em.
All right, junior.
Come on, jimbo.
You're going to take it easy,
feel like a million dollars.
A million dollars...
well, this is
more like it.
Oh, ace,
it's gorgeous.
Beautiful!
Not bad,
not bad at all.
But, ace,
i don't think we should...
forget it.
Junior, go out
and buy yourself
a pair
of roller skates.
And, junior,
uh, pick up
some shaving cream,
toothbrush, you know,
all that jazz, huh?
Jimbo, how do you feel?
Ace, i'm tired.
I got to sleep.
Sleep? What's
the matter with you?
We're going to do the town,
have some fun.
We just got started.
Come on.
Well, i'll see you boys
in the morning.
Now, look, don't
you fold up on me.
Honey, will you get him
some aspirin?
Oh, yes, i've got some
right here.
I'll get some water.
Come on, come on.
I'll fix your head.
There you are.
Ace?
Yeah.
I can't do it no more.
Can't do what?
It's wrong, ace.
It's cheating.
Cheating's wrong.
Jimbo, you're right.
You mean it?
We're going to quit?
Sure, jimbo.
We're going to quit.
Ace, you promise?
Sure, kit, sure, after
just one more time.
Come here.
There you are, jimbo.
Okay?
One more time? Is it okay?
Well, okay.
One more time.
All right, you take it easy
and rest tonight,
and tomorrow
we'll fracture them.
Kitty, you and me,
we're going out,
and we're going to
tear the town apart!
Ace, let's go
home right now.
Home? What's
the matter with you?
This is
my big chance.
But i don't
want to take it.
You've been very lucky.
Think of all
the money you've won-
enough to last you
for the rest of your life.
Can't you leave well
enough alone, honey?
Well, well enough isn't good enough for me.
Don't you understand?
By tomorrow, i'll
have enough dough
to own this state.
You understand that?
The whole state.
Aceville, u.s.a.
Ace, you're sick.
Honey, i've never been
healthier in my life.
I want you to know that,
by tomorrow night,
i'll be able
to get you...
wait a minute.
Where you going?
Back home!
Look me up when
you're through
playing
little caesar.
What's the matter with her?
You've been ignoring her all night.
Ain't very polite, ace.
Well, i've been busy.
A man should never be that busy.
Why don't you go after her?
Kitty's worth more
than all the money in the world,
isn't she?
Yeah. Yeah, she is.
Well, then go after her.
Kitty?
Kitty, will you be reasonable? Will you?
This is my big chance.
Are you going
to gamble tomorrow?
Yes, but...
well, good-bye then.
But, kitty...
kitty!
Cigars?
Cigarettes?
No. I don't...
anything wrong, sir?
No.
Nothing at all.
What's your name?
Sheila.
Sheila, how
would you like
to quit this crummy job
and work for me?
Doing what?
Spending money, hmm?
Come on.
Here's a little salary
in advance- a grand.
When do i start?
Right now.
We'll have a ball.
Something wrong here?
Are you the manager?
That's right.
Well, i'd like to hire
your cigarette girl
for the evening.
Would it be all right?
Why, yes, yes. I believe
it'll be all right.
I thought it would.
Well, come on, sweetie.
We'll have...
oh, one more thing.
Who's the biggest
gambler in town?
Well, let's see...
and i mean big.
No limits.
Well, i believe mr. Nolan is
visiting with us this week.
Phil nolan?
Right.
Well, you tell phil nolan
that ace wants to see him.
Ace?
Ace... ace larsen.
That's me. I live here.
You tell him to call me
tomorrow at the hotel,
and bring plenty
of lettuce-
and i mean this
kind of lettuce.
Okay?
Okay.
Live a little.
We're going to tear
this town apart, honey!
What do you say?
Great, but will you
wait till i get dressed?
All right. But not too much.
Hello.
Yeah, he's here.
Just a minute.
Who's calling?
Mr. Nolan?
Just a minute, mr. Nolan.
Ace.
Come on. Leave me alone,
will you?
Ace, telephone.
It's mr. Nolan.
Nol...?
Uh... um...
hi, phil.
Good to hear from you, baby.
This is ace larsen.
From where?
From here. From nevada.
Now, wait a minute, phil.
Wait a minute.
That's not a nice way to...
all right, so you never
heard of me. You will.
Now, you listen to me, buster.
I got $200,000 in this room,
and i'm hot for a game.
I'm ready to bet any part of it.
Now, of course,
if the stakes
is too high for you,
i can always call somebody else.
Ah. Well, that's better.
All right. Room 208, right away.
And, uh... phil, uh...
bring your friends.
Yeah.
Ace, uh...
that mr. Nolan...
he's from chicago,
isn't he?
Yep.
Isn't he a gangster?
Yeah, he's a gangster.
So what?
I hear he's awful mean.
What are you
worrying about?
You see, when
it comes to gambling,
these guy have
their own code of honor.
What about kitty?
I can't hear you, jimbo.
I can't hear you at all.
You
larsen?
No, sir. My name's cobb.
Come on in, phil.
I'm ace larsen.
Who's your friends?
Let's see
the stuff.
Jimbo, he wants
to see the stuff.
Well, i'm going
to have some breakfast
while you're counting it.
Would you want something?
Cup of coffee maybe, glass of juice.
I never gamble
on a full stomach.
This is
ace larsen.
I want room service, and i want...
ace.
A-c-e. Ace
larsen. Yeah.
Uh... your boys want anything?
They don't eat.
They don't eat?
Okay.
Suppose we start off
with, uh... oh...
ten grand.
Ten grand?
What's the matter?
Too high?
No, ten
grand's fine.
Now, let's...
suppose we play
with my dice, huh?
Well, be my guest.
Happy?
Now a little natural...
a natural...
and a seven
it is.
Well, what
do you know?
Starting off
great.
Uh... suppose
we let it ride?
You're covered.
You know, 11 would be nice now.
Just a little old 11.
11!
Seven.
Natural!
A point.
Two fours.
And two fours
it is.
Some say that you can't
make a mistake...
go ahead.
But remember
this, larsen.
People cheat
on me just once.
Understand?
Sure. Now that
we got that straightened out, am i covered?
You're covered.
Well, i guess this is
my lucky day, huh, fellas?
Hi.
Hi, sheila,
baby.
You ready to take me
to lake mead?
Who's the dame?
My good luck charm.
My sweetheart. Any objections?
Sheila, honey,
these are
some friends
of mine.
We're playing a little penny ante game,
but stick around. It
won't take much longer.
Ace, there's something i...
now, look, this is getting
to be a drag.
What do you say
we separate the men
from the boys, huh?
So what do you say we...
we shoot the works?
Jimbo?
What's the matter,
nolan?
You're supposed to
be a big operator.
You chicken?
All right,
larsen.
Go ahead. Shoot
the works.
You're covered.
And where's the dough?
My credit's good.
Sure, it is, phil.
Sure, it is.
Lot of fun, huh, honey?
Right?
Win a million,
lose a million.
Just like that. Right? Okay...
11 is the number.
Ace, i...
you got it?
11... and this is it.
Ace...
now, don't bother me.
Ace, listen. I...
11, 11, 11!
And there it is!
Tough luck,
trouper.
Huh?
You got
nerve, pal.
I like that.
Next time
you want
to play a little
game, trouper,
give us a call.
Ace, uh...
look, i'm sorry,
but i was
trying to tell you.
I... something happened.
I lost the power.
I guess a fuse
blew out.
You're not mad at
me, are you, ace?
I mean, i
couldn't help it.
You mean we're
not going to lake mead?
Well, he...
he blew his fuse.
You blew...
you blew a fuse.
You sure you don't
want to stop them?
What are
you talking...?
Who needs that hunk
of junk anyway?
That's strictly
for suckers.
Come on. Out, out,
out, out, out.
Go on, you
one-armed bandit.
Go rob somebody else
for a change.
Um... kitty... kitty,
look, i was thinking,
you know, now that that
thing's out of here,
i bet you
that jimbo and me
could, you know,
we could
pull enough money
each month to...
after what we,
you know...
will you marry me?
Why don't
you be quiet!
I'm proposing,
for crying out loud.
Jimbo, do you
have a quarter?
Call it.
Heads?
All right, mr. Larsen,
iwillmarry you.
Oh, baby.
Some people possess talent,
others are possessedbyit.
When that happens,
the talent becomes a curse.
Jimbo cobb knew
right from the beginning.
But, before ace larsen
learned that simple truth,
he had to take a short trip
through the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, mr. Charles beaumont
and mr. William idelson
deliver a story on your doorstep
with the title
"long distance call."
It's uniquely
a flesh-and-fantasy tale
involving a small boy,
a toy telephone
and the incredible faith
of a child.
I hope you're around next week
at the usual time-
which, depending
on where you are, varies-
and in the usual place-
the one that never varies-
the uncharted regions
of the twilight zone.
Be sure and see
the colgate-palmolive company's
new comedy show,
my sister eileen,
wednesday night
on many of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org