Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Yes, sir.
Yes, i'll send you a check
first thing in the morning.
Right.
Need some help?
No, thanks.
I enjoy kicking around
broken-down chairs.
It's good for
the circulation.
Oh? Yours
or the paper's?
Very funny.
Come on, now, doug,
things aren't that bad.
Don't be such
an old gloom cookie.
I am not now,
nor have i ever been
a "gloom cookie."
Thanks.
Oh, hi, andy.
I'd like to talk
to you, mr. Winter.
He's tired, andy.
Can't it wait
till tomorrow?
It's all
right, jackie.
What's on your
mind, andy?
Well, sir, the...
the fact is, i...
well, i...
that help, andy?
Yeah, thanks.
Mr. Winter, i...
i hate to have
to tell you this,
but i'm resigning.
All right.
When?
Right away.
I mean, i know
it ain't your fault,
but it's eight weeks
since i've been paid.
Oh, i understand.
I really hate to do it,
mr. Winter,
but a man's got to eat.
Andy praskins,
you ought to be
ashamed of yourself!
Jackie...
the best boss
a man could work for.
Who said that, andy?
Who said it?
I did, miss benson,
and i meant it.
And this is the
way you repay
the best boss a
man could work for?
By quitting him
just when he needs
you the most?
I said i hate to do it.
Well, then why do it?
I mean, just because
of a little setback...
it ain't just a
little setback,
and you know it.
And so does
mr. Winter.
This paper is finished,
miss benson.
It was finished
the minute
thegazettemoved
into town.
How you gonna buck a syndicate
like that?
They can pour thousands
of dollars into that operation,
lose every penny
and still not feel it.
They've got a half
dozen reporters,
a morning edition,
a night edition.
I ask you,
how you gonna lick that?
You're not.
Right. So i
say, join 'em.
You mean you are going
to work forthem?
Yes, miss benson,
beginning tomorrow.
And if you're smart...
get out of here, andy.
Just get out of here.
Andy.
Yes, mr. Winter?
Good luck.
Thank you, sir.
I still say
you're the best.
Good-bye.
Oh, boy!
That's gratitude
for you.
After all the times
you've stayed up
until midnight
correcting
his mistakes.
Jackie...
the days off
you gave him.
Jackie...
well, can't you
ever get mad
at anything around
here except chairs?
That wasandy praskins
who walked out.
Our linotype operator.
Don't you
realize that?
I know.
Well, then why didn't
you do something?
Do something?!
I'd do anything i could
to save this place,
anything...
but andy's right.
It's too late.
I'm through.
Oh, no.
Oh, don't say that.
Please don't say it.
Why, this was
your dream, doug.
Well, right now,
i'm... i'm awake.
Miss benson,
why don't you go home?
I've got a lot
of work to do.
Oh, doug, let
me just stay.
You heard me.
You go on home.
I'm a very busy man.
Well, what are
you going to do?
Right now, i'm
going to see you
to the front door.
Will you be all right?
Yeah, sure.
It's not the end of
the world, you know.
Call me if you need me,
will you?
Young man.
Might i trouble
you for a match?
Yeah. Sure.
It's a lovely night, isn't it?
Lovely spot, too.
Smell the pines.
It's a pity
you have to leave it all.
What do you mean?
Well, you were about
to commit suicide, weren't you?
That's none of your business.
I agree.
If a man wants
to do away with himself,
i say that's his decision,
nobody else's.
But i do think you ought
to make a good job of it.
This looks very uncertain
to me, frankly.
You might end up with nothing
more than a head cold.
I certainly
wouldn't want
to risk it.
By the way,
did you find a match?
No, i... i don't have one.
Well, doesn't matter.
Good night.
Aren't you
going to jump?
Why, do you want
to watch?
No, heavens no.
But i was
just thinking,
if you aren't
going to,
perhaps you
wouldn't mind
giving me a
lift into town?
Now, i don't want you
to change your plans
on my behalf, you understand.
Yeah.
Come on.
Well, thank you.
Wait a minute.
I found a light.
Take away a man's dream,
fill him with whiskey
and despair,
send him to a lonely bridge,
let him stand there
all by himself,
looking down
at the black water,
and try to imagine the thoughts
that are in his mind.
You can't, i can't...
but there's someone who can,
and that someone is seated next
to douglas winter right now.
The car is headed
back toward town,
but its real destination
is the twilight zone.
Thank you very much.
Young man,
i hope you're
not planning
to drink alone.
I was...
unless, of course,
you'd like to join me.
I'd be delighted.
Well...
feeling better?
Not yet.
Hi, mr. Winter.
Oh, hi, molly.
Give me a martini,
will you?
Make it a double.
The same.
Uh, mr. Winter,
could i see you for a second?
What about?
Well, um...
oh, yes.
Yes, the tab.
I'm sorry, but mr. Foster says
that from now on,
it's got to be cash.
Please, allow me.
Now, molly, run and get
those drinks, will you?
And tell mr. Foster
to make them strong.
Will you do that?
Run, girl, run.
Mm!
That's a lush
one, isn't it?
Full of fire,
too, i'll wager.
I wouldn't know.
You wouldn't? Pity.
Uh, thank you very much
for the drink, mister, uh...
smith.
Um, my name
is douglas winter.
Thedouglas winter,
the editor?
Ex-editor.
Wait, why "ex"?
It's a long, sad story,
mr. Smith.
You wouldn't be interested.
Oh, but i would.
I would indeed.
You see, you are the reason
that i've journeyed to dansburg.
You must be a creditor.
No, not yet,
anyhow.
No, the fact is,
i'm a newspaperman.
I was hoping to secure
a position with your paper.
I'm sorry.
If you'd have called,
i'd save you a trip.
Why?
Thecourieris dead,
mr. Smith.
L-l-i don't
understand.
There's not much
to understand.
The bragg syndicate
opened a paper here
called thegazette,
and they murdered us.
Ah, i see.
No, uh, keep it,
my dear,
in payment
for your lovely smile.
Thank you, sir.
She moves fast
for a big one.
Mr. Winter...
do you suppose
thegazettecould use
a good linotype operator?
I doubt it.
They just grabbed
my best man today.
Why?
That's my specialty,
along with the reporting.
You mean you're a reporter
and a linotype operator?
Absolutely.
If i may dispense
with false modesty,
i'd count myself
among the best in both fields.
Perhapsthebest.
You were about
to say something.
Well, then
i'll say it.
You put me to
work at once,
ithinkwe can
save thecourier.
How can i put you
to work?
I can't even pay
my bar tab.
Well, that's simple.
I'll waive salary until
you're in the black.
That's crazy.
I might never be
in the black.
Well, it's a chance,
but it's better
than anything
you have now.
Are you sure you know how
to operate a linotype machine?
Mr. Winter,
that's like asking paganini
if he can play the fiddle.
I'm a virtuoso.
Show me.
With pleasure.
Good night, molly.
Good night, mr. Winter.
Doug!
Jackie.
Doug, where have you been?
I've been calling your home
all eve... ning...
oh, uh, jackie,
i'd like you to
meet mr. Smith.
Uh, this is
miss benson,
my most valuable
employee.
Secondmost valuable,
mr. Winter.
Secondmost valuable.
Very good,
mr. Smith.
Let's see how
long it takes you
to copy this
lead story.
Right over there.
Certainly.
Who is he, anyway?
I don't know.
Well, it's not the latest model,
but it's agoodone.
Now...
ah! Listen to it hum.
Kindly hold
that cigar for me.
Keep it burning.
Well, if he doesn't play
chopin'spolonaise,
i'll be disappointed.
May i have my cigar back?
Oh... yes.
Put it in my mouth, please.
I may have to make
a few modifications,
but on the whole,
it's infinecondition.
A little stiff, perhaps.
What's the matter?
Matter?
Why did you quit?
Finished.
That's impossible!
See for yourself.
Mr. Smith...
why would a man with your talent
want to work for a hick paper
like thecourier?
Call it a challenge.
Well, miss benson,
are you impressed?
No. I'm amazed.
It's understandable.
Well, i must confess
that this is not
my true vocation.
It isn't?
No. I'm a reporter.
Oh.
Some people have a green thumb.
I have a green nose.
Wherever there is news,
this old nose smells it.
I'm afraid there isn't
much news to smell
around dansburg,
mr. Smith.
There will be.
Well, am i hired?
You would be,
if i had a paper.
But i haven't got one,
and there's no use
kidding myself.
This all belongs
to the banks
and the finance companies,
and they're ready
to collect.
Aw. How much would
it take to pay them off?
Oh, roughly $4,861.23.
Oh... i might be able
to manage that.
Uh...
you want to
make us a loan?
Perhaps.
Would you excuse us
for a minute, please?
What do you think?
Well, if he'd made
that offer ten minutes ago,
i'd have thought
he was kidding or crazy,
but now l-i don't know.
I mean, what's in it
for him?
Beats me.
But i'm going
to give it a go.
Yeah, but there's
something...
it's a chance to
stay in business!
After all, what
have i got to lose?
That's right.
What have you got to lose?
Gives you a funny feeling,
doesn't it?
"Paid in full."
Who but that old rooster
would carry $5,000 cash
around in his pocket?
Well, speak
of the devil.
Excuse the interruption,
but how long
would it take you
to get an edition
onto the streets?
We're not due out
until 4:00.
I mean, an
extraedition.
A couple of hours
on a short run.
Be a hassle, though.
Would it be
worth the hassle
if you could beat the
gazetteto a scoop?
Depends on the scoop.
Here.
Holy...
10:20?
Well, that was
only a half an hour ago!
I'll check it out.
You doubt my
veracity, hmm?
It's standard operating
procedure, mr. Smith.
You ought
to know that.
Uh, let me speak
to mr. Underwood, please.
Well, never mind.
Maybe you can help me.
We just had a report
of a robbery...
thank you.
Okay, let's go to work!
Yes, sir.
I told you
i had a nose for news!
Hey, extra!
Big bank robbery today!
Extra! Read all about it!
Extra!
Read about the
big stick-up!
Robbers take
$15,000!
Read about it!
Extra! Extra!
Robbers take
$15,000!
Here you go, sir.
Thank you.
Get your extra!
Read about today's bank robbery!
Read about...
thank you, sir. There you are.
Read all...
there you are.
Read all about today's
bank robbery!
There you are, sir.
Follow me.
I don't believe it.
I'll check it.
I don't think
she trusts me.
Of course, it
isn't much,
but it sells papers.
How did
you find this out?
Hmm?
How did you find
this out?!
I told you i had
a nose for news.
You like it,
don't you?
Mr. Smith, i can't think
of anything i like better.
Harold j. Swanson!
"...for 13 years,
"principal
of dansburg
high school
"confessed to
police today
"that he is married
to two women
and is a bigamist."
I just talked to mr. Swanson.
And?
It's true!
He has two wives.
High school principal
exposed as bigamist!
Hey, late paper's out!
Read all about it!
Subscriptions!
You're kidding.
I amnotkidding.
Do you realize
that in two weeks,
our circulation
has tripled?
Beautiful!
Well, well, well,
mr. Franklin.
How are things
at thegazette?
That's exactly why
i'm here, mr. Winter.
Miss benson.
I'm not a man
to beat around the bush,
but you're giving us trouble.
Now, this
quick success
that you've had
just can't last.
You've had a few lucky breaks.
That's all.
But i'll admit, we're hurting.
How does it feel, mr. Franklin?
I'm authorized
to make you an offer,
and if you're
a smart young man-
i understand that you are-
you'll take it.
An offer for what?
Thecourier.
We buy it; you and your staff
go to work for us.
Now, how does
that sound?
Sorry. Thecourier
isn't for sale.
Not at any price?
Not at any price.
Now, you certainly don't think
that you can fight us, do you?
Oh, we can try, mr. Franklin.
Well, then you're not quite
as smart a young man
as i thought you were.
But i will leave that offer open
until 7:00 tonight.
If i don't hear from
you by that time,
you better lay
in yourself
a good supply
of tin cups.
Thank you.
How much do you think
he'd give you?
Well, if they're
as worried as
franklin looks,
i imagine around
$100,000. why?
I was just wondering.
Honey, what's
the matter?
Things have never gone
better, have they?
I'm not so sure.
Here we are.
Oh, hi, mr. Smith.
I have
a little surprise for you.
I don't think
i can take another one.
You'll take this,
all right.
Happens to be
the biggest scoop of them all.
You read it, and
i'll get things going.
Almost afraid to look.
Twilight zonewill continue
after station identification.
Look, i don't blame you
of being upset,
but that gives you no reason
to toss allegations around!
Allegations? Facts.
Now, you started that fire,
and you're going to pay for it.
I told you a thousand
times, i didn't
start the fire!
Now, how many times
do i have to tell you?
I don't care how many times
you tell me.
Your newspapers were
out on that street
exactly one half hour
after it happened,
and to me, that means
only one thing:
That youknew
it was going to happen.
All right, i'll
explain it to you
one more time.
Our new man
was walking by
your building,
and he saw the smoke,
and he came in...
yeah, and then back here,
and in one half hour,
he wrote the complete story,
ran off 5,000 copies
on that dilapidated equipment
of yours,
delivered it
to the corner newsboy,
and you expect me
to believe that?
Now, what kind
of a stupid idiot
do you think i am?
Well, let's not get
into that, shall we?
It just so happens
i have witnesses
as to my whereabouts
for the whole day.
Now, will you
get out of here?
We have a lot
of work to do.
You haven't heard
the last of this.
Doug?
Yeah?
Howdidwe hit on
the street so fast?
I don't know.
Well, do you
believe him?
Who?
Mr. Smith!
Do you believe
he justhappened
to be passing by?
Well, boss, what
can i do for you?
Answer a question.
Did you start
thegazettefire?
I?
You.
I'm afraid i don't understand
the question.
I don't see why not.
It's very simple.
Did you start thegazettefire?
It was started
by a faulty electrical system.
Are you sure?
I never write up anything
i'm not sure of.
It's a question
of ethics.
Oh, by the way...
andy praskins called.
He's the linotype
operator
i told you about.
I think i'll hire him back and
put you on full-time reporting.
No, no, no,
that wouldn't do.
Now, i've made certain, uh,
modifications to this machine.
I wouldn't want
anybody else to touch it.
Would spoil everything.
Besides, it breaks up
the day for me.
You can hire him back,
by all means, but, uh,
give him another job.
I insist.
Okay.
Hey, come on, now,
you still haven't told me.
Exactly how did you meet
mr. Smith?
Oh, brother.
You don't give up
very easy, do you?
Well, i want to know.
I told you, i
just ran into
him that night.
That's all.
Where?
Pine trail.
What were you doing there?
Shooting butterflies.
What else would
i be doing there?
Well, you don't
have to get so
sarcastic about it.
I was only asking.
Well, i told you.
I just met him...
and i hired him,
and he put us back in business.
What's wrong with that?
I smell trouble.
Trouble?
We just picked up
1,500 new subscriptions.
We're selling out every day.
I've been dreaming about that
kind of trouble all my life.
Hey, what's the matter
with you?
There's nothing
the matter.
Yes, there is.
You're different.
You've changed.
"You're different.
You've changed."
You're beginning to
sound like a wife!
Well, i'm not your wife, and
i never will be, at this rate.
Well, that's okay with me, too.
Mr. Smith?
What's on
the machine?
I was hoping to surprise you
with it later.
"E.j. Macleod
wins $250,000 on
sweepstakes ticket."
"Macleod, for 16 years
clerk at the dansburg
water and power comp..."
uh, mr. Macleod?
This is doug winter
down at thecourier.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
I was just wondering,
have you heard anything
on your sweepstakes ticket?
I see.
Oh, no, no, sir,
l-i haven't heard a thing.
Sorry to bother you.
Right. Good night.
Mm?
I hate to tell you...
but i'm afraid this time,
you pulled a boner.
Macleod doesn't know
anything about it.
I didn't say he knew
I said hewonit.
What are you talking about?
How can you win $250,000
and not know about it?
By not bothering to
look under the door
for a telegram.
Courier. Winter speaking.
Congratulations.
You see?
Now, boss, would you have
a chair, please?
I think that the, uh...
time has come when you
and i should have
a little chat, hmm?
I think the occasion
calls for a touch
of "the creature,"
if i may say so.
Sorry. I'm fresh out.
I think you'll find
you're mistaken.
Right there
in that top drawer, hmm?
With my compliments.
You think of everything,
don't you?
Now, first of all...
i should like to ask
whether or not
you are happy
with the way things
have been going.
Just what are
you leading up to, mr. Smith?
A simple
proposition.
I hereby guarantee-
you understand-
guarantee-
that you will become
the most successful
newspaper editor
in the world, if...
you will affix
your signature
to this little
document.
"I, douglas winter,
agree to relinquish
"my immortal soul
to the bearer upon my death
in exchange
for his services."
"I, d..."
what?
Huh?
You're the devil!
Oh, mr. Winter.
As a sophisticated,
intelligent
20th-century man,
youknowthat
the devil does
not exist. True?
True.
But you also know
that the world
is full
of eccentric,
rich old men-
crazy old men doing
all kinds of things
for crazy reasons.
Now, why don't you
think of me like that?
Here's a pen.
This is ridiculous!
Yes, isn't it?
Could i, uh...
trouble you for
another drink?
Uh, you don't
really believe
that i'm the
devil, do you?
No.
Well, then, why don't
you put it this way:
You're humoring me.
After all, what good
is the soul, anyway?
It's sort of like an appendix
these days,
particularly since it doesn't
exist in the first place.
Well, just for the sake
of argument,
why do you
particularly want mine?
Well, for the sake of argument,
let's say i'm something
of a connoisseur,
and you have a very choice soul,
and as the vintners say,
it's a good year.
Well, then
again, uh,
just for sake
of argument...
yes?
Why don't you
just take it, huh?
Now, if you're
the devil
as you say you are,
why, you can
do everything.
No, unhappily,
not everything.
I am bound
by certain rules,
and i do have
my limitations.
You're nuts.
Yes.
Let's drink to that, huh?
Here you are.
I think i should
warn you, however,
that if you do not
sign this,
then the certain
gloomy predictions you made
about thecourier'sfuture
will certainly come to pass.
Yes, i'll have
to resign, and...
well, let's not even consider
such a proposition.
After all, you don't want
to go visiting
that bridge again,
do you?
Hardly.
No. Yeah.
Now...
why not humor
an old man?
It'll mean
such a lot to me.
And if you don't
sign it,
it would be admitting
fear and belief.
You're not afraid,
are you?
No.
Fancy that!
A grown-up man who believes
in the devil!
Give me that
stupid thing!
There.
Now, let's not hear
any more about this, shall we?
Good morning, miss benson.
Good morning, mr. Smith.
Doug?
Doug, wake up.
Hmm?
Wake up!
Hmm? Oh.
What, you sleep
here last night?
What happened?
Here, have
some coffee.
Oh. Yeah, i worked late
last night.
Guess i fell asleep.
Thanks.
Have you seen this?
Ah. What?
Oh, no!
Doug, what
is going on?
What is the matter?
Why, these papers
were on the newsstand
less than an hour
after it happened.
Who ran them off?
Who delivered them?
Ask mr. Smith.
I'm askingyou.
Leave me alone,
will you?!
Lovely dress you're
wearing, miss benson.
What do you want?
A bit of fire, hmm?
Ah, yes.
Hmm?
Keep them.
Thank you.
You and i are
going to be great
friends, my dear.
Extra, extra!
Honeymooners drown
in lake bundy!
Read all about it!
Thank you, sir.
Extra, extra!
Extra! Banker murders wife!
Read all about it! Extra!
Get your late papers here!
Doug, i'm scared!
These things
just can't be happening!
You've got to fire him.
I can't.
Why not?
You paid back
the loan.
You don't owe
him a thing.
I know, i know,
but i can't, that's all!
Now, believe me,
i can't!
Why? Just kick him out!
On what grounds?
I don't know-
incompetence.
Oh, come on,
now, you know
he's a very competent
linotype operator
and a great reporter.
Do you want him
around?
It isn't a question of
wanting him around...
then what is it?!
He'srunning the newspaper now.
Not you, him!
He's doing a pretty
good job of it,
too, isn't he?
We're selling out
every edition!
Oh, you're selling out
more than that.
A lot more.
Good-bye, doug.
Jackie?
Aren't you being
a little hasty?
Would you mind
you own business?
Thisismy business.
I have a
proprietary
interest
in everything
connected with
thecourier.
Well, i am
no longer connected
with thecourier,
mr. Smith.
Miss benson, i wish
you'd reconsider.
The fact is,
i've developed
a very special
fondness for you.
Will you please get
out of my way?
You'll besorry
you did that!
Where's jackie?
Love's labor
lost, my friend.
She's gone, vanished.
But don't worry...
we can do withouther.
The person we can
do without isyou.
That's an ungrateful thing
to say to a friend
who pulled you
out of bankruptcy
and turned thecourier
into the hottest journal
in the state!
Well, let me tell you
something, mr. Smith.
It's not worth it.
I had a nightmare
about a weird little man
with a crooked cigar who caused
terrible things to happen
so he could get scoops
for my paper.
Well, i'm awake
now, and i want
you out of here!
Not so fast!
What about our contract?
What about
our contract?
You said
you'd doanything
to make your paper
a success.
I heard you.
That's why i came.
Well, i've carried out
my part.
You are a success.
If you're not a nightmare, then
you're something even worse,
because somehow
you'vemadethese things happen.
You've caused tragedy.
You've destroyed life
and property.
I didn't bargain for this!
Oh, yes, you did,
but you put it out of your mind.
You thought you'd get everything
for nothing.
That's not the way life works.
Well, don't worry
about it.
You're not the first editor
i've helped.
I don't want your help.
I want you
out of my life!
Can't do that now.
We have an obligation
between us.
There is no way out.
Hold it!
There's one
way, of course.
And what's that?
You can pay
up, right now.
I suppose that means
that you can't take
my immortal soul
while i'm alive
and walking around,
is that it?
Something like that.
Now, wait, wait.
This old nose smells
a story coming in.
May solve everything.
Ah!
A shame- poor miss benson.
What about miss benson?
"At 11:30 tonight,
miss jacqueline benson,
"former secretary
to douglas winter,
"editor of
thecourier,
suffered grave
injuries..."
"...suffered grave injuries
"resulting from a head-on
collision between her car
"and that
of james edward slocum,
"returning from a skiing trip.
The accident
took place on
bascomb road."
That won't stop it.
You still think
i'm a nightmare, do you?
You change it.
I can't change it.
The little modifications i made
altered this machine
quite a bit.
Whatever it writes
comes to pass.
But why jackie?
What did she ever do to you?
She slapped me.
And you'd destroy her for that?
Of course not!
You're
an intelligent man,
but you keep missing
the point.
Don't you see
i've spent
too much time
with you already?
I have other
clients waiting.
I want to move on.
I figured this story
about your girlfriend
would hurry things up.
Let me point out
that the item
did not say
that she died
of her injuries-
not yet.
I can add a few
lines either way.
Whether she lives or
dies depends on you.
Now, if you decide to
conclude the contract,
you'll find this a lot
surer than the bridge.
Quicker, too.
That leaves youthree.
Where you going?
There's got to be some way
to stop you,
and i'm going to find it!
That's the spirit.
Never give up.
But remember, you only have
one hour and 15 minutes.
Jackie?
Jackie!
Hush!
You want to wake up
the whole building?
Where's miss benson?
She ain't in.
Well, where did she go?
Well, that's none
of my concern.
When did she leave?
Well... well,
what's the mattter?
When did she leave?!
Oh, a-a-about 15
minutes ago, i think.
But what's the... what's...?
Mr. Smith,
i want to talk to you.
Oh?
First, i want to apologize
for slapping you.
Tush, it's nothing
at all.
Second, i want to ask
something of you.
What might that be?
I want you to go away.
Now, i know you've done
a great deal for the paper.
We appreciate that.
But i love doug.
I want to marry him.
But the way he's been acting
ever sinceyoucame-
i don't even recognize
him anymore.
He's a different person!
You think that's
due to my influence?
Yes, i do...
and i am going to get you
out of this town,
away from this paper,
away from doug,
or, so help me...
hold it, hold it!
Don't become
hysterical.
Well, i mean it.
Ireally...
no need to say
another word,
because... i'm
leaving of my
own free will.
You are?
Of course! I never stay
where i'm not wanted.
I have other offers, you know.
In fact, i'm quitting
this very moment.
You are?
Certainly.
My only request
is that you drive me.
I have no car, you know,
to drive me to the airport.
Well... certainly. I'd love to.
Very well. I'm ready.
Well, what about doug?
Oh, i thinkhe
can take care
of himself, hmm?
Would you like
me to drive?
All right.
We'll go
by the bascomb road.
Hi, mr. Winter.
Have you seen jackie?
Oh, miss benson? No.
She hasn't been in
since lunch time.
What's the matter,
mr. Winter?
You look terrib...
well, can i get you something?
Too fast!
Why, this is too fast!
Oh, look out!
Mr. Smith?
Mr. Smith?!
Doug!
Oh, doug!
Jackie!
Oh, jackie!
Doug, mr. Smith-
he tried to kill me!
He tried to kill me!
I know.
We were in this car,
and he kept going faster!
And there was this other car
coming at us,
and he headed
straight for that car!
But it's all
right now.
It's all over.
He was sitting
right there next to me,
and then...
then he was gone!
What's going on?!
What happened?!
Tell me!
Listen to this:
"Mr. Smith, former
star reporter
"and chief
linotype operator
"for thecourier
resigned his position
"and left dansburg
for his home
"at 11:29 this evening.
"His contract with
mr. Douglas winter
"was declared
null and void
"owing to mr. Winter's
incomplete understanding
of the terms of
the document."
Contract?
What contract?
It means that
he'sgone!
Gone?
And he won't be back.
Did he say so?
No, but...
he never goes anyplace
he's not invited.
What do you mean,
invited?
Did you invite him here
in the first place?
Well... in
a way, i did.
In a way, i did.
And i'm going to spend
the rest of my life
making up for it, too.
The first thing
we do is get rid
of this machine!
Why?
And then we're going
to take on thegazette!
Doug, will you please
explain this?!
I don't know what...
i will, i
will, i will.
I'll tell you-
maybe tomorrow.
Right now, let's
get out of here.
Exit the infernal machine,
and with it,
his satanic majesty,
lucifer, prince of darkness-
otherwise known as mr. Smith.
He's gone, but not for good.
That wouldn't be like him.
He's gone forbad.
And he might be back...
with another ticket
to the twilight zone.
For our next show,
mr. Dana andrews
makes his first visit
to the twilight zone
in a show called
"no time like the past."
You'll see him
as a discontented inhabitant
of the 20th century
who goes back in time-
back to what we assume to be
the inviolate past-
and violates it.
A walloping performance,
a strange and odd-ball theme,
and an ending most unexpected
in the tradition
of the twilight zone.
You and i both share
this dubious distinction
with several million
of our peers
who inhabit the 20th century.
And you don't care
for the 20th century?
I do not.
How did you know?
You did, didn't you?
Yes, i knew.
I knew there'd
be a fire.
But what i didn't know-
i didn't know that
i would cause it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org