Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Mommy!
I'll get it.
You're going?
I'm just putting
my slippers on.
Mommy!
All right, sweetheart,
i'm coming.
Hush up, mac.
Shh!
What's the matter, baby?
What'd you do, fall off?
Come on.
Well, what'd you do,
roll underneath?
Daddy!
All right, honey.
I'm right here.
Now, come on out.
Come on, you just crawled
underneath the bed.
Tina.
All right, honey,
come on, take my hand.
Come on.
What in the...?
Daddy.
All right, just a minute.
Chris, what is it?
I don't know.
One frightened
little girl.
Bettina miller.
Six years of age,
average height and build,
light-brown hair, quite pretty.
Being tucked in bed
by her mother a few hours ago.
"Ay, there's
the rub," as hamlet put it.
For bettina miller can
be heard quite clearly,
despite the rather curious fact
that she can't be seen at all.
Let's say for the moment...
in the twilight zone.
What's the matter?
She's not here.
What do you mean
she's not...
look for yourself.
Tina?
Mommy!
I turned on
the light.
Oh, no, no,
it's crazy.
It just sounds
as if she's...
mommy, pick me up.
Chris, where is she?
I don't know.
Well, what are
we going to do?
I don't know, honey,
but we're not
going to panic.
Tina!
Shut up, mac!
Bill?
Bill, this is chris.
Can you come over
to the house right away?
I'm sorry, bill,
this is an emergency.
Tina has disappeared.
No, no, she hasn't
been kidnapped.
Tina is... tina is here...
but she's not... here.
Bill, for crying out loud,
will you get over here?!
Hurry.
Shouldn't we...
wake her?
Bill's coming
over, honey.
Bill?
Well, he's
a physicist.
Maybe he can
help us out.
I don't know,
i couldn't think
of anything else.
Oh, god, where is she?
Where is she?
Listen, i'd better go
and let that dog in
before he wakes up
the whole neighborhood.
Honey, i'm going to check
underneath the house.
Mac, come here.
Come here!
Come here, mac.
He's gone.
No...
they're not
under the house.
What's wrong, chris?
Listen, tina woke us
up with her crying.
So i went into
the bedroom
and i couldn't
find her.
I let the dog in
and he went
under the bed
and he's gone, too.
Let's move the bed.
Oh, bill, where is she?
I'm about to
lose my mind.
Hold on, ruth.
She's breathing
normally, she
must be all right.
Now wait a second.
We'd better mark
where the legs go.
Here.
Still there?
Yes.
Now, you've felt
all over here?
Yes.
And?
Nothing.
Okay.
What are you
looking for?
The opening maybe.
The opening
to what?
I'm not sure, ruth.
You're...!
It's as if you
were going to
step on her.
No.
Are you sure
that you felt
all over here?
Well, maybe not
every single inch!
Take it easy.
I just don't
get it.
Now, wait.
What is it?
The opening.
The...?
To what?
I think...
to another dimension.
Another what?
I don't know
if i'm right,
but i can't think
of anything else.
Tina must have
fallen out of bed,
accidentally rolled
under it and...
...gone through.
And that's where
mac went, too, huh?
Probably
sensed it.
Animals are sharper
about these things
than humans.
He knew she was
in there and...
went after her.
Then why can't we?
No.
We don't know
what's in there.
My daughter's in there!
I know that, ruth,
but we can't.
Bill, for crying out loud,
she's right here!
All we have to
do is reach in
and pull her out.
If it was as
simple as that,
why hasn't mac
found her yet?
Nope...
if it's what i think,
it's kind of a...
gap opening
on another
dimension.
Probably the
fourth dimension.
It just wouldn't
be laid out
like our
world, chris.
Well, there must be
something we can do.
Have you got a...
a crayon,
a piece of chalk?
Here.
All right, now let's just see
how big this thing is.
Bill, i just don't
understand...
understand it.
The third dimension
is... just a... step
below the fourth, chris.
It's a big step, granted,
but it's just one step.
Now, every point in our space
is part of a
perpendicular
line in the...
fourth dimension.
So?
So... although all
the lines forming
the fourth dimension
are perpendicular
to every point
in the third,
they're not
necessarily
parallel to us.
But if enough
of the lines
are parallel
in both dimensions
in a given area,
it might create... an opening.
What, has this opening
always been here?
It might have been.
I doubt it, though.
Believe me, i'm
no expert on this.
Who is?
But i suspect that...
junctures
between dimensions
are freaks of nature
that happen...
who knows how often.
Rarely, i'd say.
I hope.
There it is.
Shh.
What's
the matter?
I can't hear
her anymore.
What?
Oh, no!
Tina!
Hold it down.
Start moving around.
Huh?
Move around.
Shh!
Oh, what in
heaven's name...
start looking
for her.
Where?
Anywhere-
the whole house.
In here!
I want my dolly.
What is this?!
Chris, i told you what i think.
But if she went into
this other dimension
in the bedroom, and if
she's still asleep,
then what is she
doing here?
Chris...
if she's beyond our world,
her movements might seem to us
to be coming from
all over the place.
Actually, she might be
just turning in her sleep.
Call the dog.
Huh?
Call the
dog, hurry.
Mac.
Here, mac.
Come on, boy.
That's it, that's a boy.
Mac...
where are you
taking me, mac?
Mac, don't.
Tell her to go with the dog.
Go on.
Tina!
Mommy!
Go with mac, baby.
Go with him.
Where are you?
I'm here, baby.
Never mind.
Just tell her to go
with the dog- hurry!
Sweetie, go with
mac, right away.
Will he take me
where you are?
Yes, baby,
he will.
All right, mommy.
Let's go.
Call the dog again.
Mac, here, boy, here.
Oh, bill,
can't we try...
it'll have
to be the dog.
We can't take the chance
of going in there.
Mac, here, boy!
Here, mac!
Hold it.
He's doing it.
Man, what a mutt.
Come on, boy.
Come on, mac,
here, boy.
Tina!
Mommy!
Come on, mac.
Come on out, boy.
Tina!
Mac, bring her out!
Daddy,
where are you?
We're here, baby!
We're here.
We're right here!
I can't see you.
Mac, bring her out.
Why doesn't
he do it?
Maybe he can't.
No!
Tina.
Tina, take my hand.
Chris, don't do it.
My hand, honey.
Take ahold of it.
Here.
I can't see
it, daddy.
Here, honey.
Chris!
Can you hear me?
We're right here, pal.
Don't move.
I've got to.
Don't move
an inch.
I've got to find her.
Let her come
to you, chris.
Call her.
Tina.
Daddy, where are you?
I'm right here.
Come to the sound of my voice.
That might
not work, chris.
Get mac to bring her
to you and hurry.
Tina?
Where are
you, daddy?
I'm right here, baby.
Is-is...
is mac with you?
Yes, but where are you?
I'm here, baby!
Grab onto mac's collar.
You hear me?
Hurry up, chris.
Grab onto his collar.
You got it?
Yes.
Get a good grip.
Yes, daddy,
but...
don't let go.
Mac.
Here, boy!
Bring her here.
Daddy...
hold on to
him tight.
Don't let go.
I won't, but where
are you, daddy?
You'll be with me
in a minute, honey.
Now just hang on.
Come on, mac.
Come on, bring her here.
Is he bringing you, tina?
Yes.
All right, hang on
tight, sweetheart.
Don't let go.
I won't, but where
are you, daddy?
You'll be with me
in a minute, honey.
Now just hang on tight.
Come on, boy.
Mac, bring
her to me.
Come on, mac.
Hurry, chris!
That's a boy. Attaboy.
Come on.
Can you see her?
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
Here, boy.
Come on, boy.
That's right.
Bring her
to me.
That's right.
Come closer now.
Okay, i got him!
I got tina!
All right, now hold on...
hold on tight.
You got a good grip?
I mean a good one.
Yeah, but what are
you going to do?
Tina!
Mommy. Mommy.
Oh, darling.
She's fine.
Oh, i got to get her
out of this room.
Mommy! Mommy!
Oh, man.
What happened?
I pulled you out.
How could you see me?
Half of you
was still here.
You mean to say
you had hold of me
all this time?
That's right.
Oh, bill.
You know, i didn't
even feel you.
Say, listen, why didn't you
want me to reach in there?
And how come i kept
telling you to hurry?
Yeah.
That's why.
It was closing up
all the time you
were in there.
Another few seconds
and half of you would have
been here and the other half...
the other half, where?
The fourth dimension, the fifth?
Perhaps.
They never found the answer.
Despite a battery of
research physicists equipped
with every device known to man-
electronic and otherwise-
no result was ever achieved.
Except perhaps
a little more respect for
and uncertainty about
the mechanisms of
the twilight zone.
Rod serling, creator
ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you about next week's
story after this message.
And now mr. Serling.
Next week we again borrow
from the considerable talents
of charles beaumont,
and we take a fast track
on the wild side.
Picture if you will a man
who wakes up in a strange world,
knows everyone,
knows every place,
feels every much at home.
The strangeness comes
from the fact
that no one knows him.
Try this on for size
on the nexttwilight zone.
It's called
"person or persons unknown."
Habit is something you do
when pleasure is gone,
and certainly this is not
the way to smoke.
I prefer to smoke chesterfields
and get the rich taste
of 21 great tobaccos.
Blended mild, not filtered mild.
Smoke for pleasure,
smoke chesterfields.
This is james arness.
You know it's only a short hop
fromthe twilight zone
to dodge city andgunsmoke,
saturday nights
over most of these stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org