Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
I don't see him.
He's in the box
in front of the pulpit.
I thought he'd
be in a coffin.
Silly fool.
That's what the box is,
a coffin.
Thank you, sister.
Brothers and sisters,
we are congregated
here today to pay homage
to our dear brother,
jefferson myrtlebank.
We all know that jeff myrtlebank
was a good boy.
He didn't always show up
to sunday school on sunday,
but we never saw him
at the bootlegger's
on saturday night, either.
Amen.
We're all
going to miss
this fine youth.
The good lord
must have had
a powerful reason to want
to take him so young in life.
Hallelujah.
But we all know
that the lord moves
in mysterious ways
and today...
he's alive.
The mid-20s.
The midwest-
the southernmost section
of the midwest.
We were just witnessing
a funeral,
a funeral that didn't come off
exactly as planned
due to a slight fallout
from the twilight zone.
Who in tarnation
put me in that coffin?
Brethren, let's not
give way to panic.
A small mistake seems
to have been made.
Brother siddons,
it seems
you got a little
sense left.
Now, what's going
on around here?
Son, we was about
to bury you.
Bury me?
We was real
certain you'd died
the day
before yesterday.
Died?
Well, that's silly.
Doc bolton
pronounced
you dead.
That's right, son.
Your heart stopped beating
two days ago.
I was at the bedside.
Well, i... that couldn't be.
I'm... i'm breathing now.
It wasn't beating
day before yesterday.
You was sick, son,
real sick.
Worst case of flu
i've ever
come across
in my whole
medical career.
I'm surprised he lasted
past last wednesday.
I hate to cast a shadow
on your medical career, doc,
but i won't crawl back
in that coffin
just to save face with you.
Yes, sir.
There was no question about it.
There was no pulse.
Well, i'm sure glad
you didn't embalm me.
How do you
feel now, son?
Well, i feel good.
I feel a little weak
but, uh... rested.
Hungry.
I could eat the hide off a bear.
I'm real hungry.
I reckon you should be.
I know you ain't et
for three days.
Ma!
Pa!
Surprise!
I sure hope
you got a good supper
on the calendar.
What's the matter?
You act like
i'm some sort of
ghost or something.
Hello, son.
Well, i'll be double-dogged.
My own folks
are a-scared of me.
Comfort?
I'll bet you ain't scared of me.
I'm the man
you're going to marry.
Well, i guess you are at that.
Liz?
Now, you ain't a-scared
of me, are you?
Jeff, you
fooled them,
didn't you,
jeff?
Yeah, honey,
i fooled them.
Son.
Son!
Praise be.
We ain't lost you
after all, son.
I know what it is.
I know
what it is.
The miracle that happened
here in our county.
"Ipso suspendo animation."
Very rare.
There have been only 30 cases
in the past 1,500 years.
Ain't you just
covering up
for your
miscalculations?
I ain't heard
of that sickness.
Ain't likely you would-
30 cases in 1,500 years,
all them in europe.
You should
quit trying to slandering
my name and take him home,
give him some soup.
He'll need
some rest.
Well, i...
i'm a mite weak.
We'll get you
right on home.
Just as soon
as i crank up.
I'll fry you
a nice rabbit.
I'm sorry i acted
so funny, jeff.
It was just that...
it was so sudden.
Sure nice
to have you back.
Oh, thank you
kindly,
comfort, honey,
but i ain't never been away.
That was a larruping
good breakfast, ma.
Well, i guess i'll get
over to that east 40
and mend that fence.
Oh, i wish
you wouldn't.
It's only
been two weeks
since you was
at the brink
of the grave.
You oughtn't
to be toiling
from sunup
to sundown.
I feel great, ma.
I never felt
better in my life.
I'll see you
down there, pa.
All right.
I... i'm real concerned.
I... i just don't like
the way he's behaved
the last two weeks.
What do you mean?
He's different,
not like he was at all.
Seems the same to me.
He only et
two eggs again.
Why, ever since
he's sprouted teeth
he's been having
three eggs
at breakfast.
Well, a man's
taste can change.
And he goes around
fiddling with things
night and day.
And the way he goes
at that hard work.
Why, he was never that
friendly with work before.
Yes, sir, that's
true at that.
I recollect
worrying many times
that he leaned
just a shade
towards the side
of shiftlessness.
Not lazy, exactly, but...
no.
No, just uninterested.
And since his sickness,
he's been fighting
in that work
just like he was
a year behind.
No, it ain't like
him at that.
All right, big ears,
you run down
to the mailbox
and wait
for the mailman.
I'm expecting
a new catalog.
Sure hope it gets here.
You've about wore that out.
Make way for the queen!
He ain't been
here yet.
Can i shoot?
Sure.
Here's your ammunition.
I ain't afraid of frogs.
It's just that they're dirty.
How's your brother?
All right, i reckon.
Only ma and pa
are a little bit concerned
the way he's been
behaving lately.
How's he been acting?
I don't know, just... different.
He eats different,
works different,
always fiddling
with things.
Besides, it ain't
none of your business.
He loves me not,
he loves me...
is that a fact?
Well, i was wondering
if you'd heard anything.
Well, as a matter of fact,
i have heard a little something.
I...
just a minute.
You run out and play.
Why? I want to listen.
Go on now. Scoot.
Aw, shuckin'.
You want to hold a mouthful
of black pepper for ten minutes?
Little pitchers have big ears.
Well, now, i know for a fact
that those poor folks
are scared to death.
Why, he's been acting
like a complete strangers
ever since the funeral.
Yes, sir, i mean,
i sure wouldn't
want to go sleep
in a house
with that boy around.
Not me.
They say he's started fiddling
with things now, like axes.
I don't know.
He was always
such a good boy.
Gents.
What do you say, doc?
We was just discussing
that myrtlebank boy.
Yeah, what
about him?
Just wondering
about him.
I guess you've heard
how peculiar
he's acted lately.
Yeah, i heard.
I ain't one to
pass on gossip.
Still, you gotta wonder.
Where was he them 48 hours
he was supposed
to be dead?
Had to be
somewheres.
If he was dead.
Doc says he had
that rare sickness.
Maybe i told
a white lie, strauss.
Maybe i was thinking
of his folks' feelings
when i brought up that disease.
Can you straighten that out?
I'm not the kind to bury a body
unless i'm positive he's dead.
You know me better than that.
Shoot, yes,
we know you, doc.
I did more
than feel that boy's pulse.
When his folks
left the room,
i gave him
the pin test.
I stabbed him
with a pin.
He didn't
even flicker.
I held a mirror to his lips.
If there was any life left
in the man at all,
his breath would fog up
the mirror.
Well, what happened?
I pronounced him dead, didn't i?
Then where could
he have been
for them
48 hours?
Why don't we say it?
We're all a-thinking it.
You say it, peters.
You're daggum right i'll say it.
How do we know
the man who got up
and crawled
out of that coffin
is really
jeff myrtlebank?
I wouldn't talk
like that, gentlemen.
It could cause
a lot of trouble.
Well, i don't know.
My grandma,
she used to tell me
about evil spirits
roaming around the world
trying to find a body
to take over.
She said that they'd
steal a corpse sometimes
before a man
was good dead.
That kind of talk's
dangerous, peters.
Although i must confess this
throws a lot of dry kindling
on the fire that's been
smoldering in my brain
ever since the funeral.
Have a good day, gents.
It's him.
Dagnabit, comfort,
now's the time to tell him.
Right now.
No.
I don't tell you who to see.
And you leave me alone.
Well, maybe
orgram's right, dear.
You know what everyone in the
county is saying about him.
Well,
he's not visiting the county-
he's visiting me.
Well, you're just plain
rotten stubborn.
I bet all your kids
are born with horns.
Orgram!
You two just get on
into the kitchen
and let me
entertain my guest.
Well, bless my soul!
Comfort...
look at who's here.
Well, come on
in this house.
And how's your
ma and orgram?
Just fine.
How's your folks?
Just fine,
except ma.
She'll be
madder
than a hornet
tomorrow.
Mad?
You see, i...
i robbed her
pet rose vine
just so i could
bring you a bouquet.
Oh, you oughtn't
have done that.
Oh, it's not much.
They're dead,
aren't they?
I guess tame roses-
they don't
last very long.
When did you pick them?
Oh, i picked them
just before
i came over here.
Oh, well.
Why... why don't
we have some music?
Yeah, i'd like that.
We just bought a new
country blues last week.
Yeah, i see you did.
Don't touch me.
What's the matter
with you?
I'm sorry.
Just the way them flowers died.
Maybe you've got poison
on your hands.
I ain't got no poison
on my hands.
That's not what's
bothering you.
Everywhere i go
it's just the same.
I expect it from the others
but not from you.
I'm getting sick and tired
of everybody treating me
like a vampire.
Oh, jeff.
Now, you tell me.
Are you my girl or not?
Well, land's
sakes, child,
you're scared
half to death.
What'd he do?
Nothing.
It's time to put
a stop to this.
After all, i'm the
man of the family.
He didn't do
nothing wrong.
I ain't liked him
since we were both
three years old.
Unhand me.
Orgram,
you be careful.
Jeff?
Now, what
do you want?
I don't want you hanging
around here anymore.
Now, let me give you
some advice, orgram.
I'm mad right now.
I ain't mad at
you in particular,
but it'd be a shame
if you got in my way
and i had to take
it out on you.
You threatening me?
Huh.
You forget who i am.
If i had a dime
for every time i whopped you,
i'd have a hundred dollars.
That's right...
but you ain't whupped me lately.
Now, you get out of my way.
Make me.
Oh, my baby.
My poor little baby.
Get out the wagon
and the team.
He broke my jaw.
Oh, we'll get you
right into
doc bolton.
Poor jeff.
He hasn't got anybody.
Poor jeff?!
Orgram, your
jaw ain't broke
or wouldn't be trying
to talk so much.
You ought to do something
about that dandruff.
I tell ya, i'm convinced.
How long i been whupping jeff
in a bareknuckle fight?
As far back as i can recollect.
I used to chase him home
from school every day
like it was
one of my regular chores.
He never was
no match for you, orgram.
How come
he bested you tonight?
'Cause it weren't
jeff myrtlebank i was fighting.
Whoever it was,
he had ring training.
He hitting a different way
that we do around here.
That man is dangerous enough
to kill with his bare hands.
That's exactly what i'm
afraid of, gentlemen.
We seem to be living
with something
evil in our midst,
and we got to
put a stop to it.
We've all discussed
what we're going to do,
and i for one
can't see any reason
for putting it off any longer.
You through talking now?
Let me have another
look in there.
I rode out to warn you:
There's a group of men
coming out from town-
they're going to ask you
to move out of the country.
Well, now, how do you
feel about that, comfort?
Well, i'm a
fickle woman, jeff.
I'm the kind
who believes
whatever is said
by them i'm with.
I've heard some bad
things said about you
and sometimes i
ain't strong enough
to turn a deef ear to them,
but in my heart,
i reckon i love you
or else i wouldn't be here
with you now.
I got a great love
for you, comfort,
and i want you to marry me.
I reckon you better give me
your answer right now.
Gents.
What do you say?
Jeff, we are here
as a committee
to speak
for the community.
We talked
this over
and we came to
the conclusion
that jeff myrtlebank is dead.
We think you're a hant.
That's right, a hant.
We don't know who you are
or where you come from.
We figure
you stole jeff's body.
We don't even like you
as a neighbor.
We're asking you
to move out.
Move out, you hear?
What do you say, jeff?
Well, i think that depends
on miss comfort gatewood.
I just asked her a question
and she ain't answered it yet.
I reckon i'm with you no
matter where we have to go.
You stand behind me, then.
Gents, my wife-to-be and me,
now, we was born
and raised in this county.
We like it.
We don't aim to raise our kids
anyplace else.
Now, you...
wait a minute!
I heard you out.
Let him speak.
We're going to stay,
and that means just two things:
One, if you're wrong about me,
then you ain't got nothing
to worry about
because that means
i'm just a poor
ol' country boy
by the name of jeff myrtlebank.
But on the other hand,
if you're right about me,
then you better start
treating me pretty nice
because you just
don't know all
the trouble
i can cause you.
I might wave my right hand
and bring a whole grove
of locusts down on your crops.
Then i might wave my left hand
and dry up all your wells.
Then i might snap my fingers
and burn a barn or two.
And then some morning
if i get up
and i feel exceptionally ornery,
i might have the hawks come down
and steal your chickens.
Yes, sir.
You folks better start
treating me and mine real nice.
That's a different picture
with you aiming
to marry comfort.
We ain't wanting
to hurt her none.
Yes, sir, it'd sure
be wrong to hurt her
trying to get
at somebody else.
When are you fixing
on marrying her, jeff?
Right away, i reckon.
Let us know
about it, boy.
We'll picnic that day.
Well, come on, gents.
They got a lot
of talking to do.
You couldn't really do
all that, could you?
Of course not.
I hate lying to them,
but i find
that when something comes up
you've got to cope with it.
How'd you do that?
Do what?
Light that match?
You didn't strike
it on anything.
It just lit.
Comfort, honey, first
thing you've got to learn
is not to imagine things.
Jeff and comfort
are still alive today
and their only son
is a united states senator.
He's noted as an
uncommonly shrewd politician,
and some believe he must
have gotten his education
in the twilight zone.
Mental illness
is no longer hopeless.
Many are now being saved.
Help fight mental illness.
Support
your mental health association.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org