Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension
a dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
There was a village
built of crumbling clay
and rotting wood
and it squatted, ugly,
under a broiling sun
like a sick and mangy animal
wanting to die.
This village had a virus
shared by its people.
It was the germ of squalor,
of hopelessness
of a loss of faith.
For the faithless, the hopeless,
the misery-laden
there is time, ample time
to engage in one of the other
pursuits of men.
They begin to destroy
themselves.
Ladies and gents,
it's me, peter sykes
peter sykes, back from st. Louis
stocked up with everything
that's necessary
for kitchen and barn
and the dry throat
and the swollen tongue.
Ha, ha!
Young mr. Gallegos,
i believe.
Now, this is a very
special day, isn't it?
Now, let's see.
What is this special
day, eh?
Ah, now i remember.
It has just this moment
come back to me.
Today you gonna get hanged.
Today, young mr. Gallegos,
killer of children
dances on the gallows.
Well, what will it be
for you today, mr. Koch?
Don't need any more
rope, do you?
You ought to see
the fancy, five-strand hemp
i sold the town
for your party, gallegos.
It could lift five of you.
Any more at home
like you, gallegos?
Well, what will be
your fancy, mr. Koch?
What do i fancy,
sykes?
I'll tell you
what i fancy.
I'd like you
to take your
fat carcass
and your
loud mouth
out into
the open air.
This is a small room
and it's a hot time
of the morning.
Well, what about you, gallegos?
What would your pleasure be?
Nice hacksaw, maybe?
There's going to be
a funeral procession
down that street, gallegos.
You better go to the window
and watch.
They're burying
the little girl
that you mangled
under your wagon.
You sobered
up now, eh?
You remember
the little girl
don't you?
You got stinking drunk
and you raced your wagon
down that street
and what you did
to that poor
little girl...
uh-uh, gallegos.
Hey...
you'll have
plenty of chance
to move around
this afternoon.
You'll be
able to kick
and kick
and kick.
You ought to take a drink
of this, sheriff.
It's a good tonic.
Just the thing
to set you up fine
for a hanging.
Makes you strong
and firm.
Here, feel this.
I don't touch
dog meat, sykes.
You talk big
behind a badge, koch.
Just sounds big to you
because you're a midget, sykes.
You know, i always had
a little question about you.
You always had a thing
for foreigners and strays
but you're mighty tight-lipped
when it comes to
one of your own.
You're not my own, sykes,
so don't claim any kinship.
As for that boy
in there
he had his trial
and today he's going
to swing for it.
There's nothing
in his sentence
that says he's got
to be tormented
by a pig who sells
trinkets at funerals.
Go on, sykes.
Get out of here.
When this day is over, which
one will you weep for, koch?
I have tears enough for both.
Mr. And mrs. Canfield,
i'm real sorry about this.
My condolences
to you.
This afternoon
will be
a lot more
cheery.
Yes, we going
to string up
the dirty
little animal
that done this.
She going to
be avenged.
You can set
your mind to rest
on that score.
We'll string up that
mangler of children
if it's the last
thing we do.
Some other time,
huh, sykes?
Some other time
you act like a man
with no brains
but... not now.
Now you keep quiet.
Now, look at that,
will you?
Ain't that
the most gall
you ever seen
in one place?
Gallegos' old man
shows his face in town
in broad daylight
and during the funeral
procession, too.
Somebody ought to take
a horsewhip to that...
that...
my father
wishes me
to tell you
that...
my father
wishes for me
to tell you
that his heart
is broken.
That if
he could...
if he could
give...
his own life in return.
His own life in
return, estrelita.
return, he would.
He would do so with
great willingness.
He... he
understands...
get out of the way,
little girl.
Get out of the way.
Can't
you see...
can't you see
that we're burying
our daughter today?
Oh, please, please.
My son did not mean
to do it.
He... he's a lover of children
as you
all are.
He's a lover of children.
Hey, ozzie!
Vayase a la casa.
No se le necesita aqui.
He's not
needed here.
Is that what you say
to your old father?
Father, take
estrelita home.
They will hurt you.
Please, go home now.
Vayase a la casa,
por favor.
Luis... luis.
My lucky coin.
It is said one can
make a wish on it.
Go home,
old man.
Make your prayers
and make your wishes.
Luis is right.
You'll do
no good here.
You never been drunk,
mr. Sheriff?
You never felt such
misery rising in you
that salvation seemed
to look at you
from only out of a bottle?
You never felt pain?
Such pain that you had to ride
through the night
and not look behind you?
My son was hungry
and he felt such pain
and he drank too much.
He rode
down the street
not looking,
not seeing.
And he had a sadness...
deep inside.
Sadness that there was not
enough to eat
sadness that he had no work
sadness the earth
all around him
was growing barren in the sun.
He did not see the little girl.
He never saw her...
for an instant.
Psst, little girl.
Wait.
Now, you stay here.
I won't hurt you.
Don't be afraid.
You go tell your papa-
you understand?
Tell your papa
i want to help him.
You tell him that
his coin is no good-
it's worthless-
but that i have
a magic dust
that turns hate
into love
but it is very,
very precious
very expensive,
comprende?
Understand?
Now...
now, you tell
your papa
to bring 100 pesos
to my room
in one hour
and i will sell him
the magic dust
that makes people
love and forgive.
You understand, eh?
Tell your papa,
comprende?
Good, now you go.
Magic dust.
100 pesos of worth
of magic dust.
It should be
a good attendance today.
When was it
god made people?
Was it the sixth day?
He should have stopped
on the fifth.
They're tired of hating
this place.
The sun...
the ground that is dead
under your feet.
They must go out and find
something else to hate.
This isn't
a carnival, rogers.
It's a hanging.
You mean the kids?
They ain't never
seen a hanging.
I figured it was time.
Why?
Why not?
They'll learn
a lesson.
They'll see what happens
to drunks that kill kids.
I guess that's pretty vital.
How do you teach them
pain, rogers?
Shoot one of them
in the arm?
All right, you kids.
Get down and stay together.
Is that the man they're going
to put the rope on?
Si, little one.
I am the man.
Will it hurt?
If god wills it.
Go on, boy.
Get ready, luis.
It's about that time.
I'm ready, sheriff.
Come on, let's
get it over with.
Yeah, you should've done that
in the jail.
Hang him!
What are we waiting for?
Let's get to it.
Come on, sheriff,
do your duty.
Get it over with.
The little girl
told you?
Yes, she told me.
She said that
you had the dust.
Dust with magic
properties.
That's the idea.
Little of this
sprinkled over the
heads in the crowd
will make them feel
sympathy for your son.
It's very rare.
Magic, you know.
You brought money
with you?
Yes.
Gold pieces?
Where did you
get them?
All my friends.
All my friends went
into the city.
One sold a wagon,
another sold a horse
some borrowed.
We got many pesos
and we converted them.
It will work,
mr. Sykes?
The magic dust,
it will work?
Yes.
You sold the rope
to hang my son.
Now you sell me that
which will save him?
Well, i'm a businessman, mr. Gallegos.
I sell that
which is needed.
I make no
distinctions.
This will work.
I told you,
it's magic.
Luis!
I'm coming, my son.
I'm coming!
Just throw some in the air
over their heads
and then watch the magic.
Yeah, that's right.
Then watch the magic.
String him up.
We waited
long enough.
Let's not
stall it.
Get it
over with.
What are we
waiting for?
Hurry it up,
sheriff.
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
You must pay heed
to the magic now.
You must stop all of this
and pay heed to the magic.
Magic.
Magic!
You must pay heed
to the magic.
All of you!
Magic...
magic... for love.
For compassion.
Magically so,
that my son can live.
As you yourselves...
you once used to live.
Magic... magic.
You... you must pay heed
to the... to the magic.
It's only
for love.
The magic is
for the love.
Magic...
magic.
You must pay heed to the magic.
Magic...
it is for love.
It is
for love.
The magic... is for love.
No!
No...
but it was a new rope.
Five-strand
hemp.
Nobody could have broken it.
It couldn't have gotten broken.
What about it, mr. Canfield,
mrs. Canfield?
Oh, please,
please.
It's the magic.
You cannot try
to defeat the magic.
Let's try
it again.
There are only two people here
who have the right
to ask for an eye for an eye.
What about it, mrs. Canfield?
No more today,
john.
No more.
He killed our child.
And part of himself
while doing it.
And he's suffered
enough.
Sheriff koch,
there must be...
there must be another
hand in all of this
for the rope
to break like that.
Another hand.
Maybe...
maybe the hand
of providence.
You want to stop it
then, mr. Canfield?
John?
We leave it
like this?
We leave it like this.
One victim is enough.
I think we should
all go home now.
I...
i'm free.
Are any of us
free, luis?
Well, you can
go home now.
You have
that much freedom.
Luis,
it was magic.
It was...
magic dust.
It brought back love
to the people.
Yes, father, it was magic.
It's time to go home now.
Please, let's go home now.
New rope.
Brand-new rope.
Go ahead. Take 'em.
They're yours.
Why?
Don't understand.
It must be magic.
That's what she is, magic.
It was a very small,
misery-laden village
on the day of a hanging
and of little
historical consequence
and if there's
any moral to it at all
let's say that
in any quest for magic
in any search for sorcery,
witchery, legerdemain
first check the human heart.
For inside this deep place
there's a wizardry
that costs far more
than a few pieces of gold.
Tonight's case in point
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling, the creator
oftwilight zone
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
In this rather posh club,
you'll see a group of men
argue a somewhat metaphysical
subject like time travel.
One of them maintains it's
possible to go back in time
make a few changes in history,
and, as a result
do quite a job on the present
in this case the assassination
of one abraham lincoln.
Next week, a story called
"back there."
I'd like you all
to come with us.
I think you'll find it
a most exciting journey.
Thank you and good night.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access. Wgbh. Org
see the newandy griffith show
each week
over most of these stations.
Consult local listings.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org