Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You're traveling
through another dimension-
a dimension not only of sight
and sound, but of mind,
a journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries
are that of imagination.
Your next stop,
the twilight zone.
Yes!
You see what i mean?
Did you see that?
The right english, the right
draw, perfect position, right?
What do i get?
Fats brown, that's what i get,
fats brown.
Well, i'm sick of it.
I'm sick of hearing his name!
I'm the best pool cue
on randolph street.
Me, jesse cardiff,
and you know that!
All right, all right...
fats was good.
I mean, hewasgood, right?
But he's dead.
You hear me? He's dead.
He's been dead
for over 15 years,
but every time i turn around
i hear his name!
"Oh, you're pretty good, jesse,
but fats is better.
Fats is the best!"
Fats, fats!
I'll say it again-
fats brown is dead!
And buried in the ground.
And if he was alive and
in this room i could beat him.
I'd give anything...
anything to play him one game!
Fats brown, fats brown,
report to lister's pool room
randolph street, chicago.
Fats brown, fats brown,
lister's pool room,
randolph street, chicago.
If you were here, fats brown,
i'd show you who was the best.
One game, one lousy game...
at your service.
Jesse cardiff, pool shark-
the best on randolph street-
who will soon learn that trying
to be the best at anything
carries its own special risks
in or out of the twilight zone.
You called?
Um, but you're...
dead?
Not really.
As long as people
talk about you,
you're not really dead.
As long as they speak your name,
you continue.
A legend
doesn't die
just because
the man does.
Oh, no...
no, it's impossible.
Nothing's impossible.
Some things are less likely
than others, that's all.
It isn't a rib.
I mean, it's you.
You're...
james howard brown,
known to my friends as "fats."
I know it's a shock,
but you called me,
i didn't call you.
Oh, well, i... i didn't
mean anything, see?
I understand,
it was just big talk.
Is that it?
You like to play
with fire,
but you don't
like to cook.
You're not as good as you claim,
and you know it.
Deep down, you know
you're
second-rate.
Now, wait a minute!
Are you afraid?
Look, i've come a long way, boy,
and not to be fooled with.
I've seen your kind before-
a little skill, a knack, style,
but when the heat's on,
you fold.
That isn't fair-
you never seen me play.
Maybe i can beat you.
That's possible, isn't it?
It's possible.
Things change.
Records get higher.
But you'll never get
the job done with your mouth.
All right, fat boy,
dead or alive,
let me tell you something.
Maybe you are a
legend- a tin god.
You know what
you are to me?
You're a big balloon
waiting for someone to
stick a needle in it.
Well, i'm the someone
and here's the needle.
You're like all
the other legends.
You live on
a reputation.
I heard a man swear
that he saw you make
a nine-cushion bank.
And you don't believe it?
It's impossible.
You hit the
ball that hard,
it won't stay
on the table.
He had more imagination
than brains, huh?
Then you'll
play me?
Yeah.
And what about
the stakes?
The stakes?
Something to make
the game interesting.
Here, any
or all of it.
Come on,
use your wits, boy.
What good is money to me?
Then what?
Something to make my
long journey worthwhile.
Name it.
You said you'd give
anything for a game with me.
Anything?
What are you talking about,
mister?
Just what kind of stakes
are you talking about?
Life or death.
You beat me and you live.
You lose and you die.
It's interesting
to see how much faith
you have
in yourself.
You know something?
For my money, you don't want
to be the best bad enough, boy.
Why, when i
was your age,
i would have jumped
at the chance.
But then, i was
something better
than second-rate.
You better watch yourself.
You know it takes more
than skill to be a champion.
It takes equal parts of talent,
luck, work and nerve-
a quality you sadly lack.
Nerve, you mean insanity.
Risk my life on a game of pool?
Insanity,
if you prefer.
I am just a pool player.
There's probably no less
important thing on earth.
But mark this in your book-
i'm the best.
It's a proud thing
to be the best.
You wouldn't
know about that.
Where you going?
I'm going back.
Wait.
You say i don't
want to be the best
but you're wrong.
Do you know how many hours,
how many years,
how much of myself
i've put into this game?
How many nights i've slept
on that table right there?
I made a deal
with the owner
so i could
practice
after the
place closed.
I haven't been
to the movies in years.
I haven't dated a girl,
read a book
because it would take
time away from the game.
Still talk and nothing else.
I'm good, mister!
I'm...
i'm good.
But am i that good?
You'll really
never know
until you're ready
to risk everything.
Look, will you
stop pushing, huh?
You know,
where i come from,
there's a race driver.
Go to the track
and whisper his name.
Say "tazio nuvolarl"
and watch the heads
nod up and down.
Or go to a bullring
and hear of manolete.
Both men faced
death daily
and both are legends.
You never make
the grade at anything
by playing it safe.
Oh, boy, this is nutty.
No.
You accept
the terms-
life or death?
You know, the big game hunter
has his elephant gun.
And the fencer,
he uses a blade from lima.
This cue was made for me
special, st. Louis.
Cost $600.
Yep, i made my living with it
for 35 years.
Name the game.
Rotation?
Kelly.
14.1 rack.
8-ball.
Well, let's
let's see
how good you really are.
Uh, 14.1 rack,
one game, 300 points.
You got a coin?
Toss for break?
You call it.
Tails.
Change your mind?
You can, you know.
Heads-
my break.
I know what you're
thinking, son-
"the man who breaks
is at a disadvantage.
"Once he scatters
the balls
the other man
has a clear field."
Sure.
Safe.
Wow.
Two balls
into the rail-
a perfect break and
no advantage given.
Now it's you turn
to scatter them.
Safe.
Do something
with that.
15 ball in the corner pocket.
There's a funny thing-
i was thinking if i sink it,
you're really in trouble.
With luck, i can run the table.
And if you miss, you
leave me wide open.
Nine ball in the corner.
Ten ball, three cushion,
in the side.
How about that, fat boy?
Not bad.
That was great.
You're like all the others.
When i was a kid, i knew
a lot of guys like you.
Guys who were
good at things
like music
and basketball.
Guys who would
do anything
to make me feel
about that big.
But you fooled
them, right?
Yeah, i did,
that's right.
I did.
Two ball in the corner pocket.
I knew there was something
i could be good at.
One day, i was about 16,
i wandered into here.
It was cool
and dark
like... like
being underwater.
I used to come back.
I used to watch them play.
One day i picked up a cue,
i asked an old man,
he was sitting right over there,
right there,
i said,
"you want to play, mister?"
And i beat him.
The first time i ever played
him, and i beat him!
I knew i had an eye
for this game.
What happened to it?
I almost made it.
Funny thing, in geometry,
"almost" isn't enough.
Geometry?
Mm-hmm.
Pool is geometry...
in its most
challenging form-
a science of precise angles
and forces.
14 in the end pocket.
Angles and
forces, huh?
You sewed yourself up
pretty good.
13 ball...
corner pocket.
Ha!
Your shot.
Six, corner.
Four, corner.
Twelve.
13 in the corner pocket.
Four ball, corner.
Two ball, corner.
Five ball in the side.
15 in the side pocket.
I've got 59, you've
got seven points.
The game is young yet,
very young.
Rack them up.
One ball, end pocket.
Seven.
Five.
Eleven.
Eight.
Ten ball
in the corner pocket.
You needed those
four balls to win.
See the score?
I got 299, you got 296.
Yeah, yeah,
i see the score.
Well, i need
that one to win.
You need all of them.
Just that one.
Bank the five...
in the corner.
You know something,
jesse?
There's more to life
than this pool hall.
It isn't right, your being
all cooped up in here.
You ought to
get out a little
see what's going on.
You didn't get to be the best
sitting on a park bench.
You spent a lot of time
with that cue in your hands.
Of course
i did.
But i took time out
to live, too.
I've been places where
they never heard of billiards.
15 ball in the corner pocket.
I may not
look the part, jesse,
but i made love,
walked uphill,
swam in the ocean...
when i think of
the wonderful things there are
to see and to do, it hurts me-
yeah-
to see you rotting
your life away
in this miserable,
dark hall.
You're lying.
You're trying
to distract me.
That's a lousy
thing to do.
15 in the corner.
You made
me do that!
You made me miss!
Aw, come on,
a little gamesmanship,
a little fun
and you come apart.
Kid stuff to make you
break your concentration
and you get wild.
There it is-
the game ball.
All my life i've been
waiting for this, it's...
it's a pocket hanger.
I sink that...
i become the greatest.
If you sink it.
You're sweating.
Why you so
nervous?
Oh, for reasons i'm afraid
you wouldn't understand.
I understand all right.
It means a lot, doesn't it?
Even as a dead man...
have your name
up there-
"the unbeatable
champ of all times!"
Carries certain
satisfactions.
"I'll give you a
chance at my crown,
but only if you stake
your life on the game!"
Couldn't be a nice
friendly, little game!
I take them as i find them.
To you, pool is not
a nice, friendly game.
It's a win-at-any-price affair.
I acted accordingly.
It didn't do you any good.
There's still one
ball on the table
and it's taking you a mighty
long time to get at it.
Why?
You wouldn't believe
this, jesse,
but personally,
i'd like to see you win.
Yeah.
Believe me,
i've only been doing my job.
Someone has to keep the flame.
Someone has to weed out those
who haven't got what it takes.
You see, the champions,
the legends,
they serve as a purpose,
a challenge,
an incentive.
I don't need a challenge.
Everyone needs a challenge,
jesse-
someone great
out of the past to say,
"match what i've done, boy,
and make it better."
That's true in all
walks of life-
music, politics, sports,
you name it.
Me- i'm only a pool player,
but i'm the best.
Youwerethe best.
Wait a minute, jesse.
Before you shoot,
think of this-
shoot that ball,
and you may win more
than you bargained for.
There's nothing you can say
that will stop me.
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
I was required to say that.
Win more than i
bargained for, huh?
No... i beat you.
I'm the best.
I'm the best
at something.
Thanks.
What do you
mean, "thanks"?
I beat you, i'm the best,
and i'm going to live.
Of course you are,
those were the stakes.
Then what's with
the thanks, fat boy?
You'll find out
when the time comes
for you to leave
randolph street.
You sore loser.
I beat you.
I beat you fair and square.
Take...
hey.
Come on.
Well, you saw it, didn't you?
I beat the king of the hill,
fats brown!
Me...
jesse cardiff.
And now i'm the best.
And i'm going to stay the best
because nobody is ever going
to take it away from me.
Nobody ever!
It's me, jesse cardiff,
you hear?
Jesse cardiff, jesse cardiff!
Jesse cardiff,
jesse cardiff...
jesse cardiff, jesse cardiff,
jesse cardiff.
Report at once to mason's
pool hall, sandusky, ohio.
Mr. Jesse cardiff, who became
a legend by beating one,
but who has found out
after his funeral
that being the best of anything
carries with it
a special an obligation
to keep on proving it.
Mr. Fats brown,
on the other hand,
having relinquished
the champion's mantle,
has gone fishing.
These are the ground rules
in the twilight zone.
Rod serling,
creator ofthe twilight zone,
will tell you
about next week's story
after this word
from our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
We've had some performances
of great depth
onthe twilight zone,
and next week is no exception.
A distinguished and incredibly
talented young man
lends us his services
when peter falk
stars in "the mirror."
This is the story of a tyrant
and his assassins,
a shattered dream
and the death of a cause.
Next week onthe twilight zone,
"the mirror."
Be sure and watchgunsmoke
starring james arness,
saturday nights over most
of these same stations.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org