Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
Yes, sir, we'll get
that information to you
as quickly as possible.
I understand.
Supervisor's office.
It's cape kennedy.
I'm sorry, colonel.
We're still trying
to get agnes working.
Call us tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Yes, mr. Secretary.
The minute the machine
is back in shape.
Good-bye, sir.
Why hasn't
elwood gotten here?
He's on his way.
Well, thank heaven
for small favors.
Good morning, sir.
Elwood, something urgent
has come up
and i need your help.
Yes, sir.
Agnes has broken down
completely.
We've checked her
thoroughly.
We can't seem
to locate the trouble.
Probably her subroutines
need debugging.
That's what i want you
to find out.
Suppose we take a look.
Fred.
All week.
Day and night.
No sleep,
no food.
I've tried everything...
everything.
It's all right, fred,
it's all right.
Are you taking over agnes?
What happened, fred?
Why don't you see for yourself!
That'll get you nowhere.
Press all her buttons
from now to doomsday.
That's not going to help you.
She's been out of her mind
for a week.
I tell you,
nothing's going to help.
Go on,
press 'em, press 'em!
Remarkable.
State the first
prime number
larger than
the 17th root
of
9,000,355,126,606.
That's right.
Congratulations,
elwood.
You did it, you did it.
You really think you did it,
don't you?
No, agnes did it.
Agnes.
Watch out for that female.
Look out
for that femme fatale.
James elwood, master
programmer.
In charge of mark 502-741,
commonly known as agnes,
the world's most advanced
electronic computer.
Machines are made by men
for man's benefit and progress.
But when man ceases to control
the products of his ingenuity
and imagination
he not only risks
losing the benefit...
he takes a long
and unpredictable step
into the twilight zone.
Indicate maximum
permissible velocity
of the stated
aerodynamic missile.
Millie!
Here are the latest statistics,
mr. Elwood.
Thank you.
Did you hear about
my newest assignment?
Yes, of course.
Congratulations.
She's the greatest brain
of the century.
She beat the world's chess
champion four games out of five.
She's the foremost
expert on missile
ballistics.
She can solve logistics problems
in less than a millisecond flat.
Of course,
i tell her what to do.
Oh, how satisfying for you,
mr. Elwood.
Say, millie...
um, uh, could you, uh, could we,
could you have lunch with me
sometime?
Oh, why, thank you, mr. Elwood.
I, i really must be
getting back now.
Uh, millie?
Why don't you call me jim?
All right... jim.
She called me jim.
Hello, millie.
Uh...
half chocolate-covered
cherries, half marshmallows.
Oh, how sweet
of you
but i started
my diet today.
No lunches either.
How about dinner?
There's a lecture
on thermodynamics tonight.
Doesn't that sound like fun?
Yeah, i'll let you know later.
Oh, jim?
Be sure and
get a refund.
Hello,
mr. Elwood.
Are you
on a diet?
Me?
Not tonight.
Tomorrow night?
About 7:00?
Oh, thank you, millie.
Good-bye.
There's no lecture
tomorrow night.
Where can i take her
after dinner?
Planetarium.
She's been there.
State magnitude
of radiative correction.
I have stated the problem.
State magnitude
of radiative correction.
Answer, please.
I've asked
an important question.
Stick to the subject.
Listen, you may be
an oracle of wisdom
when it comes to atoms, rockets
and missiles,
but i don't need an electronic
brain to advise me.
All right.
Tell me where to take millie
after dinner tomorrow night.
No!
From me?
Millie's not
that kind of a girl.
Are you sure?
The interpretation is that
einstein's theory of relativity
does not postulate the universe
as infinite
but as a closed system
of a spherical type.
Millie?
Here i am,
jim.
Did you
get that?
Millie, i can't read
this chapter to you
without proper lighting.
Couldn't we have
some music, jim?
Well, sure, if you like,
but i thought we might
compare notes on borstein's
treatise on einstein's theory.
Hmm?
Forget einstein
and the universe.
Your universe
is here with me.
Now, stand up.
Come on,
stand up.
Dance, eh?
Listen
to that music.
I used to play trombone
in high school.
Really?
Father played
the tuba.
Confess you feel
something strange.
Yes, i do.
You know why?
Yes, i have
a sore toe.
Oh, you're
impossible.
I'm sorry, millie.
I, i, i wasn't thinking.
Uh, champagne, huh?
Elwood!
You're an idiot.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
i'll get a towel.
Don't bother,
you've done enough already.
Thank you for dinner,
i'll see you tomorrow.
Good night!
Millie, i'm sorry...
let me explain...
consider series of real numbers
arranged in order of magnitude.
What?
Oh, oh, very... oh, we...
we danced and drank champagne
until dawn...
and we took this taxi ride
all around the park.
And, uh...
oh, it's no use.
I'm a dud.
I can't even dance.
I spilled champagne
all over millie.
I've always been shy with women.
Now she's angry,
she'll never speak to me again.
What kind of flowers?
Translate, please.
Oh, thank you, agnes.
You're just like a mother.
Gesundheit.
I'm sorry
about last night, millie.
It won't happen again.
I'm glad
you like the roses.
Say, are you catching cold?
L-i'm aller...
allergic to roses.
Oh, millie.
Elwood, just please, go away.
And take these roses
with you.
Gesundheit.
Agnes, i don't understand.
No other computer contains
as much recorded knowledge
as yours.
You're the star
of all the mechanical brains.
But...
whenever i follow your advice
i seem to louse things up.
Agnes, what's the matter?
Agnes, stop that.
Stop it.
That's ridiculous,
she's a wonderful girl.
Better girl? Who?
Who, agnes?
Agnes, tell me who.
Agnes, who?
Who is it? Who?
Who, agnes? Who is it?
Agnes? Who?
Here are 220 pages
of data, curves, graphs,
the latest astronomical factors
involving the flight.
Now feed all the pertinent
questions to agnes.
She has to come up with answers
in a week.
I guarantee it.
And remember,
an error of one millisecond
can cause a 400,000 mile
divergence from the trajectory.
Do you understand
the problem, jim?
Yes. Can this
new spacecraft
execute six
eccentric orbits
around the planet venus
and return to earth safely.
Right. Now let agnes
work it out.
Yes, sir.
You better be careful here,
agnes.
Better correct escape velocity
for solar radiation factor.
Give answer.
Now, stop that.
Just give the escape velocity
and forget about millie.
Yes, yes,
we've got a date tonight.
The truth is i'm scared.
I've got to impress her-
it's now or never.
How?
Name someone inferior
to me, please.
Walter holmes?
Walter with the red sports car?
Walter with the suntan
and the muscles?
Introduce walter and millie?
Are you sure?
Oh, all right, i'll try it.
Hello, walter,
this is jim elwood.
What are you doing
for dinner tonight?
He insisted
that we stop by
for a drink
before dinner.
Come in.
Walter,
this is millie.
Millie,
this is walter.
Elwood,
you didn't tell me
millie has the most
incredible eyes.
Tell you?
Thank you,
walter.
Come on in,
come on in.
I'll get the door.
Nectar for a goddess.
Looks just like
an ordinary martini to me.
It is nectar.
All this time at superdata
and we've never met.
Shall we make up
for lost time?
You bet.
Do you like
sports car races?
I've never been to one.
I'm driving
my mustang 500 this weekend.
Sounds dangerous.
Danger adds spice
to living
and my car does 160.
Astronauts do 17,000
miles an hour.
17,000.
Would you like to drive
my little bug?
I'd love to.
Hello.
Oh, hello t.t.
Yes, he's here,
hold on.
Supervisor, for you.
Hello.
Sorry to spoil your evening,
jim, but this is an emergency.
Washington insists
that blast off of venus project
be advanced three days.
We need your data.
Right.
Can you get on it right away?
Good.
See you in an hour.
Right, good-bye.
I'm sorry, millie,
but i have to get
back on the job.
I'll have to
take you home.
And deprive me
of taking millie to dinner?
That sounds lovely.
Well, really, you...
just because
you get hung up,
you don't want
to ruin millie's evening,
do you, old man?
No, but...
good!
You're a nice guy.
I hope you understand, jim.
Perhaps tomorrow night.
Yeah... sure.
Well, good night.
Uh, excuse me.
Uh, elwood?
Uh, say, elwood, uh,
you and mill don't
have anything special
going for you, do you?
"Mill"?
Millie.
Well, no, not exactly,
but i...
fine. Fine.
I don't like to cut in
on closed territory.
Thanks for the all clear.
Good night.
And good luck.
Now, uh, where
were we, mill?
No, no, no!
Agnes, forget
the radiation factor.
Will you concentrate?
Now answer this:
Do new conditions permit
six successful eccentric orbits
of venus and reentry?
Go ahead.
Agnes, concentrate.
All right, all right,
i'll tell you.
Walter and millie had...
martinis
and walter took millie
to dinner...
i'm starved.
Why did you tell me
to introduce millie to that...
that sex fiend?
I will not give her up,
i love her!
And what's more, and i'm going
to make her love me.
Has all the new data been
stored in her memory units?
Yes, sir.
Fine,
let's get to work.
Ready, jim?
Question:
Do new conditions permit
six successful eccentric orbits
of venus and reentry?
What the devil
does that mean?
I... i don't know...
i think it's russian.
What?
Wait, please.
Translate into english.
Into english.
She... she's
a little disturbed.
Do something, jim.
We've got to have
that information.
I believe
i can get the answer, sir,
if you'll just leave me alone
with her.
All right, jim.
I'll be fired-
is that what you want?
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to get help.
Don't go away.
Oh, you.
I know it's late,
but i need help.
Oh, take it easy, old man.
Jimmy boy!
Uh...
walter,
you're a senior programmer.
Agnes is all fouled up.
I need help.
Sure, anything at all,
old boy, in the morning.
That's too late. Now.
And leave this lovely girl
all alone?
Don't be silly.
Don't worry, jim.
Wally will help you
in the morning.
Oh, sure.
Well, good night, millie.
I'm sorry...
where did she ever learn
to dance like that?
Millie...
what did i ever do to you?
Why do you want to ruin my life?
Why do you hate me?
Make sense.
Stop speaking in riddles.
You mean...
you were jealous of millie?
You wanted me all to yourself?
No, that's impossible.
I'm going crazy.
You're just a machine.
You're just a bunch of grids
and computer circuits.
You're nothing but a bunch
of tubes and data drops.
You're just
a fancy automatic tape recorder.
You can't love or hate.
It's amazing, sir.
Jim elwood is one
of the finest
computer programmers
in the country.
So was fred danziger
and he couldn't handle
agnes, either.
I'm positive i can.
Elwood!
Two and two are four,
shut the door.
Two and four are six,
pick up sticks.
It'll be
all right, jim.
You've been working very hard
and we appreciate it.
How about a long,
long leave of absence?
Meanwhile,
walter will take over.
You?
Oh, no, you don't have a chance.
She knows all about
you and millie.
You haven't got
a chance.
Watch out for that female.
Watch out for that femme fatale.
He was a good man.
Well, do your best, walter.
Don't worry, sir,
i'll have the answers
to the venus project
in no time at all.
Advice to all future
male scientists:
Be sure you understand
the opposite sex
especially if you intend
being a computer expert.
Otherwise you may find yourself
like poor elwood,
defeated by a jealous machine,
a most dangerous sort of female
whose victims
are forever banished
to the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next onthe twilight zone,
the stalwart typewriter
of richard matheson
brings us a most intriguing tale
of riders, pale horses
and peeks into the future.
It stars diana hyland
and it concerns itself
with some very unlooked for
and some unpredictable events.
It's called "spur of the moment"
and it's recommended
for those of you
who'd like to take a look
at the next page of the calendar
before it's time.
Ontwilight zonenext,
"spur of the moment."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org