Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
You unlock this door
with the key of imagination.
Beyond it is another dimension-
a dimension of sound,
a dimension of sight,
a dimension of mind.
You're moving into a land
of both shadow and substance,
of things and ideas.
You've just crossed over
into the twilight zone.
You know
who they are?
No, i don't know.
Strange type
for this neighborhood.
And you stay away
from them, young lady.
Is that it, boys?
Yeah, man,
that's it.
Ain't you got any furniture,
any chairs or rugs or anything?
Man, i said
that's it.
Okay, mac, okay.
We got work to do.
Three strangers
arrive in a small town.
Three men in
black leather jackets
in an empty rented house.
We'll call them steve
and scott and fred,
but their names
are not important.
Their missionis...
as three men
on motorcycles lead us
into the twilight zone.
What's wrong with the tv?
It's not
just the tv.
All the lights in the
house are flickering.
Did you leave something
on in the kitchen?
Dishwasher,
anything like that?
No, dishes
are all stacked.
Tv's still off.
It might be the
aerial wire, stu,
it slipped loose or
something once before.
I doubt if that would affect
all the lights in the house
but it's easy enough to check.
It seems all right.
Martha, come here a moment.
Look.
That wasn't there
this morning, was it?
No. The andersons
took their antenna
with them when
they moved.
Just our luck.
What?
Ham radio operators.
You know what they do
to radio
and television reception.
Daddy?
Yeah, ellen?
I don't know what's the matter,
but i was listening to my radio
while i was studying
and all of a sudden, it began
picking up these weird voices.
Ham radio
operators.
Is there anything
we can do about it?
We can make sure they've
got a license to operate.
Well, do you think
you should, stu?
Those men seem so, kind
of threatening, somehow.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Good evening.
I'm stu tillman.
Live over next door.
Been having a little
trouble over there
with my electricity-
it fades on and off.
Now you boys don't happen to
be ham radio operators, do you?
What's so funny?
Big daddy want to know
what's so funny.
Who are you boys any way?
We are monsters,
daddy-o.
We came from outer space.
Take us to
your leader.
Now just a minute...
cool it, daddy-o,
or i'll disintegrate you
with my ray gun.
Now you...
look at this cat dance.
No, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait. Wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
I'm going to get the
police on you fellas.
And i'm going to
call my lawyer.
You're going to be sorry
that you did this...
forget it.
Stu?
Stu, what is it?
What's happened to you?
Stu, those men, what
have they done to you?
Nothing.
They didn't do anything.
Well, you were... you
were going to ask them
about the
television interference.
Oh, it wasn't them,
they're nice boys.
They're three
very nice boys.
Oh, hey, wait for me.
Darn you.
Trouble?
Did you see that bus?
It pulled right away.
It's like a game with them.
They like to make people suffer.
Why do they do that?
Beats me.
Thank your lucky stars
you don't have to depend
on buses to get around.
Stars are lucky?
You know that old expression.
I understand
about the constellations-
the nature of
the galactic structure, but...
i mean, i dig stars,
but they're lucky?
That's a gas.
Yeah, so are you.
One minute you
sound like a professor
and the next minute, you're
talking like a beatnik.
You need a ride?
You're not going by
the library, are you?
I could.
With me on
the backseat?
Why not?
You ready?
Yes.
I told her to stay
away from those boys.
She missed her bus
and he offered a ride.
I'm sure
that's all it is.
I would
have driven her.
But you're not a
handsome, young man
on a motorcycle, dear.
I don't see any library.
Well, it's on
the other side of park,
but you got me here
so quickly,
i thought i'd walk.
Would you like to walk?
Sure.
Pretty, isn't it?
Mm-hmm.
You know, this is kind
of a special place with me.
I come here some times
and i just try
to figure things out.
Like what?
Well, for one thing,
did you know that you have
lived next door to me
for a week and you've
never said hello?
Hello.
My name is ellen.
My name is scott.
Where are you from?
I mean, where did you live
before you moved next door?
Long way from here.
Where?
Oh, i doubt you ever
even heard of it.
Could be- geography
is one of my worst subjects.
Have you finished school?
Yes. Ten years ago.
Ten years ag...
oh, you're not that old.
I'm older than you'd think.
My people just don't
show their age.
Well, my family's
the same way.
You know, my grandmother
lived to be 90
and you would've
taken her for 60
until the day she died.
What's the matter?
I've never seen
anything so beautiful.
Thank you.
Well, i guess
i'd better be going
before the
library closes.
It's not as late
as i thought it was.
Tell me more
about yourself.
He'll be here,
he got delayed.
I'm not interested
in excuses.
Be at ease.
Where is your brother?
We no longer
trust our brother.
What has he done?
Formed an attachment here
with one of the people.
What kind of attachment?
I'm not sure yet.
He's with a young girl,
in spite of our orders.
Proceed
without him.
We've been in touch
with all units.
The second wave has
landed successfully
and is concealed as planned.
With the landing
of the third wave
we will be in key positions
throughout the country.
Excellent.
The people-
are they suspicious?
Not a bit.
They're a stupid race,
as our research told us.
An inferior breed
given to killing, hatred,
making war, greed
and cruelty to one another.
The universe can
well do without them.
You will receive your
instructions for the final move
in a few days.
Once again, your brother
has failed to report.
He has ignored our orders.
He has spent
the past five days
in the company
of the girl.
We have seen it.
Now there is no other choice.
Proceed without him.
His fate is his own making.
Where are you from, scott?
Does it
really matter?
No, i don't suppose so.
It's just that
you're so different
from anybody else
i've ever known.
Is that bad?
No, not really.
You like me,
don't you?
Well, you know that, scott.
Very much?
Yes, very much.
Do you know the word...
"love"?
Well, of course, silly.
What an odd question.
What's odd about it?
Don't you read your
newspapers, your magazines?
Listen to your television
programs? Your radio?
We have.
We? Scott, who is we?
Well, that doesn't matter.
Your planet is
filled with hate, ellen.
Hate, violence,
mistrust.
I don't see how anyone
as nice as you
has survived
this long.
I'm certainly no
different from anybody else.
I haven't seen a single report
on anyone like you.
Report?
Scott, you talk in riddles.
Sometimes you make me feel like
an insect under a microscope.
Please, i'd like to go home.
I'm very sorry
but i feel as though
you have been lying to me.
I don't know why or what
it is you're trying to hide,
but i know you're
not what you seem.
What if i'm not?
Do you think you're in
any position to judge me?
Any of you?
Please, i would
like to go home.
I'm sorry, ellen.
It's my fault.
I expected too much.
I've done no harm.
I'm telling you the truth.
What have you been doing
the last few days?
Yesterday when i sent you
to the ship for food?
Last night, when you were
supposed to be on guard?
You think
i don't know?
I've been watching you
every minute.
I told them before we came
you were too young.
Loose your head,
you'd run into situations
you couldn't handle.
I told you, i've done no harm.
Didn't tell her a thing?
No.
You're not getting a chance to.
We're too close
to finishing this mission.
From here to the end,
you're just along
for the ride.
Report.
Bacteria unit 59,
reporting in.
The test has been
an unqualified success.
Good.
Units 70 through 100 have
reported the same results.
What is your time estimate?
30 minutes
to the reservoir.
Approximately 24 hours
for the bacteria
to contaminate the water.
How soon before you see results?
Within 30 hours, we shall
witness 50% fatalities.
I'd estimate a total
of approximately 48 hours
before
complete extermination.
Have you coordinated
with other units in your area?
We have.
There are 29 bacteria units
covering water supplies
in this state.
We should easily reach
complete population saturation
within two days.
Very well.
Begin operation invasion
phase two
at once.
Scott!
It doesn't matter anymore.
Scott...
come down, i've got to see you.
It's so late.
It's important.
All right.
Scott?
You're making
a mistake, scott.
These people
aren't worth it.
Scott?
Ellen, you've got
to get away from here.
What do you mean?
Get away, you're in danger.
I don't understand.
Something terrible will happen,
many people will die.
I'll take you someplace
where you'll be safe.
You're frightening me.
What's going to happen?
I can't tell you that.
It wouldn't matter if i did.
We have to leave right now.
Are you frightening me
into running away with you?
Listen to me!
In 24 hours, every man, woman,
child, cat, dog,
everything alive
is going to be dead.
Oh, scott, don't, please.
Not just in this town.
All over your country,
all over your world.
My world?
Scott, it's your world, too.
No, it isn't.
What do you...
scott, who are you?
We came from out there, ellen,
from beyond those stars.
There are thousands of
us on this planet now.
We need space,
we've come to set up colonies.
Scott, you can't be serious.
We have had bacteria units
in every country on this planet
for months.
Each unit has enough germs
to poison the drinking supply
of the entire world population.
I will walk with you
to your friends' house.
You had better let them
call you a doctor.
No, you've got
to listen to me.
Scott, please, i love you,
but you're not well.
Ellen!
All right, ellen,
what's this all about?
Oh, daddy, i don't
know what to do.
Begin by telling
me what you were
doing outside.
Scott said
he had to see me...
i think he's lost
his mind, he's never
been like this before.
He was almost raving.
What did he say?
Crazy things.
He's a space man, they're
taking over the earth
and we're
all going to die.
We better get
him some help.
Deputy sheriff harper.
No, sheriff holly's on vacation.
This is his deputy.
Well, this is stuart tillman.
I live at 11575 amanda drive.
There's a young man
next door to me
i think might be
a little mentally disturbed.
I feel he
ought to be picked up
before he can do harm
to himself or somebody else.
What makes you think
he's mentally disturbed?
He's been scaring my daughter
with man from mars stories.
He claims he's part
of an invasion force
that's going to take over the
world or some such silly thing.
All right, mr. Tillman,
i know exactly what to do.
Thank you for calling.
Yes?
Please listen to me.
You may speak.
What we're doing is wrong.
We should save these creatures,
not exterminate them.
It's true they murder
and hurt one another
and they're subject to
unreasonable hate and prejudice.
But these are only the brutes,
and you find them in any race.
Most of these people have
the capacity for love.
I know it.
Our research disproves that.
They are a world of angry,
frightened people.
No, i tell you,
they learn love from their god
and teach it to their children.
There's more of love here
than hate.
There's no need to kill them.
It is too late.
Not if you order them to stop.
For you... a defector?
A traitor to your own people?
No, i'm not.
A traitor.
Mr. Tillman?
Yes.
Deputy
sheriff harper.
Oh, won't
you come in?
Martha, ellen!
This is my daughter,
ellen, and mrs. Tillman.
How do you do?
Hello.
Go ahead, tell
him, ellen.
I don't know...
your father said the boy
was mentally disturbed.
How did you
decide that?
Well...
ellen! Ellen!
Ellen, there's no more time.
Come in, son.
Tell us all about it.
Don't listen to him.
He's one of us, he's
with the advance units.
Advance units?
What kind of
advance units, son?
They told me
you were ill, son
so i took the
necessary precautions.
No...
no!
Don't fight them, son.
It'll only make it more
difficult for all of us.
Don't worry, folks.
We'll take good
care of him.
Someday i'm sure
he'll thank you.
Portrait of an american family
on the eve of invasion
from outer space.
We know it's merely fiction.
And yet, think twice when you
drink your next glass of water.
Find out if it's
from your local reservoir
or possibly it came
direct to you...
from the twilight zone.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next time out
onthe twilight zone,
richard matheson provides us
with a tour de force
in suspense and the unexpected
with a show called "night call."
It stars one of the most
immanent actresses of our time,
miss gladys cooper,
and it poses
the kind of question that arises
when a telephone keeps ringing
and you realize that the caller
has not been on earth
for a number of years.
I hope this intrigues
because i think the show will.
Next time out, "night call."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org